Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 10]
If you meet a sincere person,
it can change you.
The person whom I'm meeting now
can change my life.
It can be a source of hope
for a person... or despair.
You asked me if I trust you?
As a doctor, I trust you.
Should I bow down in thanks?
As a patient's guardian,
I don't trust you.
If this surgery goes wrong...
I will kill you.
Even if you try,
I will live a long life.
Until I grow very old.
I'll be going now.
I really didn't like you before, Doctor.
I'm a bit of a show off,
but you're pretty bad yourself.
But I think I like you a bit more today.
Is that a compliment?
It is a compliment.
We're rivals over one woman.
Have you even had a meal in the cafeteria
with Hye Jung before saying this?
Well, we're going to eat soon.
Eat first before
calling yourself a rival.
Gosh, why is he poking my weak spot?
You came out of nowhere, as usual.
Doctor, your hand is really big.
Oh, yeah?
I think I can absorb your entire head.
What is it?
Just because.
Let's walk a bit.
You're being very good to me today.
What is all of this?
Oh, give it to Teacher Hong.
I prepared it with the heart
of a mother-in-law.
It's chicken stew that's really healthy.
You're really...
I'm really great, right?
However, this is not free.
Pi Young Gook?
Correct!
Hey, what do you expect me to do?
You don't need to do anything.
Just send him to my store.
I'll take care of the rest.
Here you go.
- Yum. It's so good.
- Right?
Seriously, you make me do
the strangest things.
I'll do my best.
Oh, my pretty child!
How do you always know
exactly what I need?
Teacher Hong wasn't only your teacher.
He was my homeroom teacher.
Once my teacher, always my teacher!
Let's get married.
I thought you were serious.
- I was joking.
- Stop eating that.
Bon appetit.
[YOO HYE JUNG]
Yeah, Hye Jung.
Oh, yeah?
I'll tell you my pin,
so go in and wait for me.
Hello.
- When are we going to eat together?
- What?
You don't even remember?
We are supposed to eat
in the cafeteria together.
That was so long ago and
we still haven't eaten yet.
Then should we have lunch together today?
Sounds good.
What? Why are you laughing?
You're just funny, Doctor.
Don't get ahead of yourself, heart.
What are you doing?
Put that down!
Don't touch a thing.
It might look like a mess,
but there is an order to everything.
Did you wait long?
No. You haven't had
breakfast yet, right?
Of course not. What is this?
Soon Hee wanted me to give this to you.
Soon Hee? Not you?
I wanted to bring it for you too.
But, we didn't make this for you.
We bought it and warmed it up.
You had this side to you?
Yes, I do have this side to me.
You may not have known because
I don't show it very often.
First, have some of the soup,
then have some of the meat.
Okay.
It's hot.
I'm going to be assisting
with your father's surgery.
I know.
Did you find your grandma's
anesthesia records?
How can he worry about me
at a time like this?
You're not answering me again.
Records that are over
10 years old are destroyed.
So, what happened?
The doctor who filled out my grandma's
records is still at the branch hospital.
He's a section chief there and
I'm going to hear it from him.
Why are you so certain that
the doctors made a mistake?
It was a cancer that had not spread.
If the surgery was successful,
a chance for complete recovery was high.
It was a table death, at that.
I found out later that a table death
for stomach cancer is highly unlikely.
What about your parents?
I think they took a settlement.
They covered it up quickly.
Can we work on that assignment together?
Take care of yourself first.
- No, you can't.
- You're very resolute.
How many hours a day do you sleep?
I sleep a lot.
Don't be vague.
Give me an approximate answer
like I gave you.
I sleep at least five hours.
Sometimes, I stay in bed all day.
You're able to focus on
multiple things at once too?
Yes, I can.
I'm not like you who can
only go after one thing.
I see.
Then, are you happy, Doctor?
I'm happy.
How can you be sure that you're happy?
I'm alive and I have a person I like.
We're eating together like this.
This is happiness.
I think you're a really good man
and you're a strong person.
What's with you suddenly?
Something's up, right?
[DOCTOR JUNG YOON DO]
It's Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
I have to go get ready for
your father's surgery.
Finish up eating.
Yes, Doctor.
About Kang Mal Soon's file...
it was Director Hong Doo Shik
who read it.
- You're sure?
- His code was used to open it.
It was either someone on his staff
or someone connected to him.
Look into it further.
Also, he has not gone home yet.
Then, where is he?
His car is still at the hospital,
but we don't know where he is.
Where is he and what is he up to?
- Find him.
- Yes.
Hong Doo Shik.
Just how far are you going to chase me?
[KIM CHI HYUN]
My name is Hong Ji Hong from the
Neurosurgery department at headquarters.
Can I speak to
Section Chief Kim Chi Hyun?
- Are you running some tests?
- No.
What is she up to?
Is this an opportunity for me?
I'd better get in on this thing
and stand in line.
You never know.
Is there a VIP in our department?
You can't find them in our
computer system anyway.
Stop digging around and
let's just order chicken.
You little punk. Digging?
You have no respect because
Yoo Hye Jung has your back?
I didn't even hit you.
Don't pull that Hollywood move on me.
That little punk!
[RISKY MEDICAL TREATMENT UNVEILED IN
LIGHT OF HOSPITAL'S COMMERCIALIZATION.]
How are you feeling?
How would I feel?
I haven't had surgery yet.
You don't have to act so tough
in front of me.
Because I'm in front of you,
I'm acting tough.
What?
I'm looking at you because I have
nowhere else to look.
You have no idea how secure I feel
because I have you.
This must be why people need children.
They'll be coming in for tests.
I'll be here doing rounds.
Okay.
- I'll see you later.
- Okay.
Why are you running?
To get here quickly.
- Goodness.
- Oh, I'm fine!
You should've just stayed put.
It fell because you're avoiding me.
It's a bit awkward.
Co-workers can be like this.
Why is it awkward?
It's uncomfortable when you
come at me like that.
It's like we're very close friends.
- Can't we become closer?
- No.
- Doctor!
- Do you see me now?
Were you visiting your father?
Yes.
When are you having lunch?
Let's eat lunch together.
You can't do that!
She made lunch plans with me, right?
Ah... I did.
Should we have dinner later?
You should have dinner with me.
It makes sense, right?
If we succeed with the surgery later,
you should buy dinner.
You're trying too hard.
Fine, let's have dinner.
Gosh.
You two must be close.
No, let's go do those tests.
Hello, Doctor.
Oh, you're here.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
Once you recover, let's go fishing.
Do you like to fish?
I really like you.
Ji Hong doesn't like to fish.
But I think he wouldn't mind so much
if you were there.
- Let's go together.
- Yes, Doctor.
This is Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
Yes, you're going to lead my surgery.
Yes, Doctor.
- Doctor, we're going to draw some blood.
- Okay.
Doo Shik's been admitted to the VIP ward.
You move fast, Dad.
So he must've been admitted
since his car is here. But why?
He had a relapse.
Are you going to visit him?
No, I think he's getting surgery
in secret because of us.
He knows that the board members will be
swayed if it's known that he's ill.
Kim Tae Ho went too far.
He should be penalized for that.
Deputy Director is too much for him.
I don't think we should
keep this surgery a secret.
It's too much of a burden for you.
You'll have to face it
head-on eventually.
Yes, I agree.
I lived comfortably until now
being shielded by your father.
I think we should let him fish
and do what he enjoys now.
Thank you, Doctor.
- I need to go to the ICU.
- Okay.
- Doctor.
- Yes.
About the patient Lee Gyu Hwan,
he's been NPO since midnight.
His vitals are stable.
The anesthesiologist is getting ready
in operating room 2.
He's off of warfarin, right?
Right. He hasn't had it in two weeks.
Okay, it will be this afternoon.
Set it up.
Okay.
Will Doctor Yoo Hye Jung be assisting?
Oh... tell Doctor Jin Seo Woo to come in.
Okay.
[YOO HYE JUNG]
Yes?
Where are you right now, Doctor?
Hospital station.
I have your father's lab results.
Can you come look at them?
Should I bring them to you?
No, it's not a secret surgery anymore.
Can I use that computer?
Yes, Doctor. I'm done using it.
His blood sugar level is 300.
I think it might be best to
push the surgery back a few days.
Get an Internal Medicine consult.
Give him insulin and
watch him for a few days.
All right, I'll tell Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
Okay.
You're making me feel awkward.
Why are you staring?
Don't you have work to do?
Work? I'm sorry. I...
What are you sorry about?
I'm going on rounds.
- Okay, can I tag along?
- Come.
Professor Hong wants you in surgery.
You know Lee Gyu Hwan, right?
The cavernous malformation removal.
Are you mistaken?
He told me not to come into
his surgeries for a while.
It's been more than a while.
What about Hye Jung?
She's going into
Doctor Jung Yoon Do's surgery.
Board Director Hong's surgery.
- He's getting surgery?
- Yes.
The hospital is up in arms about it.
Why would Hye Jung do an
important surgery like that?
She didn't get it because it's important,
but because it was the right fit.
Hey, am I really awful right now?
- Yes.
- I've succeeded.
Gosh, I can't get any rest at all.
Let's just pay half each.
Why should I pay?
You were in the car too, Nurse Hyun.
You were the one driving, Doctor.
I thought you had a license.
Doctor Yoo knows everything.
She's not saying anything for now,
but we need to come up with a plan.
What's going on that you're not even
acknowledging a person?
I was just trying to become Cinderella.
I couldn't even do that and now
I'm about to lose two months' pay.
Just know that I can't pay it.
- Hey...
- What's that about?
The car that Doctor Yoo got from Boss,
we took it and crashed it.
She actually accepted that car?
That's accepting bribes.
It's against our hospital rules.
I don't know anything about that.
Nurse Hyun and I are about to
lose months of pay to cover the damage.
Isn't there something we can do?
I'll take care of it.
This is Jin Seo Woo from the
Neurosurgery department.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung from my department
was gifted a car by a patient.
Yes.
Yes, I understand.
- Seo Woo.
- Dad.
You're going to the Science Council
in Jeju Island this year, right?
- Yes.
- I like that about Kim Tae Ho.
He helps you grow regardless of me.
Here comes that tiger now.
I never dreamed that Director Hong
would be admitted to the hospital.
I should have told you earlier,
but I didn't want to worry you.
I should worry, of course.
Director Hong is such an
important person in our hospital.
Is there anything you need?
Gosh, I know I can be fake,
but your pretension is over the top.
No, your concern is more than enough.
- Please do what you can.
- I will.
I thought it was strange.
They tried useless methods.
No matter what,
the ball will always be in our court.
We have been friends for 50 years,
haven't we?
I bought the soup that you always liked.
Have it after your surgery.
How is your face after being punched?
It's fine, of course.
It takes more than that to hurt me.
Do you know how much I'm holding back?
Do you think I don't know
about your slush fund?
What are you going to do?
I wanted Myung Hoon to
step down on his own.
But now... there is no chance.
All right, do it your way.
In return, give me the records
for my slush fund.
We are friends.
No matter what anyone says,
we have a history together.
You're sick, so rest.
Aren't you sick of it all?
Focusing on work your entire life?
Give it to Ji Hong. I'll cooperate.
Aren't you even going to say hello?
- Have you thought about your mistake?
- Yes.
I'll make sure it doesn't happen again.
Seo Woo, I was your homeroom teacher.
Don't forget that.
How could I forget that?
I genuinely want the best for you.
Finally, we are having
that cafeteria meal.
Let's sit here.
It's really hard to eat a meal with you.
Are you usually this quiet?
No.
Then, is it just me who makes you quiet?
That's not it.
You're laughing again.
I'm like that, you know.
If you get to know me well,
I'm a really funny guy.
I told you I thought of you as a woman.
Did you not fully understand
what I meant?
I understood. I'm not that stupid.
So why are you putting up walls?
Is it because of Doctor Hong Ji Hong?
Doctor, we're here to eat.
This topic is a bit heavy over a meal.
Why is it too heavy?
Eating and love...
What I mean is that you can
talk about anything while you eat.
That's all I'm saying.
Doctor... thank you.
Why are you suddenly thanking me?
I'm getting a bad feeling.
This is what people usually say
before they say something bad.
I don't believe in love
between men and women.
Should I stop?
Keep going. Let's finish this.
If I were to love someone at all...
that one person would be
Doctor Hong Ji Hong.
I'm sorry.
It's not something to be sorry about.
I am thankful that you
feel sorry to me, though.
It means that you have
good feelings towards me.
Hey, there's no need for you
to get up and leave like that.
Let's eat.
I guess I am funny even in my own eyes.
- Let's get up.
- Okay.
This is the Neurosurgery department.
What? Yes.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung?
Yes, okay.
Who was it?
The internal audit team is looking for
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
If they're looking for her,
she received a bribe.
I knew it. She acted so clean
all by herself.
Doctor Choi, do you think
this is about that car?
No way.
What if it is? I'd feel so bad.
- What are you doing?
- I have to call Doctor Yoo.
Hey.
Hey!
Run now and tell Doctor Yoo to
go to the internal audit office.
- I can call.
- But then you won't suffer!
Run now! Run, run, run!
Gosh, seriously!
What am I supposed to do with him?
Doctor! Oh no.
Doctor!
You could've called. Why are you running?
The internal audit team wants you.
Do you know where their office is?
I know it's upstairs.
Do you recall that you signed an ethics
contract when you started working here?
Yes.
Then you must recall that you are not to
ever receive gifts from patients.
Yes.
Is it true that you received a car from
your patient, Gong Byung Doo?
No, he left it here for me.
I didn't know how to take care of it,
so I needed some time.
This is the car, right?
That's right.
So, you lied.
You already drove the car.
I didn't drive the car.
An accident occurred while I was
getting things sorted out.
Do you want to see my car?
Wow, that's a nice car.
The gift that Gong Byung Doo gave me
is not something I would want.
We're both employees here.
Can't you help me out with this?
I'd like to do that for you.
We'll see what we can do.
[DNR: DO NOT RESUSCITATE]
I don't want you to resuscitate me.
I'm sure the surgery will go well,
but just in case.
I'm older now so it's possible
that I might not wake up.
I don't want to lengthen
my life by force.
[GENERAL SURGERY, NEUROSURGERY,
PLASTIC SURGERY]
What did Director Hong say?
He has us by the throat.
It's the slush fund file.
He found out about your slush fund?
He has been following my movements.
I got this from him for now.
- He just gave it up.
- I made a deal.
I gave you up.
No! I can't give up my position.
We have time until he recovers,
so we need to get rid of the evidence.
With a personality like his,
he must have evidence hidden elsewhere.
Neurosurgeons tend to be
paranoid and persistent.
I hope the surgery doesn't succeed.
Then we'll be free of this.
It's a very hard surgery,
so even Jung Yoon Do won't find it easy.
Are you serious?
How can you say such a thing
even out of anger?
It's because I'm angry
that I'm saying this!
You're here?
Have you had your dinner?
Of course I ate.
Gosh, have you even been
taking care of your health?
Is it time for me to be lectured again?
Your BST was at 300.
It could be temporary. Don't worry.
Did you bring the paperwork for the DNR?
I brought it.
Get me my reading glasses and pen.
Where do I sign?
- Here.
- Okay.
Here.
It's your turn.
Dad, is this really necessary?
I'm only preparing for the very worst.
Don't take it too seriously.
I'm not going to die.
I'm going to retire as
director of the board.
That's good.
You think it's good that
I'm going to be unemployed?
I'll feed you and take care of you.
Once you recover,
you should go on vacations.
I use a lot of money, you know.
How much monthly allowance
are you going to give me?
We have enough money.
Look at you backing down right away.
Go to bed, Dad.
I'll take your glasses.
When you're removing the tumor,
check on the facial nerves frequently.
Make sure not to damage
any of those nerves.
That's right.
I know.
Use the CUSA to get the
central part of the tumor.
You have to be careful not to damage
the lower cranial nerves, as well.
Yes.
Why are you laughing?
The two of you suit each other so well.
We are like that.
A surgeon must be cool-headed
and have a heart that can
withstand all pressure.
As well as deft hands.
Nice words, right?
That's from your book, Doctor.
My surgery is in your hands,
Doctor Jung.
Do a good job.
If you don't do a good job,
he might wake up and do it himself.
What, Doctor?
Stop that now. He might cry.
Doctor, how do you feel?
Well, I'm just all right.
It seemed like you were just laughing.
Weren't you very good, then?
Even if I'm laughing,
I'm just all right.
Oh, that's not good enough.
Doctor, should I do a trick or something?
Okay, then sing a song.
Something upbeat.
Come on, Doctor!
How can I with all these kids here?
How can I sing a song?
That's very upbeat!
This is great!
You should go on up.
- You're not going to watch?
- No.
Where will you be?
Where other patients'
family members wait.
Okay, let's get started.
Scalpel.
Suction.
To the left.
Farther inside.
I found it. Suction.
Use the CUSA to get
the central part of the tumor.
What are you doing?
If you're going to take part like this,
why don't you do the surgery yourself?
Doctor Jung!
I cannot operate under such conditions.
I'm sorry.
Let's start over.
[HONG DOO SHIK]
Is it working?
It's not working.
Yes, it is.
Do you see this?
- Yes.
- We need to push that.
Suction.
Is the surgery going well?
As long as you do the suction well,
it will succeed.
Waiting was difficult, right?
The time was moving so slowly.
I know how that feels.
I will now tell you
the results of the surgery.
It's written all over your face.
Ji Hong, the surgery was a success.
Yes.
Good work.
Yes, well...
Looks like we'll be having dinner.
You said I owed you if you succeeded.
There's no need for that.
No, I did make a promise.
Buy me dinner too if you're buying.
You stay out of it.
Gosh, I thought I was going to die.
It was so hard waiting.
Yes, what is it?
Patient Kim Jin Han is in
a lot of pain and vomiting.
Should I increase the painkillers?
There was nothing wrong in the CT, right?
No.
Wait a little longer.
If the pain still persists,
give her half an ampoule of morphine.
Morphine? Okay.
Where are you right now?
Me?
Oh! Hello.
- Get me a cup ramen too.
- Okay.
Did you put in the order for Kim Jin Han?
Yes.
Is there any kimchi?
Here you go.
You don't have much common sense.
Kimchi is a necessity in cup ramen.
I'm very sorry.
- Were you going to eat it all?
- No.
It's because I'm on a kimchi diet.
There was some research done
on white mice
that showed kimchi is good for diets.
Why would you eat ramen though?
You're a second year,
but you gain weight.
Life must be pretty easy.
Should I help you lose weight?
Eat, eat, eat.
It's so good!
You have to eat ramen with kimchi.
Doctor, if you have
something to say, just say it.
Stop playing around.
- I came to do business.
- What?
Sooni Hawaii is a cafe my friend owns.
I want you guys to go often.
This is kind of weird, right?
I know it is.
She's a really close friend,
so let me off the hook.
You can eat this.
What was that? That was cute.
She's unexpectedly charming.
I'm going to start living at
Sooni Hawaii from now on.
Okay, just live there and you can
have your bones buried there.
Deal.
I'm relieved that Director Hong regained
consciousness and his vitals are stable.
Yes.
Gosh, let's try to be friends.
You always give me a short reply.
Either that or you dump me.
I didn't dump you.
Anyway, you're saying I'm not the guy.
I'm trying to heal that wound
by talking about it like this.
The doors are now closing.
Senior, are you all right?
I don't what you're
referring to, but I'm fine.
You stabbed a person in the heart,
but you're doing fine.
You're perfectly okay?
Yoo Hye Jung, the guy that likes you
is a lowly person like this.
He said he'd take anything from me
except for slapping his face.
Yes.
I'll get going first.
Wait for me.
Why would you follow me?
I have to live too.
How can I be in the same space as her?
I really hate being like this
with Seo Woo.
Do you think I enjoy it?
You don't have to.
Seo Woo is pretty.
Why did you reject her?
Then, why did you reject me, Doctor Yoo?
I know Seo Woo creates a problem for you,
but don't only think about your survival.
I'm done living for other people.
I can seduce men if I want to and
I can become a femme fatale.
- You can never become that way.
- Why?
People who really intend on
living that way don't announce it.
They just do it.
You don't know me that well yet.
I've already done it.
He was just talking and now he's asleep.
He's like a baby.
Please keep a
close eye on him, Nurse Yoo.
Okay.
Thank you, Nurse Yoo.
Were you really going to exclude me
and take Doctor Jung out for dinner?
Seriously, what's with you?
I'm just happy to get this over with.
Yes, this is Kim Tae Ho.
Yes, Doctor Yoo Hye Jung is
a fellow in our department.
What?
That can't be true.
I will check with her.
That day and time work for me.
Okay.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung is being called
before a disciplinary committee.
I don't know what it's about.
She returned the car.
Isn't it a bit overboard to call a
disciplinary committee over this?
I didn't want things to
go this far either.
The person who called in the tip
was too powerful.
Who was it?
Is that person more powerful than me?
It was Doctor Jin Seo Woo.
The hospital director's daughter.
Yes?
Come on in.
Sit down.
It's been a very long time since
just the two us met like this.
How have you been
adjusting to the hospital?
Yes, it's been okay.
I got a call from the
internal audit team.
They wanted to set a date for you to
go before the disciplinary committee.
I am one of the committee members.
They say Gong Byung Doo gave you
a foreign car as a gift.
Is that true?
It is true.
I wanted to give it back to him,
but I couldn't find a way to return it.
Of course, I don't believe that you
accepted that car with strings attached.
However, the committee members
won't all agree with me.
There is a thing called
a "strange coincidence."
It's best not get into
situations that arouse suspicion.
It was a stone that came
rolling your way.
I was careless.
You may have to take a pay cut.
Or a suspension, at least.
Worst case scenario,
you may have to leave the hospital.
Do you want to go for coffee?
I'm sure you were in a good mood
after your father's surgery.
I ruined it, right?
I wasn't thinking that at all.
You should go home and rest.
Today was a tiring day.
I'm not tired. You must be exhausted.
I bet you want to go home and rest.
Yes, I do.
Then, go rest.
I looked into the disciplinary committee
and I can go too, as a board member.
So don't worry too much.
I'm not worried.
It's not my goal to
remain in this hospital.
Yeah, you shouldn't
take it too seriously.
Doctor, are you okay
with everything I do?
Yes, I'm okay.
That's a fantasy.
Even with parents and children,
everything cannot be okay.
Why are you being so cold to me suddenly?
Just because.
Doctor! Doctor Choi, Doctor Choi!
What, what, what?
Doctor Yoo is going to
get disciplined because of us.
That's what the internal audit was about?
- Yes.
- Darn it.
Good. You should be punished
if you did something wrong.
That's how the world works.
You'll be hit by a boomerang, Chief.
Is this place some sort of
water cooler?
Is the station a place for
you guys to gossip?
I thought he was too quiet lately.
Hey, you. What are you whispering about?
It's nothing.
How is Kim Yi Chul's mental state?
It's drowsy.
Why isn't it on the chart, then?
You're all too busy playing around here!
Kang Kyung Joon, follow me.
Doctor, it's not that we want to gossip.
Something big happened,
so we had to discuss it.
What is it?
If it turns out to be nothing,
you'll be punished for one week.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung is being called
before the disciplinary committee...
Tell me all the details.
Why are you stopping in the middle?
Okay, so... so...
Stop stuttering!
Boss came to the hospital
because he was hurt, right?
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung
performed surgery on him.
The surgery went well and
he wanted to thank her...
- Do you know?
- I know.
Do you even know what I'm
talking about before answering?
You're talking about
the disciplinary committee.
Well, it's nice that you
understand very quickly.
I got rejected by Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
- You knew that would happen?
- Yes.
Do you know how long I've known her?
We're still only in the flirtation stage.
I see. She's at a very high level.
You are amazing to even be
at a flirtation stage.
Right? I think I'm amazing too.
I'm still going to like her though.
I'm not going to do anything
because it seems low.
If I see any room between you two,
I'm going to make my move.
Okay.
I got rejected.
Aren't you going to console me?
Buy me dinner.
You said you'd buy me dinner.
I can't today. I'm meeting someone.
He always leaves first.
Hello, there.
I'm Hong Ji Hong.
Sorry to make you come all this way.
Oh no! No need to be sorry.
I'm Section Chief of General Surgery,
Kim Chi Hyun.
- Let's sit down.
- Okay.
It's an honor to meet you.
To meet the son of the board director
and a renowned neurosurgeon like you.
What would you like to eat?
You're uploading more?
I'm getting a very good response.
If this gets turned into a movie,
I could rake in a lot of money.
What will you do with that money?
I should give some to
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
I feel bad about
the disciplinary committee.
You just feel bad?
I don't have any money right now.
I didn't know it at the time.
I didn't realize the threat that was
coming for the female doctor.
I'll be taking a break
before the next installment.
Gangster Female Doctor is so good.
Why are you going on a break?
Wow! People really anticipate it.
I told you so.
Okay, let's just go.
Doctor Yoo was promoting a business.
Is Doctor Yoo running a business?
Can we order something?
Hello!
Hello, cute doctor.
- I'm here too.
- Yes, I know.
But...
is our Doctor Pi Young Gook not here?
No, can you give us some ramen?
You must like ramen a lot.
You could make some in the hospital.
You should save your money
since you're a resident.
- Yes.
- Is there anything like rice?
Yes, come on.
- Sit here.
- Okay.
- I'll bring you a menu.
Thank you.
- Can I help you with anything?
- Oh! You scared me!
Yes, you can help me.
What can I do?
Please move your face aside.
Don't try to comfort me.
Don't comfort me.
I'm extremely curious what it is
that you wanted to talk to me about.
You were part of the team that
operated on this patient, right?
I wanted to hear the details
of what happened that day.
Oh, I can't remember it very well.
It's been so long.
It's rare for a table death to occur
for stomach cancer.
I think you would remember that.
There was a young woman who came by
who was the patient's guardian.
Do you have a connection to her?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I was very close to the person
that passed away.
Ah, I see.
Gosh, I'm suddenly feeling so fatigued.
Hello.
Seriously, why are you showing up
so early and ruining my day?
If you don't want me showing up,
you could just tell me.
Gosh, seriously!
- Do you want something to drink?
- No, thank you.
I'm here because you didn't call.
There was excessive bleeding
during the surgery, right?
Why do you think that?
I saw people running in panic,
holding blood packs.
There is more than one operating room.
Did you touch her liver
or was a blood vessel cut?
I really can't converse with you.
Do you know why I'm even talking to you?
What's your relationship to
Professor Hong Ji Hong?
He has nothing to do with this.
So, you do know him.
Professor Hong said he didn't know you.
You acted like you had a great cause
and you wanted to find out the truth.
Then you used Professor Hong
to threaten me.
This is extremely upsetting to me.
Please leave.
I'll be back again.
I'll keep coming back.
Come in.
Good morning.
Why did you do it?
I was very clear with you.
I said this was my own assignment.
I told you to stay out of it.
That young woman came again,
Kang Mal Soon's guardian.
I told you to be more aggressive.
Professor Hong Ji Hong wanted to
meet me last night.
If Professor Hong is involved in this,
I can't ignore it and let it go.
What?
What would happen to me if I got on
Director Hong's bad side?
Director Hong is going to retire.
You just need to listen to me.
That woman said she's going to come back.
A person who wanted to resolve it
through law would be easier.
Why is Hong Ji Hong involved?
Are you this angry because I met up
with Section Chief Kim Chi Hyun?
Yes.
It's easier and faster
if we do it together
rather than you, alone.
You do everything with Soon Hee.
It's no different than that.
Then, why don't you tell me anything?
You sent me off earlier
when we were fishing.
I didn't ask you about it.
It was because the hospital got audited
by the tax administration.
You didn't even tell me
your father was ill.
I heard it from someone else.
Who am I to you?
That's because I thought you would worry.
I feel the same way.
Why should you have to go through
hardships because of me?
It's not hard.
It's not hard for me either.
Why won't you share your worries with me?
It's because I've never shared
my worries with anyone before.
I've always made decisions on my own.
It's become a habit.
It has nothing to do with you.
It does...
if you and I are to start a relationship
as man and woman.
You say we should do everything together.
So why do you want to
stick to your old habits?
Is that love?
That's just being a burden.
I'm not going to be in a burdensome love.
In the past, he gave me
the desire to become a good person.
Being a good person is different than
being a good man or woman.
Subtitles by DramaFever