(Episode 11)
You try to persuade me that we should do everything together.
Then why can't you give up your habit?
Do you think that's love?
That's just burdening each other.
I have no interest in such love.
True love helps you realise your true self.
She woke up something in me that I didn't know existed.
I had no idea I was this kind of man.
Hello.
I'm hanging up if you're not saying anything.
The number is from this hospital.
(INCOMING CALL)
Say something if you called.
Hello.
Hye Jung.
It's President Jin, isn't it?
- Do you know me?
- Of course I do.
You're President Jin of Gukil Medical Center.
I didn't know you'd call.
(OPERATION RECORD)
What does she have to do with Hong Ji Hong?
(DISCIPLINARY ACTION REQUEST)
What's this?
Yes, the auditing team asked for it.
Yoo Hye Jung of the Department of Neurosurgery?
She took a bribe for compensation?
What did she take?
She seems to have accepted a car from a patient.
I thought she accepted something outrageous. That's nothing.
That's what I said,
- but the informant is...
- Who was it?
It's Dr Jin Seo Woo.
Gosh.
- Wait a second.
- Hurry!
Why isn't she answering?
Why do you still have all these patients here? Where's Dr Jo?
She was supposed to be here, but she isn't answering her phone.
- I came without answering my phone.
- I'm sorry.
- Where's the patient?
- Over there.
I'm here. You'll be okay.
What happened?
I suddenly got hit by a car.
Where does it hurt the most?
My stomach hurts the most.
Let me take a look.
I think it's a contusion. Do a CT scan.
Okay, got it.
- Please save her.
- Calm down.
I'll die without her.
I told you to calm down.
How can you say that? I can't live without her.
You have to calm down. She'll be okay.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Please hurry!
We have patients streaming in today.
You can't go in there.
I have to be next to my wife.
- I have to be with her.
- Please calm down.
Can you tell me what happened to your wife?
I heard she rolled down the stairs at work.
I think she lost her footing.
Was she unconscious since then?
I'll be right next to you.
Don't worry. I'll be right here with you.
Honey.
- Oh, no.
- Please calm down.
I'll just look at her.
What should I do?
I think she's seriously hurt.
Let me see her.
- When did you get here?
- I must have woken you up.
I brought you the dumplings you like from Hongeun-dong.
We used to order them all the time when I was in high school.
Get back to work.
Don't worry about me.
How can I not when I'm worried? Would you like to try some?
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
I call myself your father,
but you grew up on your own.
I relied on you more than you did on me.
When we first met,
you told me I was like a junior in middle school.
You were immature when you were with me...
while you were strict with everyone else.
I'm sorry.
Why would you say that?
I think this is the first time in my life,
resting on a bed like this.
I'd like to see you get married...
before I die.
You'll see your grandchildren.
I'd really like that.
What's with you today?
I don't know.
It must be the female hormones that are making me cry.
Come on.
I don't normally do things like this because it makes me cringe.
I always loved having you as a father...
and I still love it.
I loved it too.
In Joo.
- Enjoying your first day at work?
- What do you think?
I'm sorry. I shouldn't have asked something so obvious.
I heard Chairman Hong had surgery. Why didn't you tell me?
You told me not to bother you until you started work.
Let's get a drink later with Ji Hong.
Sounds good.
I'm going to go see Chairman Hong first. My heart broke for him.
Ji Hong was just here.
Your blood pressure is normal.
Do you feel any pain in your head?
No, it's fine.
What is it on a scale from one to 10?
You're definitely a neurosurgeon. You're very meticulous.
This is interesting. It's what I used to ask my patients.
It's a three.
- That's fine then.
- Yes.
Chairman Hong, it's In Joo.
Hi, In Joo.
It must be your first day.
Yes, I did.
You shouldn't do this. Who cares if you were the best surgeon?
You didn't even take care of your own health.
Stop that. Ji Hong scolded me enough.
Meet Dr Yoo Hye Jung.
She's a fellow at the Department of Neurosurgery.
- Hi.
- You've grown a lot.
You look good.
We've met before.
(NEUROSURGERY, CHOI KANG SOO)
Take it, and you can leave.
A doctor's priority should be patients.
Got it.
I should've come seen you earlier.
- I was busy with life.
- And you should be.
You should be busy when you're young.
The bleeding from the liver injury is too severe.
Okay.
A 30-year-old female patient rolled down stairs and was brought here.
Her CT scan shows a fraction in her calvaria...
and an epidural haemorrhage three times her bone.
I suspect a damaged superior sagittal sinus.
Her pupils are normal, but her limbs don't show any motor response.
She lost too much blood due to her liver injury,
so a general surgeon is coming right away.
Does she live in a flat?
I don't know.
What stairs did she fall down from?
He's the patient's husband.
Hello.
Doctor.
It's all my fault.
I shouldn't have let her go to work.
Did she fall down the stairs at work?
- Yes.
- We took a CT.
I'll explain the results soon. Bear with us for a while.
Sure.
Ms Cho. Ms Cho.
Shall I call Prof. Hong?
Yes, and book an operating room.
Okay.
We need to do an emergency operation.
The bleeding's bad. Don't you have to as well?
Call your doctor. We need to decide who will go first.
Yes, Doctor.
Vitals?
When she came in, BP was 90 over 60, pulse was 95.
She came into the ER.
An abdominal CT shows grade three liver damage...
with active bleeding.
She needs emergency surgery.
Okay, I'm coming.
(CHO SOO JI)
What about her history?
Nothing worth noting.
Book an OR and call Anaesthesiology.
I already did.
- Good.
- General Surgery's joining us.
We have to consult their doctor.
The liver's bleeding heavily. You have to decide...
who should operate first.
Very well. I get it.
Can't you even brief me?
You're terrible.
Why didn't you tell me she'd hurt her head too?
Sorry.
In Joo.
I heard you'd be joining us. When did you start?
Today. Let's have a drink with Pa Ran.
We meet again.
You two should talk. I'll prepare for surgery.
She doesn't look so happy.
Are you dating?
No, don't answer that.
I don't want to know yet.
You still ask questions and answer them yourself.
As if I'd change.
What should we do?
We'll go first. The bleeding is critical.
Where is it?
The superior sagittal sinus.
We need to rush as well. Wrap it up in two hours.
Two hours? Okay.
Set things up after they're done and call me.
Yes, Doctor.
(CHO SOO JI)
Prof. Hong, this is the patient's guardian.
Hello. Have a look.
The white parts here are all bleeding.
It's putting pressure on the brain.
If we don't operate now,
her brain will be damaged forever.
Can you get rid of all the blood?
Yes. That doctor will explain the rest to you.
Come with me.
I'll explain the surgery and the details of the consent form.
What are you doing here?
Honey.
You can't do this.
You can't leave me.
Even if you die...
Even if you die, you are still mine.
Don't ever say you want to lave me again.
Okay?
Are you listening?
Are you?
You can't come in here.
I just...
wanted to see her before the surgery.
You don't have to worry.
Prof. Hong's a great doctor.
Take good care of her.
We will.
Do you want to join us for drinks later?
You know In Joo.
Are you trying to be The Giving Tree?
- What?
- Or Daddy Long Legs?
You should be angry with me. That's the usual response.
Nothing's as infuriating as being misunderstood.
I'm not your usual guy.
This is infuriating, though.
Gown, please.
Okay.
Drill, please.
Ji Hong's assistant.
Dr Yoo Hye Jung. Do you know her?
Are they dating?
Are they?
Keep irrigating and suctioning.
Okay.
Change the drill bit.
- Prepare a lot of gauze.
- Okay.
Thanks.
Have you seen a case like this before?
- No.
- This requires a wide opening.
Blood will gush out.
You need to secure a visual.
Elevator.
- Irrigation.
- Got it.
Bipolar.
BP's dropping. Squeeze the blood. Anaesthesiology.
I'm so scared.
These things scare powerless people like me.
What if we get fired?
Why would we get fired?
My position's temporary anyway.
Yours isn't, so you must be scared.
That's not funny.
Why are you here?
Sir.
- What is it?
- We have something to tell you.
Go on, then.
The car Dr Yoo got as a gift.
It's our fault she couldn't return it.
She wanted to as soon as she got it.
I had a life-long thing about expensive cars, so...
Okay. You can go.
Will nothing happen, then?
- Thank you.
(DISCIPLINARY ACTION REQUEST)
More gauze.
The BP's still falling.
It's fine. Get a larger suction tip.
Prepare a heamopad.
Where's the heamopad?
Gauze.
Irrigation.
We got it under control now, right?
Ji Hong is still the same.
So? Do you still love him like back in the old days?
Stop talking nonsense. Am I still in my 20s?
- Wrap it up.
- Yes, Professor.
Call Prof. Jo In Joo and let her know the surgery is almost over.
Yes, Professor.
There's no need. I'll coming down now.
What is wrong with your shirt?
I'll need to take it off when I give up my presidency anyway.
Don't you trust me?
We're taking 1 step back to take 2 steps forward.
Look at the bigger picture.
I haven't told you, but I've been keeping files on all patients...
whose cases could be seen as medical accidents.
Chairman Hong viewed the file on one of those cases.
Why did you keep those files? You should've disposed of them.
I've altered the record so that it won't cause trouble for us.
You should've spent that time to just get rid of it.
It's my record.
I treasure every part of my life.
Making mistakes is what makes us human.
That was one crazy remark.
Did you come this far because you're smart?
You wouldn't be where you are now if it weren't for my support.
Why did you do such a bizarre thing like a lunatic?
Why aren't you answering?
- I'm sorry.
- Let's go. We should visit Doo Sik.
It hasn't been two hours yet, right? I kept my word.
They're still finishing up.
All the finishing touches were supposed to be completed too.
It'll be done in time. The fellow is very capable.
We'll see. There's only five minutes left.
See?
Don't blow your own horn.
(OPERATING ROOM)
- The surgery went well.
- Thank you so much.
But the damage was severe,
so we're not sure whether she'll fully regain consciousness or not.
So is there a chance that she might not fully recover?
We won't be able to tell you exactly until she wakes up.
Could I see her now?
She's in the recovery room now.
She'll be transferred to the ICU when she wakes up.
Then I guess I can see her there.
Thank you very much again.
(DISCIPLINARY ACTION REQUEST)
(DR KIM TAE HO)
Did that patient's fever go down at all?
Yes. The fever reducer made it go down a bit,
but it's still at 39°C.
We still need to do all-culture and septic lab, right?
Yes, they will get the results this morning.
- Yes.
- Is there any way to make them...
withdraw the disciplinary action against Dr Yoo?
I'll meet with President Jin about it. Have you met him before?
I just introduced myself briefly.
I see. You'll deal with him a lot,
so you may want to get to know him better.
All right.
Are you okay?
You seem to be in the pink.
I was very worried, so I'm relieved to see you looking well.
- Did I let you down?
- Yes.
Please recognise all of the contributions I've made.
Myung Hoon.
If I hadn't, I wouldn't have kept you in that role for this long.
We both know that you're doing a good job.
We just want you to take a short break.
- It's good to see you.
- Hello.
Thanks to you, I don't have to worry about Doo Sik as much.
I've always been worried about him because he never got married.
I'm so glad that you two became family.
Thank you for your concern.
Visit me in my office too.
I won't be the president for long, but let's be on good terms.
As you know, our families are close.
Sure. I'll visit you often.
Then we'll get going now. Doo Sik.
- Take good care of yourself.
- All right. See you later.
So now, will Gukil Medical Center be ruled by Prof. Hong and Dr Kim?
Do you have no pride?
- Why were you like that with him?
- What can I do?
I have to pretend to be on my knees in order to survive this battle.
How many times do I have to tell you to trust me? We'll find proof soon!
Why do you keep visiting me like this?
No reason.
It doesn't look like President Jin wants to step down yet.
You're not planning it by yourself, are you?
People will side with those who will help them earn money.
Chairman of Jungsoo Jung Il Sung, Congressman Nam In Soo,
Sung Jong and Myung Hoon...
are working on founding Gukil Medical Corporation.
The four of them share the same ambition and greed.
Why is Jungsoo Insurance involved?
They're expanding their private insurance programmes...
to prepare for privatisation of medical insurance.
Let me handle looking into the case about your shares.
No, you shouldn't get involved.
I'll take sole responsibility and end it myself.
Just be a good doctor.
That's who you are.
(DAD)
- Hi, Dad.
- I heard that you...
reported the fellow getting a gift from a patient to Internal Affairs.
Yes.
Let me hear what you have to say before I accept your request.
Do you know who tipped off Internal Affairs?
It was me.
You once said that my speciality...
is ruining people's lives by using the invisible majority.
I no longer do such things.
Do you feel falsely accused?
Do you want to ask why it should be a problem when other doctors...
- also get gifts from patients?
- No.
Regardless of how it happened, it was my mistake.
I don't like you.
All right. Be upfront about disliking me.
Be honest about hating me. I prefer that.
I like that you don't deceive anyone at least.
You hover around me and get what I want so easily.
Hadn't I met you,
I would've been able to become a much better person.
You think I get things easily?
No matter how hard I try, it wouldn't be as easy as for you.
What?
I didn't ask you to hate me.
You're responsible for your own feelings.
It goes the same for liking someone.
I never asked you to feel that way.
Why do you have to take it out on me?
You're right.
You never asked me to feel that way.
You never told me to like him.
Why am I like this?
What I want to know is why you had to report it.
Did you want to get credit for it? Or are you not fond of that fellow?
It's one of our rules. We cannot accept gifts from patients.
So your intention was to get credit for it?
Valuing such useless things is what I despise the most.
Why is it useless? To sustain any organisation...
You had to do this when I told you to focus on growing your power?
I told you to be friendly with everyone.
Will people like you if they find out that you reported it?
I like the fellow who received that gift.
She's going to be very successful.
You should bring her sometime.
Why aren't you saying anything?
You should be hanging out with people like that.
You should learn from her. Learn!
Let's see.
She bled a lot,
so get a CT scan again within 12 hours.
And while he's on respirator, check ABGA every day.
Look out for draining when you do dressing.
Yes, Professor.
By the way, why isn't she waking up?
She might still be under the influence of anaesthesia.
It still hasn't been too long, so let's wait a little more.
Okay.
You're here.
- Hey.
- Hello.
- Are you the guardian?
- Yes. I am her husband.
Her liver wasn't badly damaged,
but due to her ruptured hepatic artery, and she lost a lot of blood.
But we stopped the bleeding well, so don't worry too much.
Thank you.
- Is she awake?
- She's not awake yet.
Follow up on the CT scan.
There can be delayed bleeding, so observe her carefully.
- Okay.
- Don't be slack...
because she's in our department. Come and check her often.
Okay, Professor.
Okay.
Don't nag my resident. That's my job.
- Aren't you done for the day?
- I am.
Do you want to come later too?
No, I have something to do.
Did you fight?
But you don't fight with anyone.
I don't want to fight, but she keeps starting a fight.
That's a good thing.
That means she loves you.
I kept doing that to you before.
I think you subconsciously refuse...
someone getting deeply involved in your life.
When a man and a woman love each other...
and when they can't get involved in each other's life deeply,
they become lonely.
You sound like a philosopher.
I was once married, and I got a divorce.
It's a nice timing for some philosophy.
See you later.
Right.
In the past, I had made a mistake to Hye Jung.
I was too young...
to take care of her.
- I am sorry.
- What are you talking about?
(DR KIM TAE HO)
Yes, Doctor.
I met with President Jin,
regarding the disciplinary action.
I am sorry.
I acted foolish, and it caused you such an inconvenience.
I'll comply with a disciplinary action,
so you don't have to worry.
You never know what's going to happen in life.
President is not going to hold this against you.
I'll tell you what's even better.
It seems like he's very fond of you.
Now, let's put all of it behind.
Thank you.
Thank Prof. Hong.
He tried to help you a lot with this case.
Usually when he helps someone,
he only gets involved when he has a direct control.
But this time, he asked me for a favour.
Come in.
I just came from Dr Kim's office.
I heard you asked him to help me.
I heard from In Joo that she had...
made a mistake to you in the past. Why didn't you tell me?
Don't change the subject.
What happened between In Joo and me stays between us.
There's nothing to tell you.
Hye Jung, I am so flustered to see you acting like this.
Be genuine with me,
and please come to terms with your self as well.
Do you know why I said I'd do my homework alone?
It's because I didn't want to put you in danger because of me.
I'm trying my best to stop you from entering the dark part of my life.
I know that you are a person who'd give me everything you have...
and even look for things you don't have.
If I receive everything you give me,
I wouldn't be able to live without you.
You'd have a control over my entire life.
You give me everything,
and yet you aren't letting me in even just a little.
I want to give everything to the man I love too.
I want to go deep into his life...
and dominate his life.
But you...
do everything alone.
You don't need anyone other than yourself.
What happens when you no longer...
love me?
That will never happen.
You can never say never.
Do you know what I'm the most afraid of?
Being abandoned.
What do you want me to do?
Change.
I don't believe in love between a man and a woman.
But if I have to be in love with someone,
that person would be Prof. Hong.
Jung Yoon Do, you loser.
(DR YOO HYE JUNG)
(DR JUNG YOON DO)
Yes, Doctor.
- Dr Yoo.
- Yes.
You know that I'm a fickle-minded loser, right?
Of course I know.
You said if you have to love a man,
that man's going to be Prof. Hong.
But that means you don't love anyone yet.
What do you mean?
I'm going to go where my heart takes me...
even if it's a messy road.
Good night.
What do you want me to do?
Change.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
All right.
Let's go.
- When are you having lunch?
- I'm not sure.
Hello. You're awake.
Do you hear me?
Please blink your eyes if you can hear him.
All right. Try following my finger with your eyes.
You understand everything and move your eyes.
Can you open your mouth wide?
Can you move your finger for us?
Do you feel me holding your hand?
All right, thank you.
- Let's get an MRI scan.
- Okay.
(RADIOGRAPHY ROOM)
What do you see?
I see a damaged brain stem.
What do you think it is?
It's locked-in syndrome.
If it's locked-in syndrome,
are you saying that she is conscious,
but cannot move as if she's locked inside her body?
That's right. It's what she's suffering from.
I've only read it in books. This is my first time seeing it.
We need more time to be sure, but it seems most likely right now.
Can she get better?
There's a very low possibility.
But there are cases where the patient recovered miraculously.
Let's keep an eye on her. Explain it to her husband.
- Okay.
- Good.
You come to see me too often. It doesn't feel good.
Why not?
It makes me feel like I received my death sentence.
I can't believe how bad you are at understanding how I feel.
I won't come see you any more.
I'll only come when you beg me to.
Whatever you want. I'm fine with that.
I feel so bad for the husband.
He's been here day and night without even going to work.
At least she's alive.
He has hope as long as she is alive.
He'll endure it if he really loves her.
I think he really does love her.
All the female neurosurgeons are saying that he's their type...
because he only has eyes for her.
Hello.
What's going to happen to her?
She isn't talking, and I don't think she can move at all.
Calm down, and let's have a seat over there.
Do you think I can calm down?
She's lying there like a corpse.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
It's not as bad as I thought.
You can think and feel everything,
but you just can't move or express yourself.
Oh, right. You used to love to dance.
You won't be able to dance again.
But that's fine with me.
Now I don't have to see you laugh and dance with other guys, right?
You can open your eyes.
Open your eyes.
I love you.
Make sure you keep Kim Jin Hwan's pain under control.
- Give him antibiotics first.
- Okay.
Why are you avoiding me?
I didn't avoid you.
Tell him we'll start radiation treatment next week.
Okay.
There he goes.
- Who?
- What?
She's talking about the husband of the locked-in syndrome patient.
I see.
He's amazing.
He's so sweet and only has eyes for one woman.
I know that kind of man who only has eyes for one woman.
Who is it?
- Is it Dr Jung Yoon Do?
- He's a piece of trash.
Why am I even standing here when you have nothing nice to say?
Dr Jin is the only one who can scare Dr Jung.
Dr Jung turned Dr Jin down.
- What did she see in him?
- He's the full package.
Seo Woo.
You're at work. It's a public place.
I don't want people gossiping about you.
Why? Do people gossip about Dr Jung rejecting me?
Yes.
This is embarrassing.
- Why am I hung up on a man?
- It's because you're a girl.
You always have a clear answer to everything.
You're right. It's because I'm a girl.
You should change your taste in men.
You won't find a man you can respect.
Here is your food.
Why did you cancel on us yesterday?
I'm sure you two got a drink.
Soon Hee.
Mr Hong!
Hello.
Don't you remember me? I remember you.
Goodness, you're starting again.
We'll meet again.
Go out with me the third time we meet.
Sure!
Is the business going well?
Yes, it's going pretty well.
By the way, didn't Hye Jung come with you?
I think she's sulking.
She won't sulk for no reason. I'm sure you did something wrong.
Fine, it's my fault.
I forgot you girls are best friends. Give me many delicious things.
All right.
I know that you can think.
I also know that you can feel.
Only you can open the door that's been shut.
You have to keep moving forward.
You must.
Help me.
(CHAIRMAN HONG DOO SIK)
Please give us some privacy.
What brings you here at this hour?
- Are you feeling all right?
- I'm okay.
Tell me. How can you do this to me?
What did you say as you were handing me the file on my slush funds?
You said that's all you have.
- So what?
- What?
Did you just say "so what"?
That wasn't the only file you had on my slush funds!
I rummaged through your office and found a copy!
What did you do?
What did Myung Hoon do so wrong?
Who grew this hospital this much?
Growing the hospital just filled up your greedy bellies.
It hasn't benefited us in any way.
It just looks good on the surface.
Why did we become like this?
That's precisely what I want to say.
Your son has you wrapped around his finger.
When you age,
your children's goals become your own goals.
I think that's where our paths diverged.
You've lost your mind.
The war begins now.
The two of us, Ji Hong and Myung Hoon. Let's have a showdown.
I told you to leave the kids out of it!
Then why are you targeting Myung Hoon like that?
Do you think I'll leave Ji Hong alone?
Hey, wait. Sung Jong.
Sung Jong! Gosh...
Sung Jong! Sung...
Cheers, guys.
- Cheers!
This makes me happy. I love drinking.
In Joo is the best drinker out of the three of us.
I come after her, and you come dead last.
Do you know how hard it is for me to keep up with your pace?
Hold on a second. And quit drinking already.
(DR KIM TAE HO)
- Yes, Dr Kim.
- Where are you now?
Sooni Hawaii.
Come here now. It's about Chairman Hong.
I need to go to the hospital.
- Hey! Where are you going?
- Wait! Where are you going?
Oh, Mr Hong...
Did he exhibit any signs of this?
It's cardiac embolic cerebral infarction.
Blood clots have formed in the left carotid artery.
Let's hurry.
Let's call Dr Jung Yoon Do...
and book his angiogram first.
Kyung Joon, take my father back to his room.
Okay.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
Code Blue. Doctors to the VIP ward on the 17th floor.
- Code Blue. To the VIP ward.
- It's Father.
Hey.
What's going on?
It looks like arrhythmia has caused ventricular fibrillation.
His blood pressure is dropping.
Bring the defibrillator.
Chairman Hong has signed the DNR confirmation form.
I do not want cardiopulmonary resuscitation.
Bring it!
That's not what Chairman Hong wants.
I might not be able to wake up because of my age.
I do not want to be forced into being resuscitated.
It's arrest.
Please bring the defibrillator.
Bring the defibrillator!
200 joules. Charge it.
Shock!
Clear.
One, two, three, four, five...
To a man, a father...
is someone he identifies himself with.
Losing a father...
is like losing oneself.
That day, I lost myself.
(DOCTORS)
Don't you have to win her heart when Prof. Hong isn't around?
You regret it, don't you?
You really don't know men.
You need to enter his life now.
You know nothing about dating, do you?
What do you mean by that?
I kept thinking about you.
I waited for your call.
I want to be in your life.
I'll stay by your side.
Can I?