(Episode 12)
Dad.
I'm sorry.
(Hong Doo Sik)
Cells that make up the human body...
constantly maintain a state of instability.
Being alive is unstable.
In the end, the essence of life is change.
Father always told me this.
Making decisions and taking responsibility is a man's duty.
It's a new beginning.
(Three weeks later)
(Gukil Medical Centre)
When dawn breaks on the window.
My heart becomes.
Bigger than yesterday.
On the frosted window.
I write and erase.
You.
I love you.
Open your eyes.
You used to love this song.
I'm singing and washing for you. You should look at me.
Gosh, you're so selfish.
Hello, Doctor.
She's not even opening her eyes.
I think something's wrong.
She's all right.
Ms Cho, please open your eyes.
Ma'am, please follow my fingers with your eyes.
- Kang Soo.
-  Yes, Doctor.
- Check her motor status often.
Prof. Hong is coming in this afternoon, right?
I think he's making me look after his patient far too long.
He doesn't contact me, so I'm not sure.
You don't contact him?
Have you not spoken to him since he left to the States...
to settle the inheritance issue?
Yes.
I see. You can always speak to him first.
I can't because I might distract him.
Distract him from what?
He might want to be alone.
You really know nothing about men.
If you really love the person and you want to keep him,
you should get involved in his life right now.
The timing is perfect.
- Is that right?
-  Why am I teaching her this?
Dr Jung, have you eaten?
- Why?
-  I need someone for advice.
You're new to dating, aren't you?
- What's that?
-  You definitely are.
Prof. Hong must have a hard time.
He deserves it.
(International Arrivals)
- Welcome.
-  You didn't have to pick me up.
I thought you'd be sobbing, but you're talking instead.
Did you get everything done?
Almost everything. There was a lot to do.
Shall we eat at the hospital?
It's Director Jin's inauguration.
The food will be good.
Let's eat somewhere else.
Shouldn't you attend? You're on the board.
I missed my father's inauguration. I'll skip this one.
- Will you ignore him, then?
-  I'll say hi.
Okay. It's great to see you again.
It's way too hot for that.
Let's go to the hospital.
Hello.
Congratulations.
I'll need your help.
Do your best for me.
Especially you.
Let's all go inside.
Gukil Medical Centre's Director Hong Doo Sik,
a great neurosurgeon, has passed.
"My patients are family," he said.
With that, he spent his life working tirelessly to advance...
Korean medicine.
He is now a legend of neurosurgery.
You led a beautiful life,
and we will never forget you.
(2nd Director Inauguration, Jin Sung Jong)
I was...
a friend of the previous director...
and his work partner.
I promise to carry on his legacy...
as I lead Gukil Medical Centre and Gukil Foundation...
into the future.
(2nd Director Inauguration, Jin Sung Jong)
Here you go. These are for you.
What are these?
Rice cakes and towels to celebrate the inauguration.
Rice cakes? Nice.
Is this it?
It's a simple affair.
Is our stash finally here?
Hello, Doctor.
Have some rice cakes.
Dr Pi, check on Patient Lee Sang Hoon. He's in pain.
- Okay. Come with me.
-  Sure.
- See you.
-  Bye.
- What are you doing?
-  What?
Why are you always eating something?
Sorry.
Why are you here?
Are you studying for your exams instead of working?
No, not at all.
Why do you study when you're going to fail it anyway?
Didn't I tell you to get Patient Kim Mi Ae to sign the consent form?
I'm curious. Did I or did I not?
I have to go to the ward to change the dressing.
I was going to ask her to sign it then.
- Then?
-  Yes.
Go!
- Sorry.
-  Those fools.
They'll look for any excuse to waste time.
We got quite a few this time.
Excuse me.
He's here.
I brought you some food.
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
I should thank you.
You look after my wife so well...
whenever I'm away.
Why don't you hire a caretaker?
It is exhausting, to be honest,
but being with her puts me at ease.
Eat up.
Thank you.
"It is exhausting, to be honest,"
"but being with her puts me at ease."
I got the chills. Isn't he so nice?
No, he isn't.
Now I have the chills.
He's jealous.
Don't be silly. That's not love.
He should work hard and love hard.
Who will pay the bills?
He's a freelancer. A freelancer.
There are many kinds of freelancers.
Not all of them earn a lot.
Why are you all so negative?
- What?
-  She's right.
I've never seen...
such a dedicated husband since I became a nurse.
It's so beautiful.
What is so beautiful?
Being around someone all day is a nightmare.
I just can't understand men.
What's wrong? Are you sick?
No, I'm fine.
When did you get back? Is it over?
Yes, and I was bored to death.
Did you check on Lee Sang Hoon?
Yes. I gave him a painkiller.
Come in.
Hello.
- Have a seat.
-  Thanks.
No need for tea. We had snacks after the inauguration.
- I see.
-  Did I disturb you?
I was working.
Try lying just to be polite.
I know you're a perfect guy, but it's not an excuse.
Sorry.
How are things with Seo Woo?
We decided to break up.
It's not over just because you two say it is.
You have parents. You aren't an orphan.
I have to go somewhere.
You'll never find another girl like her.
I know I'm her mother, but I believe that she's a gem.
I really don't want the parents to get involved.
I'll talk to my family.
Wait until you're older. Family is all you'll have.
Thanks for the advice.
I want my daughter to be happy as a woman.
Owning a hospital will only cause headaches.
I don't see why they're forcing it on her.
What will you do with Tae Ho? Will you keep him on?
Yes. I like having smart people like him work for me.
Ji Hong, too.
You sound like a wise old man.
I'm the one who pays them.
It's such a great feeling.
What will you do about building a new centre?
I'll call a board meeting to finalise the issue.
You have my full support.
Do whatever you want.
Dr Kim Chi Hyun is here from Namyangju.
What's he doing here?
I should let you get to work.
Congratulations, Mr Chairman.
Thank you.
You've been very busy recently.
I brought you some health supplements.
You can take them back.
Sir.
I hate people...
who show their true colours around weak people.
Were you afraid of upsetting Chairman Hong?
Sorry, Sir.
Prof. Hong was pretty aggressive back then.
I don't care. Lie low in Namyangju.
You might lose that job too.
Some people abandon a hound once the hunt's over.
You taught me more than just how to operate.
Don't beat around the bush. What do you have?
Our operation records are disposed of after 10 years.
Did you keep it all these years? The statue has expired.
It can't harm me.
There's a reason people say violence comes before law.
It's Prof. Hong you're up against.
Go home.
Give me a job here, Sir.
I'll be of some use to you.
Go away!
Please, Sir.
Thank you.
I made choices and decisions on my own.
It became a habit.
It's not about you.
(Hong Hong Hong)
(Hong Ji Hong)
(Hye Jung)
The door is opening.
Aren't you getting out?
You're here.
Of course I am. I work here.
Why are you here?
I just dropped by.
Professor, I know it's late, but I offer my condolences.
You're good at changing the topic.
Don't you remember?
My memory feeds on kindness.
The offer's on the table.
I'm a kind person.
I'll remember that.
(Neurosurgery, Choi Kang Soo)
What?
Prof. Hong's here to see Patient Cho Soo Ji.
Okay.
The hospital felt so empty without you around.
How's Patient Cho Soo Ji doing?
She can breathe spontaneously now, so we removed the intubation.
But she's still not exhibiting motor responses.
I see.
- Let's go.
-  Okay.
Come in.
- You must be exhausted.
-  Not at all.
I'm just happy to take care of her.
Excuse me, I'm getting a phone call.
I'm sorry. I need to step out and take this.
- Please take good care of her.
-  No problem.
Thank you.
Oh my, you're moving.
I'll bring the doctor!
He's not my husband.
Prof. Hong, Ms Cho's motor ability has returned.
That's good news on my first day back. Shall we go?
Yes.
What's going on?
She can feel pain in her hands now.
- That means she's recovering.
-  Thank you.
Thank you, Doctor.
Don't mention it. She's fought a hard battle.
No, she's recovering thanks to you.
No, that's not true.
- Hello.
-  Oh, yes. Hello.
Please take a look.
- Let me check the surgical site.
-  We'll see you later.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
Excuse me, Doctor.
How hopeful can we be about her recovery?
When will she be able to talk and walk?
I can't give you an exact answer. Her condition might not improve.
I see.
Then I'll see you again on your next visit.
Sure.
What does the guardian do?
I've heard that he does freelance computer work.
He pretty much lives in the ward.
Hye Jung, have you noticed anything out of the ordinary?
I haven't seen anything unusual. Why do you ask?
- It's nothing. Get back to work.
-  Yes, Professor.
Dr Jin!
- I was just about to call you.
-  Why?
Dr Jung wants you for an emergency surgery.
- Me?
-  Yes.
Is it true that I'm needed?
Yes, I'd never make the mistake of misinforming you.
You have Hye Jung. Isn't it a good opportunity for you?
Don't you have to win her heart when Prof. Hong isn't around?
I don't break into empty houses.
I did decide to walk the messy road,
but I refuse to be petty.
Put your surgical gown on and scrub in.
And by the way, Prof. Hong is already back.
(Operating Room)
What kind of assistant arrives later than a staff member?
Shouldn't you be preparing inside by now?
Why are you picking on me? I'm already in a bad mood.
Being picked on can be a good distraction.
Don't live to fulfil your father's expectations.
You're not an 18-year-old girl any more.
I'll go in first and prepare the surgery...
despite being a staff member.
Stop boasting.
Why should I?
Wake up already.
Isn't it time to reconsider our cleaning contractor?
I will speak to them, Sir.
- Jin Myung Hoon's time has arrived.
-  He seems to be in a good mood.
Go and bring Prof. Hong Ji Hong.
President Jin.
- Did everything go well?
-  Yes.
Why are you prying into my background?
I'm trying to find out what happened in Patient Kang Mal Soon's surgery.
How is that considered prying?
You should ask me directly since I was the operating surgeon.
I heard you went to see the doctor who was my assistant back then.
What would you like to know?
Do you remember that surgery?
I don't remember.
I choose to remember happier things.
I hope we get along well.
We should continue the friendship and success our fathers shared.
That would require mutual trust.
Let's trust each other.
You're my type of person. I like smart people.
A 21-year-old male traffic accident patient has multiple fractures.
We took a CT scan since he's unconscious,
and it seems like one of his middle cerebral arteries is ruptured.
His right pupil is dilated by about 4mm.
Fortunately, his vitals are stable.
- How is the bleeding?
-  It's around 30cc.
Will you perform ligation?
One of the staff members will have to decide.
Staff member? Shall I call Prof. Hong?
Let me see.
You saw the CT scan results, right? The neck is wide.
Call Anaesthesiology. Prepare for surgery right away.
Yes, Mr Hong.
Have you been well?
I haven't seen you since Chairman Hong passed away.
Yes, there were a lot of things to take care of.
Thanks for all the hard work.
Bipolar cautery, please.
When we open the sylvian fissure,
we must be careful not to damage the veins.
They're near the temporal lobe.
- Yes, Professor.
-  Irrigation, please.
Why are you waiting out here?
- Hello.
-  Let's go in.
That's okay. It seems like you're expected. Please, go in.
It's not a planned visit.
Ji Hong and I don't set up appointments to see each other.
He's just a guy friend.
Between you and Ji Hong,
if I must someone right at this moment,
it would be you.
I've been wanting to see you,
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
but I didn't reach out to you because I didn't want to.
I thought that I'd run into you anyway through Ji Hong.
Why didn't you reach out to me if you wanted to meet?
It's because I had to face the childishness of my youth.
Back then, I thought I was an old-enough adult.
But I was only 27 years old.
I'm sorry.
Shall I forgive you, or not?
Just forgive me! I'm stressed out these days.
In neurological terms,
I'm in a stupor.
We'll have to drink to that.
You haven't forgotten about buying dinner, have you?
Where are you?
Come on in.
Hey, what's up?
Who wants ramyeon?
I want one without an egg,
but with chopped green onions.
I want one with an egg. Don't break the yolk and hold the green onions.
I don't know why I invited you over.
I was out of my mind to trust you, Uncle.
Let's get a drink while he cooks for us.
In Joo will be here soon.
You're making quite an effort today.
Why does your place look bigger than mine?
Why is there a difference when we work at the same hospital?
Let's discuss this after I've seen your place.
Are you planning to come over?
In Joo.
Where do you live?
Over there on the third floor.
In Joo.
I can't stand up.
Hey!
Hong Ji Hong!
Jeong Pa Ran!
In Joo, you're going to wake up everyone in the neighbourhood.
How much did she drink?
Stand up, Missy.
What? Missy?
That hurts. Let go of me.
Wait a second. Help me, Yoon Do. Let go of me.
- Hi, Dr Yoo.
-  The greetings can wait.
Fine.
Hey.
I can walk by myself.
- All right.
-  Come with us.
Okay.
She didn't use to get that drunk.
Do you want to go in?
No, I'll leave.
All right then.
All right then?
How could you say that?
You said you wanted to leave.
Since when did you do as I say?
So what is it that you want?
Do you want to go home or do you want to talk?
Come in.
Would you like some tea?
You have this at home?
Yes, I do. Do you want to give it a try?
No.
Have a seat.
I'm sorry.
For what?
I don't know how to comfort someone when they're sad.
I've never had someone console me when I was sad.
I was alone when my grandma passed away.
I thought sadness was something you had to get over alone.
I missed you.
I was alone like I always was.
I went through my father's belongings by myself.
My old self would've felt comfortable and at ease,
but I couldn't stop thinking about you.
Why didn't you call?
I was waiting for you to call.
Whenever I wanted something,
I'd act first.
That's how I ended up telling you how I felt about you.
But I realised...
that waiting for the woman I love could be the most active act.
I learned that through you.
I didn't know what to do.
I'd pushed you into a corner, telling you to change.
I'm sorry.
I wanted you to love me the way I am,
but I asked you to change.
You're good at figuring things out and admitting to your faults.
You were always like that. It's one of your strengths.
I want to be part of your life.
I'm sorry for telling you to change.
You can think and make decisions by yourself.
I'll just be by your side.
Can I do that?
Of course.
I'll get going.
Okay.
But you haven't had the tea yet.
I can't ask you to stay, can I?
No, you can't.
Do you know how scared I was?
I thought your feelings had changed when you didn't answer your phone.
I didn't answer my phone?
No, you didn't.
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Please answer your phone from now on.
So many thoughts went through my head.
You lied to me today, didn't you?
No.
- Are you sure?
-  Yes, I am.
You wanted to give the claw machine a try.
How did you know?
Give it a try.
Wait a second.
- This is interesting, isn't it?
-  Yes it is.
All right. Use this hand.
Too bad.
Gosh.
Go up.
- There.
-  Right here?
Try going up a little.
I didn't get it.
How am I supposed to do this?
Just do it. Look.
That was so close.
Gosh, you guys.
- Uncle.
-  Don't wake me up.
Get up. You're going to be late.
Aunt.
Aunt, wake up.
What time is it?
It's 6:50am. I can sleep a little longer.
Aunt, why are you doing this too?
Who are you calling "aunt"?
You're a grown man.
How disturbing.
I provided you with accommodation and food.
- How can you be like that?
-  Why am I your aunt?
I'm more like your elder sister.
You're my uncle's friend, so you're more like an aunt.
What kind of a logic is that?
I'm going to take a shower.
Squeeze me some orange juice so I can drink it when I get out.
What?
Gosh, my uncle is so useless.
Even his friends are strange.
She's just as bad as Prof. Hong downstairs.
She's as bad as him.
Gosh.
Orange juice.
Go to sleep.
I've been tracking Ms Cho Soo Ji's motor progress,
but there isn't much improvement.
Let's go.
Dr Yoo.
Yes.
Join us.
(With Investment Security)
(Your purchase order is successful.)
Darling.
You see?
I think...
I do everything for you, Darling.
Right?
Open your eyes.
Honey, let's talk. Open your eyes.
That's it.
How do I look today?
If I look great, blink once.
- Hello.
-  Hello, Doctors.
All right, let's see.
How are you feeling today?
Yes, it looks normal.
Let's check this side too.
Yes.
There's no noticeable change.
You'll have to keep this up a little longer.
- Thank you, Doctor.
-  Sure.
Let's go.
Can we separate her from her guardian for a while?
He practically lives in the room.
So can we, or not?
We can.
Wait a bit longer. It's not time yet.
What?
If you're not going to regret it, then go ahead.
Let's speak later.
I...
want your advice on stock investments.
I have quite a bit of debt.
- Stocks?
-  I accumulated sudden debt.
Please help me this once.
Sure.
- May we consult with you outside?
-  Sure.
- I should stay beside my wife.
-  We might distract her.
Yes. Let's go. I'll buy you coffee.
I am interested in stock investments,
but I have no idea where to start.
There's a good coffee shop over there.
This is how we'll communicate from now on.
Please blink once for yes,
and blink twice for no.
Are you discomforted in any way?
Is it related to your husband?
He's coming, Mr Hong.
What's going on?
I got it. This fell.
She's not going to get worse, right?
I think we'll have to run some tests.
You shouldn't worry too much. Let's get another CT scan.
- Dr Yoo.
-  Yes, Professor.
Excuse me, Sir.
You are not permitted inside.
If you rest in the waiting room,
she'll be right with you soon.
- Okay.
-  Let's go.
Professor.
(Assailant)
Yes.
She'll be fine.
We'll notify you immediately when the CT scan results are out.
Thank you, Doctor.
We called the police.
Ms Cho has was reported as a missing person.
- She's a missing person?
-  Yes.
Her parents sent the report.
Why would they report her missing when she has her husband?
My beautiful darling.
You are so beautiful.
Honey.
Do you remember when we first met?
I felt like I was struck by a lightning.
I told you to stop.
I like you so much.
Please give me an opportunity.
Why would you do this to me?
I...
I will bet everything I have...
and protect you, Soo Ji.
And...
when I went to the borough office and registered...
ourselves as married after pestering you about it,
I felt as if the entire world had become mine.
A man who bets his everything on me will only do me harm.
Why didn't I know that back then?
Ms Cho Soo Ji's parents are on their way here.
Why did they report her missing when she has her husband?
Ms Cho isn't married.
He registered themselves as married without her knowledge.
So does Ms Cho not know him at all?
That's not really the case.
According to her parents,
they went out for a few months because he chased her.
But she broke up with him because he was too obsessed with her.
So he got back at her for breaking up with him.
That's correct.
We can't let him be near her.
Where are you going? They're here now.
He's not wary of me. I'll go and bring him out.
It'd be great if you could do that for us.
- I'll go.
-  No.
I should allow other people to protect me.
Please do it for me, then.
Doctor, I don't have to look at the CT scan while you explain.
It'd be easier to understand that way.
If it's not about anything specific...
May I ask you a quick question?
- I need to go and relieve myself.
-  The name is Cho Soo Ji.
The patient is female, and she's my daughter.
How can I find out which room she's in?
Sir.
Hurry!
(Gukil Medical Centre)
This is Patient Cho Soo Ji's consent of operation.
It contains the guardian's...
contact information, national insurance number and address.
Okay, thank you.
He seemed like a nice guy.
Hey, people with those eyes are real scary ones.
You're wrong.
I'm right.
Thank you for your help.
- You're welcome.
-  It's our pleasure.
Did the catch him?
No, they just asked us for his personal information...
and how he has been acting here.
The emergency room has been swamped since the morning,
and we're like shooting a crime movie here.
It's been such a long day.
- Are you going home now?
-  I should. What about you?
I have a night shift today.
I'm on night shift all week long as a punishment.
Hey, it's all for you guys to...
I'm doing it to help you become a great surgeon.
Of course.
- Have a good night.
-  Bye.
This is on the house.
I don't know whom you're meeting, but you've been waiting for so long.
You should try calling.
I'm not waiting for anyone.
I see.
Poor thing.
He looks totally normal.
Seo Woo!
What brings you here?
Did you come alone?
Yes.
I'm here because it's the closest bar to the hospital.
Sure thing.
Do you even drink alone these days?
Yeong Gook will join me. He's super busy because he's in his third year.
I'm glad that you have him at least.
Look who's talking.
You used to console me so much when I got dumped in the past.
- You miss it, right?
-  I do.
I'll never do that again no matter what you say.
Good. You shouldn't.
Don't let me treat you like a doormat.
The CT and MRI scans are done.
You're on night shift every day.
Well, that's what happens when you're in your first year.
All first-year residents go through that.
Dr Yoo, you haven't left yet?
I'd like to go and see Ms Cho before I leave.
Claiming that it's love when abusing someone is such a horrible thing.
I must say that he did look a little weird.
- Get back to work.
-  Okay.
I'll go and bring more water.
Gosh, you startled me. Why are you so surprised?
Did you think it was all over?
You'll always be mine even after you die.
You can never leave me.
And I've been thinking about us.
If I have to give you to someone else,
I'd much rather kill you with my own hands.
You're okay with that, right?
All right.
Dr Yoo, I think there's a problem in Room 410.
What?
Let go!
- Check the patient!
-  Yes, Doctor!
I said to let go!
Stop now. What you're doing is violence, not love!
No!
- Prepare to take a CT scan.
-  Okay.
(Hye Jung)
Yes.
Patient Cho Soo Ji is in semicoma now.
She has haemorrhage in the surgical site.
Why all of a sudden?
You'll find out when you get here.
I really want to save her life.
It's not active bleeding, so the surgery won't take long.
I can't see well. Rinse it.
She didn't bleed too much.
Please pass us the haemostasis patches.
Irrigation.
This smells so good.
Gosh, it's hot.
Good stuff.
Yoon Do, you're home.
What are you doing? Where did you find that?
It was in the refrigerator.
There's nothing else to eat.
Gosh, it's delicious.
Goodness, why are you here again?
You've made a mess.
That model is still at my place.
And my place is too far from the hospital.
I have an important surgery early tomorrow morning.
You dumb general surgeon.
How can you be a surgeon when you can't even do a mental assessment?
You paranoid neurosurgeons are much worse than us.
Go, my In Joo!
Uncle.
Stop calling your uncle with a sad voice...
and bring me some ramyeon. Don't you have ramyeon?
- Aunt.
-  Okay. Call me whatever you want.
Bring me ramyeon instead.
What are you talking about?
I want to eat ramyeon.
Now you know what I'm talking about, right?
- I like cup ramyeon.
-  So?
- I'm telling you to buy it.
-  I'm telling you to leave.
I'm going to work from here.
My place is too far from the hospital.
You have enough space.
We're surgeons and should be used to sharing...
a small amount of space by now.
This is a dream. It has to be a dream.
I'm dreaming.
No, it isn't a dream.
Yoon Do, can you bring me some salt and radish kimchi?
Get it yourself.
Gosh.
Can you hear me?
You put up a strong fight.
It's a relief that her motor response is returning.
Me, too.
That was a long day.
Yes, it was.
Dr Hong.
Can you take me home?
Of course I can. I'd love to do that.
Let's go.
You can leave now.
We're almost at your place. I'll leave after seeing you go in.
- Go in.
-  After you leave.
You go first.
No, I want to watch you leave.
All right.
See you.
- Bye.
-  Bye.
Back hugs are touching.
It gives me the feeling that someone is supporting me from behind.
This is the biggest joy your loved one can give you.