(Episode 13)
Subtitles by VIU
Love is history written as a joint project by two people.
The key is...
to see how much you can understand and accept...
the other person's past.
- You're tired, aren't you?
- Yes.
I'm on duty all week as punishment.
- He won't let you off easily.
- It used to be two days.
Dr Yoo, did you finish your surgery?
Yes, what is Patient Lee Hye Jung's mental state?
She's drowsy.
(NEUROSURGERY, CHOI KANG SOO)
- What is it?
- I have a patient in ER.
While trying to pick up a chopstick he dropped at dinner, he fainted.
His CT scan shows chronic extradural haemorrhage.
He's showing symptoms of confusion at a grade four.
Did he fall hard or bump into something recently?
He fell from his bicycle around three weeks ago.
He likes to drink.
Tell Kyung Joon to book an OR and get up here.
- Have a nice day.
- Good luck.
(HONG HONG HONG)
(HYE JUNG)
- Hi, Hye Jung.
- What were you doing?
Should I go see you?
I only asked what you were doing. I might get disconnected.
(ONE NEW MESSAGE)
(CALLING)
Why aren't you asking me the second question?
Do you want me to be your girlfriend?
My answer is yes.
Please press 1 to save and 2 to delete.
Did that just get recorded?
I have to delete it.
Thank you for calling.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
Elevator.
Hand me the retractor.
Irrigation.
- What time did you go to sleep?
- I'm sorry.
Do you want to go to sleep forever?
Go home.
- What?
- Leave before I change my mind.
- I'll finish up here.
- No, I'm fine.
One...
- Two...
- Okay, thank you.
Bipolar forceps.
Hello, everyone. I've brought your late night snack.
He's here!
Over here.
I'll place it right here.
Dr Ahn likes me the best.
Of course.
He likes the food, not you.
- Here you go.
- Thank you. Enjoy the food.
Enjoy the food.
- Bye.
- Come on and eat.
- Let me finish this.
Hurry up and come on.
- You scared me.
- Hi, Dr Kang.
- Hi. And bye.
Did you order food? Why didn't you tell me?
The food just arrived.
Excuse me, can I ask you one thing?
You can ask two things.
If a seven-year-old boy...
limps when he walks,
something is wrong with him, right?
Who is this seven-year-old boy?
It's my son.
You have a son? I thought you were single.
I have two kids, one is nine and the other is seven.
You're so lucky.
How does he limp?
He drags his legs when he walks.
I went to a clinic, but he told me to go to a hospital,
saying there might be something wrong with his brain.
I'll set up an appointment. Bring him in.
I'll set him up with Dr Hong Ji Hong.
- Really?
- Yes.
Thank you. Thank you, all.
- You're welcome.
- Thank you.
- Call me before you come.
Okay.
Did you have two surgeries in a row? You must be tired.
It's just work.
You're awesome.
Prof. Hong.
Why are you here? You aren't on duty.
I was passing by and decided to check on everyone.
I just don't know how you do it, Professor.
You care too much for your patients. Doesn't he?
Yes.
- I have to go.
- Bye.
Why are you here?
You called me.
- Did I?
- You asked what I was doing.
Stop staring at me.
Will you get some rest?
Yes. I'd like to have a nap.
I can't let you do that.
What's the time?
- Are we late?
- No, we're fine.
Hye Jung.
Stop it.
We can't let people see us.
We can just go somewhere no one will see us.
This is actually the safest route there is.
Why did you bring me to the safest corner?
I like to go on walks.
Oh, right.
I saw this in a movie and wanted to try it myself.
Lend me your hands.
Are they in?
It's my turn.
(NEUROSURGERY, CHOI KANG SOO)
Kang Soo...
What?
A 29-year-old male got hit by a billboard.
Mentally deep drowsy with a GCS of seven.
Get a CT. I'll be right there.
Okay.
Our romance will have to end here.
There's still time left. Let's walk to the ER.
- Bye, Hye Jung.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
My baby.
You're always laughing. You're my vitamin.
What about me? What am I?
You're Dal. That's your name.
You're Dal, Nam Dal.
You're his vitamin.
You're my vitamin.
Nam Dal.
- Yes?
- Come in.
Let's go inside.
Go on inside, boys.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Have a seat.
Thanks.
Hello, Dal.
Say hello.
Hello, Doctor.
Are you the dad now?
What's the problem?
He wasn't like this before,
but now he walks with a limp.
- Dal.
- Yes?
Can you walk for me?
Show him.
Stand beside the nurse and walk over to me.
Well done.
Now walk back to your dad.
(NEUROSURGERY: 25)
Neurosurgery's revenue really went up.
It's up two million from last month. My nagging helped.
Like I said, hiring Prof. Hong did us a lot of good.
It's because of the video...
of Olympic gold medalist Lee Soo Jeong's DBS.
I keep telling you. It's all about marketing.
I am so pleased that you are finally listening to me.
Keep it up.
I'll increase your credit limit...
and give the holidays back to your staffs.
Do you see how reasonable I am?
It's time for a new beginning.
We'll build a centre to cater to the elderly...
and become a 21st century hospital.
I think there's a problem with his brain.
We need to take an MRI to be sure.
I see.
Is there a problem?
No.
Dad, I need to pee.
- We're almost done.
- I can't wait.
Hang in there just a little longer.
Are MRIs covered by insurance?
Not all the time.
They are if they show evidence of an illness.
I see.
I can't wait.
- Hae!
- Hey.
I'm so sorry.
That's fine. Your boys are so cute.
Hello.
Are you okay? You should be more careful.
Where's the toilet?
Over there.
Ta-da.
Thank you.
You're cute when you laugh. Where are your parents?
I don't know. I just ran out to pee.
They'll be where you left them.
Let's go.
Are you a doctor too?
Yes.
You're pretty.
Thank you. That's just what I needed to hear today.
Do you always laugh a lot?
Yes. That's why I'm sad.
Why does laughing make you sad?
My name is Hae and my brother's Dal.
I laugh even when Dal is sick.
I feel bad to laugh when it's sad.
Hae.
Dad.
Are you okay? Let's see.
You pee way too often these days.
I don't know.
Try to hold it in.
- What?
- He's a bit weird.
Sir.
Does Hae always laugh so often?
Yes.
We call him our happy virus because he always laughs.
He even laughs in his sleep.
How old is he?
Nine. Why?
I think his laughing is a sickness.
How is that a sickness?
Yoon Do, he urinates often and keeps tripping up.
You saw him laugh.
I'm thinking gelastic seizures.
Right?
Let's run some tests.
The leader is most important in any organisation.
- From now on, Gukil Foundation...
- Gukil Medical Center is now...
at the centre of a recruitment scandal.
The Head of Administration and the Head of Accounting...
rigged this year's recruitment where over 100 people applied.
They smuggled out the written exam questions and answers...
so their daughters could pass and get a job.
First, it was tax embezzlement, and now a recruitment scandal.
What is going on?
What's this corruption scandal regarding recruitment?
How did I know about this?
- Did it really happen?
- It seems so.
"It seems so"? These scums.
Jung Yun Tae that psycho. Is he really out of his mind?
He's trying to send all unconscious patients off to our department.
Hey, let's go upstairs and come back when we get a call.
If we stay here, we'll just end up doing things for the guys in the ER.
I'm so annoyed. Who's calling now?
Yes, Choi Kang Soo speaking.
Hello, I'm Writer Lee Yoo Sun of SBC's "Focus People".
You're the one posting "Ms Doctor Gangster" on your blog, right?
Oh, yes. You sent me the message the other day, right?
You said that the story is based on a real-life person.
We'd love to invite her to our show.
Why?
We believe that she'd be the perfect guest on our show.
A beautiful female doctor who overcame her unfortunate past.
She wouldn't want to be on a television show, though.
You can't just assume that.
Speak for yourself. Anyway, I apologise.
Please just enjoy my work as a webtoon.
Hey, what was that about?
Dr Yoo will probably beat me up to death if she finds out.
Dr Yoo, where are you going?
- I'm going to get food.
- Shall I join you? The cafeteria?
Do you guys actually have time to go to the cafeteria right now?
No, we have a pile of work to do. We'll just order something.
This one has lost his senses a little.
- Kang Soo, let's go.
- But we can...
But I should...
It's so hard to eat with you.
(CHEER UP.)
Ji Hong, sit with us.
Sit here!
Darn it.
When we asked you to join us, you said you couldn't.
Didn't you guys say that you were going for food earlier?
Why? You don't want to eat with us?
Dr Yoo.
- Come and eat with us!
- Sure.
I haven't seen you in a while.
Why am I getting a feeling that these two came to eat together?
- Should we not have called you?
- No.
- What?
Let me officially introduce to you, my girlfriend, Yoo Hye Jung.
Hello. I'm Prof. Hong's girlfriend,
Yoo Hye Jung.
Hey, what is going on now?
- I didn't know you had this side.
- I did. Don't tease me.
Eat up. You have to see outpatients soon.
You two must be over the moon now. It reminds me of the old days.
This is the best phase. Soon, the relationship will tire you out.
You start demanding reassurance and get obsessed.
Then you get bored and exhausted.
- Gosh, you two are so mean.
- Congratulations, seriously.
It's a big achievement, considering your age.
- We will keep it to ourselves.
- Of course.
When you date a colleague, doing things like this secretly...
is the best part.
You're naughty.
Thanks. He's had nothing to smile about as of late.
Thanks, In Joo.
Eat up. Do you want this too?
What is this mess?
Our hospital's reputation will go down the drain.
Didn't it happen because we got audited by the National Tax Service?
An applicant who didn't get a position here must've reported it.
Where were you when they were doing such thing?
- Why didn't you know?
- Call the Prosecutors' Office.
The prosecutor who took on the case...
is a VIP member of our health programme.
Okay.
I hope it doesn't turn into a bigger problem.
Why is there so much noise about our hospital these days?
People are asking if doctors are hired through connections.
It's because of the news. Someone said the same thing to me too.
Who even wants to work as a resident in Neurosurgery these days?
They have no idea how tough the job is.
By the way,
did you hear that Dr Choi's webtoon could be published?
Isn't he so impressive?
He's also doing a great job as a first-year resident.
I was wondering why he's been out of it. That's what he was busy with.
This little...
- You should be nice to him.
- Why do you say that?
That way, you'll benefit if he becomes a bestselling author.
I must say that Kang Soo is quick-witted.
Joong Dae is the problem.
What did I do?
Get off me! Gosh, you're so heavy. Go away.
Why is Patient Ahn Se Yeong still on warfarin?
- That shouldn't be the case.
- Did you double-check?
I think Kang Soo did.
Why did you make my precious Kang Soo do it? It's your job.
You fool.
Go check it right now.
- Go.
- Okay.
Hurry up!
Is Kang Soo good at drawing?
He has hypothalamic hamartoma.
It is a case of gelastic seizures.
You did a good job.
- What's that look?
- I got two compliments today.
One was from this boy, and the other from you.
How did you become like this?
- Why? How do I look now?
- I'm beginning to pity you.
Pitying someone has nothing to do with loving someone, right?
- No.
- I knew you'd say that.
Do you still have feelings for me?
Do you still have feelings for Hye Jung?
You know my weaknesses so well.
I should meet this patient's guardian.
I heard that this patient's little brother is Prof. Hong's patient.
- What's his condition?
- I don't know.
That patient's MRI result should be out by now.
Call them.
- What is it?
- I hate you.
I hate you terribly,
but I also like you.
I like you so much.
Why do you like me?
Why do you like me so much?
- It's because you like what I have.
- That's how it started.
I liked you because you have more to offer than me.
Most of the guys who liked me in the past...
were attracted to me because of what I have.
With you, I don't have to worry about that.
Look deep into your heart and find out...
whether it's love...
or just a feeling of relief.
How are the two different?
Trust and love are two different emotions.
When you love someone,
you can go until the end even if you don't trust the person.
That's too foolhardy.
That's precisely why people love.
Don't get flustered when you get caught while being lovey-dovey.
Just say that you're talking as a staff member and a fellow.
Isn't it a perfect alibi?
When lovey-dovey? We're not kids.
- You know that this isn't enough.
- You're not getting anything else.
- Yes.
- Patient Nam Dal. Age seven.
Have you checked his MRI result yet?
No, not yet.
His older brother is Dr Jung's patient.
It looks like we need to talk about the two patients.
All right.
The wind feels nice.
I spent extra time to do my hair today, but it's so windy.
Shall I fix it for you?
Dr Yoo!
- Hey, what's up?
- I have to talk to Dr Yoo.
- Good for you.
- It's not like that.
I'll see you inside. Trust is important.
- What's the matter?
- Promise me that you won't kill me.
What is it?
This is me?
- Am I this ugly?
- Gosh, what are you talking about?
My character is much prettier than you.
Her looks aren't modelled after you.
I just took a bit of inspiration from your story.
You have a lot to say when you used my story without any permission?
I'm telling you that I can make you super famous.
SBC's "Focus People" receives high viewership ratings,
and it's known as a great show as well.
I'm sorry.
You'd better behave yourself.
Do not give them my phone number. Don't try to set up anything.
Okay.
(NAM DAL)
I'm sorry. I'm a little late.
No, I just came too. Have a seat. Have a seat and take a look.
What do you think it is?
It's medulloblastoma.
Did you hear that? She says it's medulloblastoma.
What are you doing?
What do you think? We're diagnosing.
But it feels very different.
What do you think?
I don't know what it is, but something has changed.
Then stop talking about it. How's your patient, Dr Jung?
I'm planning to put him under radiation therapy.
The size of the tumour is big, but the risk is too high.
- Any family history?
- Nothing significant.
Then let's talk to the patient's guardian...
and decide how to go about it.
You should talk to the guardian since you'll be in the surgery.
Okay.
(NAM DAL)
Dal has tumour called medulloblastoma.
This tumour occurs...
in vermis cerebelli and fourth ventricle.
It causes nausea, migraine, hydrocephalus...
and even motor disturbance.
It suddenly impairs your walking or makes you falter.
That's why Dal was...
Yes.
Dal's tumour is big, so I want to start the treatment right away.
Will he regain his health completely when the treatment is over?
Yes.
We will remove the tumour through surgery...
and treat him with radiation therapy and medication.
I see. Let's get him the surgery as soon as possible.
Prof. Hong Ji Hong will be performing the surgery.
I'll be joining the surgery as his assistant.
You can ask me any questions.
I am sorry, Doctor, but can I know how much the surgery would cost?
I am not so sure about that.
The Administrative Office will get in touch with you.
I guess you're burdened because of the medical bill.
I'm a single dad.
I don't have a wife.
Can I know what Hae's condition is?
Dr Jung Yoon Do is in charge of him. He will tell you.
All right.
Can you get him admitted to the hospital first?
I'll ask the Social Contribution Team about the medical bill.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thank you.
(NAM HAE)
Hae's seizures occur in a form of laughing.
People suffering from gelastic seizure laughs all the time.
I don't understand. Why is laughing a sickness?
He was laughing not because he wanted to smile,
but because the tumour is pressing hypothalamus.
Hypothalamus controls everything including...
body temperature, breathing, emotion and even development.
He was really sick, wasn't he?
I am his dad, yet I didn't even know it.
Most people don't know. You don't have to blame yourself.
How we treat it now is more critical.
Doctor, then what should we do from now on?
He's growing fast, so let's start the treatment as soon as we can.
If his life is not at risk,
I want to get him the surgery around next year. Will it be okay?
Hypothalamus affects the growth and development.
If he's not treated, he might develop precocious puberty.
His respiratory organs might get in trouble too.
Then I will get Dal the surgery first...
and then treat Hae next.
We'll do that then.
If you have any questions, please ask Dr Jin.
Okay. Thank you.
Rock-paper-scissors.
Yes.
I'm sorry to ask. I know that you're struggling too.
How much do you think you can lend me?
Yes, of course, Sir.
If you pay me in advance,
I will make sure to pay you back in three months after the surgery.
Of course I already got loans from the bank.
I still need more after the bank loans.
That's why I tried to borrow some money from you.
No.
Thank you for worrying about it.
Okay.
Stop it.
You're the vice president. How can you be so carefree?
What do you mean?
The hospital's image fell to the ground.
You should come up with a recovery plan.
What will you do...
about the two administration staffs?
- I fired them.
- Fire the recruited staffs too.
Only then the hospital will seem unassociated with them.
I have nothing to do with what happened!
It was done without my permission!
Gosh, those troublemakers.
I asked you for the plan. Why are you changing the subject?
You should end the situation before looking for countermeasures.
The chief communications officer is here.
What's wrong with you?
You should've planned for this ahead of time!
Instead, you even made this go on air!
I am sorry.
Release a press release.
Announce that we fired everyone associated...
and apologise for not being able to prevent corruption.
Yes.
What will you do now?
Is there anything that can improve the hospital's image?
SBC's television show called "Focus People"...
and said they want to cover Dr Yoo Hye Jung from Neurosurgery.
- Why?
- They said Dr Yoo Hye Jung...
is a heroine of a webtoon series.
She got over her unfortunate past and became a doctor.
They said she can give hope to other people.
That's nice.
Yoo Hye Jung? Is it that fellow?
- That's right.
- That's good.
I think that fellow and I would get along very well.
Push for it.
But she had already refused the offer.
She'd better accept it.
Make sure it happens.
You must've brought that fellow here.
Will Kyung Joon be in charge then?
No, I will.
I should tell Kyung Joon to come.
He should learn too.
It seems like Prof. Hong and Dr Yoo are going out.
I don't care if they are dating.
Don't argue with Dr Yoo about love problem.
I don't.
I'd lose anyway.
Even my dad told me to be close to her.
It seems like gold dust is sprinkled all over her.
She makes friends very easily, and she's flexible too.
You should've seen her singing with the head.
- Show me.
- Do you want to see it?
Let's see.
Here. This is it.
- What?
How did she become like this?
You're much prettier.
That's good to hear.
Yes, Dad.
There's a fellow named Yoo Hye Jung in your department, right?
- Yes.
- Bring her. Let's have tea.
I want to meet her.
- Why?
- You'll find out when we meet.
What's going on?
Mr Lee's getting the transcranial doppler every day, right?
Yes, and he's fine.
Check again tomorrow morning.
If ever he shows the signs of vasospasm, let me know right away.
Yes, Professor. Hello, Sir.
Hello.
Please share this.
And please give this to Dr Jung Yoon Do.
You packed it for him specially for your doctor.
He often eats at our restaurant.
He's Dr Yoo's father.
- Hello.
He's Dr Yoo's boss.
Is that right? Please take good care of Hye Jung.
She's doing well.
You don't remember me, do you?
I am not sure. My memories are faint.
Do you have time for a cup of tea?
Sure.
(DEPARTMENT OF NEUROSURGERY, PROF. HONG JI HONG)
I remember it now.
You came when my mother passed away, right?
That's right.
I was Hye Jung's homeroom teacher once.
I am sorry.
I should've visited the school.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
- Please eat.
- Thank you.
By the way,
how did you become a doctor?
I was a doctor to begin with.
But I worked as a teacher for a short while.
I see.
Please give me your business card.
I sometimes miss your soup.
Sure.
It's not the same.
But those aren't too sensitive don't really notice.
They think it's my mum's cooking.
(GRANDMA'S DINER)
Did you tell Hye Jung you were coming?
No.
She hates me.
I didn't call because I thought she might avoid me.
I don't think she'd avoid you.
(FATHER)
- Yoo Hye Jung speaking.
- This is the president's secretary.
He'd like to see you.
All right.
How do you like working at this hospital? Do you like it?
Yes, I do.
I feel like Seo Woo is having a hard time working...
because she isn't flexible and takes things too seriously.
Why don't you be friends since you're the same age?
I heard from the Communication Department...
that SBC's "Focus People" is going to come film you.
Good luck.
I already turned it down because I don't seem fit for it.
Why would you say that?
We all have to work together when the hospital is facing crises.
Seo Woo would love to do something like that, but she doesn't qualify.
I'll believe you'll do it. It was nice meeting you.
I like young doctors.
This is my life.
Not everything is served to me on a silver platter.
Let's go home.
Drive me home today.
I like this.
I was feeling down, but you just made me happy.
What? Why were you feeling down?
I had a talk with President Jin and Seo Woo.
It's better to watch our lives from afar.
It's cruel when you see it from up close.
Do you still want to be part of my life?
I will gladly become part of it.
Then let's go.
- Please get in.
- What an honour!
Watch your head.
I started the adventure of becoming part of someone's life.
My heart is fluttering.
I try not to,
but you come to my mind when I face hardships.
Why can't it be me?
Why not?
You and I are good together.
We know each other so well.
You idiot.
The problem is me, not you.
Do you know how good we look together?
You're tall.
I'm the perfect height for someone as tall as you. Look.
Our heights match. I like how tall you are.
I have nothing to say, now that you admitted it.
My height was the only thing I was confident about.
Go home.
People are going to see.
Who cares whether someone sees me or not?
People like us have two choices.
We can either do what our parents want or not.
We have to give them something satisfactory when we decide not to.
You can't do that.
No, I can't.
Nothing I do can live up to their expectations.
Do you know why?
Expectations are a form of greed you set up...
to your standard and hope someone else will fulfil.
My dad is a good person.
He used to be when I was young.
You should go home.
Stop whining like a little kid...
and break away from your parents.
Yes.
No, I...
All right.
Got it.
- Hey!
- Yes?
Do you feel like eating right now?
Why didn't you get a CT scan when Kim In Yeong is drowsy?
I told Nurse Hyun to do it.
- Didn't you do it?
- When did you tell me?
I called you early this morning.
I didn't get a call.
You have to give me an official order for that.
I'll go check on it.
Are you serious?
You made Kang Soo do your work earlier, and now you're blaming her?
I'm not making excuses. I'm telling you the truth.
Do you have problems...
communicating with nurses and the other doctors?
Don't you know how to communicate?
Are you going to take responsibility if something happens to the patient?
Can't you pull yourself together?
Goodness. Why are you standing up?
Hey, hey! Leave the rice.
Hey!
I think you're being too hard on him.
How am I being hard on him?
I'm trying to prevent you from making mistakes later.
- Have one of these.
- Good boy.
That was garlic.
It'll make you a better person.
Enjoy.
- Did you come by yourself?
- Yes.
Please give me something to drink and a lot of food to go with it.
Okay.
Here you go.
If anyone asks for me,
especially from the hospital,
tell them I'm not here.
I can't tell them that.
Anyone can see you're here.
Is he crying?
- What are you doing here?
- Hi. Did you take a shower?
What are you doing? Are you homeless?
You can't suddenly show up here like this.
I'm tired. Bring me something cold.
Look.
I heard you like girls with a story.
Don't fall for me.
I don't fall for girls with just any story.
That's why I'm telling you not to fall for me.
I have a lot of stories.
Don't you worry now.
Please stop coming to my place. You are making me miserable.
Yoon Do, your uncle is here!
In Joo. You're here too.
Gosh, you two are driving me nuts.
Uncle, please stop coming to my place.
Why do you keep coming here when you have your own place?
I'm lonely.
Me too.
I like coming here these days.
Likewise. We're both divorced singles, so it's sort of...
awkward for only the two of us to hang out.
Exactly. The two of us will look pathetic together.
That youngster helps us look not so pathetic.
And most importantly, teasing him is so much fun.
Great minds think alike. You're my best friend, indeed.
I will be sure to get a girlfriend.
I'll make her stay here so that no one can come by like this.
Do it.
But I must say you aren't really the type...
that girls like because of your personality.
- Aunt.
- Did you buy instant cup noodles?
If you did, I'll tell you that you're a pretty nice guy.
I'll go buy them then.
- Now?
- No! Tomorrow.
In Joo.
Go away.
We're here.
Help me with this.
- Sorry?
- You like these things.
Protecting and looking after people. Am I wrong?
You know too much about me.
I learned a lot about you when you devastated me.
You still don't know how to let go of grudges.
What's wrong?
It could've seen as a bit suggestive.
Are you hungry? Do you want to come in for food?
- No, it's okay.
- Then what about the crane game?
Fine.
You're good at this now.
I pick up things quickly.
How did you think of getting a claw crane machine for home?
I wanted to give myself a reward for what I couldn't enjoy as a kid.
Then I need one too.
I met your father.
Should I stop?
Go on.
I don't really know where to start.
I don't like him.
I know.
If anyone tells me that I should make up with him,
I will never see that person again.
But I can visit him, right?
Why do you want to do that?
I want to eat the food there at Grandma's Diner. I miss it.
I miss it too.
I haven't told you this yet.
Do you know why I don't cook?
It's because I think I might turn out to be a good cook.
It'll remind me of Grandma.
Thinking about her only makes me cry.
I don't know what to do at times like this.
I like that you're not afraid to admit what you don't know.
I'll teach you.
At moments like this...
Wrap your arms around me like this and...
Just hug me like this.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
Dal, getting a surgery isn't a big deal at all.
Just close your eyes if the doctor tells you to,
and fall asleep when you're told to do so.
- That's all there is to it.
- Okay.
What about Hae? Will he come in with me?
No, my surgery isn't today. Right, Dad?
Yes. Hae will get his surgery after yours is done.
Gosh, my Hae...
My vitamin.
Hi, Hae and Dal.
Please don't worry too much.
Thank you. I'm not worried.
Dal, how are you feeling today?
- I'm feeling great.
- Me too.
Best of luck to us both.
Sure, let's shake hands!
Dal hasn't had any water since last night, right?
No, he hasn't.
Give me my gown.
Just stay there.
Keep going.
Please pass me the suture.
Number 19.
The microscope, please.
I opened the arachnoid mater for you.
Good work.
Hand me the bipolar forceps.
Let's do this.
CUSA, please.
The tumour has spread to his brain stem.
Yes. We cannot make a mistake.
Any damage could lead to severe disability.
There seems to be a problem with his BAEP.
How bad is it?
The amplitude dropped in half.
The latency is a bit delayed as well.
Stop, everyone.
How is it now?
- It came back to normal.
- Okay.
Am I good?
Very good.
(ONGOING SURGERIES: PATIENT NAM DAL IN OPERATING ROOM)
The surgery went well.
Thank you, Doctor.
Let's see how he's doing after the anaesthesia wears off.
I don't think you need to worry too much.
Yes. Thank you, Doctor.
Do you have a surgery today?
I'm already done. I joined Prof. Hong's surgery.
Actually, I am constantly pressed by the president.
He's asking me to push you to go on television for hospital's publicity.
Is it too much to ask?
I will do it if you tell me to.
My likes and dislikes are clear when it comes to people.
What? That was too easy.
I never knew you were this easy, Dr Yoo.
Yes. I am a very easy person,
to you.
When the surgery ends, I become relaxed and get sleepy.
What do you want to eat?
I'll cook everything you want to eat.
Really?
Then I want...
Then you want...
Put everything in here. I'll buy you everything you want to eat.
Yes!
This is dessert.
I want ramyeon.
This too.
That looks delicious.
How is this?
It looks fresh!
- This won't do.
- How about this?
Should we cut it half?
- Scalpel?
- It's at home.
- I'll buy this then.
- Okay.
This is today's highlight.
I don't think this is it.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
What is it?
It tastes like my grandma's soup.
- Is it good?
- It's really good.
Where did you buy it?
At Grandma's Diner in Mangwon-dong.
The start of relationship is getting into each other's life.
And it is also welcoming your other half trying to...
enter your life.
But it's going to be really difficult to welcome him.
(DOCTORS)
I gained some points.
You still didn't give up?
Gosh! Aren't you going back to the hospital?
Whoever that is, I won't be able to forgive him.
Don't you want to give up?
I thought you were a very good person.
- Can I do something bad?
- That's my job.
- Do you want to stay for coffee?
- They look like men's shoes.