(Episode 14)
(Grandma's Diner)
Entering the life of another...
requires remaining oblivious...
to the silent but apparent scar in his or her life...
and not asking about it.
It's about being by the person's side in quiet support.
First, the scar must be identified.
Welcome.
It's you, Doctor!
- Hello.
-  Thank you for coming.
I missed Ms Kang's soup.
I can't care less about the reason.
Anyone close to Hye Jung is most welcome here.
I won't be eating here, but I'll take out three servings.
Please wait a moment. I will prepare it right away.
By the way,
are you familiar with Dr Jung Yoon Do?
Yes.
He's here right now.
- A lot of hot sauce, please.
-  Sure thing.
Were you the operating surgeon?
Yes. I earned some points with that.
You haven't given up yet?
I hope I had a zipper on my heart...
so I can open and shut it as I please.
I know why you got rejected.
Don't say such cheesy things.
There's no reason for getting rejected.
It's only because I was denied the first goal.
Your takeout is ready!
Here you go.
I have one for you too, Doctor.
- Thank you.
-  No problem.
You visited my father?
I went to Grandma's Diner.
It's the same thing.
It's not the same thing. I had a different purpose.
I went to buy soup. You said that was okay.
I did.
But hearing that you met my father again...
upsets me.
The fact that it upsets you upsets me.
What's wrong with you?
- What?
-  Why don't you lose to me?
I lost to you before.
It seemed to me that you didn't know the value of losing.
Do you know that you sound like a teacher right now?
That's my job. Of course I sound like a teacher.
Mr Hong!
You should experience it too.
You should experience the feeling I had...
when I had a meltdown because of you.
You're very stubborn.
You still hold grudges like you used to.
Look who's talking. You're just the same.
Let's eat.
I told you to taper the doses of steroid. Why didn't you do it?
I was going to make Kang Soo do it, but the emergency happened.
Is Kang Soo the only person at the Department of Neurosurgery?
If Kang Soo's busy, you should've come and done it yourself.
You're still a resident.
Are you already used to giving orders?
I am sorry.
Do you have to mess things up...
and ruin my morning?
It won't affect Hae's radiation therapy. Let it slide.
Go find Joong Dae, or make sure things run smoothly without him.
Let's go.
Darn it! Where is Joong Dae?
Tonight tomorrow night I can't stop thinking about him
Oh gosh!
- What are you doing?
-  I'm cleaning.
Don't you have to go back to the hospital?
- It's already been two days.
-  I won't go.
They don't even care about me.
I will recuperate here for a week and return home.
You're going to recuperate here?
Yes. I feel comfortable here.
What should I do after cleaning?
- Have you eaten?
-  I ate the food in the fridge.
Why would you eat my food?
You locked the door on the way out, so I couldn't leave.
Should I have just starved to death?
When did I tell you to die? You should've called me!
But what if Dr Yoo finds me? I'll be sent back to the hospital.
I can tell Hye Jung myself.
But you won't tell her.
I believe you to be a loyal...
with a good conscience.
Then put your back into it.
Think of it as your lodging fee.
- It's your lodging fee.
-  Let's make it shine!
Gosh.
You're here.
- I'm going mad without Joong Dae.
-  That's how it is.
How can he not come in without notice?
- He did contact me.
-  Did he really?
I can't put up with the insults any more.
Thank you for everything you've done. I'm never going back.
What? Who insulted him?
Was it me?
Yes. You're so old-fashioned.
- I am?
-  Why would you beat him?
I do what I do to ensure you become great doctors.
You can't beat someone who will be great.
You should buy him jokbal like Yeong Gook.
You're unbelievable.
How can the second-year resident run away?
You should've been nicer to him. Why would you beat him up?
What? It's so easy to make a person seem devilish.
The one who ran away is at fault. I want to run away too!
Gosh, what in the world?
Call Joong Dae.
(My lovely Dad)
- Hello.
-  Hello.
Surprise!
It's all yours.
- Hae, are you feeling good today?
-  Yes, I feel great.
You're getting the radiation therapy with me today, right?
Yes.
Just like the robot you love, you'll be wearing a helmet.
It will last for 40 to 50 minutes. You can handle it, right?
Yes.
Today's the first day, so let's cheer up.
See you later.
Have you seen Hae and Dal's guardian by any chance?
I have to settle the medical fees, but I can't find him.
I think he comes in at night.
If you see him, please call the Administrative Office.
Sure.
I feel really bad for Hae and Dal's father.
His wife passed away from cancer, so he accumulated a lot of debt.
How will he afford the boys' medical fees?
Shall we go?
Hello.
I prescribed a small dose of pain killers to Nam Dal...
to ease the pain on the wound. He's not vomiting.
- Did he have any seizures?
-  None.
What are you doing in the evening?
I have to meet Dr Kim. We have to plan a project together.
What project?
It's a project that develops dopamine sensors for DBS.
What's that?
If it goes well, I can overturn the hospital's political climate.
Hae, Dal, I'm here.
Dr Yoo!
Walk slowly.
Dal, what have you been doing?
I'm waiting for Dad.
Are you all right, Dal?
- It hurts here.
-  Does it hurt a lot?
No, it doesn't hurt that much.
How do you know how much your brother's hurting?
I know everything. Right?
Yes. My brother knows everything.
It's because we do everything together, right?
Daddy told me to take good care of my little brother when he's gone.
- Right?
-  Yes.
He told me to listen to my brother well when he's not around.
- Right?
-  Right?
Tickle, tickle.
He's not feeling nauseous?
Yes. He eats well.
I want to see their father. Did he go somewhere?
He's a parking agent by day and a driver by night.
Please come again.
(Gukil Medical Center Administrative Office)
- Yes, hello?
-  This is the administrative office.
You are Dal and Hae's guardian, right?
Yes, speaking.
The medical bills haven't been settled.
The operation fee alone will be about 20,000 dollars.
The bill will change according to the duration of services.
Sure, I'll be paying soon.
Please drop by the Administrative Office when you visit the hospital.
Sure, I'll do that.
Why are you here?
He's Dal's brother.
I have some interest in him.
You're nosy.
A doctor needs to be nosy sometimes.
Be quiet.
Did you have to say that? You're so slow.
He isn't exactly quick-witted, is he?
You tend to save yourself and bury everyone else.
(Neurosurgery, Choi Kang Soo)
The camera crew is here.
She'll be here soon.
Hello.
He's the producer of "Focus People".
Hello, I'm Kim Do Jin.
I have to go.
Joong Dae's killing us.
See you.
Have a seat.
I think that's my line.
That's right. You are heading this.
How should we do this?
The new DBS dopamine sensor will place...
less pressure on the brain when operating on...
patients with hand tremors.
Yes.
I'll discuss the details with Prof. Hong and call you back.
Bye.
MH Meditech agreed to invest.
In exchange for the research and investment,
they want the patent and royalties.
They can have it. How much will they invest?
Sixty million dollars.
That's great.
Use this to stop President Jin's new centre...
and gain the upper hand at the next meeting.
Do you want coffee? I'll get some.
He looks like a baby.
Look after him for me.
Yes?
Come on in.
Have a seat.
I meant to ask you,
but I hoped you'd tell me first.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't. I felt so guilty.
If I had stayed in the room,
your father might not have passed away.
You're right.
Had we found him sooner, we could have helped him.
I'm sorry.
Why were you away from your post for so long?
Chairman Jin came by and told me to leave...
so they could have a chat.
Then the head nurse called...
Did Chairman Jin Sung Jong come by?
Yes.
What do you want to say?
I heard you were the last person to see my father.
Was I?
Did you notice any symptoms before he fainted?
If I had,
would I have left him alone?
He was fine when we had dinner together.
I wonder if something happened...
after you two talked.
We didn't say much.
Your father and I didn't need words...
to communicate, did we?
Nurse Yoo said...
you told her to leave so you could talk in private.
Did you tell her to leave to discuss mundane issues?
What are you trying to say?
I know you used to argue about how the hospital should be run.
And?
I just want to make sure my father left in peace.
That's all I can hope for...
as I wasn't there.
If that weren't the case,
I don't think I can forgive whoever was responsible.
Your father and I always argued.
And we always reconciled.
That time was no different.
(Father)
Hello?
I came by after buying some groceries.
Why are you doing this?
I have something for you.
I thought you'd want it.
It's the last copy.
It was taken in your mum's second year of college.
I think it was about six months after we met.
I had an inferiority complex and I ruined it all.
Saying this won't make you warm up towards me.
Does it bother you that I'm so cold?
If I weren't a doctor,
would you be as nice as you are now?
Would you try to make amends?
You think I'm a terrible person.
I'm not that bad.
Think about it.
Deny it all you want,
but you're like me.
I brought some soup.
Come in.
Hi.
I drove you home last time.
It's your turn today.
I'd love to. What's that?
My dad came by.
You have it.
Don't blame the food.
You want it too.
Food and your father are two separate issues.
I can't separate the two.
Okay then. I'll eat it.
Shall we go?
Let's do some homework on the way.
That sounds like fun.
There's a rule though.
You wait here.
Aren't we going in together?
I don't want to show him my hidden card.
I'll do what I can, and if it doesn't work,
that's when you come in.
I'm your backup. Roger that.
What do you do?
You gave me your number but didn't tell me who you are.
Why wouldn't you unless you're ashamed of what you do?
It's not because I'm ashamed.
It's because I'm not yet sure if you're someone...
I can speak openly to.
I saw you at Gukil Medical Center.
It was a passing glance,
but I think it was you.
Why do you suddenly care who I am?
I want to talk to you.
I think I stand a better chance with you than with Prof. Hong.
I'm a fellow at Gukil Medical Center.
A fellow?
You're fully qualified.
Yet you're doing this to a fellow doctor?
Yes. To a fellow doctor.
How nice and simple.
My hospital...
botched my wife's C-section,
and she suffered for months.
I let it slide because I'm a doctor.
I understand mistakes.
I don't have to accept your view of medical practices.
Just tell me what happened in the OR that day.
I'll decide what happens next.
Nothing much happened.
(Current time)
The tumour's bigger than I thought.
Keep it still.
Sorry.
President Jin did his best.
That's the truth.
The nurses didn't bring the blood bags into our OR.
That was a different surgery.
My grandmother's surgery was the only one at the time.
- How did you know that?
-  You're admitting it.
I just threw it out there.
Well, this is encouraging...
since I got to peek into the operating room.
Let's make more progress next time.
Hae, how are you feeling today?
- Is Hae going to die?
-  No, he'll be fine.
How is he doing?
He keeps vomiting. He feels weak too.
Let me take a look at him.
Let's see, Hae.
I'll take a look, okay?
Can you hold my finger?
Try to hold it tightly.
Good job.
Do you remember the thing you wore on your head earlier?
Only brave, cool kids get to wear that.
But since you're so amazing, it might be a bit difficult.
Do you think you can do it?
- Yes.
-  You're an amazing boy.
Then get some sleep. You should sleep it off. Got it?
Give him IV drips with vitamins.
Since he can't eat, he'll at least need the nutrients to get by.
Okay.
Dal, where's your dad?
He went out to earn money.
Are you two going to be okay by yourselves?
We're always by ourselves, so it's okay.
Dad will be here later.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Let's go to bed.
I'll bring you a new blanket.
Making money is important, but how can he just leave the kids alone...
even without a caregiver?
I just realised why I don't feel a spark with you.
I know why I subconsciously reject you.
When I heard you asking Dal where his father is,
my heart sank.
- Why?
-  What I used to fear the most...
when I was a child was, "Where did your mum go?"
What does that have to do with this?
Who do you think those boys need the most right now?
It's their dad.
They need him a lot more than you do.
Do you know why I'm attracting to strong women with emotional wounds?
Those who know how to take care of their pain...
also know how to be considerate.
Let's go.
You're here.
What are you doing? Are you busy?
- What's up?
-  Can I do something bad to you?
Yes, you can.
That's what I'm here for.
Hearing you say that makes me hesitate.
Then can I do it?
Sure, whatever it is.
Are you really not going to return?
I won't. I just make everyone's life difficult.
Becoming a doctor is so hard. Why would you give that up?
Go back.
Yes, it's very hard.
I gave up my personal life to become a doctor.
But what is this?
Then just go home. Don't hide here like this.
How can I go home?
My parents fully supported me for all my schooling.
Do you know how much money they've spent on me?
If they find out about me running away, my father will kill me.
- Are you scared of your father?
-  Yes, I am.
I'm scared of my father too.
But sleeping here must be so uncomfortable.
I'm a bit of a germaphobe,
so I don't want to sleep at a motel.
You're seriously a handful.
- We're here.
-  Thank you.
Do you want to come in for a cup of tea?
Sure. I would've been upset if you didn't mention it.
I've been wanting to visit your place.
I'm very tender-hearted,
so I'm only letting you stay for a few days since you're a vagrant.
I can sleep with Hye Jung for a few days...
Neither Soon Hee or myself have brought men home before.
- Hye Jung is home!
-  What should we do?
Hide. Hurry up!
Come on! You have to hide!
I've never been to a house shared amongst women.
It looks like Soon Hee is home.
- Whose shoes are these?
-  They look like men's shoes.
Please have a seat.
- Shall I sit over there?
-  Sure.
- What are we going to do?
-  I don't know.
Go away! Gosh, that was too loud.
Soon Hee, are you home?
Yes, I am! I'm coming out now!
Stay right here.
Hye Jung! You're home so early! I'm so happy to see you.
Hye Jung!
Hey, why are you home so early?
I just came to pick up something.
Whose shoes are those?
Oh, those.
I'm collecting them.
What?
Wearing men's shoes is the trend these days.
Mr Hong! When did you get here?
I've been here for a while, but you didn't even notice me.
- Is that what happened?
-  Yes.
Girls, is there anything that needs to be repaired?
Not at all, Mr Hong!
Nothing needs to be repaired.
Hey, you asked me to replace the burnt light bulb in your room.
- Really? I'll do it for you.
-  It's okay, Mr Hong!
I'll do it. I want to start doing everything on my own.
- I can change the light bulb.
-  You're acting strange today.
That's because...
Mr Hong is here to officially meet me as your boyfriend.
Hey.
Why would I do such a thing?
Yes. Why would he come to formally greet you?
Look, Hye Jung.
You like him more than me now, don't you?
How could you side with him and gang up on me?
Don't look for me.
I'm going to go to my room. I won't open the door for you.
Mr Hong, have a good time.
All right.
I'm serious! Do not look for me.
How can she call herself my friend?
What is wrong with her today?
Wouldn't it be because she wants to hide something?
- What happened?
-  Goodness!
Gosh, seriously!
Oh, no.
Why did you whisper like that in my ear?
Give me this book for getting the top score in math.
(Moore's Clinically Oriented Anatomy)
Why do you want that book?
No reason.
You're so quirky.
Please autograph it too.
(Hye Jung, I will always be rooting for you. Hong Ji Hong)
I'll do my best so I don't let you down.
- You still have this.
-  Of course.
I didn't throw it out because it's an expensive book.
I don't think I've ever been in your room before.
- I should go.
-  Why?
We shouldn't be in a room alone like this. It's getting steamy.
That's how we should be.
You've learned so much from me.
I'm good at more than pouncing.
Don't test me.
Walk me to my car.
And hug me from behind. It felt nice.
Should we go back to the bed?
- Let's go out.
-  Okay.
(Gukil Medical Center)
(All Capital)
Hello.
I called you a few times and left a text message.
You're hard to reach.
I'm very sorry. I'll pay you back as soon as I can.
Stop saying you will and bring us the money.
Why did you borrow money you couldn't afford to pay back?
This will affect your credit if you don't pay us back by tomorrow.
I can do this.
Dad.
Dal.
Hae, daddy is here. Wake up.
It's hard making money, isn't it?
No, it isn't hard at all.
I'm a superhero...
that protects you and Dal.
Go to sleep now.
Good night.
My grandmother was one of the biggest reasons...
I became a neurosurgeon.
When I was a troubled child, she once said...
that being born into this world, you should at least dream big.
Can I have the chart?
Dr Yoo has a strong sense of justice.
She's also good at beating people up. Girls look up to her.
Gukil Medical Centre does not only have Dr Yoo Hye Jung.
We are the most qualified hospital with the best doctors.
We all have a past.
Misfortunate pasts aren't hindrances...
from growing in the present.
This is the reason why...
the neurosurgeon, Dr Yoo Hye Jung is beautiful.
Dr Yoo!
The hospital must love you for helping with the publicity.
I decided to think positively about it.
You look beautiful on television.
It's because you have a small face.
Right? I look amazing on television, don't I?
I was talking about her, not you.
Doctor! Doctor!
Yes?
Something is wrong with Dal.
He has a headache and is throwing up.
It was the same with me yesterday. He must be copying me.
Come on.
It hurts...
Dal, how bad is your headache?
Kang Soo, I think Dal has hydrocephalus.
Prepare for the CT scan.
Don't worry.
Hae, you know your dad's number, right?
Yes.
(Nam Dal)
I think it's hydrocephalus.
Yes, you're right.
Call the guardian for his consent and book an OR.
It's a simple procedure, so you do the surgery.
Okay.
(Hae)
Hae?
This is Dr Yoo Hye Jung.
Oh, yes. Hi, Dr Yoo.
You need to come to the hospital right away.
We need your consent to perform surgery on Dal.
Surgery?
Mr Nam Ba Ram!
(Waiver of Consent)
Please review the terms and sign below.
You're saying that you'll be inserting some sort of tube, right?
You can think of it as draining the liquid accumulating his brain.
I see.
(Waiver of Consent)
Don't worry too much.
It's a common post-surgery side effect.
I understand.
(Nam Ba Ram)
Is Nam Dal in surgery?
I think the father is signing the waiver of consent.
Why is it taking so long?
Hi, Dr Hong. Where is Nam Dal's guardian?
He's probably in the office.
Thank you.
What is it?
I think Hae and Dal's father is financially struggling.
It think it's because of the overdue bills.
Dr Yoo.
Please take good care of Dal.
Don't worry. I'll see you later.
Okay.
I finally found you.
I'm very sorry.
Do you think avoiding my calls will solve your problem?
I'm so sorry.
- I'll pay you as soon as...
-  You keep saying that.
When will that be?
I keep getting nagged at for not collecting the bills.
What am I supposed to do?
I think we should talk after the surgery.
If this bills aren't settled before conducting additional treatment,
I'll have to file a report.
I consulted with the Social Contribution Team.
Doesn't he qualify for medical assistance?
I'm not a social welfare beneficiary,
and I am employed.
I've been told that I don't qualify for support funding.
Let's perform the surgery first.
Isn't there anything you can do?
Then you'll have to sign as the guarantor.
I'll do it.
- Dr Yoo, you shouldn't...
-  Let's save Dal first.
I'll see you soon.
How long have you been standing there?
It's been a while.
- Go and get the surgery done.
-  Okay.
Please visit the Social Contribution Office.
There might be an organisation that can support you.
Yes, thank you.
Come in.
Dr Hong Ji Hong is here.
Hello, President Jin.
What brings you to my office?
It's nice to see you. Please have a seat.
I look forward to this.
You said you had something to tell me.
I think it's about time to check...
our hospital's welfare system.
Welfare?
For example,
we can readjust the hospital's balance accounts on a weekly basis.
You're very confident with your demand.
You're mistaken.
Settling accounts quickly helps patients.
It's more brutal to ask them to pay the bill...
after it snowballs.
If adjusting the settlement period is difficult,
then why don't we expand our support?
You haven't brought any money to the hospital.
How can you demand such generosity?
I am bringing money to the hospital.
I'm planning a project...
that will receive 60 million dollars of funding from MH Meditech.
The contract will be signed soon.
Why do you mention such an important event so late?
I thought now to be the most suitable time.
Anyway, please consider expanding our welfare system.
If you ignore my opinion, I'll bring it up at the board meeting.
Be my guest.
I'm not sure if you'll receive any support.
You must've forgotten.
Half of the board is my father's people.
They are good to me.
What's wrong?
We decided to be friendly.
I'm doing this because I want to get closer.
Let's be friends, President Jin.
I ask you for your support.
Yes, President Jin.
Did Prof. Hong come again?
Did he come looking for the patient record from 13 years ago?
No, he didn't.
By the way, it turns out the guardian of that patient...
is a doctor.
The guardian is a doctor?
Where does she work?
I'm sorry. There's no support system suited for your situation.
You must be burdened, and I sincerely apologise.
Don't mention it. Thank you for your hard work.
(Full Financial Assistance Programme for Childhood Cancer Patients)
What is this?
It mentions total medical expense support.
"We Are Parents" is an organisation that supports orphans.
Your children's conditions qualify for the application.
But only orphans can apply, so they don't qualify.
(Full Financial Assistance Programme for Childhood Cancer Patients)
Gosh...
(We are a support organisation for children battling cancer alone.)
How can it...
How can it be better not to have a father?
I am sorry.
Daddy.
Anaesthesiology, let's begin.
(Operating Room)
- Is the angle all right?
-  Yes, it's all right now.
Thank goodness.
Dr Yoo, even if they get better, the medical bill must be a problem.
It's too bad, isn't it?
His elder brother is sick, and he's sick too.
We're in surgery.
Stop empathising with the patient and focus on the surgery.
Yes, Doctor!
(Nam Dal is in operation.)
Daddy.
Dal is too nice.
He listens to me well even when you're not around.
Can you take care of Dal well even if I'm not here?
Of course. I am the elder brother.
That's right.
You're the elder brother.
An elder brother must take good care of his little brother.
Don't forget that.
(Operating Room)
Dal's surgery went well.
We'll move him to a room as soon as he wakes up.
- Thank you, Doctor.
-  Thank you.
- All right.
-  Wait, Doctor.
I have something to tell you.
I'm really sorry, Doctor. I'm being a nuisance to you.
It must be tough raising two children by yourself.
No, it's not tough at all.
I feel bad that my children has me as their father.
I am sorry.
(Boss)
I have to get back to work, Doctor.
I will make sure to repay you for your generosity.
Do you ever think about giving up?
Give up what?
Your children.
You could live freely without the boys.
I thought you were a very good person,
but it seems you're not.
You're here.
You're so comfortable. Some people will think this is your house.
- What's that?
-  What do you mean?
They're ramyeon noodles.
Did you want to be recognised as a decent man?
You're way ahead of yourself.
I bought them for myself.
You didn't buy them for yourself.
Uncle!
What? Did you think she was here alone?
Were you nervous because you thought I was here alone?
You two are...
Yes, Yoon Do. I will approve if you choose to date In Joo.
Why are you doing this to me, Uncle?
What if we get married?
- I'll approve that too.
-  You're the best, Pa Ran.
We're in the minority. Divorced people should help each other.
Is that more important than blood relations?
I feel so offended, Uncle.
I don't think I can live here any more.
Good luck.
Were we too harsh?
He will be back in an hour.
What brings you here?
Hey.
You keep something like this at home?
- I have.
-  Can I try it?
No, you can't. Go home. There's a guest.
Who? Don't tell me it's Dr Yoo.
It's me.
We're dating.
I have two choices.
I can return to the beagles upstairs...
or watch something dirty here.
I'll go.
I was just about to leave.
- I'll drop you off.
-  Don't worry about it.
- I'll drop her off.
-  Wait. This is strange.
I don't have money either.
- Have you eaten?
-  No, not yet.
No.
Are you on the way to see Hae?
Are you on the way to see Dal?
Yes. How's Hae?
I have to go confirm.
Hello.
- You're here, Doctors.
-  Hello.
- Hello, Sir.
Yes, hello.
I guess you don't order in late night snacks these days.
I rarely see you nowadays.
Oh, our glutton disappeared...
I'm glad to see you today.
Yes, Doctor.
Thank you very much for taking such great care of Hae.
Then I'll see you all later.
Mr Nam.
Why are you being like this?
I've made it clear to you.
I am really sorry.
Please don't do this. You need to pay off your bills.
If you keep this up, you'll get on our blacklist...
and will have to move to a different hospital.
Why are you yelling at our dad?
Our dad is stressed out. Why are you scolding him like this?
Boys, he's not scolding me.
We're just talking.
Please don't do that to our dad!
Don't be mean to our dad!
You two are being disrespectful now!
Stop it.
Boys, come on.
Dal, it's okay.
(Producer Kim Do Jin, Culture and Current Affairs, SBC)
Hello, Producer Kim. This is Yoo Hye Jung.
Yes. Did you just watch the show?
No, I'm calling to give you an idea.
It's a great idea.
What is it?
The number you have dialled cannot be reached.
Please leave a message after the tone.
Mr Nam.
I found a way to help you pay off the hospital bills.
Please call me back.
(We have not received payment. Your payment is overdue.)
(Full Financial Assistance Programme for Childhood Cancer Patients)
(One new message)
I love you.
I'll protect you boys forever.
Even if we aren't together,
I'll always be right by your side.
Mr Nam.
Why is the elevator going up?
(Full Financial Assistance Programme for Childhood Cancer Patients)
Dad...
isn't giving up.
I'm doing this because I love you boys.
It's because I love you so much.
Please don't.
Please don't come near me. I'm doing this for a reason.
Is it because of this?
Do you think your boys will be happy when they find out...
that you're not around after they recover?
Do you know how it feels to have to walk on eggshells when you're sick?
My kids are constantly doing that...
every time they take their medication...
or get a shot.
I don't know how much more will be added on their hospital bills.
I really don't think I can do this any more.
The programme gives orphans full financial support.
And if I die,
people will help my kids more out of pity.
Don't do this if it's because of money. I've found a way.
Do you know the television show, "Focus People"?
They want to cover Hae and Dal's story.
When the show airs...
I'm so sick and tired of this.
I don't want to live any more.
I want to end everything.
Is this what life is supposed to be like?
Every morning, I get woken up by harassing phone calls...
asking me to pay off my debt.
My boys are so adorable,
and I want to do anything and everything for them,
but there's nothing I can do.
I am beyond exhausted.
It's just an excuse...
that I'm going to die for my kids.
I was looking for an excuse, so this is good.
I don't want to miss this opportunity.
Don't!
How do you think your kids will feel when they find out that you died...
because of their hospital bills?
Something that a stranger blurts out...
could heal your emotional scars...
or change the direction your life headed.
It's not always your loved ones that mend your wounded heart.
It could be one of the people whom we cross paths with.