(Episode 15)
Don't!
How do you think your kids will feel if they found out that you died...
because of their hospital bills?
You're only making this choice because you can't handle your life.
You're a dad.
Do you want to cast a shadow on your kids' lives?
I won't stop you from dying,
but explain to your kids before you kill yourself.
Tell them it isn't their fault.
No one can replace a dad no matter how much others can help.
That's how it was for me.
I want to die all the time.
My mother showed me...
how to take your own life when you feel cornered.
Is that what you want...
for Hae and Dal?
Drink this.
Where is Mr Nam?
He'll be with his boys.
I'm exhausted.
You did well.
Wounds are so ironic.
Your wound helped heal Mr Nam.
I guess you could say that.
Am I wrong?
I think we helped heal each other.
Seeing Mr Nam...
reminded me of my dad, and it'd make me feel confused.
But now I don't feel so stressed when I think about him.
I don't know why. I just do.
I know what you mean.
You can't explain it logically, but you feel at ease.
That's it.
I don't know anything about your childhood.
What were your parents like?
They were both teachers.
They both worked,
so I came home to an empty house on weekdays.
My mom taught at my school,
but instead of waiting for her to finish work,
I always came home first.
That bothered me a lot later on.
Why didn't I wait and come home with her?
I like doing this.
I like it that you like doing this.
Tell her to come and see me tomorrow.
Yes, Sir.
(Operating Room)
Neurosurgeons are sensitive.
We always use microscopes when we operate,
and operating on parts thinner than paper...
creates a lot of pressure.
Our sensitiveness...
is our virtue.
(Alarm: 5am)
You scared me.
Do you think you're small enough to hide?
No.
(Dad)
The recipient cannot be reached. Please leave...
Call Seo Woo.
What for if she doesn't want to be reached?
What kind of a mom says that?
I said that because I'm a mom.
She isn't ambitious.
She did her best until now to live up to your expectations.
Is this her trying? What did she do?
What's so hard about following the road I paved?
The road you paved? Nonsense.
What?
Are you deaf? You heard me.
I won't help you this time.
- What?
-  I'll go in alone.
I can't show up with you.
It's better if it looks like I caught you...
rather than you disappeared and no one cared.
Follow me.
How is Nam Dal?
His ventricle's back to normal,
and he has almost no headaches or nausea.
He goes home today.
Being on TV solved their money issue.
That's great. You?
What are you looking at?
Wake up, will you?
There's so much to do.
We need to find Joong Dae. It's been a week.
He'll be too embarrassed to come back voluntarily.
Where on earth is he?
I called all his close friends...
but they haven't seen him.
That's why he's the worst kind. He's sneaky and cunning.
I wondered why he's in neurosurgery.
Turns out he's the typical psycho.
He might actually become a surgeon.
Is that a compliment?
Is it a curse?
- Joong Dae.
-  Joong Dae.
Make him work harder so he's too tired to run off.
Yes, Doctor.
- Joong Dae.
-  Yes?
Go and check Patient Lee Joo Young's dressing.
Okay.
- Joong Dae.
-  What?
Get changed first.
Your gown. Did you miss it?
- Thank you.
-  Work harder.
I will.
You got fatter. I like that.
I'm sending Dal home. What about Hae?
He's an outpatient now.
Dr Jung discharged him.
- What?
-  President Jin wants to see you.
I don't.
(Receipt)
You're here.
Hello, Doctors.
I saw the show.
Thanks for everything.
I just finished the paperwork.
Don't let the boys wash in hot water.
Bring them in if they vomit or have headaches.
I will.
I'll check on Dal.
Excuse me, Dr Yoo.
I'm happy for you.
People are rooting for you,
and you don't have to worry about money.
I'll remember this forever.
Do you think I'm a good person now?
Yes. I did, then I didn't.
You're a good person.
The world is still a warm place.
Hae and Dal are lucky to have a dad who loves them.
Don't say that.
All dads are like me.
My grandmother was one of the biggest reasons...
I became a neurosurgeon.
When I was a troubled child, she once said...
that being born into this world, you should at least dream big.
Can I have the chart?
You should feel bad if someone died despite your best effort.
Does doing your best guarantee forgiveness?
If you can prove that I didn't do my best,
I will accept the accusation.
Come in.
Oh, it's you.
Come and have a seat.
- Are you busy these days?
-  Yes, a little.
Why did you need to speak to me? You've been doing this frequently.
I summoned you once last week, so this is the second time.
It's only once a week. Does it feel too frequent to you?
So what would you like to talk to me about?
Nothing special.
I just want to see you from time to time and remind myself to work hard.
We tend to become lazy as we get old.
(Neurosurgery, Choi Kang Soo)
I'll get back to work. I think they need me at the emergency room.
Yes, go ahead.
How is Seo Woo doing?
You should talk to her directly instead of asking me about her.
Well, then.
Oh, you're the one who was on television.
- I enjoyed the show.
-  Thank you.
I like her.
I got many calls from my friends after that show aired.
Use it to promote the hospital.
I want to fire her, but I can't do it because of it.
- Why do you want to fire her?
-  You don't need to know.
Ji Hong is signing the investment contract today, isn't he?
I think so.
He'll try to do something with it, but it won't work.
He'll find out that he's just a clueless frog in his little pond.
Gosh, how can something like this happen? Thank you anyway.
No problem.
The patient is a 27-year-old male. Due to a gas explosion, a battery...
at the construction site got stuck in his eyes. On the CT scan...
- A battery?
-  Yes.
- What's his mental status?
-  He seems alert.
Let's go.
- Please stop moving. Stay still.
-  My eyes!
- You're here.
-  Sir, can you hear me?
Yes, I can.
But I'm in so much pain, Doctor.
Please calm down. Could you raise your right arm?
Yes.
Now, your left leg.
Just a second, please.
His pupil reflex and motor ability are normal.
Let's take an X-ray right now. Call Prof. Hong.
He's off until this afternoon.
Why?
- It's very nice to meet you.
-  Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Hello.
- I'm happy to meet you in person.
-  Nice to meet you.
- This way, please.
-  Okay.
(Hong Ji Hong)
- Thank you.
-  Thank you.
(Park Hyun Joon)
The battery pierced the upper walls of the eye socket in his left eye.
It caused intracerebral haemorrhage...
and extradural haemorrhage in the frontal lobe.
We should work on this with Ophthalmology.
I already called them. They're on their way.
We'll go in after Ophthalmology removes the battery.
Fortunately, it doesn't look like there's too much bleeding.
It doesn't look like the dura mater is torn. Let's hope it's the case.
Book an OR first.
- Yes.
-  We need an operation room.
Oh, okay.
Why did you call me by the way?
Shouldn't you call Prof. Hong exclusively as his fellow?
Not when we work.
Then do you call him exclusively at other times?
You're so funny.
I'm sorry.
Prof. Hong is at the board meeting.
I'm surprised. I didn't think he'd enjoy doing those things.
In life, we all have to do things that we don't enjoy at times.
I see. Is that right?
(President Jin Myung Hoon)
President Jin is calling.
Aren't you going to answer it?
Do you know when I love being my father's son the most?
At times like this.
He can't touch me even if I do this.
Good for you.
- I hope you aren't being sarcastic.
-  Not at all.
We can't choose the environment we're born into.
Having a great background is a good thing, indeed.
I like that you're straightforward.
By the way, you must be on cloud nine these days.
Yes, I'm happy.
Gosh. Now you're being too honest.
My heart has been wounded.
I'm walking a messy road because of you.
You don't need to look all apologetic.
The messy road doesn't feel so bad...
because my competition is Prof. Hong.
And you're smiling again.
Stop teasing me, Dr Jung.
Today, we will be discussing appointment of a new director...
as well as building the geriatrics centre.
I thought the plan for the geriatrics centre has been vetoed.
The situation has obviously changed.
Change is what enables us to survive.
I'm Director Hong Ji Hong.
I also agree with President Jin.
We must change in order to survive.
I agree with President Jin as well.
I think that we should redirect our goal in order to change.
We've been working to achieve growth that is rather superficial.
The plan for the geriatrics centre is an extension of it.
We should focus on solidifying internal stability...
and enhancing the value of our brand...
instead of growing the size of the hospital...
and having to be burdened with risks and expenses from it.
It's easier said than done.
Solidifying internal stability will also result in extra expenses.
How will we take care of those expenses?
I'm sure all of you know that Prof. Hong has been...
working on developing a deep brain stimulation dopamine sensor.
MH Meditech has decided to invest 60 million dollars in it.
This will bring in immense profit to the hospital...
and solidify our brand image as an influential research institution.
We believe that we should use the profit...
to examine and improve the hospital's welfare systems.
A hospital must be a place where doctors and patients can coexist.
That was a great attack.
You're a Johns Hopkins graduate, indeed. That was impressive.
I owe it all to you. You're the one who brought up the topic of change.
So you're really going to push for expanding the welfare system?
I trust that the board will make the right decision.
I guess you're confident. All right.
I learned a lot from you today.
How is Patient Lee Jin Seong doing?
His blood pressure is 160 over 100.
His headache has worsened after a bowel movement.
- Has he gotten diclofenac yet?
-  Yes.
- You're not avoiding me, are you?
-  Why would I?
Well, I think you're treating me differently.
How could I treat you the same way?
Emotions change.
Why?
Are you scared that I might say I like you?
- No.
-  I see Dr Jung.
Are you making fun of me now?
I'm making fun of myself.
Why didn't you answer my calls?
What is your problem? Why aren't you coming home?
I'm working like a dog as you wished. What is your problem?
Do you know what Hong Ji Hong did to me at the board meeting?
Do you know how he messed with me today?
I told you to become close to him. What have you been doing?
You should've given me a heads-up about what he was going to do!
Do you think I became a doctor to work as your spy?
- What?
-  I have a dream...
as a neurosurgeon too.
So what? Did I say that you can't have a dream?
I wasn't born into this world to fulfil your expectations.
How can you say that to me?
I'm your dad who loves you and supports you more than anyone else.
I love you too.
- That's why I've endured this much.
-  What have you endured?
What did you say in front of Hye Jung?
"Seo Woo is too unbending and straightforward,"
- "so she's not good with people."
-  It's true.
Then can I also tell you the truth?
I got into the university you failed to get in.
I also have good looks which you don't have.
- I also have...
-  That's all I gave you!
If you grew up in the environment that Hye Jung was raised in,
you wouldn't be where you are now!
You wouldn't be here without all of Grandpa's help either!
I was a good student at least.
I am sorry.
So why did you...
(Department of Neurosurgery, Professor Hong Ji Hong)
Gosh, you surprised me.
Did I surprise you?
A little. You didn't tell me you were coming.
Do I have to tell you I am coming?
I think I need to answer carefully to that.
Have a seat.
Why didn't you tell me that you're attending the board meeting?
Why do I have to hear that from Kyung Joon?
- I'm scary, aren't I?
-  A little.
You have to make sure to take vitamin D.
It's important for people like us who don't see any sunlight.
What are you doing right now?
I'm worried that you're going to get sick.
Can we get off work together today?
I have an appointment today.
Fine.
I am eating dinner with Dr Kim to discuss about the investment.
Did I pass?
Yes. You pass.
What's wrong with me?
I want to check on you all the time.
You're going to get tired of me, right?
I won't. It's okay if you check on me all the time.
What's this now?
Drink up. It's vitamin C.
I don't like this. It makes me feel like a child.
No, you don't get to say no. This is for your health.
It tastes just fine. Gosh.
Finish it.
Yes, Ma'am.
Am I right? Dr Pi...
Dr Pi's coming too? Is he?
No, I'm here alone today. Give me some drinks.
Okay.
By the way, is Dr Ahn Joong Dae at the hospital?
I guess he is.
He's probably going to get punished for a month.
He ran away, and he got caught just today.
I heard Hye Jung caught him.
I see.
But she wouldn't say where he caught him.
Did she tell you?
I don't know anything about it.
You two have secrets too?
We don't have secrets.
Then do you know why Hye Jung came to our hospital?
She must've gone there because it's a big hospital!
Your hospital's cafeteria has the best food.
You two have secrets.
She didn't tell you about it.
Gosh, what is she saying?
You look happy. Are you in love?
I will tell you later.
You are in love.
I love you.
What's that? What was that sound?
It's nothing.
I feel good to see you happy.
Ever since your father passed, we haven't done this.
I miss him a lot today.
You were his most beloved student.
Ji Hong,
you understand the part of me...
that neither my wife...
nor my friends understand.
It's hard to understand for people who are not us.
They won't understand the life of a neurosurgeon.
So you should treat me well.
I am older than you, and I'm dying earlier than you.
Thank you for what you did that time.
You went against my father's wishes for me.
Later...
Later when I meet him again,
I will ask for his forgiveness.
Then he will probably say this.
"You never listened to me. I knew this would happen."
Gosh,
why do I have to be worried about entering my own house?
Gosh, those beagles are driving me crazy.
No. I will kick them out if they are there.
I will show them how serious I am.
They are not here.
They aren't here.
Yes!
Who's that?
But they know the password.
Beagles would never press the bell.
Why are you here?
You said you still love me like a sister. I'm not going home.
Hey!
I already feel like this isn't my home! This is...
You're home early.
We came late today to give you some alone time.
- You're here, Seo Woo.
-  Hello.
I've come to be a nuisance tonight.
Gosh, you're no nuisance.
This is the haven for homeless people.
Welcome to the haven, Seo Woo.
Thank you, Uncle Pa Ran. Thank you, In Joo.
Isn't this too much?
I have this thing called privacy too.
Uncle Pa Ran, let's not do this. Please take them with you.
- You should leave.
-  Right.
We will be comfortable here if you leave.
What? But this is my place.
Stop bragging that you own a house.
I am not so sad since I own a house of my own too.
I will leave.
I hope you live happily.
Do you want to know Ji Hong's door lock password?
Do you have it?
What are you doing here?
You're here. I got kicked out from my place.
- Isn't that your place though? – Fist came first before law.
Still, how can you break into my place? Gosh!
Do you think that will make me go up again?
I rather be beaten to death here...
than sleep in the same house with those beagles.
I didn't try opening your fridge.
I thought we weren't that close yet.
We're not close enough,
and yet you're trying to sleep in my place.
We can get close now.
You are the only human in this building.
We humans should get along well.
I will open the fridge then.
Would you like anything?
Bring out some beers.
What are you? A teenager? Why did you leave home?
- How is it for you?
-  What do you mean?
Living in general.
Do you ask how to live before you live life?
You just live because you're alive.
I think my life is just getting worse.
That's good that you know it.
I'm going to sleep.
I'm going to sleep on the couch. Where do you want to sleep?
I'll sleep a little later.
Okay then.
Thinking back,
I think I didn't know I was bad...
when I was in my worst shape.
I realised it only later.
I'm going to bed.
(Pi England)
The phone is busy.
I will call you later.
You are my friend.
I won't do anything that will make me lose you.
Sooni Hawaii.
- Are you leaving now?
-  Yes.
No way.
You're not packing lunch for Dr Yoo, are you?
- What? Can't I?
-  No, you can't.
- Why not?
-  This is too much.
Shouldn't you have breakfast with me...
and go to work with me since I'm here?
Why are you being so needy?
I'm leaving. You can have the ones I messed up.
Prof. Hong!
Can I borrow some underwear? I need to take a shower.
You look like a neat freak. Are you okay with my underwear?
I'm totally okay with it.
But I'm not. I don't share underwear with others.
You're weird. Why would you want to borrow underwear?
Prof. Hong!
I feel sorry for myself.
I wonder where he leaves his underwear.
Ta-da!
I didn't make anything but used a mixer.
It's watermelon juice.
I want to try your food.
I wonder how it will taste.
I've started wanting to cook lately.
Why?
- I want to cook for you.
-  Great minds think alike.
- I think I was right.
-  About what?
Answering your second question.
What are you doing today?
I'm going to work on my dissertation if I'm not needed in the ER.
I bet you won't be able to get very far with your dissertation.
- Don't say that. This looks good.
-  Try it.
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
- Is it good?
-  Yes.
I think they're here.
What happened?
We were on our way to our wedding when a car ran into us.
I think you're hurt pretty bad as well. Are you okay?
I'm fine. Please just help Hye Young.
She's pregnant with my baby.
She's pregnant!
Please hurry. Call Gynaecology.
- Right now!
-  Please hurry.
Please... Please save Hye Young.
Please calm down and wait in the waiting room.
No.
Ma'am, do you hear my voice?
- Did you take an X-ray?
-  Yes.
But the patient is pregnant.
- Did you call Gynaecology?
-  They'll be here soon.
I'm finally in a wedding dress.
- Are you that happy?
-  Yes.
Our Jin Jin...
I wanted to hold our wedding before Jin Jin is born.
I'm sorry.
And thank you...
for being patient, taking care of me,
helping me and trusting my lead.
Don't say that. It was harder for you.
You worked day and night to buy a home for us.
Yes, now we have a home, and we're getting married.
When Jin Jin is born, we'll live happily ever after.
Honey, I love you.
Lee Gi Hwan went from a stupor to drowsy.
Is he in pain?
He says it doesn't hurt except the parts operated on.
Wait a second.
(Hye Jung)
What is it?
A female was brought into the ER because of a car accident.
She's 29 years old...
in a semi-coma, and her GCS is five.
I'm not getting any motor in her limbs.
What about her CT scan?
There is bleeding in her left parietal lobe around 80cc.
I suspect arteriovenous malformation.
She's 20 weeks pregnant.
She's 20 weeks pregnant? All right. I'll be right there.
(Radiography Room)
That's a lot of bleeding. What did Gynaecology say?
The baby is safe. Are you going to perform surgery?
What is your medical opinion, Yeong Gook?
I think this is up to you.
- I'm not the operating surgeon.
-  No one told you to operate.
I'm asking you what the best decision a surgeon can make is.
- Kyung Joon?
-  I don't think you should do it.
- Why not?
-  Her GCS is at four.
Her midline is pushed 15mm to the side, and her pupils are dilated.
What about you, Dr Yoo?
I don't think surgery will make her better.
But I believe...
that her guardian's opinion matters the most in this situation.
You think like an amateur.
That isn't how a surgeon should think.
I won't operate on her.
There is no possibility for her to get any better.
It'll only bring more pain to the patient and the guardian.
Bring the guardian to me.
Dr Hong, this is Lee Hye Young's guardian.
I am afraid...
that the patient...
is severely hurt and shows almost no possibility of getting better.
You said almost.
Isn't that better than having no possibility?
Doesn't that mean she has at least a tiny bit of hope?
Shouldn't you operate on her?
No, I won't.
- Why not?
-  Even if I operate on her,
she won't get better.
I'm also sorry to tell you...
that I can't guarantee...
the safety of your baby.
This can't be possible.
We're finally getting married after three years of living together.
Do you know how happy she was?
This can't be her funeral day.
I know it's hard for you,
but I hope you can accept it...
for the patient and the baby.
I'm sorry.
This is the best I can do in my medical opinion.
Please.
Let's move her to the ICU and keep an eye on her.
Tell me if anything changes.
I must be an amateur.
I was convinced after meeting the patient's guardian.
I think you should operate on her.
Surgeons have to stay away from emotions.
Aren't you thinking from the patient's point of view?
What other point of view would a doctor have?
She's unconscious.
Her guardian's opinion would have the biggest effect on her life.
So?
It's the same result whether you operate on her or not.
It isn't the same.
She has to fight through surgery. Why would put her through that?
What if we decompress her brain so it isn't damaged any further?
We can extend her life.
She can't even breathe on her own.
She might die during surgery along with the baby.
But you never know.
She might miraculously recover.
You're getting rid of the chance...
for that miracle to happen if you don't operate on her.
Whom is this for?
Give her guardian some time.
The possibility of his wife and baby's death must be a big shock.
If you're hesitant about this surgery,
may I do it?
- Hye Jung.
-  I'll do it.
I can do this.
You're overstepping your bounds as a fellow.
If you're doing this because of our relationship...
Had it been the case, I wouldn't have been able to do this.
I'm telling you that I think...
as a doctor.
Then go strengthen your argument before you try to persuade me.
What if I'm the patient?
Will you give up?
That's not fair.
You're not persuading me as a doctor.
Gosh, my back.
Hello, President Jin.
Mr Congressman, what happened?
I hurt my back while playing golf.
So it happened because you're still full of energy.
It proves that you're still youthful.
Gosh, not at all.
Please take good care of me.
Of course. I can do anything for you.
Thank you.
Who will look after me during my stay here?
Let's go in first.
Sure, let's go. Gosh.
Hello, Prof. Hong.
I called you because Congressman Nam here wants you to be his doctor.
I'm Prof. Hong Ji Hong of Neurosurgery.
Prof. Hong, don't you remember me?
I couldn't make it to your father's funeral,
but I paid my condolences.
Thank you.
Oh, right. I watched the video clip about the archer, Lee Soo Jeong.
Gosh, I was so fascinated and impressed by it.
He's the most famous surgeon at our hospital.
Please come in!
I finally get to meet you in person.
I'm a fan of yours.
Hello.
I called you because Congressman Nam wanted to meet you in person.
I like people who appear on television.
I heard you can fight like a gangster.
I heard that you hurt your lower back.
Yes, while playing golf. I'm in so much pain.
I'll take a look and see exactly where the pain is coming from.
- All right.
-  Please lie down.
- Please lie on your side.
-  Okay.
Please raise your left leg.
Gosh, I can't do it.
I'll try lifting it for you.
- Please let me know if it hurts.
-  Okay.
All right. We'll stop there.
The ligaments seem to have been injured,
and you might have a herniated disc.
We'll do a MRI scan and find out exactly what's going on.
Dr Yoo, let me know when his MRI scan is done.
Sure.
Do you still think that you're right about the surgery?
Yes. What about you?
Me too.
Doors are opening.
Doors are closing.
Kyung Joon.
Is Patient Lee Hye Young in the intensive care unit now?
That patient who arrived in her wedding dress, right?
She's still in the emergency room as the ICU is full.
We'll move her there as soon as we can.
All right.
Doctor.
I won't be able to live...
if I have to send her without being able to do anything for her.
If we could...
extend her life by just 10 minutes...
If she can live for another 10 minutes...
to spend more time with our baby inside her...
I want to do anything and everything for her.
Bring the defibrillator.
Chairman Hong has signed the DNR confirmation form.
Bring it!
That's not what Chairman Hong wants.
I might not be able to wake up because of my age.
I do not want to be forced into being resuscitated.
It's arrest.
Please bring the defibrillator.
(Restricted Zone)
Please give me the gown.
I opened the dura mater for you.
Gynaecology, keep monitoring the foetus.
- Yes, Professor.
-  The microscope, please.
Irrigation.
Cottonoid.
The foetus' heart rate is dropping.
We're almost there. I just need to cut the draining vein.
Microsurgical scissors.
Bipolar forceps.
It keeps dropping. We have to close it up as soon as possible.
Why did you do it so late?
I did?
No, you did a good job.
Did you check Patient Lee Change Je's mental status?
That's Kang Soo's job.
I'm in my second year, you know.
There's no need to divide tasks amongst you two.
We should divide the tasks. You're right.
Yes. Thank you.
Are you two chatting away again?
He thinks we're slacking off whenever he sees us talking.
What are you grumbling about now?
- Nothing.
-  Nothing.
- Ahn Joong Dae.
-  Yes.
How can you run away when you're in your second year?
You must set an example for first-year residents.
- Kyung Joon.
-  Yes.
You must pick on him a lot.
What will you do if he runs away again because of you?
Even if I bully him, it's nothing compared to...
how you bully me.
- What?
-  Doctor.
Prof. Hong once bought us a night snack.
Why are you saying that to me?
I know. Why did I suddenly think of that?
I don't understand myself either.
He ordered steamed seafood dish, and we really enjoyed it.
Right? I love you at times like this, Joong Dae.
Do you want to come into my heart?
You brats.
Express yourself clearly. What are you trying to say?
Prof. Hong has his own rules, and I have my own.
Do you want to go check on Mr Lee Chang Je?
- Would you like to?
-  Let's go.
Okay.
Hey.
Hey!
The foetus' heart rate dropped to 90.
The foetus will die when it drops any lower.
Microsurgical scissors.
Bipolar forceps.
That's it.
- We have to hurry up.
-  Okay.
Take out the Microsurgical scissors. Prepare for a suture.
(Operating Room)
We have to wait and see to find out the details.
But the damage was too big from the start.
And she's not responding at all.
- But the surgery went well, right?
-  Yes.
Then she can wake up later. She can get better, right?
We can't promise anything.
How about the baby? Is he all right?
The baby is healthy.
His heart beats well,
and both amnion and placenta are safe.
But the patient is in a very bad shape.
I'm prepared for the worst.
But I did everything I can do.
Okay.
Thank you.
Why did you suddenly decide to have the operation?
I realised that I might stop the chance of a miracle happening.
But you think doctors and miracles don't go well together.
I used to think so.
Neurosurgeons and miracles don't go well together.
We always doubt and doubt again.
Nevertheless, we hope for a miracle.
It's because we are incomplete.
(After one week)
Where is her husband?
He's waiting outside.
Let's go.
The patient is...
nearly in coma.
Soon, her other organs will slowly stop working.
She will eventually stop breathing too.
You must be in a lot of pain having to go through this.
But you have to make a choice.
What choice?
What choice am I to make?
Your wife won't be waking up.
In this case,
there's almost no chance that the baby will live.
Are you telling me...
to give up on my wife and my child?
The only thing we can do...
is to maintain the current state using machines.
What will happen if you maintain the current state?
If we presume that a miracle will happen...
If your wife manages to hang on,
the child can continue to grow inside her body.
The baby is 20 weeks old, so he can't live outside the womb.
Can she hang on though?
We don't know.
But we will try to extend your wife's life...
using life-support machine...
until we can deliver the baby.
She will hang on.
She's a good-hearted woman.
She won't take the child...
and leave me alone.
The miracle didn't happen.
It's normal that miracle doesn't happen.
That's why it's called "miracle".
(Doctors)
I was asked to be a director of Gukil Medical Center.
- I thought about it.
-  Did you get muddled?
I brought a new story.
You have the anaesthesia record, don't you?
- You must be hungry.
-  You became conscious, didn't you?
Do you feel a sense of rivalry towards Prof. Hong?
What's gotten into you? Why can't you remember?
Come to me. We shouldn't do this often though.