Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor Crush]
[Episode 16]
You said I could check on who accessed
medical files within the past five years.
I was told I would receive the records,
but I haven't received them yet.
Yes, I sent my fax number.
Yes.
[South Yangju Gookil Hospital,
Kim Chi Hyun]
We're not always alerted to danger.
I was digging into someone's past,
but I thought I would be safe.
While I'm working on this,
others are not sitting around idly.
Vitals and hemoglobin count are normal.
APCT is showing a bleed of grade two.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Okay, see you soon.
Just go to sleep, would you?
You always go on and on
about mental this and that.
Why don't you take care of
your own mental state, you baby?
Why, you--
What are you going to do?
Are you going to hit me?
You're just a little--
Just try calling me a baby
one more time, seriously.
I'll get you real good then.
Blood.
Gosh, really?
What's wrong with you?
Did you get hit? Who hit you?
Seriously, what the heck?
What's wrong with your kid?
Why would he hit someone?
Did it hurt a lot?
I'm fine.
Of course he's saying he's okay.
Would he say it hurts?
You need to discipline your kids better.
Who hit one of my kids?
He's coming.
Let me see. Both nostrils are bleeding.
Don't you hate hitting too?
I do hate it.
I'm sorry.
Why did you hit him?
He kept mouthing off to me.
What do you mean I was mouthing off?
I was just joking.
There is only so much I can take.
What kind of joke is that?
We are doctors. We need to be the best.
Can't you control yourself?
I'm sorry.
- Why should you be sorry?
- Huh?
Kang Soo, I've only worked with you
a little bit, so I didn't know.
But you're not a bad guy.
If someone treats you this way,
you treat them the way you see fit.
You can go.
Go now.
Hey.
Isn't this wrong?
I think so too.
What's with the cotton for a nosebleed?
You are a doctor.
That's for show, like in Hollywood.
Are you really going to be like this?
Trouble usually starts in the home so...
If you get hit again,
you're in big trouble.
- Okay.
- Let's just go eat.
What a waste of your physical size.
It was a surprise attack.
What surprise attack? Come on.
What's wrong with you?
Are you that tired?
I'm in my first year so it's expected.
First years don't quite have
the knack for it yet.
Still, you should utilize your time.
Thank you, Doctor.
- High five.
- Yes.
What kind of mother are you?
Can you actually eat?
Your daughter isn't even home.
Why are you causing such a fuss?
She often didn't come home
when she was last on duty.
I told you that I yelled at her.
You did a good thing.
She needs to lose some affection for you
to know how precious her mother is.
- What?
- What about it?
She's always been too attached to you
ever since she was little.
The two of you always did leave me out.
Stop saying these useless things
and go see her.
What, exactly, did you do to her?
It's not like you hit her or anything.
Forget it. Never mind.
Sir, how are you?
It still hurts so much.
Where does it hurt?
My eye, right here.
My head hurts too and there's something
that keeps oozing from the wound.
Are you giving him antibiotics?
Yes, we're getting consults from the
Internal Medicine department too.
Once he gets better,
stop the TPN and give him food.
[Director Jin Myung Hoon]
It's hard to see you.
I'm sorry.
Didn't your father talk to you?
I heard about the proposal for me
to become a board member.
We will be nominating you
at the next board meeting.
We're calling it a nomination,
but you're pretty much confirmed.
I can't accept it.
You wouldn't have much work to do.
You would just have to take up a spot
and help Seo Woo.
I like this hospital and
I want to continue working here.
Why don't you have any ambition?
I like being a doctor,
a doctor who helps sick people.
That's what I like.
Have you seen Seo Woo today?
- Yes.
- Bring her to the VIP patient room.
You know that Congressman Na has
been admitted into the hospital, right?
She should get acquainted with him.
You have to do things you don't want to
for the sake of your parents.
No matter how much freedom
Chairman Jung has given you...
You look very tired.
That's how it is for first years.
If you get through it,
the second year will be much better.
Okay.
[VIP Nurse]
Gosh, he's calling me so often.
Yes, I'll be up soon.
- Is it that congressman?
- Yes.
Go change the dressing on Lee Jin Joo,
check her mental state, and chart it.
Okay.
You can eat one too.
How are you feeling?
I called for Doctor Yoo,
but you're here, Doctor Hong.
I'm here for rounds.
Oh, is that so?
Then let's do rounds.
Hello.
Oh my.
I was going to talk to you, Doctor Yoo,
but Professor Hong came.
How are you feeling?
Gosh, I'm still in a lot of pain.
Are you giving me the proper painkillers?
- Are you controlling his pain properly?
- Yes.
If he continues to complain,
add on NSAIDs.
Okay.
We're not going to do surgery?
Surgery won't be necessary.
Tests showed that your disc issues
are not severe.
We will manage it with painkillers,
then discharge you in one week.
How can it be so simple?
Are you sure you're correct?
It is correct.
Don't worry and please rest.
Doctor Yoo.
Why don't you stay awhile
since you're here?
Let's talk a little.
I would like to observe the lives of
people while I'm here in the hospital.
Yes, sir.
How much do you make?
More than 100 million won?
Not as much as you would think.
Should I speak to someone on your behalf?
Pardon?
Let's go in.
Oh, you were here, Doctor Yoo?
How is Congressman Nam?
He's fine. I'll be going. then.
Doctor Yoo is good in the workplace.
She has the natural disposition for it.
You already managed to escape?
I wasn't saying anything,
so he told me to go.
I should go with Kang Soo next time.
You could do that.
He'll be discharged in a few days,
so wait a little bit.
I am. I have to make a living, don't I?
You've grown up a lot.
I'm all grown up, actually.
Oh! Have you had your vitamin D today?
Not yet.
I like people who are dedicated.
If you start something,
you should see it through to the end.
What about the antioxidant?
You're nagging.
I'm still healthy.
You don't need to take care of me.
Still, you're nine years older than me.
I don't want you dying before I do.
Why are you suddenly bringing up death?
It's not sudden.
People whom I love can't die before I do.
You have to do that for me.
How is Lee Hae Young doing?
Should we go check on her now?
I'm finally wearing a wedding dress.
Are you that happy?
Yes!
Our baby.
I wanted us to get the formalities
over with before our baby is born.
I'm sorry... and thank you.
No, it was harder for you.
You were always working
and getting our house ready.
We'll get married and have our baby.
We only have happiness in our future.
Honey, I love you.
Aren't you going to say it back to me?
I said I love you!
Vitals?
Systolic blood pressure
has stabilized at 120.
Her body temperature is between
36 to 37 degrees Celsius.
I know it's a lot of work,
but check on her often.
Okay.
Hey. Keep her temperature
and BP at a normal level.
Do labs every day to check on
her hormone levels.
Make a note if there are any changes.
- Get obstetrics to come daily too.
- Okay.
You two work really well together.
What is that supposed to mean?
What? It doesn't mean anything.
You're being absurd.
Doctor.
How long must she live
for the baby to survive?
The baby has a higher chance to live if
we can incubate the baby at 24 weeks.
However...
it wouldn't be a surprise to anyone
if the patient couldn't survive
even 10 minutes.
I regret it so much, Doctor.
Don't blame yourself.
You're doing very well.
No.
I never told her that I loved her.
That's what I regret the most.
I thought that words were so precious.
I was going to do it at the wedding
during my vows.
I'm sure she knows how you feel.
She's fighting with her dying breath
to protect the baby.
Where are you?
Going to the fellow room.
Stop and don't move.
[Stop and don't move.]
Is something wrong?
I've never told you, have I?
Told me what?
I love you, Hye Jung.
You ran here to tell me that?
Yes.
No matter when or what the situation,
I didn't want to end up regretting it.
Come here.
We shouldn't keep doing this
in the hospital.
Why aren't you doing it?
Doing what?
I'm not going to say it.
Why?
They're such precious words.
I don't want to say them out loud yet.
Hye Jung.
I'm going to do that assignment later.
I won't be seeing you again today.
Yes, okay.
Doctor Pi, where did
Doctor Ahn Joong Dae run away to?
It's a big mystery.
I worried about him for no reason.
Lee Mi Ja is on painkillers, right?
- Yes.
- Increase by half an ampoule.
Okay.
Young Gook.
I thought about it.
Why? Were you feeling conflicted
after the bad thing I did?
A little.
I don't want to ask about your feelings.
I'm the important one here.
I want us to continue being friends.
Okay, then.
No... I just changed my mind.
I'm suddenly curious about your feelings.
I don't want to tell you.
We're just friends, anyway.
Friends.
Come in.
You don't give up, do you?
Aren't you tired of
hearing the same thing?
That's why I brought something new.
I noticed you accessed
my grandma's medical files.
This was before they were destroyed.
Why?
You have the anesthesiology
records, don't you?
Why would I have those?
If you had no intentions of keeping them
why did you open and access files
of a surgery that happened 10 years ago?
Don't you have anything better to do?
Even if you tell me,
no one's life is going to change.
It's legally too late to do anything.
You would just be telling me
as a fellow doctor.
Give me time to think about it.
Joong Dae...
Gosh, my head hurts. Can you...
My head, my head...
Kang Soo, what are you looking for?
Acetaminophen.
You seem to get headaches often.
It's not that.
I just don't like it
even if hurts a little.
I take medicine if it hurts a little
or even if it seems like it will hurt.
Gosh, you can't handle pain.
Move aside.
Let me see.
- Here it is.
- Thank you.
Water.
Thank you.
Okay. All better.
Young Gook!
I'm here to pick up
what I ordered yesterday.
Ah, yes.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Wow! Joong Dae, you're studying hard.
You'll become a professor.
Studying like this for 100 days
won't help you get high grades.
You need to get good study notes.
- Young Gook, do you have study notes?
- No.
Aren't you going to study?
I'm not going to do well on the test.
It doesn't really matter.
I'll suffer through the embarrassment.
I'm so hungry. Order some food.
Uh... that won't be on the test.
Hey.
When did our department
get so cold and fickle?
You guys are hungry, right?
Oh my goodness! What is this? Wow!
What do you mean?
Hey, eat.
Wow! It looks so good.
Wow, is it some sort of special day?
I was hungry so this is great.
This must be about Professor Hong.
Do you have a rivalry with him?
Don't you know how to accept things
with a pure heart?
I am very sorry.
It looks so delicious.
I think I need to lie down.
This is a historical day.
Doctor Jung's buying us food
after my three years here.
Hey, you guys are really funny.
Didn't I pay for us when we
went to hospital outings?
- I don't recall that.
- Neither do I.
I think I might remember if I eat this.
This is getting more
and more interesting.
What? What do you want to eat?
You pigs. Round face, one and two.
Round face? Who is one?
One... and two.
That hurts, that hurts...
Don't hit Joong Dae.
He's going to leave again.
I get tired when he's gone.
You're right. I'll be two. You're right.
We really are round though.
Should I help you with something?
No, don't do a thing.
I get to eat the first thing
Yoo Hye Jung has ever cooked.
Are you testing it out on me
before you give it to Teacher Hong?
Are you watching a different
genre of TV dramas lately?
Things with conspiracies,
lies, and deceit in them.
You sure hold a grudge.
Doctor Ahn Joong Dae was asking me
to hide him, so what could I do?
He had nowhere to go.
Do you take in everyone
with nowhere to go?
No.
Gosh, it's been so long
since I've had time like this.
Did something good happen today?
I feel more relaxed
about my life these days.
Teacher Hong has accomplished a lot.
How could I be here today
if I didn't have you?
I feel the same way.
I think things might work out
with my grandma too.
I think a doctor who was in the
operating room might talk to me.
Seo Woo came and asked me about it.
She asked me if I knew why
you were at Gookil Hospital.
I told her that I didn't know why.
How can I tell her that her dad
led the surgery on your grandma?
I couldn't say that to her.
Cheon Soon Hee, I like you so much.
Yoo Hye Jung, I like you so much too.
But, you know...
I couldn't bring up your grandma to you.
So, I had hoped that you would find
happiness with Teacher Hong.
Then I thought that you would
forget about your grandma.
You didn't, though.
My grandma is my grandma and
Doctor Hong is Doctor Hong.
He's actually helping me out with this.
Gosh, I think we need to
get divorced now.
We've lived together for too long.
Still... you look happy, so I'm happy.
Cheers.
Ah, this is so nice!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
So nice.
How are you administering medication
to Kim Tae Soo?
We're giving it to him through PO.
- What about pain?
- As for pain... hold on.
[Collect Call]
Professor, can I take a call?
It's my younger brother in the army.
Okay, I'll go on ahead of you.
Hello? Hyung Soo.
Are you doing okay?
I'm so busy that I had
no time to go visit you.
You were given an explanation
of the surgery, right?
Yes.
Your arm has good strength too.
Don't worry too much.
Get a central line in
and we'll need to go to the ICU
after surgery, so prepare for that.
Okay.
By the way, what will you do about the
VVIP patient during your surgery?
[VIP Nurse]
You're okay coming with me, right?
I have to say it's okay even if it's not.
He keeps calling for me.
I hope he hasn't gotten worse.
He probably isn't worse.
They'd call Professor Hong then.
I'll open the door.
You say you have a headache?
It hurts. It hurts so much.
Where does it hurt?
It hurts everywhere.
You can't tell me in such vague terms.
You need to tell me more details.
The back of my head feels
very heavy and dizzy.
I feel better after eating.
I'll give you a shot of painkillers.
Let me know if you still feel pain.
Put in an order for a shot of Diclofenac.
No need to order it.
You can give me the shot, Doctor Yoo.
Congressman, can I do it for you?
Fine, then.
I'll be going now.
I have to give you a shot.
How should I do it?
How else would you do it? Just do it.
Not there. Your bottom...
Do it.
[Kang Kyung Joon]
Yes?
The anesthetics haven't set in yet.
You might need to wait.
Okay, I will get Doctor Jin Seo Woo
to take over the VVIP and go.
Okay.
I have to go into surgery.
It's going to take about five hours.
Congressman Na is calling a lot.
Can you keep an eye on him for me?
I have to go to a seminar soon.
I'll finish the surgery and
come out before you have to go.
The director said that a fellow
has to take care of him.
I said I can't. I have to watch this.
Watch it. You can take the calls too.
He has a sprain in his hip
and early stages of disc issues.
Let's help each other out.
I'll assume you're helping
and go do surgery.
Hey, hey!
Yes, okay.
I'm going into surgery now.
Please call Doctor Jin Seo Woo
regarding the congressman.
All right.
These people are so frustrating.
[Seo Woo]
Yeah. What?
Take over Congressman Na for me.
A fellow is supposed to do it.
Hye Jung's in surgery
and I have to leave.
People keep asking me to do things.
I stayed up all night
because I was on duty.
There were three emergencies
while I was on duty.
Let me off the hook.
I have no one I can trust except you.
What are you doing?
I was going to take a nap.
Don't nap. Take over Congressman Na.
- I was there before.
- You were?
Then you can keep watching over him.
I'm going back to sleep now.
You can go back out.
It's not time for you to sleep yet.
Oh, yeah. I have to change
the dressing for a patient.
What's wrong, Congressman?
Oh! Call a doctor. Hurry!
What is wrong with me?
I'm going to check your blood pressure.
Why am I suddenly like this?
[Jin Seo Woo]
Cottonoid.
[VIP Nurse]
The VIP nurse keeps calling.
- Let's focus.
- Okay.
Micro scissor.
Hello.
Yes, Nurse?
Doctor, the congressman has severe
headaches and his BP is 170 over 100.
His headache from before
has become even worse.
What are you doing? Get me a doctor!
He's yelling for a doctor to come now.
Doctor? Doctor Choi Kang Soo?
You're listening, right?
Come to the VIP room now.
[Emergency Jung Yoon Tae]
Gosh.
What? What, what?
A trauma? Semi-coma?
Okay, I'll be right there.
He had a severe headache and then
he suddenly lost consciousness.
- Bring intubation.
- Okay.
[Five missed calls, VIP Nurse]
Congressman Na has lost consciousness.
Doctor Choi Kang Soo said he'd be coming,
but he isn't coming.
What happened?
Let's save the patient first.
Prepare an suboccipital craniotomy.
Okay.
This is very interesting.
Congressman Na has lost consciousness.
What? Why?
He was in the bathroom when he got a
headache and then lost consciousness.
What was his doctor doing?
Yoo Hye Jung left him in
the care of Jin Seo Woo.
She was in surgery.
Why is Seo Woo involved in this?
Professor Hong Ji Hong is
performing an emergency surgery.
We're in trouble if the media finds out.
Things will be so noisy.
Make sure to stop it from leaking.
Okay.
We've been so unlucky lately.
First, it was the corruption in hiring.
We worked hard to fix our image to
cover that up and it's all for nothing.
Which operating room is it?
Are you ready?
Yes, we can get started.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
Where are you going?
You couldn't take care of your patient
and let him fall into that state.
How will you take responsibility for it?
I'll take responsibility for it.
Congressman Na Min Soo is my patient.
Of course, that's a given.
You should head inside.
Doctor Yoo should not
assist with the surgery.
He's my patient.
I will accept reprimand for
my actions after this surgery.
- That can't happen.
- It can.
I'm leading this surgery.
I choose who assists me.
Go on in, Doctor Yoo. Get ready.
Fine, I was once a surgeon.
I will respect your authority
as a surgeon.
However, you have more responsibility
with that authority.
- I know that.
- Then save him.
That's what I want very much.
Doctor Yoo was in charge
of Congressman Na
and I was told you helped her.
- Yes.
- So how did this happen?
If we had gotten to him a little earlier,
things wouldn't have gotten so bad.
I'm sorry.
Just give me the facts.
This could threaten the entire
Neurosurgery department.
Section Chief, I don't know anything.
I went to the congressman's room
to help out Doctor Yoo.
The VIP nurse called you.
She says you said you'd come,
but you didn't and time was wasted.
No, I really did not get a call.
Irrigation.
What kind of disaster is this?
Congressman Na Min Soo...
is someone who could even
become a presidential candidate.
We've kept it from the media.
We're in trouble if it leaks out.
What is this?
There is never a quiet day, is there?
Elevator.
Gown.
Bipolar.
Prepare the suture.
Addison forceps.
Micro scissors.
Cottonoid.
Wash this spot.
Get the hemostatic ready.
Cottonoid.
What is going on?
They're checking to see if
the bleeding has stopped.
He's done with
if he's still hemorrhaging.
Just stay put. They're checking.
The bleeding has stopped.
That's a relief.
I think they've stopped the bleeding.
The swelling of the brain is getting bad.
It's okay. Swelling can happen.
What's going on now?
Dad, don't say anything.
I'm getting scared
every time you say something.
All right.
The brain swelled up after the surgery.
When the Cisterna Magna rises
and touches the spinal cord
it will go back down.
Then, is this a success?
Yes.
Suction.
Increase suction.
Increase suction!
The spinal fluid is out. It's done.
The swelling is down now.
They're done.
Good work.
- Close up.
- Okay.
Finish up, Professor Hong Ji Hong.
Don't leave it to the doctor who
caused this trouble in the first place.
You do it.
Give me the bipolar.
Gauze.
Keep checking on him and let me know
when he regains consciousness.
Isn't there any way to wake him up?
The only thing we can do is wait.
Gosh!
That's all for now.
Until he wakes up, that is.
Yes.
What brings you by?
It seems like you're in some trouble.
I'm acting a little pathetic. Sit down.
It's Kang Soo. I called for him.
I had some questions for him.
Come in.
We need to know all the facts
to have a countermeasure.
That's my theory.
Okay, let's sort things out.
There's some empty time.
The VIP nurse called Doctor Jin.
She couldn't reach her,
so she called Doctor Yoo.
She couldn't reach Doctor Yoo.
She called you, Kang Soo.
Why didn't you go up
when you got the call?
That's the thing...
That's the thing that's driving me crazy.
I never got a call from the VIP nurse.
- Kang Soo.
- Yes?
I'm not trying to criticize you.
This issue isn't about one person.
A Neurosurgery fellow and
residents are all involved in this.
We all need to survive.
I'm really telling the truth here.
[Choi Kang Soo]
Wow! Is a ghost playing tricks on me?
She really did call me.
She did call you.
I'm telling you she didn't.
It has to be an error.
Let me take a look at mine.
[VIP Nurse]
[Today, 11:25]
It's there, isn't it?
Yes.
Is something wrong with your brain?
How come you can't remember?
I'm really sorry.
I will go and tell them.
No, I'm responsible for it.
He was a patient assigned to me.
There's nothing you should be
held responsible for.
[Director's Office]
This is Yoo Hye Jung.
The director would like to see you.
Let's talk about what happened today.
I'll take responsibility for it.
I like that attitude.
You'll come before the disciplinary
committee and will be held responsible.
I don't know what you may think,
but this is the kind of person I am.
I am reasonable and generous.
I let you off once before.
Not this time.
I understand.
- Yes.
- What happened?
Doctor Yoo will be getting disciplined.
I can't shield her.
All of the fellows and residents of
our department are mixed up in it.
They need a sacrificial lamb.
It's not that.
Doctor Yoo was his doctor.
Even if he wasn't critical,
she shouldn't have been careless.
Or she should have put him in the care
of someone she could trust.
You can't allow a disciplinary committee.
If this goes to the committee,
it will disgrace her name as a doctor.
Don't you think I know that?
But I can't make this into a
Neurosurgery department issue.
Why are you coming from that direction?
Are you coming from
the fellow room?
Yes.
Were you comforting Hye Jung?
If I can be a source of comfort...
Why would you bother doing
something so pointless?
You can do that for 100 days.
She'll only love Hong Ji Hong.
It's love because I'm doing
pointless things.
Did you always have
this naive side to you?
I did. It was just in a
deep sleep inside my heart.
Whatever, I don't know.
I don't care about Doctor Yoo's problems.
You are really a sad sight.
Don't you hate Hye Jung?
She won't even accept your feelings.
I'm doing what I feel and
Doctor Yoo is doing what she feels.
We're both just following our hearts.
Well, aren't you just a saint?
Hey.
Isn't it wrong for Doctor Yoo to
take the blame all by herself?
I know, right?
I wish Congressman Na Min Soo
would wake up.
If he doesn't, things could get
really problematic.
Isn't this all unfair though?
How can anyone know about a hypertensive
brain hemorrhage until it happens?
You only know when it happens.
It doesn't show up in tests.
- How can anyone be held responsible?
- You're right.
They want people to be held
responsible for everything.
- It should be fine if he recovers.
- Yeah.
Just go to sleep, would you?
You seem to get headaches often.
Yes, Nurse.
Is something wrong with your brain?
How come you can't remember?
One shot, one shot, one shot!
- Hey!
- Oh, hey! You're here?
I have a favor to ask.
What is it?
Yes?
Professor.
Kang Soo, what is it?
I had something to ask you.
Do you have time?
Yes, come sit down.
These are my friend's CT and MRI scans.
I was wondering if you could take a look.
He must have a doctor if he has CT scans.
He's scared and very nervous.
So, he wants to get second opinions
from other hospitals too.
Can't you give your opinion?
I can.
It looks like a meningioma.
Yes, it's a meningioma
near the sphenoid bone.
It's very large too.
He's also experiencing absence seizures.
He's been zoning out and blacking out.
He's having trouble remembering things.
A meningioma along with absence seizures.
That's pretty unique.
Tell him to get it treated quickly.
Is he a close friend of yours?
I just saw Director Jin.
This issue will proceed according to
the rules and procedure.
I was going to go meet the director now.
I don't want you to make any
requests to him on my behalf.
It's not because it's you.
I would do it for anyone
who had to go through this.
I would to protect my pride,
at least with him.
I was the congressman's doctor.
It is my fault.
I met with Section Chief Kim Chi Hyun.
He was different than before.
I have hope that I can resolve my
grandma's issue soon.
Good. That's a relief.
To a person who likes
rules and procedures
I want to deal with him in that same way.
I want you to just to watch over me.
Watch how I deal with it instead.
It's not so easy for me.
Not doing anything in this situation
is very hard for me.
What did I say you should do
in times like this?
I know I taught you.
I can't do it here.
We can find a place
where we can be alone.
Doctor...
You're right. Someone might come.
Congressman Na Min Soo has received
surgery from a brain hemorrhage.
He is currently unconsciousness.
Gookil Hospital states that
they took appropriate measures.
They claim that
the surgery was successful
and the congressman is in recovery.
However, there is concern
over the fact that
the congressman is still unconscious.
What is Congressman Na's illness
and what are his symptoms?
He had a hypertensive brain hemorrhage.
His capillaries and veins were
being damaged for a long time.
The blood vessels could no longer
withstand the pressure and ruptured.
It was not caused by any external factor.
It was a brain hemorrhage.
What state is he in right now?
Is there a chance he will wake up?
The surgery was a success.
We are checking his progress.
You say that,
but he is still unconscious.
That is common for patients
who have had brain surgery.
I cannot give you a
conclusive statement right now.
Thank you.
He's gone from a semi-coma to a stupor.
Now it's done.
Check his vitals often
and change his dressing.
He should be okay now.
Good job.
Gosh, seriously.
I'll use this opportunity to set this
hospital on the right path again.
We will make an example
of Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
Why did you call me?
I'm sorry. It's all my fault.
It's not your fault.
This should be happening to me.
I'll take responsibility for everything.
Do you think just anyone can take
responsibility for things?
It's because it's me that I can do it.
I'm kind of great.
Even the way you comfort people
is on a different level.
Thanks for recognizing
that I was comforting you.
Don't worry.
I'm going to go get disciplined now.
[Collect Call]
Hi, Hyung Soo.
Can you call at this hour?
It's not like you're my grandma.
Why would you call me just because
I was in your dream?
It was just a silly dream.
There is nothing wrong with me,
so don't worry.
If there's any place that's dangerous...
If there are any
dangerous places, don't go.
Don't get hurt.
You got it?
Hyung Soo.
You know I'm always
thinking about you, right?
[Disciplinary Committee]
As danger approaches...
I think I am getting one step closer
to the truth I've been searching for.
I need to create opportunities of danger.
Subtitles by DramaFever