(Episode 17)
The truth that can't be punished by the law.
The truth that has no choice but to rely on a good conscience.
I chased after the truth...
to hear a sincere apology.
This spread wider than I thought.
- Keep the camera steady.
-  Got it.
Are you drunk?
Don't ever step a foot in my operating room.
I'm sorry.
- She's bleeding.
-  Suction.
Call and ask for blood.
We need blood urgently.
I think you'll have to open the abdomen.
She's in shock.
Her blood pressure is dropping.
- Let's do it.
-  Okay.
It's a cardiac arrest.
Start pumping.
I don't know how my life will change...
the moment I find out the truth.
(Gukil Medical Centre)
(57th Disciplinary Committee Meeting)
We will now begin the disciplinary meeting for Dr Yoo Hye Jung...
for damaging the reputation of Gukil Medical Centre...
as the Congressman's doctor.
First, I'd like to thank you.
I personally think it's an honour...
to be someone influential enough...
to damage the reputation of this hospital.
You are the Congressman's doctor, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Why weren't you able to respond...
when he complained about being in pain?
I was operating on a patient with a ruptured cerebral aneurysm.
I asked a fellow doctor to respond to his calls during the surgery...
before starting the operation.
Why are you bringing up someone else right now?
The problem is that you handed your responsibilities to someone else.
Did you have to operate on the patient at that exact time?
It was my patient,
and a ruptured cerebral aneurysm is like a time bomb.
I couldn't delay it.
Does this mean that you think...
you did nothing wrong in regards to what happened to the Congressman?
Yes.
I'm thankful that you think of me as such an important person,
but I believe I made the right choice.
Isn't this unfair?
Why should Dr Yoo get disciplinary action?
I know. They should blame Dr Jin.
He's leaving his daughter out.
This is unfair for people without parents in high places.
Do you know what you call that?
What is it?
You scared me.
Hi.
What is this weird vibe?
- No.
-  That can't be.
Why would we?
- Tell me what's going on.
-  We were just...
talking about how sad we are that Dr Yoo is getting punished.
Isn't that right?
Go check Patient Lee Tae Sik's dressing.
All right.
Dr Jin, the President would like to see you.
Come in.
Are you still upset with me? Why are you avoiding me?
Weren't you in the disciplinary committee meeting?
We're done hearing the explanation of the person in question.
We'll decide on a disciplinary action after lunch.
I'm going to bring this up when we make the decision.
(Yoo Hye Jung)
Why didn't you tell me Prof. Hong was your high school teacher...
and that Dr Yoo is the one responsible for your burns?
Please don't bring this up.
I don't want to get involved because of this.
Why wouldn't I use such a good opportunity?
I'm here to compliment you.
I've put you through too hard of a training.
What am I to you?
You gave me the stick last time. Is this my carrot?
I don't want your compliments any longer.
I couldn't get any sleep after slapping you.
- Do you know how much I love you?
-  I want you to leave it alone.
This is my weakness.
Do you know how long I was in pain because of this?
I'm going to kill myself if you bring this up.
Are you going somewhere?
I will face disciplinary action. It's just a matter of how bad it is.
I'm getting ready for it.
Do you think this is my fault?
Yes, I do.
You handed him over to Yeong Gook when I asked you.
But I can't get anything done if I think that.
- So I won't blame you.
-  Then what?
I was unlucky.
I was scared for a second.
I thought you had feelings just like me...
and that it'd only be normal for you to blame me.
But you're different.
Are you hurt this time because I don't blame you?
Does everyone else around you blame others in these situations?
Yes.
Everyone around me does.
Don't criticise me for being different from them.
Does it look like I'm criticising you?
I never criticised you.
I looked up to you.
You're lucky you're so smart.
- You held a disciplinary meeting?
-  Yes.
Was it necessary to make such a big deal out of this?
You should've ignored it.
We have to make sure the employees are alert by showing an example.
Be careful.
I have a bad feeling about this situation.
I think it's since then.
We took a big risk...
when we put the hospital through the tax investigation to get Doo Sik.
It's okay, Father. You've become soft.
I wouldn't be who I am if it weren't for that.
- Fine. Do a good job.
-  Okay.
The different levels of disciplinary action are...
warning, reduction in salary, suspension and termination.
I believe a warning is enough for Dr Yoo.
How can we do that when she's all over the media?
She's not even showing any regret.
We should fire her.
If we fire her for this, she can fight back...
that there is a problem in the disciplinary measures.
This is an issue for the entire Department of Neurosurgery.
I don't think we should have an individual take all the blame.
Are you saying that because of your personal feelings for her?
You're the one who's letting your personal emotions take over.
He's not picking up.
Have you eaten yet?
Is Kim Soo Kyeong's CT out yet?
I'll take her over right now.
Your phone. Why do you never pick up?
You turned our department upside-down, so wake up!
Did you forget again? What a moron.
Focus on work, not your webtoon.
Do you have time to waste?
That's weird. Why didn't he talk back?
Stop it.
He must be dying inside.
He adores Dr Yoo and he might have cut her career short.
I'll keep pushing him.
They're too laid back. That's why we have issues.
- It's been a while.
-  Hello.
I've been waiting. I am glad you finally called.
It feels good to be welcomed.
Thanks for making the trip. Do you want something to eat?
My treat.
No, it's fine.
Thanks for being so kind.
I wonder if...
your offer from last time is still on the table.
Of course it is.
(Hong Hong Hong)
Hello, Mr Hong.
I have two bits of good news and one bit of bad news. Are you free?
Go on, then.
I want the good news first.
I'll give you just one, then.
- Why?
-  Good things are hard to come by.
I want the giving tree back.
I miss my Daddy Long Legs.
I won't go back.
The good news.
I will deliver the conclusion the disciplinary committee reached.
It's best to hear it from me.
That's true.
What's that bad news?
The verdict.
One month's suspension.
It's shorter than I thought.
You were great today.
I was so proud to be your boyfriend.
I was glad you asked the right questions.
I didn't want to be there just to accept punishment.
I wanted to show everyone how much I'd grown.
For the next bit of good news, we need a change of scenery.
That's a deal.
Who will look after Hee Young while I'm away?
What are you doing here? She isn't your patient.
Your patient is my patient.
We never split duties.
You don't have to feel sorry.
I adjusted her IV drops.
I only got one month's suspension.
Take good care of her for me.
(Neurosurgery, Kang Kyung Joon)
- Kyung Joon.
-  Yes?
Did you change Lee Soon Jin's dressing?
I told Kang Soo to.
Is that everyone's favourite catchphrase these days?
What's wrong with you?
She has an infection. Do your job!
I apologise.
Is that it?
I'll get right to it.
This is why the residents are in such a mess.
One forgot a call he got, and another ran away.
Where did things start to go wrong?
Kang Kyung Joon. How dare you call yourself a chief.
It's all my fault, Doctor.
He did nothing wrong.
Shut your mouth.
How dare you interrupt.
Sorry.
You're the reason I always end up in trouble.
What did I do to upset you so?
Where were you? Why didn't you pick up?
I took Kim Soo Kyeong down for her CT.
Why did you do that now?
I told you off just a while ago, and yet nothing has changed.
Are you a doctor?
Why are you so quiet? Talk back like you used to.
If you can't do better, just quit.
You got Dr Yoo suspended.
How many more must suffer...
Will you just stop it?
I feel bad.
I feel so bad I don't dare say anything.
What more can I say?
- Kang Soo.
-  Kang Soo.
- Nurse.
Kang Soo. Intubate him.
Okay.
- Check his vitals.
-  Okay.
Kang Soo. Kang Soo.
Kang Soo!
(Choi Kang Soo)
What do you see?
A meningioma by his sphenoid bone.
It's quite big.
- You're right.
-  It's near...
both the optic and motor nerves.
It could blind him or affect the feeling in his hands.
It makes sense now.
He often took medication for headaches.
He hates being in pain.
He look dazed often.
He said he was a heavy drinker...
but he collapsed at our party after one drink.
What are you doing?
Sharing witness accounts?
I wonder if he's awake.
How do you feel?
Stay in bed.
Are you embarrassed?
A bit.
You should've told us you were sick.
I...
I feel terrible. You made us look bad.
When did it start?
Was this your first GTC seizure?
I don't know.
How bad is the headache?
The back of this eye throbbed.
A dull pain.
The pain was...
a 7 out of 10?
That must've hurt.
Is your eyesight okay?
Joong Dae.
I think my eyesight worsened in my left eye.
I have absence seizures too.
Kang Soo.
Did you know you had a meningioma and absence seizures?
Did you ignoring the congressman have something to do with that?
I had an absence seizure while I was on the phone...
with the nurse.
I didn't know because I had no memory of it.
Get some rest.
- You, come with me.
-  Sure.
Yeong Gook, Joong Dae.
I'm sorry.
Get some rest.
Darn it.
You have to work tomorrow. Should you be up so late?
I'm jobless for a month, so I like being out at night.
That was quick.
You found a positive side already.
I found one, and I'll keep looking for the whole month.
I'll be very busy, then.
I must entertain a jobless girlfriend.
Do you mind?
No, I like it.
Now, you can tell me the second bit of good news.
I'm really excited.
I'll tell you later. I want to make you wait.
- You're home early.
-  Hello.
Complain as you might. But there's no place like home.
If I can't get rid of the company, I might as well enjoy it.
Where's In Joo?
She went to her own home.
The renovation's done.
I see.
I heard what's going on.
It must be hard on Ji Hong.
Dr Yoo's tough.
She'll use her time wisely.
A month's break can be good for her.
How did you end up falling for Ji Hong's girlfriend?
I don't know.
Find someone else.
I'll scour all the girls I know and set you up with the prettiest.
Forget it.
I haven't felt like this in a while.
Love is a hard emotion to come by.
How deep is it?
Uncle.
You know how much I hate politics.
I do. I hate it, too.
I'm actually considering joining the board of directors for her.
Why?
I don't want her to ever have to go through that again.
Ji Hong should watch out, then.
This is exactly the kind of moment I wanted to go home...
when I was out here fishing with my father.
When you couldn't catch any fish?
No, I just hate long silence. It's not for me.
I had to keep doing things.
But now, I like sitting here and doing nothing like this.
I can understand why Father used to like going fishing.
Why is it that people always begin to understand each other better...
after they part ways than when they were together?
Be good to people before they leave you.
Be good to me when I'm still around.
Yes, Sir!
The second good news.
Dr Kim Chi Hyun proposed a deal.
What does he want in return for the anaesthesiology report?
I suggested an alternative instead of accepting his request.
I'm waiting for him to consider it and accept it at the moment.
If he says no to it, I'll make him say yes.
I'll take care of it. All you need to do...
is to wait for me to get the anaesthesiology report,
take it to President Jin and make him apologise to you...
then take your hands off of it altogether.
Ms Kang...
Your grandmother got on her knees in front of me...
to ask me to take good care of you.
If I could see her now, I want to ask her if I'm doing a good job.
You are.
Do you know what this is?
It was always hung onto your bag.
It's a key chain I used to use before the accident.
My parents...
didn't have to die then.
They missed the golden hour because of people.
I really wanted to wipe out the entire world then.
My family used to be very happy together.
Grandma and I were happy together too...
before she got the surgery.
I don't believe in tomorrow.
This moment right now is the only thing that matters to me...
because we might die tomorrow.
What Ms Kang wants is for you to be happy,
not for you to give up today to find out the truth about her death.
To me, that's the reason I live today.
Yes. That's why I'm trying to help you.
Your fight is almost over now.
- Oh, it's you.
-  Hello.
- Are you done with dressing change?
-  Yes, I'm done.
Is there anything I can do? I'm bored out of my mind.
You got all your energy back in just one day. Go get some rest.
Chief. Is there anything for me to do?
No.
What's the matter with him?
I don't know. He's been acting strange ever since...
he saw your CT scan yesterday.
(Neurosurgery, Professor Hong Ji Hong)
Come in.
Have a seat.
(Neurosurgery, Hong Ji Hong)
Hey, so the MRI scan you showed me the other day was yours.
- Yes.
-  You little...
You need a surgery.
The tumour is creating pressure...
against your optic and oculomotor nerves,
so we won't do anything risky during the surgery.
Professor, what if anything goes wrong?
Will I not be able to work as a surgeon any more?
Let's not think about anything negative.
(Neurosurgery, Doctor Jung Yoon Do)
- You need to get a surgery.
-  Yes.
We'll use the total removal method.
If the nerves are damaged during the surgery,
my vision could drop or I could possibly lose my eyesight, no?
You haven't exhibited symptoms of diplopia yet, so it'll be all right.
I'll make time this week out of my busy schedule.
We can do it at night, too. Let me know when is the best for you.
(Neurosurgery, Jung Yoon Do)
(Neurosurgery, Hong Ji Hong)
(Office of Vice President)
I saw your MRI scan.
You need to get a surgery.
I think a subtotal removal will be better than a total removal.
You're not going to perform the surgery yourself, are you?
- Do you want me to do it?
-  No.
I'm actually here to talk to you about that.
(Doctor Kim Chi Hyun)
So did you think about it?
You're very impatient.
The faster we move, the better the result will be.
Also, it'll look better if I push you like this.
Can't it be at Gukil Medical Centre at all?
No, it can't.
Then I'll have to think about it more.
I can still approach President Jin Myung Hoon.
Of course. Make your decision after careful consideration.
It'll affect the next 20 years of your life.
- I'm exhausted.
-  You're working so hard.
Kyung Joon.
Schedule Kang Soo's surgery.
Okay.
Prof. Hong also told us to schedule Kang Soo's surgery.
- Really?
-  What?
You didn't tell him that I'm doing the surgery?
He told us to prepare for it as soon as he saw Kang Soo's MRI scan,
so I thought you two had already discussed it.
All right.
It looks like there's a bit of issue with Dr Choi's surgery.
Where's Dr Choi now by the way?
Chief.
Why are you avoiding me?
I'm not avoiding you.
You weren't there when I woke up.
I'm sorry.
I hit your head a lot.
Don't be silly. You're a doctor, so you should know better.
My Kang Soo! You're here.
What were you doing?
I was looking up the surgery procedure.
So whom will you choose? Prof. Hong or Dr Jung?
You sound so excited. There's nothing exciting about his surgery.
So which one of you will be going into Kang Soo's surgery?
I don't like it when you guys look so serious.
Who's going to assist the surgery?
Raise your hand!
You guys are hurting my feelings here.
Other doctors are lining up to do my surgery.
What is wrong with you guys?
How are we going to shave your head?
Well, I won't be able to do it myself.
You never gave up your style...
no matter how badly you were scolded, Kang Soo.
I can't go into the OR because I'm in my second year.
Hey, I'm... I'm sorry.
He's so silly.
Here's your food!
- I hope you enjoy it.
-  Thank you.
You should've just stayed home. Why are you doing that here?
I stayed home all day.
- Have you heard from Mr Hong?
-  Yes. He'll be here.
There he is.
Mr Hong!
Hello!
It's hot. Give me cold beer.
Okay. Coming right up!
You look happy.
I have a gift for you.
Can it be what I'm imagining?
It is that one.
(The Anaesthesiology Report)
Now I did everything I can do to you.
Thank you.
I want you to be freed from what happened to your grandmother.
That's the best gift you can give me.
(Operating surgeon, Jin Myung Hoon)
Gosh, you're handsome.
Neurosurgeon Dr Choi Kang Soo!
Let's do this!
(CPR was given for 30 minutes but the patient didn't come back.)
Yes.
Welcome.
Did you bring the anaesthesiology report?
Yes.
I will give you a precise interpretation of it.
(The Anaesthesiology Report)
During the surgery, around 12:15, inferior vena cava ruptured.
- It's bleeding.
-  Suction.
Her abdomen was opened at 12:30.
Let's open the abdomen.
- Yes, Doctor.
-  Yes, Doctor.
Around 12:50, cardiac arrest happened.
It's a cardiac arrest!
At 1:20, she had a table death.
Excessive bleeding caused cardiac arrest.
That caused her to pass away in the middle of the surgery.
I can manage to...
read that much, you see.
Then I will tell you something more that you don't know.
Choosing a laparoscope operation for stomach cancer...
is the operating surgeon's experimental choice.
In 2003, laparoscope operation was not common.
It was still new back then.
I think I haven't heard that it was a laparoscope operation.
What's a little strange is that...
he didn't open her up right after the inferior vena cava ruptured...
despite the excessive bleeding.
Was that the surgeon's conviction?
I am not sure.
Ask the operating surgeon.
Here's my opinion on this record...
is that the operating surgeon touched a big vein by mistake...
and caused excessive bleeding.
Had he made a quick decision to make the right decision...
and opened her up right away,
the extreme situation wouldn't have happened.
So the operating surgeon made a wrong decision.
Certainly.
Weren't you supposed to be suspended?
That's right.
Yet you are still here.
You are one passionate doctor.
Today, I've come to hand in the homework you have given me.
Don't you remember me?
I was the guardian of Ms Kang Mal Soon 13 years ago.
Let's go inside.
I was waiting for you to come.
Did you know who I was?
You're telling everybody who you are.
Isn't it even more strange to hope that I wouldn't know you?
We talked on the phone too.
Did you pretend not to remember me this whole time then?
I didn't really have to broadcast it.
You would have not come to me...
if you are a realistic person.
Please do not talk to me too casually.
This isn't exactly a casual relationship.
Please don't speak to me without the honorific.
It makes it feel like we're getting closer, and I hate it.
You told me 13 years ago...
that you would accept the punishment...
if I prove that you didn't do your best.
So?
No.
So what, Doctor?
This is the proof.
How can that prove that I didn't do my best?
Did you explain to my grandmother...
about the laparoscope operation?
You just said you were going to open her up.
We never heard about the new surgery procedure.
But the laparoscope operation is an excellent surgery...
for a patient because his stomach isn't opened up.
At the time, it was the best method.
It wasn't covered by insurance. You didn't do it for the money?
If you act like this, we can't have a good conversation.
How can there be a table death in the stomach cancer surgery?
You've clearly made a mistake.
Making a mistake is different from not giving your all.
You could do your best and still make mistakes.
Did you just say you did your best?
Why do you think I didn't do anything to you until now then?
That must've been because I wasn't threatening.
The statue of limitation has already expired,
and you won't be damaged at all if the word gets out.
You know it well.
Surgeries can go wrong.
You became a neurosurgeon, so you should grow up.
How can you still have a high school girl's sentiments?
Even if I knew who you were, I didn't torture you.
I was even giving opportunities to you.
Are you saying you hadn't done anything wrong at all?
I made a mistake.
But I did my best.
So I am not entitled to be punished like you insist.
But I will apologise.
I shouldn't have made mistakes.
Now, I don't owe you anything, right?
You're doing everything on your own.
I made the mistake, so I should be the one apologising.
Dr Yoo, you're dating Prof. Hong Ji Hong, right?
That's a good catch.
Focus on more positive aspects. Life is short.
I was so naive.
I underestimated you.
You are truly amazing.
I thought an apology would be all I needed.
But after getting an apology from you,
I feel even more upset.
I expected you to sincerely apologise...
to the victims of your mistakes.
That was my mistake.
Ask Prof. Hong.
He's just like me.
Everyone who's lived this life is the same as me.
I will leave for now.
Don't come back for this.
It would be even better if you never come back to this hospital.
Do you want to work...
for the hospital run by me?
Okay.
You dread law, so I will get you with the law.
Did you talk well?
Do you know any attorneys?
I want a good one.
Why do you need one?
I have to see if I can sue him.
Did he not apologise?
He did. He did it insincerely.
I hope he gets ruined.
How can he be so indifferent?
I thought the anaesthesiology report was the end of it. But it's not.
It's not.
Now that I have proof, I will try everything.
Can't you just stop?
President Jin said...
that you're just the same as him...
and that everyone who knows how the world works is the same.
Do you think I am just being immature,
trying to uncover the truth behind my grandma's accident?
Listen.
I'm just sad you're letting this ruin your present state.
Don't cloud the issue and answer the question.
Do you agree with President Jin?
Why are you being so aggressive? I'm on your side.
You shouldn't fight with me.
It's because I'm angry.
I don't feel like anyone in the world understands me.
Not even you.
I'll introduce you to an attorney.
Do what you want.
I'm being punished for sending you to the disciplinary committee twice.
I'm going to get surgery. See you in a month.
I'm sorry I'm not there for you.
I'll go visit you at the hospital.
You're well prepared. Are you all ready?
Who do you want as your surgeon?
I'd like for you to do my surgery.
Okay. I'm happy you chose me, but why?
I saw my MRI.
There's a high possibility my eyesight will be affected.
I see.
To be frank,
this won't threaten your life at all.
But it could be the end of your career as a neurosurgeon.
The surgeries we perform are all meticulous.
You know bad eyesight is fatal, don't you?
I'd rather have you kill me if that were to happen.
Kang Soo.
Being a neurosurgeon isn't the only way of life.
No, it's all I have.
That's why I chose you.
Dr Hong.
I have one brother. That's all.
I'm the head of the family.
Even since I was little,
I endured through struggles with the dream...
of becoming a cool doctor like you.
I thought...
that dream would come true in a few years.
How could this happen?
It seems so easy for everyone else.
Why is my life such a struggle?
(Law Firm Sunflower)
Prof. Hong gave me a call.
Yes, I heard he called to tell you what I'm here for.
(Operation Record)
This is the operation record.
This is a copy of the anaesthesiology report.
I told him over the phone that you can't take this to criminal...
or civil court for something that happened 13 years ago.
The statute of limitations has expired.
Couldn't there be something left if you look hard?
It'll be rejected because of the statute of limitations.
It can be anything. Could it be linked to anything legal?
What did you do for the past 13 years if you're this desperate?
You should've come 10 years ago.
Long time no see. Why don't you come over any more?
I've decided to accept the beagles.
I saw that Kang Soo chose you.
You said you'd do a total removal, didn't you?
- That's me.
-  No wonder he didn't choose you.
Dr Kim.
I wanted see Kang Soo before he went into surgery.
But I heard he refused to do the surgery today.
- Why?
-  I'm looking into it now.
- Kang Soo.
-  Hi, Dr Kim.
Have a seat.
- How are you feeling?
-  I'm good.
Then why are you postponing your surgery?
My brother is supposed to be here, but he hasn't arrived yet.
I want to see him first.
You never know.
I might lose my sight if the surgery goes wrong.
That won't happen.
That's why I said "I might".
It's become a habit.
I always think about the worst case scenario.
It isn't just you. I do the same.
This is a battle against time.
You and the operating team have to hold up for 12 hours.
Kang Soo!
It's my brother.
Young Soo!
Salut!
Private Choi Young Soo, reporting a furlough.
Did you eat?
Not yet.
Take a look at this.
Ta-da! I'm now a certified cook in cooking Korean food.
I'm planning to get ones for Western and Japanese food too.
Are you looking at this?
- Are you, are you, are you?
-  I saw it, I saw it, I saw it.
You little... You are too talkative for a man.
- Kang Soo.
-  Yes?
Can you not be a doctor if you get surgery?
Who said that?
No one. I'm just asking.
I think you're the coolest person in the world.
I hope your surgery goes well.
I...
don't care whether you're a doctor or not.
Got that?
The surgery will take long. You should take a nap.
Kang Soo.
I'm sorry for causing you so much trouble.
When did you cause me trouble?
Look at me.
You're one good-looking man.
- That hurts.
-  Don't be a baby.
Do you have abs already?
- Stop that.
-  You must work out a lot.
- Did you feel it?
-  Yes.
(Operation time, Current time, Anaesthesia time)
Don't you have any operations today?
Yes, I do. I'll have to leave soon.
Are you going to stay here for the whole 12 hours?
I don't know. I'll come and go.
I hope everyone does their best.
My gown, please.
Today's surgery is a battle against time.
Let's try our best...
with the patient that has to hold up for a long time.
Scalpel blade number 20.
Suction.
I'll change the blade.
(Operating Room)
(Current time)
CUSA.
I'll be back after seeing some patients.
(Current time)
Bipolar forceps.
Have some cottonoids ready.
Irrigation on this area.
Can someone wipe off my sweat?
That's good.
Right here.
Here we go.
For a biopsy.
Is there any way we can start a case on this?
No.
The statute of limitations has already expired.
There's nothing we can do.
I've been thinking how to approach it.
The anaesthesiology report is different from the operation record,
which means that one of them was probably manipulated.
Are there any legal penalties that apply for committing such forgery?
It's against Article 88 and 22 of the Medical Service Act.
The punishment will be either a jail term of under three years,
or a fine of up to 10,000 dollars.
There's a statute of limitations for these penalties as well.
When was the operation record written?
It was probably written at that time.
I guess it won't work either, then.
Also, you said that your family settled with them.
There's nothing you can do legally.
Would things have been different if my family hadn't settled?
The court wouldn't be suspicious of your intentions at least.
Didn't you agree to connive when you took the money they offered?
(Current time)
Let's take a quick break.
Seo Woo looks exhausted.
Go and fill in for her.
Let's get back to work.
Pass me the ring curette.
Dr Jin Seo Woo.
I'll assist Prof. Hong.
Take a break and get some fresh air.
It's okay. Don't worry. I'll just do it.
You look exhausted.
Thanks for the offer.
You should go drink some water.
Then I'll need to use the washroom too.
The tumour has weakened his blood vessels.
That means we can't use CUSA, right?
Right, we can't. Pass me the dissector.
(Current time)
Give me the ring curette.
We made it.
Bipolar forceps again.
Good work.
Let's take a quick break and wrap it up.
It's done.
The surgery is done now.
Let's close it up.
I made a mistake.
But I did my best.
So I am not entitled to be punished like you insist.
(Hong Hong Hong)
Hi, Mr Hong.
Were you sleeping? Am I calling too late?
No.
I'm calling to let you know that Kang Soo's surgery went well.
I thought you'd want to know.
I'm so glad.
I knew that it'd go well. It's Kang Soo, you know?
And you did the surgery.
Are you crying?
Is something wrong?
Yes.
Very wrong.
Thanks for coming.
No problem. I can come in, right?
Yes, of course.
Did your meeting with the attorney not go well?
I was wrong.
I should've sued them for medical malpractice...
right after my grandma passed away.
You weren't even 20 and weren't equipped to take such measures then.
Whether it's a civil or criminal case, the statute of limitations...
has expired.
I wanted to reach out to the media, but they aren't even interested.
I waited to gather power.
I thought I had the power to deal with it now,
but there is nothing I can do.
You wouldn't be where you are now if you had focused solely...
on your grandmother's death.
Do you really have to be that blunt?
- Yes.
-  Yes?
I don't want to see you letting this ruin your life.
Do you think I'm doing this to ruin my life?
Hye Jung.
Did you think that someone like President Jin...
would actually sincerely apologise to you...
if you could find pertinent evidence?
He did apologise to me, but it lacked sincerity.
You think that's an apology? It's not.
What he did is like giving a candy to a crying child.
He doesn't even think that you're capable enough to deal with him.
A sincere apology must be accompanied by proper compensation.
Just apologising isn't difficult.
However, people often don't want to make appropriate compensation.
Right, so I'll make him compensate me properly.
How? What will you do to achieve that?
I'll kill him.
In order to catch a monster, I have to become one of them.
I'll kill him for you.
I don't want you to get locked up in prison.
Give me some time.
I don't want to inconvenience people around me in any way,
so give me time to tie up loose ends.
I might have to be locked up in prison for life, you know?
You're so clever.
Do you think that will make me give up?
You're clever too.
You understand what I mean.
Mr Hong.
There was a time gap before Chairman Hong was found unconscious.
Don't you think it's strange? I think it is.
There is definitely something.
Have you looked into it?
I have. There isn't really anything.
I'm suspicious too.
But I won't give up...
my day-to-day life, spending time with you...
and taking care of my patients because of it.
I know that my father would want the same.
How do you know that it's what he wants?
Aside from a few odd exceptions,
all parents want their children to be happy.
I don't get absorbed in vengeance, destruction and punishment.
There's no enough time to do what I love doing.
There's no tomorrow...
for me.
I thought the world would change when the truth gets revealed.
The world...
doesn't change.
(Doctors)
I want to remove my wife's respirator. I want her to rest.
Did something happen between you and my dad?
Ask your dad.
Find out the details of the secret fund,
and then this boring fight will be finally over.
- Mr Hong. What is it?
-  Let's end it here.