Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 18]
Uncle.
Yeah, what is it?
I need to get back inside quickly.
What happened?
It's not under my name,
but another person's name.
Did you sell the house?
Yes, I did.
You're pretty quick for a young kid.
Have you been looking at that
this whole time?
It's my house.
The house I lived in
with my mom and dad.
I'm your guardian.
You should repay your debts now.
I took care of you for a year
after your mom and dad died.
I've taken better care of you
than my own children.
I've done more than enough for you.
Hello.
Ji Hong!
I've been thinking about you lately,
so I asked around at the orphanage.
You became a doctor.
Se Joon, who's in heaven,
would have been happy to hear it too.
What brings you by?
I'm getting dialysis for my kidneys.
I see.
I'll be going now.
I feel better now that I've seen you.
I knew that you'd be blessed like this.
I had dreamed of getting revenge.
I had wanted everyone to die
and I wanted to die too.
Karma exists in this world.
I am not the center of karma.
It's the world that is.
Doctor.
There was some time between when your
father passed out and when he was found.
Isn't is strange to you? I think it is.
There's something there.
Have you looked into it?
I did. It wasn't much.
It was nagging at me too.
But I'm not going to fall into that.
I'm not giving up on eating,
being with you, or being with patients.
I know that's what my dad wants too.
How do you know what he wants?
Except for the odd cases
all parents want
happiness for their kids.
Revenge, destruction, punishment...
I don't get caught up in that stuff.
Time is precious just doing
the things I love doing today.
To me, there is no tomorrow.
Please just leave.
I don't want to talk about
these things with you again.
We're only seeing things
from our own points of view.
I think we should stop that.
Why isn't he getting up?
I don't know.
Is he up?
Not yet.
He must be catching up on
all the sleep he was lacking.
He's awake!
Kang Soo! Can you see us?
That sounds like the chief's voice.
Can you not see us?
Section Chief.
Your tie color looks great.
You punk! You really scared me.
Your yelling is what's scary.
Does your head hurt?
I'm okay.
Good, then.
- Let Professor Hong Ji Hong know.
- Okay.
Section Chief is so cool.
"Good, then."
Kang Soo is sleeping again.
Let's get going.
Even if you pursue this case,
the statute of limitations has passed.
I made a mistake.
However, I did my best.
So, I have no reason
to be punished by you.
But I will apologize.
Mistakes are wrong too.
I don't want to see you falling
into this and ruining your life.
Director Jin.
You finished golfing already?
Yes.
You can all stay here.
I've been contacting
all of the board members.
Half of them are on our side.
Half is not enough.
I've been contacting them too.
I have to get the Senior Health Center
passed at the next board meeting.
What are you going to do about Ji Hong?
Are you going to keep him around?
I suppose you have to keep him.
People have a lot of trust in
Ji Hong because of Doo Shik.
Also, he's done nothing problematic.
I can always come up with
a reason to get rid of him.
Like what?
I'll tell you later.
I just need you to persuade
all of the board members.
We need two-thirds of them
to be on our side.
Who has Professor Kim Tae Ho
been meeting with lately?
He's been in touch with
the people from MH Meditech.
What's Professor Hong Ji Hong up to?
The hospital, dating,
and meeting Professor Kim Tae Ho.
[Yoo Hye Jung]
Hello?
Hello, this is Yoo Hye Jung.
What can I do for you?
I would like to meet with you.
I thought we had finished talking.
I have something new to discuss.
When are you free?
Hey, what's that you're wearing?
Get changed so that we can go.
No, thanks. Go with Doctor Hong.
Just give me some coffee.
I haven't been bothering Ji Hong.
Doctor Yoo is going through a lot.
He's focused on her right now.
What's going on with her?
Doctor Yoo had been looking into
her grandma's medical accident.
I guess she found something.
She brought the anesthesiology records
and asked me about it.
Then, was that the thing you guys
had to talk about in secret before?
You still remember that?
Of course I do.
All of my thoughts are on her.
You can think, but don't act.
What if I say I can't do that?
I can't stop you,
but I can't be on your side.
So, who made the surgical error?
Director Jin Myung Hoon.
It's something very close to our family.
Don't get involved.
Come in.
Professor Jung Yoon Do is here.
Oh, come in. Sit down.
What brings you to my office?
Is your offer for me to become a
board member still good?
You are always welcome.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
I'll see you at the board meeting.
We'll be voting on the
Senior Health Center.
You just need to vote yes.
Do not come again regarding this issue.
It would be even better if you didn't
come back to the hospital at all.
[Jung Yoon Do]
Yes, Doctor.
What are you doing?
No, let me take a guess.
You're exercising, right?
- Yes.
- I have to talk to you.
Let's meet. I'll go where you are.
Where do you want to meet?
There's no need for you to come.
I'm going to the hospital later.
I want to visit Kang Soo too.
Okay, then.
Kang Soo, how are you?
My head hurts a bit but it's manageable.
- You can present.
- Okay.
27-year-old male
in an alert mental state.
Besides the pain in the surgery location
my right lower limbs,
sensation of touch, movement...
everything is okay.
I think the fine motor function of
my right hand is slightly affected.
Let me see.
Lift it up.
Put it down and lift it again.
Okay. Let me see the other side.
Lift up.
Relax and lift up again.
Okay. Let me see your pupils.
Nothing's wrong.
Can I be a surgeon again?
You can.
Thank you.
Your face looked so happy
when he said that.
Not right away.
We need to keep an eye on you
and make sure nothing goes wrong.
You'll need to take some time off.
- Take time off?
- Yes.
Let's get him into a room.
- Okay.
- Use Ceftriaxone for one more day.
Give him 500 milligrams of
painkillers twice a day.
Rest up.
- See you in a bit.
- Okay.
About Kang Soo...
- What about Kang Soo?
- He has nowhere to go.
He didn't get a place when
he became a resident here.
His brother is in the army,
so he didn't need a place.
Good thing I ran into you.
I was about to go find you.
I found out who it was that leaked
the news about your father's stocks.
I had a feeling it was him,
but I was hoping it wasn't.
How could he hurt the hospital
just so he could be better off?
He would do anything to put
himself in a better position.
The reporter told me that he obviously
leaked it to make the public upset.
About Dad and Director Jin Sung Jong...
I think something happened
between them before he died.
I felt like something was off
and I had been looking into it.
Take a look at this.
Director Jin was in the VIP room
for about 20 minutes.
Okay.
If you consider the time my dad
passed out and was alone
I think he passed out
right after Director Jin left.
Director Jin Myung Hoon
had agreed to step down.
He isn't someone who
would agree to do that.
I think your father
had something on them.
What could that be?
They have plenty of weaknesses.
Which one is the most fatal?
What do you think it is, Doctor?
The off-site facilities for the hospital
are operated by Director Jin Myung Hoon.
What about them?
Does all the revenue from those
facilities go back into the hospital?
I'm sure some goes back
into the director's pockets
and that's embezzlement.
That's not something
to be so scared about.
Is that really a fatal weakness?
I'll focus on that for now
and look into it.
Okay. Oh, and Kang Soo...
What about Kang Soo?
Apparently he has nowhere to go.
Goodness.
Brother!
Hey, don't do that now. It's gross.
- Let me hug you.
- Seriously?
What kind of guy are you?
I thought I was going to die earlier.
They only let you visit
twice a day in the ICU.
And only 30 minutes at a time.
Is that right?
Did you eat?
No, I didn't. I wanted to eat with you.
I'm going to steal all your food.
All right. You can eat it all, you pig.
Yes?
Sit down.
Let's hear what you have to say.
I looked into some things after we spoke.
I looked into legal action I could take
regarding my grandmother.
You found something?
There was nothing.
So, I found another way.
I'm... going to kill you.
Even if I can't kill you myself,
I'll make you wither away and die.
I won't ever leave your side.
I'll keep my eye on you
to see what happens to you.
Keep watching.
You'll only get angrier.
I'll be there to get at you
whenever an opportunity arises.
You want to know why
I'm telling you in advance?
I don't usually hide when I take action.
I do it in the open.
It's all over if I fire you.
Fire me.
Then I'll use the law
that you like so much.
I'll sue you for unfair dismissal.
I became kind of famous, thanks to you.
People think we're on good terms.
That's what regular people think.
Wouldn't firing me
cause a problem for you?
I'll be back once my suspension is over
and I'll stay here until the very end.
When you're destroyed...
I'll be here to watch it.
Are you threatening me?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I'm relieved.
I want to scare you even more.
Look forward to it.
[Director Choi Tae Hyun]
Yes, Director.
Why does Doctor Yoo have to punished?
It was Doctor Jin
who didn't take the call.
She's the director's daughter.
That's what I'm saying.
We low-born people should cry.
- You were here, Doctor?
- Yes.
I don't think she heard us.
Yeah, she would say something
if she heard us.
Young Gook!
Yeah.
What is it?
I have something to ask.
Are people talking behind my back?
Why? Did someone say something?
No...
It's because of the discipline thing.
People aren't happy about that.
You are the director's daughter.
By the way, I thought the
director liked Doctor Yoo.
Why did he suddenly change his stance?
Come in.
My daughter is here?
I didn't even call for you.
I was curious about something.
About what?
Why did you punish Hye Jung?
You liked her, didn't you?
I'm just following the hospital rules.
Personal feelings have no place in it.
You said I should take part
in hospital management.
You leave me out of
simple matters like this.
How are you going tell me about
important things in the future?
This is a complex matter.
It isn't simple.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Anyway, I'm just glad to see you
taking an interest in the hospital.
This is a good start.
[Mom]
Yes, Mom.
You're meeting a
potential suitor this Saturday.
Keep your day free.
- Mom!
- Don't talk like that.
You only manage to get anywhere
if I help you out.
Since when?
Who made you who you are today?
It was me.
If I left it up to you
you wouldn't get married
until you were 40.
You're going on a date
with a potential suitor?
She should have done this earlier.
Now, she's finally doing her part.
What are you doing here?
I met Director Jin and I dropped by.
It's my room too.
You met my dad? Why?
- I had to discuss something.
- What was it?
I don't really want to
explain it all to you.
- Kang Soo's in his room, right?
- Yes.
Let's go.
Doctor Yoo!
- You're here, Doctor Yoo.
- Yes.
I missed you.
What's with you? You're happy to see me?
I didn't think I'd live to see the day.
- Did you come to see Kang Soo?
- Yes.
We're going to see him now. Let's go.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
Okay.
He's sleeping.
He is.
Gosh! You scared me.
I'm not sleeping.
Did you hear us?
Yes, I did.
Are you okay?
You rejected me and got surgery
from Professor Hong Ji Hong.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry to you too, Doctor Yoo.
You got suspended because of me.
Are you feeling better?
I'm in as much pain as
someone who's had surgery.
You still speak well.
I have to. I'm unemployed now.
I can't use my strength.
Maybe I'll look into a teaching academy.
I can talk pretty well.
You got much better.
So much that you're surprised?
Doctor Yoo!
Do you have some time?
What did you want to talk about?
I met Director Jin earlier today.
He offered me a board member position
and I took up the offer.
Why?
To help you, Doctor Yoo.
Help me with what?
I found out why you gave up
being a staff surgeon
to come to this hospital instead.
Don't you think I'm behaving recklessly?
It's not realistic.
That's your charm, Doctor Yoo.
You're doing well with it.
Hurry up and eat.
I have to go in and see patients.
Sir, please vote yes to the expansion
of the social welfare program.
You're being so straight-forward
about asking me.
I don't think I can say no.
Thank you.
[Director Jin Myung Hoon]
Yes, Director.
Let's meet.
I'm a bit busy right now.
Never mind, then.
It's regarding Yoo Hye Jung.
You must be very busy.
Being a doctor, boyfriend,
and a board member.
It's all thanks to you.
Regarding Doctor Yoo Hye Jung...
- Yes.
- She came to see me.
She said she would kill me.
With the way you acted,
it's no surprise she would get so angry.
How could she be so ungrateful?
Who is she making a living off of?
Who helped make her famous?
Yet, she wields a knife at me?
Your words are a bit severe.
I'm... going to kill you.
Are you threatening me?
Yes.
I'm scared.
I'm relieved.
I want to scare you even more.
Look forward to it.
I'm going to sue her for threatening me.
That doesn't amount to a threat.
There were no actions.
They were words said in anger.
Professor Hong, this is why
people's pasts are important.
A person's threats become something
more depending on who utters them.
Get straight to the point.
She had quite the life in high school.
She got expelled by hurting
someone in a fire.
She was transferred
many times for fighting.
Gosh, that is cool!
I really like people like that.
What is it that you want from me?
You've been busy lately, so rest.
Focus on the DBS dopamine sensor.
Don't be a doctor. Live as a researcher.
What if I say I can't do that?
Yoo Hye Jung won't be able to
work in this field again.
A neurosurgeon can't exactly
start her own business.
Oh... Doctor.
Were you at Soon Hee's restaurant?
Yes, I was helping her with work.
What brings you by?
It's upsetting to hear you say that.
What?
We're allowed to drop by and
visit each other unannounced.
You're right.
Aren't you angry at me?
Aren't you angry?
I am. I'm not over it yet.
I like your honesty.
I was angry, but not anymore.
Why?
Just because.
"Just because" means that there's
a lot more meaning behind those words.
What is it?
You saw Director Jin today, right?
How did you know that?
Are you going to lecture me again?
No, I'm not. You did well.
Are you still angry?
Yes... my feelings were so hurt.
- Hye Jung.
- Yes?
When did you wash your hair?
- Does it smell?
- Yes.
Oh no! I washed it today.
That's why it must smell so nice.
Hey! What is that?
Why are you making fun of me?
I'm trying to make you laugh.
I haven't seen you laugh in ages.
Something is definitely strange.
I feel like something happened.
It did.
I'll be going to the DBS Research Center.
What's going to change, then?
I won't be seeing patients.
- I don't like that.
- Me neither.
So why are you doing it?
- By any chance--
- Do you know?
Do you know what it's like to hate
something but also really want to do it?
I don't like complicated
things like that.
I'll either do it or not.
I'm going inside now.
You're still angry.
You're still holding a grudge.
If I didn't come to you today...
I felt like you'd never
look at me again.
I'm sorry.
For what?
Because I'm not good to you.
That's not true. You're very good to me.
How am I?
Remember what my dad said?
You're doing good just by sitting by me.
You're sitting right here.
I wish I could see
the board director now.
Me too.
But isn't it weird to call him
the board director?
- Father?
- Yes.
Yes, Father.
It would've been nice to call him that
when he was alive.
You were good at everything,
but not that.
Hey, you still refer to
my grandma as "Granny."
Look, you just said sorry,
but you never want to lose.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
For what?
Because you're not happy.
I say that I love you,
but I can't make you happy.
That's not true.
I've just never been happy before.
I look for reasons to be unhappy
because I feel anxious when I'm happy.
Can we overcome that somehow?
I don't know.
Maybe if we just keep going,
we will find out the answer.
Just don't forget that I'm by your side.
How can I forget that?
You're my rock.
Doctor, she has a fever.
Her whole body is hot.
- Chart, please.
- Yes.
- It's 39 degrees Celsius.
- That's very high.
It's not good for the fetus.
Get cold saline and cooling pads.
Okay.
Don't worry too much.
We can lower her body temperature.
Can I do the cooling pads for her?
Yes.
[Kang Kyung Joon]
Yes, what is it?
Lee Hae Young's guardian
wants to speak to you.
- Put him on.
- Okay.
Hello.
Hello, this is Yoo Hye Jung.
I'm sorry I could not be there
due to personal matters.
I couldn't stay and take responsibility.
I want to take my wife off life support.
Kim Woo Jin.
I...
I said I loved my wife more than anyone.
Yet, I'm putting her
through so much pain.
She's so swollen and hurt.
I can't even recognize her anymore.
I think I'm being too selfish.
If you were being selfish,
you wouldn't have come this far.
I want to give up.
I want to let everything go.
I want to let her rest.
If you give up now...
everything she did to protect
that child will be all for nothing.
Wouldn't she resent me?
Your wife is still holding on.
It's for the both of you.
Because she loves you and the baby.
You need to hold on too.
If you're going to hang on,
then so will I.
I love you.
Brother.
What is it?
It's to help with your hospital fees.
Are you crazy, kid?
Why not? I never even went to
the store and I saved it all.
Is it too little?
You use it.
I gave you allowance and this is
what you've been doing?
Why are you being like this?
I want to help too.
Young Soo.
If you want to do something,
can't you do something more productive?
Take this and go to the store.
Eat whatever you want.
Don't act like you have nothing.
Your brother is a doctor.
I only have to pay half of the fees.
I make 40 million won a year.
I do pretty well.
I know.
But don't you need a place?
You can't even work for a while.
Stop worrying about useless things
and just eat what you want!
Okay, okay!
I'm glad I can use it, then.
Hey.
What?
Don't be sick.
I was really scared.
Hey... why would you be scared?
Does your brother ever lose?
Of course not.
Salute!
Salute.
- I'll be going, then.
- I'll walk you out.
Section Chief.
Kang Soo, I was about to leave
because you weren't there.
I was just saying bye to my brother.
What do you plan to do
after you get discharged?
I haven't really thought about it.
- Do you want to work in our department?
- What?
- As what?
- Department secretary.
Our current one is quitting
for personal reasons.
You won't be able to start working
as a doctor right away.
You can get better for about six months
or a year while doing this job.
Then start working as a doctor again.
Thank you.
No need for thanks.
Do a good job.
Section Chief.
Take good care of yourself.
- Thank you.
- All right.
Hey, Ji Hong.
I heard. What happened?
I'm sorry, Doctor.
Tell me the reason why.
Does it make any sense that you would be
a researcher and not a surgeon?
Just think of it as taking a short break.
Do you think you can be away
from patients even for a bit?
It's only a short break, Doctor.
Have you looked into
Director Jin's embezzlement?
Director Jin did misappropriate funds.
There is lots of evidence to be found.
His property and assets should be public.
We can look into those records in detail.
I think we can figure out
what he's been doing
with the money from those businesses.
If it's money from over 10 years,
that's a lot of money in the slush fund.
I can see why Board Director Jin
was afraid of it getting out.
That is, if this is what
your father had on him.
I think the probability of this is high.
We need to investigate.
Okay.
Are you not planning on
attending the board meeting?
No, I should go.
I should go see the
Senior Health Center voted down.
All right, then. Let's go.
You're sure we have the votes?
I am the board director.
Yes, hello.
Hello.
Let's go in.
Oh, Yoon Do.
Hello.
- I'm glad you're here. Let's go.
- Yes.
I will be leading this meeting
in place of the director.
We have two matters to vote on today.
First, it is the construction of the
Senior Health Center.
Second is the expansion of the
foundation's social welfare program.
We presented these issues at the
last meeting, so we'll skip that today.
You can go over the report
in front of you.
Let's go straight to the voting.
All right. We will vote.
[Three weeks later]
She passed out on her way back
from morning prayer at church.
Okay, I'll take a look.
Are you okay?
Was she unconscious from the start?
Yes.
- Did you take a CT?
- Yes, she has a brain hemorrhage.
What about a guardian?
I called and he is coming now.
Contact Anesthesiology and book an OR.
Which professor should I call?
Professor Hong isn't doing surgeries.
Call Professor Jung Yoon Do.
Yes, okay.
How is the construction of the
Senior Health Center going?
The management team is coming up
with a budget now.
Oh! Professor Hong.
- Hello.
- Is your research going well?
It's going all right. Bye, now.
You have enough funds to build it, right?
I'm going to get quotes from
construction companies.
We'll get it done as soon as possible.
Okay.
They're very jubilant.
Because they won.
I have evidence.
These are funds that
those facilities earned
that did not come into the hospital.
These businesses say they worked
with these off-site facilities.
But these facilities never transferred
their payment to the hospital.
How much?
500 million won in the last year.
500 million won...
That's a small amount for charging
Board Director Jin with embezzlement.
It's small enough
to get out of it easily.
- How much is it?
- 10 billion won.
That's a lot.
Is Ji Hong's DBS sensor
that big of a deal?
If he can make it, it will be.
So, why aren't you
having him do surgeries?
Just strip him of his board member title.
Don't you know surgeons, Dad?
They want to be out in the field.
They don't like office work.
Watch him keep accepting
and treating patients.
A few years from now,
we won't even survive.
About the budget for the
Senior Health Center...
can't we take some money from the
investment funds that Ji Hong brought in?
I think they're taking money out
from the off-site facility profits.
When did those facilities
start making notable profits?
It's been a long time.
We've held funerals here
at the hospital for the past 20 years.
I just can't stop thinking that my dad
had a record of the slush fund.
Let's organize this.
Director Jin attacked your father first.
With the stocks and the investigation
by the National Tax Administration.
Then your father fought back
by refusing to retire.
Then Director Jin quit on his own.
Your father's attack worked.
Yes, I don't think anything would
make him quit on his own, except this.
So, what were they arguing about
for 20 minutes?
Did he get his
slush fund file taken away?
He was going to use that
against Director Jin.
Did Board Director Jin find it
and use it against your father?
That theory makes the most sense.
But, Ji Hong...
We know your father very well.
We do.
- There's another copy.
There's definitely another copy.
There's no way he would
only make one. Would you?
I would make multiple copies
and leave them hidden.
Look for it.
- It's around you somewhere.
- Okay.
You look for it too, Doctor.
If we can find that slush fund file,
this long fight can end.
I told you to come to my office.
Why did you want to meet here?
You were with the board director.
I only wanted to meet you.
Why? Did you want to apologize?
I wanted you to support me and
you voted for Professor Hong?
It's my belief that I should vote for
what I truly believe in.
I am sorry if that bothered you.
It's okay. He still only got
one-third of the votes.
Do you enjoy being on the losing side?
Your father isn't like that.
I like winning too.
So... I looked into it a bit.
What is this?
The records of our
hospital's off-site facilities.
They're a little different.
What?
I don't think this will be anything big.
But it will still be a threat to you.
Hey, Jung Yoon Do!
Leave Doctor Yoo Hye Jung alone.
Then I will also back off.
Hong Sang Tae has been
moved into a room, right?
Yes, he was moved up.
He'll need to be checked often,
and he needs to be in rehab.
- Okay.
- Doctor! Did you buy ours too?
Of course I bought it.
You should've bought snacks
while you were out.
Of course I bought snacks too.
Wow! You are great at this.
You are a natural
at this secretary thing.
Have some, Doctor.
You're lucky to be so talented.
- Doctor!
- You're back.
Shouldn't she eat some tofu?
Doctor!
Did I go to jail or something?
I'm sorry.
How is that patient with
the epidural hemorrhage?
Oh, yes. That patient is okay.
That's a relief.
Your hair grew a lot.
I can get a perm.
You look like a little chestnut.
No, don't get a perm. I hate that.
You look cute.
Have you been doing well?
Yes.
Yes, Dad.
I'm getting lunch with your grandpa.
Let's go together.
I can't. I have surgery to prepare for.
By the way...
did something happen between
you and my father?
Why do you ask?
It's just strange.
My dad liked you a lot.
His attitude changed and the
punishment was very harsh.
You should ask your dad about it.
I asked him and he's avoiding it.
What?
Will it hurt your dad if I hurt you?
Do you want to hurt my dad?
Sorry. It has nothing to do with you.
If you hurt me, it will hurt my parents.
Tell me what happened
between the two of you.
When I look at you...
I'm always reminded of the time
we hung out after our midterms.
I never imagined I'd become
a doctor back then.
This flower is so pretty.
- So pretty.
- Be careful.
Did you do well on the test?
I don't know because I've
never done well on a test before.
I've given up.
Given up on math.
Seriously!
Seo Woo, how can you be so good at math?
I work hard at it.
You don't.
You have to put in the effort
to get the results.
You sound just like my dad.
I really want to graduate
high school quickly.
Then I want to get married.
I'm only going to have one child.
I'm never going to have a kid
when I'm really old.
But out of the three of us,
I think Seo Woo will get married first.
No way! I'm going to become
a doctor like my dad.
Even if I do get married,
I have to graduate medical school.
That's going to be six years.
What are you going to do, Hye Jung?
I'm going to run the rice soup
restaurant with my grandma.
One location of Granny's Rice Soup,
and then a second location.
I'm going to earn lots of money and
let my grandma live in comfort.
I want the third location.
Me too, me too! I'll put in my money too.
I'll think about it.
I'll do the fourth and fifth location.
Let's just do it together, then.
I'll count all the money.
What do you think?
Young Gook, do people not like my dad?
Well, not everyone likes him.
But, lots of people like him too.
I don't want to know about that.
I'm going to stop everything here.
Doctor.
Aren't you going to eat?
- I should.
- Let's eat together.
- Ah...
- Ah.
Think about what I did for you.
I went into the board meeting.
Can't friends even eat together?
We're friends now, right?
Let's go.
How is your revenge going?
There's no progress.
The only thing I can do is
keep working at the hospital.
That's good. Let's go eat.
Where should we go?
Yoon Do.
Where are you off to?
We're going to eat.
- How about you?
- So are we.
How is it that you're together?
She's a colleague of mine.
We'll get going now.
The fellow who was suspended is back now.
I like her because she's tough.
I just hate that Yoon Do.
I ought to get rid of him too.
If it weren't for his dad,
he'd be gone already.
You must be really stressed.
Why are you so upset with everyone?
Why are you so worried?
Who said that I am?
You're acting as if
someone is chasing you.
When have I?
You seem that way.
There's no need for it.
All right? The world belongs to you.
Let's go. Hurry up.
It's not here.
It wouldn't be somewhere so easy to find.
I'm... going to kill you.
I'll be back once my suspension is over
and I'll stay here until the very end.
When you're destroyed...
I'll be here to watch it.
Come on in.
Sit down.
[Soon Hee]
You're calling me? What's up?
- I have something to ask.
- What?
If you ever considered me a friend,
don't lie to me.
You really came into work.
I didn't know if you would.
I keep my word.
How can one always keep their word?
People speak carelessly all the time.
You and I have a
different sense of values.
Do you want to make a living working
under someone with different values?
I was briefly in jail once.
I'm sure you already knew this
since you looked into me.
My grandma brought rice
and came to see me.
I told her I had no right to eat,
so I wouldn't eat.
She said no one needs a right to eat.
Anyone who breathes should eat.
I'm making a living to eat
with my own hard work.
I don't believe anyone is
making that living for me.
It is my values that are important
since I'm working to live and eat.
Your values mean nothing to me.
You're not normal, are you?
That's how you must
have made it this far.
But do you think that makes you great?
Do you think I'm letting you get away
with it because you're so great?
Keep your boundaries.
How can we have
a conversation if you don't?
Do you know why Professor Hong
is at the DBS Research Center?
It's because of you.
Your past and your present...
they are all roadblocks
for Professor Hong.
Do you know who took responsibility for
your reckless behavior towards me?
It was Professor Hong Ji Hong.
Leave.
Stop creating problems for others.
That's what you would like, isn't it?
You'd like it if I left.
That's why I won't leave.
I told you, I always keep my word.
Dad!
[2015 Gookil Hospital
Subsidiaries Rentals]
- Who is it?
- It's me, Hye Jung.
Come in.
This worked out great.
I really wanted to see you.
You broke the rules.
What?
This is really against
the rules if you do this.
What? What is it?
Why can't I ever help you?
Why do I always become a burden to you?
What did Director Jin do that
you went to the research center?
Why didn't you tell me?
How many questions is that?
Do I have to answer them all now?
I'm embarrassed and I feel like a loser.
I want to be confident.
This is what you taught me to do
in times like these, right?
Open up the arms and
put them around the waist.
Justice is flowing like a river
in a place that we cannot see.
It is something you can't see.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor Crush]
Hye Jung went to your hospital
because of your dad.
We have a warrant for your arrest.
Dad!
Do you like Hye Jung that much?
Can't you like me more?
It's because of love?
Should I congratulate you?
It's frozen.
Can you do something
bad to me just once?
Please take care
of my Myung Hoon.