You brought these dishes for me. Why are you eating them?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Just be a good doctor. That's who you are.
The most we can do for our loved ones is sacrificing ourselves.
However, such sacrifice...
does not beautify humanity.
(EPISODE 19)
Tell me now.
What did President Jin say that I said?
What did he tell you? I mean, you go crazy for surgeries...
I don't like how that sounds.
- Is there a different expression?
- That's the most accurate one.
Why did you give up what you love so much?
I won't get my feelings hurt. Just tell me the truth.
I'm taking a step back in order to take two steps forward.
I did it to make President Jin put his guard down.
So how exactly will you take two steps forward?
I'm looking for President Jin's weaknesses.
I'll attack him as soon as I find them, so don't worry too much.
All I can do is going to work.
"Thank goodness. I can at least do this."
Think positively like this.
You know what?
You always lecture me at important moments like this.
I'm a former teacher who is a doctor and a professor now.
I can't hide that part of me.
You have to tell me when you find his weakness.
You should go home now. I cannot tell you.
It's better for you not to find out about it.
That is for me to decide.
- Just tell me.
- I don't know anything.
Do you seriously want to make me look like an idiot?
I don't know how you felt about me, but I thought of you...
as my best friend until Hye Jung showed up.
I do know that you were very understanding of me.
Hye Jung joined your hospital...
because of your dad.
- And why is that?
- Have you met her grandmother?
I have. I don't remember her well, though.
She passed away while getting surgery for her cancer.
Your dad was the operating surgeon, and it was medical malpractice.
What?
Does that mean...
she passed away because my dad made a mistake during the surgery?
Is that what Hye Jung thinks?
She told me recently that she found pertinent evidence.
- That's nonsense.
- Do you think that she would've...
kept it to herself for 13 years if it were nonsense?
It's not like Hye Jung is dumb.
You know it too.
Her dream was running Grandma's Diner.
She wanted to live happily with her grandma for a long time.
I'm sure she's mistaken. There's no way my dad would do such a thing.
Seo Woo.
Good to see you, Father.
Likewise. Why were you guys waiting for me at the door?
I'm just here for a cup of tea.
We should greet you at the door, of course.
- What about Mother?
- She's sleeping.
- It's citron tea.
- Thanks.
- Where is Seo Woo?
- She's not home yet.
I need to talk to Father about something.
All right, fine.
What do you need to talk to me about?
Darn it.
Are you feeling unwell?
No, it's just from stress.
I heard you skipped the annual medical checkup last year.
- Get it done.
- I will.
What's stressing you out? You can tell me.
I want to invest more...
in Sangil Pharmaceuticals' shares, but I don't have money.
You've already invested a lot. Why do you want to do more?
Don't do it if you can't afford it.
I should become the main shareholder.
I'd like to own a stable company aside from the hospital.
- What about the subsidiary?
- I should give that to Seo Woo.
I heard that a new drug the company is developing will be a huge hit.
Then their share price will certainly go up.
The return will be a few times the investment.
Then I'll buy the shares for you.
What will we do with the slush fund anyway? Let's use it.
I honestly cannot live without you.
Let's go on a cruise when we start building the geriatrics centre.
Don't worry. Your stepmother goes on trips all the time anyway.
I miss your mother.
She was so good to me.
Why are you talking about Mum all of a sudden? I miss her too.
I must pave the road for you to be able to make her proud.
Don't worry about a thing.
- Oh, Doctor. Why are you...
- What brings you here, Ma'am?
I'm her dad.
My goodness. I sincerely apologise.
My granddaughter made a big mistake.
I'm so sorry.
Did you get hurt badly? I'm really sorry.
I thought you left for the day.
Why did you come back?
Yeong Gook.
Yes.
Do something you shouldn't to me.
It'll be okay.
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
How is the patient doing?
Her temperature is normal at 36 degrees.
That's a relief.
Dr Kim asked you to be at all the conferences.
- After we check on the patient.
- Okay.
You're impressive, truly.
Patient Lee Hee Young is a 29-year-old female patient.
She was brought to the ER after a traffic accident.
She was in a semi-coma when she was brought in.
According to the brain CT scan, she had an intracranial haemorrhage...
which was around 80cc in the left parietal lobe.
It was due to an arteriovenous rupture.
We concluded there was almost no possibility for her to recover,
but did an emergency surgery because she was 20 weeks pregnant.
How is the baby?
She's growing without any problems so far.
Keep a close eye on the patient.
If anything seems wrong, we'll have to bring the baby out right away.
- Keep Gynaecology in the loop.
- Got it.
That's enough for today.
I have something to tell all of you.
There were several issues within and outside of Neurosurgery...
for the past few months.
A colleague was sick,
disciplinary action was taken on another...
and people were critical of us...
because of a patient that became a social issue.
We might have to endure this for a longer amount of time.
However, we only have one another...
to bear through this together.
Neurosurgeons deal with the brain.
The brain controls the human body.
That means...
The Department of Neurosurgery controls everything.
(TEST RESULT SUMMARY)
I heard about it from Dr Jung Yoon Do.
You're Dr Yoo's father?
Yes.
What are your symptoms?
I'm always tired...
and my upper stomach hurts. I went to a small clinic,
but they told me to go here after doing a blood test.
Your liver index is a bit high.
Let me check your eyes. Could you open them wide?
Okay.
Do you drink a lot?
Yes, I drank a bit recently.
I don't think it was a bit.
There seems to be an inflammation in your liver.
I'll do an ultrasonic wave test on your liver.
Okay.
How do you know Dr Jung?
He's a regular at my diner.
He also did my wife's surgery.
Dr Jung must be going the extra mile because you're Dr Yoo's father.
I'm thankful.
The prosecution just needs the slush fund transactions, right?
This will end faster than I thought.
Dr Kim.
I'm sorry, but I can't use it now.
Why not?
President Jin is holding Dr Yoo as collateral.
Dr Yoo?
I don't believe it. You turned out to be a total romantic.
Dr Kim.
When I heard that you're going to the research centre,
I knew there must be some big reason.
But who knew it would be for love? Should I congratulate you?
Stop making fun of me.
I like seeing you dating someone and I hope it works out.
But Ji Hong, we don't have much time.
Once the geriatrics centre takes its initial steps,
the hospital would face too much loss.
Whoever takes President Jin's place...
will have to start with a burden of a great deficit on his shoulders.
That's why I'm thinking about it.
Wait.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Did you come to work here...
because of my dad?
Yes, I did.
Do you think your grandma died from my dad's medical malpractice?
It's a fact, not an opinion. I confirmed it.
How could you confirm something that happened 13 years ago?
There can't be any records left.
There were records.
Someone still had them.
Why would anyone keep it if it's not even his own?
There was a good enough reason and I accepted it.
Did you read out the records accurately? Who helped you with it?
Dr Jung Pa Ran.
Things we can't control happen in the operation room.
You know that.
They made a settlement.
My dad and the hospital.
I came to ask you something.
- What is it?
- Did Dr Yoo come see you...
to ask for help in reading out an anaesthesiology report?
Yes, I did and I told her the surgeon made a mistake.
Does Prof. Hong Ji Hong know about this as well?
He probably does.
He was the one who introduced me to Dr Yoo.
Then does Yoon Do know about it too?
Yes, he does. He likes Dr Yoo.
I've never seen anyone have such a creative crush.
Thank you for telling me.
Did you become a director...
because of Hye Jung?
- Yes.
- To help her?
Not just her, but also Prof. Hong.
You never cease to surprise me.
You weren't like this before.
You never interfere in other people's affairs.
You don't like fights or politics.
There was no other way for me to get closer to Dr Yoo.
Is that all that matters?
What about me?
You've known me for a long time.
We're close friends.
You've relied on me during hardships.
How could you do this to me?
- I'm sorry.
- Then act like you are.
What do you want me to do?
Don't make this hard for my dad.
You're siding with Hye Jung to bring my dad down.
Don't do it.
Am I asking for too much?
My dad isn't a bad person.
Hye Jung is mistaken. You know that, don't you?
Doctors are supposed to save people's lives.
There's nothing we can do when we make a mistake.
None of us can.
Dr Yoo is so pretty.
Dr Jung looks pretty good too.
(THANK YOU FOR WAITING.)
- Kang Soo.
- Yes?
The printer ran out of ink.
Could you help me with it? I'm flowing with ideas right now.
You're writing non-fiction.
You're plagiarising Dr Yoo's life.
Come on, Joong Dae.
Could you live a life I'd want to plagiarise?
- How dare you...
- What are you doing?
Joong Dae, did you do a CT scan for Patient Lee Chung Hyun?
- Yes, I did.
- So you did.
You're doing a good job without any of my nagging.
You're doing better without me.
I'm about to drop to the floor, covering for you.
Don't drop to the floor. No one will be able to catch you.
That's just your luck.
Who knew that would happen to Kang Soo?
Joong Dae, I did the CT scan for Patient Lee Chung Hyun.
It's hard to do everything by myself.
It was already too much work when we had Kang Soo.
- Are you whining at me?
- No.
It's okay. I can give him a hand. You can't hire someone new now.
There's too much work for Joong Dae to take care of alone.
Guys, shall I help you?
- It worked!
Go pick up some paper.
Hey, work on the night duty schedule. I had to take care of it.
I had no idea that knuckling you on the head a few times...
would make me become your slave.
Why do I have to be your slave?
I told you. The boomerang effect.
It taught me that such effect actually exists.
Joong Dae, Ahn Joong Dae. You little...
How dare you mock me? I shall teach you a lesson!
If Joong Dae leaves, you and I need to absorb all of his tasks.
That's right.
- I was going to say I like him.
- Were you?
People may not know this, but I like you.
You need some paper, and you want the schedule. Okay.
- I secretly like you.
- Joong Dae, let's go.
- Podgy Number 1!
- Podgy Number 2!
Cross!
- I like you.
- All right.
I don't like you, though. He's a bit delusional.
(GENERAL SURGERY, JEONG PA RAN)
- Yes, Doctor.
- I have your father's result.
- Pardon me?
- He came to see me.
I'm calling to give you a heads up because I thought you'd be worried.
I guess you didn't know.
The ultrasound shows that you have a fatty liver.
That also caused hepatitis.
Is it serious?
No. You can just visit me for appointments and take medication.
I see.
Your next appointment has been made. Please arrive on time.
You can make your payment on the ground floor.
Will I get my medication today as well?
You can pick it up when you make your payment.
Okay.
- Thank you.
Why did you summon me?
I can call you anytime, right?
Yes, that's right.
I'd like to consult you on something.
What is it?
My father was here.
- To see you?
- No, as a patient.
I was so worried, thinking that it might be something serious.
It'll be hard to turn away from him if he's ill.
Right. Family relationships are usually the most difficult ones.
You get hurt the most by them yet feel the most attached to them.
- I don't want to be close to him.
- No one is asking you to do so.
You're putting that pressure on yourself.
- You won't tell me to do so?
- I won't.
I can't tell you to do something that I don't do myself.
That makes me feel better.
- How can you be so cool?
- Why are you sweet suddenly?
I'm so happy that you're my man.
- Am I your man?
- Yes. You're mine.
It's been a while.
It looks like those beagles have stopped coming over to your place.
Yes. See you around.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
- Gosh, you startled me.
- Did I surprise you?
It looked like you were out on a date. Why are you here?
Hey, do you want to have dinner with me later?
No. I don't like how you're looking at me.
- It looks like you pity me.
- That's not what it is.
Come over to my place later. I'll have food ready.
- No, thanks.
- Bring a bottle of wine.
I said no.
Why are you ignoring my opinion altogether...
Darn it.
- Where did he go?
- He should be back soon.
He just stepped out because Chairman Jin came by.
All right.
I am going to...
kill you.
I'll torture you to death even if I can't actually kill you.
Did you say Seo Woo is here to see me?
Hey, you're here.
What's up?
- Hye Jung told me.
- I don't want to hear that name.
It was just an accident. It's not like I intended it.
She should know better as a doctor, but she's stressing me out.
What did she do to you?
I don't want to talk about it. My head hurts because of it.
Are you feeling sick?
I have a lot of stress because there's too much on my plate.
- You're leaving already?
- I want to look into something.
I kept researching after I spoke to you the last time.
I was looking for a way to make you...
take responsibility legally for what happened to my grandmother.
- Did you find any?
- There was none.
So I found another way.
I am going to...
kill you.
(OPERATING ROOM)
He's my dad, so I obviously have to think from his perspective.
Do it, then.
I heard how you threatened him.
You said you'd harass him and torture him to death.
Did he tell you?
No. I found a recording.
Recording?
A recording of the conversation you two had.
I guess he recorded it.
It's so cruel. How can you say that when you're a doctor yourself?
Has every single one of your surgeries been successful?
I'm sure some of the patients you operated on died too.
Any doctor can make a mistake during a surgery.
But do you know what he said to me after the surgery going wrong?
"I did my best, so I'm not scared of anything."
Then he said that he'll talk to my parents.
You were underage, so he had to talk to your parents.
He should've expressed condolences for her death first.
Had he apologised properly...
and showed me that he respects my grandma's life,
I wouldn't have come this far.
Why didn't you tell me any of this?
I wouldn't have misunderstood you if you had shared it with me.
I wanted to be considerate of you.
Why though?
Your kindness helped me do well on the math test,
and it inspired me to study hard.
You gave me so much through that experience.
That's why I kept it from you.
You're acting strange. I think something happened to you.
Something happened.
I became the head of the DBS research centre.
- Will that change anything?
- Do you know this feeling?
You hate it, but you want it badly.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
I made steaks. I grilled the meat how I like it, though.
I'll just eat whatever you give me. Here's a bottle of wine.
It's an expensive vintage wine.
Cheers.
It's so awkward to be wining and dining with a guy like this.
I haven't had a chance to thank you...
for what you did after my father's death...
and the vote you gave us at the board meeting.
Do you like me that much?
You know I didn't do it for you.
Do you like Hye Jung that much?
Yes.
Could you like me more?
- Are you okay?
- I almost threw up.
Why are you acting like this?
It's because I like you.
This is an interesting way to make me give up.
Do you think you'd give up if I act like this?
Yes, it's working.
It seems like I stand no chance.
Can't you try working things out with Seo Woo?
She's just a friend to me.
I feel like I should be taking care of her.
That's why I've decided to stop putting my nose in your affairs.
When did you put your nose in it?
I could help you...
find President Jin's weakness.
It's okay. I've already found it.
- You did?
- Yes.
Why haven't you used it against him?
Cheers.
You can tell me whatever is on your mind.
Do you know Prof. Hong went to the research centre because of me?
Yes, I do.
When are you going to marry him?
Please save that old man from his misery.
Dr Kim.
I'm not joking.
I want to know what else he's holding back because of me.
President Jin...
called me a stumbling block in Prof. Hong's life.
I respect and trust you.
You won't...
make me become a stumbling block to Prof. Hong, will you?
You've put me in a hard spot.
What your grandma wants...
is for you to be happy.
She wouldn't want you to give up your present because of her.
My girl...
(KANG MAL SOON)
How are you, Grandma?
I'm not doing very well.
As you know, I only go after one thing at a time.
I was obsessed with your death until now.
But I'm not happy.
I'm not becoming happier.
(KANG MAL SOON)
You know Mr Hong, right?
He was the goofy tenant at our house.
Whenever I'm with him,
I find myself smiling.
I feel happy.
(KANG MAL SOON)
You want me to be happy, right?
Is it okay...
if I only think about you only from time to time?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Have a seat.
I cooked, so we could eat before going to work together.
Did you come from home?
No, I went to see my grandma.
I should go see her too. Let's go together next time.
That's two fouls. One more, and you're out.
When did I commit a foul?
I met Dr Kim.
You look nervous.
Yes, I'm scared I'll get in trouble.
You seem to scold me often.
Do whatever you want with that USB.
I know President Jin recorded our conversation.
I also know you're hesitating because of it.
I used to think it was fake...
if I made a decision but didn't take action.
Now, I think differently.
How could I do everything?
Make President Jin sorry for me.
You have the strength that I don't.
If you lose this opportunity because of me,
I won't ever be able to live with myself.
He said he'd sue you for threatening him.
Your past will be brought to the surface,
and I don't know what kind of harm it might do you.
I'll deal with it when I have to.
That's how I lived my life so far.
I'll have to ask you to have that much trust in me.
All right.
This looks good.
The construction for the geriatrics centre...
which has been our long-term wish is finally starting.
If you take a look at the data in front of you,
you'll see that we've decided to work with Moonjung Construction.
We are planning to spend 120 million dollars in the construction.
It's finally happening.
It's like the weight has been lifted off of my shoulders.
Did you see how upset Dr Kim was?
I wish Prof. Hong was there.
I didn't see Yoon Do today.
He isn't interested in management but came for fun last time.
What is this?
Who are you?
We're from the Seoul Prosecutor's office.
What for?
Chairman Jin Sung Jong?
That's me.
Chairman Jin Sung Jong.
You are under arrest...
for embezzlement and malpractice.
This is ridiculous.
You have the right to appoint an attorney and to remain silent.
The right to remain silent could work against you in court.
Who is your boss?
Would you like to come with us?
I feel like you'd be related to the crimes.
No, he has nothing to do with it.
Let's go.
Father! Father!
Father!
(GUKIL MEDICAL CENTER)
Chairman Jin of Gukil Medical Center established an agency...
and embezzled 3 million dollars,
using it for personal stocks...
while taking care of the facilities since 2006.
Chairman Jin also took 2 million as a rebate...
in exchange for the operating rights of subsidiary facilities.
Would you like to get some coffee?
Let's go.
- Let's go.
- Chairman Jin has been arrested...
for embezzlement and malpractice. Those involved are being prosecuted.
The prosecution found out about other crimes,
regarding the supply contracts of medical goods.
They are planning to expand the investigation.
This is Ha Gang Yoon, SBC.
Hi.
The hospital seems to be in disorder.
President Jin won't sit still.
I'm ready.
The past isn't as strong as the present.
We can do this.
I'm a bit scared.
You're cute.
I didn't expect to hear that.
People say that I'm gentle and charismatic.
I would've been scared if this concerned you.
But I'm okay because it's about me.
You're kind of cute.
You never lose, do you?
What do you mean? I always let you win.
You let me win?
That's so not true. I won fairly.
You're seriously obsessed with winning.
I'm not really obsessed. Don't jump to your own conclusions.
Why?
I want to kiss you.
Are you doing all right?
- Are you feeling unwell at all?
- No.
Has the prosecution interrogated you yet?
It'll happen soon.
- I did everything.
- No!
I might get released on bail due to my old age.
One getting locked up is better than both of us ending up in jail,
and I should be the one between the two of us.
Father, please!
I won't be able to sleep a wink with you locked up in prison.
What about me, then? I can't sleep with you here, either!
I must teach that jerk, Hong Ji Hong, a serious lesson.
He's the one who tipped off the prosecution!
Where did it go?
The attorney is here.
Why in the world did they arrest him?
It looks like they were concerned about him destroying evidence.
They already put in a request for a trial.
Chairman Jin isn't a victim. He's the defendant of the case.
- Can we apply for release on bail?
- We should do it.
It'll cost you a lot, though.
Who cares about how much it'll cost? Get him out as soon as possible!
Whatever it is, just say it. You probably want to console me.
It's not like anything I say will make you feel better.
You've never gone through anything like this, right?
I have. Twice.
Thanks.
(DAD)
Hey.
What is that girl, Hye Jung, up to now?
Did you want to see me to ask me that?
Hong Ji Hong literally punched us on our faces. I won't let it slide.
When he sees that girl getting all stressed out because of the media,
he will learn his lesson.
How exactly will you make the media bother her?
I hid a recording, but it disappeared.
I should be able to find it, though.
I destroyed it.
What?
I took your side when I heard about her grandmother's death...
because you're my dad.
I wanted to avoid it altogether because I felt like it was my fault.
I didn't do anything wrong. She's overreacting.
Her family settled, and it happened 13 years ago.
Do you think she's normal for coming here because of it?
She's not normal.
If that had happened to you, I would have killed the doctor right away.
Why did you do that? You should've just apologised for your mistake.
Why did you have to hurt her feelings?
Do you know how many people will try to make money off of you...
when you apologise for things like that?
How have you been living your life?
Have you only seen those kinds of people? What about nice people?
Do you think weird people like that make up the entire population?
Is that how you decide to treat people?
I'm embarrassed of you. You humiliate me.
I'm embarrassed of myself too. I'm mortified.
Don't listen to what people are saying. This mess will end soon.
Your grandfather will be released on bail too.
Do you know what Hye Jung's dream used to be?
Making sure her grandmother could live comfortably.
She wanted to run her grandmother's diner after graduating.
Her only dream was to continue living with her grandmother.
Why can't you empathise with people?
"I did my best, but I'm so sorry that the result is this."
"I'm truly sorry for your loss."
If you had said that, she wouldn't have come this far.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Patient Song Jin Young is in the ICU now, right?
Do a follow-up CT scan and let me know when she wakes up.
Okay.
Hi!
What brings you here, Professor? Good to see you.
Am I not allowed to come here or what?
You're allowed, of course. You must be here to see Dr Yoo.
I am? Who said that?
- Gosh, we know everything now.
- What are you talking about?
The two of you...
Professor, there's something I have to tell you.
Really? Let's talk, then.
Do they actually think that we don't know?
No way. If that's the case, they're way too slow.
People might find out soon.
They already know. Can't you tell from the looks they give us?
Well, Dr Kim knows, which means everyone must know by now.
Don't you think we should pretend not to know about it, though?
- Why?
- To entertain people.
Sure, let's do that.
You seem so unworried. Are you going to stay at the research centre?
- That's up to President Jin.
- Tell him you want to come back.
Aren't you hungry? I'm quite hungry.
I want to eat cold noodles before I go home. Shall we get it now?
Don't do these things.
- What did I do?
- Changing the topic.
You can't make your moves because of the recording, right?
I guess you won't give up until you go all the way to the end.
That's right.
Yes, I can't because of the recording.
However, we'll get a new president when Chairman Jin gets dismissed.
I'll lay low because he's probably furious at me right now.
You're a coward.
Just a second.
(JIN SEO WOO)
Yes.
You're on night duty today, right?
I have something to tell you. Meet me briefly.
I'm sorry, but I can't. I'm with someone now.
It's something important.
Here.
Did your dad tell you to give this to me?
No. I stole it.
I've met your grandmother.
She came to visit me with juice when I was hospitalised.
It was 100 percent fruit juice.
I've never thought of you as my competition.
I was kind to you...
because you weren't my competition.
The reason doesn't change the fact that you were kind to me.
I didn't want to admit that you were better than me.
I think that's where my tragedy began.
I provoked you.
I didn't know...
because it was before I entered the system called competition.
I'm sorry.
I had my chances.
Especially when you came to see me to get Soon Hee out.
I justified my decision and thought that time would take care of it all,
but our situation has worsened.
I think this is my chance now.
Seo Woo.
I'm sorry.
I want to apologise to you on behalf of my dad.
- Did the talk go well?
- Yes.
I'm so glad that I decided not to hate Seo Woo for all these years.
Hye Jung, marry me.
- Sorry?
- You don't want to?
Well...
Don't you think it's a bit much?
What do you mean?
Marriage isn't a joke.
How can you ask me that so thoughtlessly?
It wasn't thoughtless at all. I've been thinking about it for a while.
Still, this is wrong. There was nothing romantic about it.
I thought you hated those things.
Why would I hate it?
That's right. Why did I think you hated it?
I don't.
Should I do it again?
Yes.
Don't you have something to say to me?
Fine, it's not because I want to hear you say it.
I already know how you feel.
But you should learn how to express yourself.
I'm not going to say it.
Why not?
It doesn't seem right today.
I want the lights to be darker.
You're funny.
I'm happy.
You surprise me when I least expect it.
I'm holding back because we're at work.
Good night.
President Jin, Prof. Hong would like to see you.
I liked you, Prof. Hong.
I had no idea you'd stab me in the back.
I'd like to come back.
You seem to think you have the upper hand now,
but don't flatter yourself.
I have the recording of your conversation with Dr Yoo.
I have no reason to do as you say.
However, I'll show respect since you're still the president.
Should I come back after you step down?
Then you'll never come back.
Nothing must have gone your way recently.
I hope this goes the way you want it to.
Dr Yoo is waiting for you.
I just met Prof. Hong.
Are you working as a team to get back at me?
I'll quit now.
I take back all the curses I cast on you.
What are you doing?
It was a hard decision to make.
I'm going to live my life free from you.
I'm here to end what I've started.
Do you want me to thank you?
No, please don't.
You don't have to say a thing.
I'm just here to get closure.
I've learned a lot from you.
Who does she think she is?
Chairman is being released on bail and you should go see him.
All right. Let's go.
What are you doing here? Are you looking for Hye Jung?
I'm here to see you. Let's go eat.
No.
You always skip meals when you're feeling down. Get up.
If you're just repaying me for being nice to you,
you don't have to.
Do you think I'm here to repay you?
I'm only doing it because I want to.
Seo Woo.
- Hi.
I'm here to get lunch with Seo Woo.
Okay, let's go.
Hey!
Why did you turn me down when I asked you to lunch?
I can choose whom I want to have lunch with, can't I?
Yes, you can.
Go and have lunch with Yeong Gook.
But you're mean.
This is nothing compared to what you did to me.
I'm just saying.
I feel relieved now.
Go and buy her a nice lunch.
I'll even let you get something expensive and reimburse you.
He's trying to look cool.
He isn't trying. He is cool.
It's okay to like him. You can't stop your feelings.
It's not like that.
It's because I feel upset,
thinking about what an idiot I was.
Idiot?
(MUM)
I haven't seen you for a while, Seo Woo.
Yes, Grandpa. It was hard for you, wasn't it?
I'm fine. Let's eat.
Father, have some of this.
What is wrong with you?
I told you to get a medical checkup.
It's because of stress. Why are you treating me like a patient?
You haven't gotten your medical checkup yet?
I'll get it since you're back.
Seo Woo, make an appointment for your dad.
Okay.
The war begins now.
You have to be healthy for it.
Okay.
- Let's eat, Seo Woo.
- Okay.
- Eat up, Father.
- I will. Thanks.
Dr Yoo.
Isn't Prof. Hong coming back?
There is a process, so the President has to approve.
Your father is coming in today.
Father?
Your father has an appointment with Uncle Pa Ran.
I was at the diner two days ago.
The food is delicious. I heard it's your grandma's recipe.
Yes.
Dr Jin.
Did you give Kim Jin Kyung pills to take and is she ambulating?
Yes, I started wheelchair ambulation yesterday.
I'll have to take a look.
Okay.
Don't feel intimidated because of what happened with your father.
I chose you as a fellow for our department...
because you were a good fit for the job.
Thank you.
(DAD)
Take it.
Okay.
Hello.
This is Kim Tae Ho speaking.
Dr Kim, this is Lee from the test centre.
I'm calling because of President Jin's checkup results.
What is it?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
Hi.
Take a look at this.
There are tumours in number three and four.
It must be either an ependymoma or a astrocytoma tumour.
This is serious.
There must have been symptom. Who is it?
President Jin Myung Hoon.
It'll be a difficult surgery.
I don't think the result would be good, either.
I'm quite a good surgeon,
but this is hard even for me.
I'm sure it is.
But you're the only one that can handle the operation.
(MUM)
- Yes, Seo Woo.
- Mum.
I have Dad's results.
It isn't bad, is it?
He has a tumour.
Long time no see.
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
Do you visit Doo Sik often?
I go at least once a month.
I see.
I should go see him too.
He was my lifelong friend.
That's why I feel sad about how he passed away.
Could you...
operate on Myung Hoon?
I'm currently at the research centre.
You can come back. That won't be a problem.
President Jin won't want me to do the surgery.
Leave that up to me.
Both the surgeon and the patient need to be up for it.
He is hostile toward me right now.
He won't be able to fully trust me,
which means the possibility to succeed will drop.
Also, this is a highly challenging surgery.
The success rate of the surgery itself is already low.
I'd still like to ask you to do it.
The surgeon matters way more than the patient.
Did you schedule the surgery...
for Kim Soo Ryeon's cavernous angioma?
No, not yet. Why?
I was thinking of asking Mr Hong to do it since it's complicated.
Dr Kim is a good surgeon too.
Do you think Mr Hong isn't as good because he's taking a break?
No, I bet not.
He spends most of his time watching surgery videos.
His hands are swift and delicate.
How did you feel when you found out your grandma had cancer?
I found out about it at the visiting room in jail.
The sky came crashing down on me.
My grandma was my haven.
I couldn't stop crying.
I hated that I couldn't do anything.
I wondered if my grandma would be fine if I were nicer.
What's wrong?
My dad was always nice to me.
I made a lot of memories with him when young.
Did something happen?
We're not on the best of terms at the moment,
but it's because he had high expectations.
I hated him, didn't listen to him...
and didn't even go home recently.
(NEUROSURGERY, KANG KYUNG JOON)
- What is it?
- A male patient in ER.
I think he went to sleep after taking sleeping pills.
What are you doing?
Why are you notifying me of a patient that took sleeping pills?
It's President Jin Myung Hoon.
His wife says he found a tumour after a recent checkup.
- I'm on my way. Call Prof. Hong.
- Okay.
Are you okay?
Why did you bring me to the ER? I was just sleeping!
I'm fine, but your mum is embarrassing me.
You should've checked into the hospital when I told you to.
This wouldn't have happened if you checked in right away.
- Let me check you.
- No, it's fine. Let's do it later.
Mr Hong.
Hi.
You have to wait until the final moment in life...
to see what life is trying to teach you.
You have to wait until the very end.
(DOCTORS)
I want to make a family.
I wish you a long and happy life.
How do you feel about Seo Woo?
Be nice if you want this to work.
You're always first.
- You don't like my dad.
- He's a patient.
I don't want to die, Father.
Will you let Prof. Hong operate on you?
There is a problem. Dr Yoo will be assisting me.
(DOCTORS)
Would you like to have ramyeon at my place?
That's provocative.
Move that toy.
(I'M TOUGH, AREN'T I?)
This is too funny.
Why are you apologising?
What was the next line?
What?
(A WALK TO PARIS)
This is hilarious.