[Doctor's Crush]
[South Yangju Girls High Sshool]
[Episode 2]
You are really something.
Our school is not some place
that cleans up trash.
If you cause trouble one more time,
you're going to expelled, okay?
Living recklessly is like
abusing yourself.
It is more cruel and vicious than dying.
All abuse can become
amusing in its own way.
I hope that person doesn't become
my homeroom teacher.
But, I think he will become
Life never gives me what I want.
[SHE HAS NO INTEREST IN HER FRIENDS...
SMART, BUT BEHAVES BADLY.]
Even while living recklessly like this
deep inside my heart,
I wonder how long I'll live like this.
I will show you just how good I am at
doing something I really hate.
Turn around.
You're the one who wants to get hit.
I don't even like you.
Why should I do something I hate for you?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Are you upset because I'm
blunt about disliking you?
No, I like that you're blunt about it.
It's better than saying
you're hitting me on my behalf.
What would you have done
if I had really hit you?
That would have been fine.
I feel like I'm indebted to you now.
Anyway, I told you to hit me
and you chose not to.
So, I don't have to
write the apology, right?
You're very calculating.
You'd be great at business.
Didn't you say that you'd be helping
your granny with her store?
Why do you call my grandma "Granny"?
What's wrong with "Granny"?
It makes us seem close.
It's not demeaning.
It's just local dialect.
It makes my grandma sound really old
and she isn't even that old.
You say it's not demeaning
and it's local dialect.
But it comes off demeaning to me.
Hey! It's a term that's commonly used.
You're the weird one
for feeling that way.
Whether I'm strange or it's commonly used
I said I don't like it,
so shouldn't you stop saying it?
Are you Granny?
Granny told me to call her Granny.
You're just a third party.
She's my grandma so I have a say in this.
You weren't even here last New Year's.
You're not even close.
Why are you suddenly here and
acting like a good granddaughter?
That's what being a family is.
Don't you know what that is, Teacher?
You have a family.
Family...
Mom!
Hey, you punk!
Why is it important who was first?
This is my district!
Hey, who cares about such a thing?
Please save me...
People are selfish.
They think of themselves before
saving others who are dying.
That was how I learned about people
and lost my family.
Can I leave now?
You can do what you want.
You can do what you want,
but you have to take responsibility.
I won't be protecting you.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
Seriously!
That girl. I ought to just...
Hey, hey! You want to get hit again?
Leave her alone.
She's on a different level than us.
Yeah, hold it in. Hold it in.
My name is Yu Ra.
I told you my name already, right?
Where in Seoul are you from? Gangnam?
I have a brother who lives in Gangnam!
But, I only visited him
once when he moved.
Your name is written right here,
Cheon Soon Hee.
Oh, my mom had me
when she was 45 years old.
So, she's always ill and always in pain.
Don't you have any pride?
I don't have very good genes.
My dad's sperm and mom's egg met
when they were very old.
I got all the bad parts of them.
I do have pride, but I really like you.
When I first met you,
my heart beat a little faster.
I believe in fate.
Are you a "les" by any chance?
What? Like a waitress
in one of those bars?
I don't go to those places.
A girl who like girls. A lesbian.
Oh.
I do like girls!
Ah, I'm a lesbian.
But, are there girls
who dislike other girls?
You're kind of cute.
I'm cute?
Hey! I knew you'd like me too!
Please turn around.
How long have you been feeling sick for?
I've been sick all my life.
Then why would you come to
the hospital now?
What are your symptoms?
I can't digest food very well.
I get stabbing pains and
sometimes I find it hard to eat.
Let's run some tests.
Why don't you just give me
some medication to help with the pain?
Why would you come to the hospital if
all you wanted was medicine?
The medicine from the pharmacy
doesn't work anymore.
They told me I should get a prescription.
Grandma, there could be
many reasons for your illness.
You could have a hole in your stomach.
You could have an infection, as well.
How much will the tests cost?
Yes, Father?
What did Director Hong say?
How could you not have
discussed it with him yet?
I'll be up there again.
Who is that?
Wow, his motorcycle is cool.
Get on.
Stop bothering me.
Are they dating?
Yeah, right. That guy is mine.
Soo Chul, give me a ride.
Stop bothering me.
Seo Woo, I'm going to get going.
You can come over today.
Let's go over to my place.
No, it's okay. I'm going to go.
I'll call you.
Hi!
Don't you have any friends?
What do you mean? I have you.
Aren't you buying a uniform?
Is there a place I can buy used ones?
I don't know about that,
but I know where you can get a free one.
Let's go. I'll take you there.
Hello.
Are you going somewhere?
Why aren't you eating dinner tonight?
To Seoul.
- Is it to see your father?
- Yes.
Turn off the music. It's noisy.
Do you have something to discuss?
Did you see Hye Jung today?
- Who's her homeroom teacher?
- I am.
Oh, what are you doing?
I've never gotten on my knees
in my entire life.
I never had much,
but I always kept my pride.
I know. Please stand up.
I, Kang Mal Soon, respect teachers
and doctors more than anyone.
Sometimes, I wonder about people's past.
We judge and point fingers at people
because of it.
But, teachers aren't supposed to do that.
She has more days left to live than
days that she has actually lived.
I don't know how much you really know
about my granddaughter.
Erase it all.
Please take care of my granddaughter.
Hye Jung is very bright.
She needs motivation rather than praise.
That's why she's acting out,
so don't worry too much.
When her mother was alive
the whole neighborhood talked about
how smart she was.
She would read all the signs
even though no one taught her.
What is this now, seriously?
You're already in a good mood.
You're a simple person.
Don't tell her we had this talk.
Oh, my legs are cramping.
She should be home soon.
Oh, it fits you well.
Why did you buy another one?
I think this would still fit you.
To show you my affection.
I'm deficient in affection.
Look. Ta-da!
You look so pretty.
You have big breasts.
I envy you!
- Should I tell you a secret?
- Yes, please.
They're different in size.
What the heck!
- I think I should confirm.
- Are you insane?
- Sorry, but I want to see.
- No way!
What's wrong with you?
We're here!
Wait for me!
Wait for your mom.
Hello, kid.
You bought a uniform?
You're not even going to answer me now?
Mom!
Mom, are you sick?
Sis, please do something.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
Stop.
Patient, are you all right?
- Call an ambulance.
- Okay.
Hello, someone has passed out here.
She's pregnant.
We're at the Geumgok-dong bus stop.
Teacher... Teacher, there's water.
Her water broke.
She's going to have the baby.
What are we going to do?
You had a minor surgery.
Why are you still in bed?
We have lots of work to do.
I might resign from being director
and go to the US.
Why would you go to the US?
I want to study business
and social welfare.
You're a surgeon to the bone,
so why would you study that?
You and I both need to change now.
[SON]
I have an emergency patient.
Call Doctor Kim Tae Ho for me.
All right.
It's okay. Your mom will be okay.
Don't cry.
- It's okay.
- Both of you, be quiet.
A pregnant woman in her mid-thirties.
Both her pupillary reflex
and her pupil dilation in the right eye
are five millimeters.
She's experiencing paralysis in the left.
It has to be a hemorrhage or
cerebral infarction in the right brain.
It could be a
cerebral arterial hemorrhage.
How can I confirm?
You won't know with the naked eye.
Did you call an ambulance?
Yes, I did.
But, her water broke three minutes ago.
There is no hospital here with
both neurology and obstetrics.
Get us in your hospital, Dad.
Okay.
Teacher, Teacher!
Hello? Hello?
What's going on?
She just threw up.
She's having trouble breathing.
I think we need to intubate her.
If the ambulance doesn't come on time,
I'll have to make do a trachea incision.
Don't do it.
How can you do it without
any proper surgical tools?
If something goes wrong,
you really can't be a doctor again.
If this goes wrong...
you can harm the artery, cause bleeding,
and damage the thyroid gland.
Hold your mom's hand
and give her strength.
Why would we do that?
You hold on too.
You don't love with the heart.
You love with the brain.
It's what lets you decide
whether you like or dislike a person.
The brain can feel too.
Are you really a doctor?
Do you have a knife?
Do you need it for the trachea incision?
You pick things up fast.
I'll go get one.
What if things go wrong?
Can things get worse than this?
- They can.
- But you still have to do it.
We need to intubate her.
Give me an an tube for her trachea.
- Are you a doctor?
- Yes.
Give me the laryngoscope.
Please hold on a little longer.
Tube, please.
Please take that out.
Gookil Hospital in Seoul. Hurry, please.
- Get off.
- No, I can't.
Hold your mom's hand.
Doctor.
You must have been in quite a rush
to come to this hospital.
How did you get in?
Connections, of course.
How did it feel to watch a patient dying
and not be able to do anything?
It's a relief that it was only a
hypertensive cerebral hemorrhage.
The real relief is that
she met a doctor like you.
It's also a relief that
she didn't have an aneurysm.
If that were the case...
that patient would have died while
you were debating intubation.
Then you would have spent your whole life
blaming yourself again.
Because you blame yourself for the death
of every patient who doesn't make it.
You've become very harsh lately.
Does it hurt?
You need to see the real dangers
of a real neurosurgeon now.
I am going to save that patient.
Why?
Because it's me.
Because I am Kim Tae Ho.
Defibrillator.
I'll go contact someone.
Did you check that patient for a fever
before the surgery or not?
The intern probably did that.
Probably did?
"Probably did"? You punk!
What were you doing?
If this becomes a problem,
you take responsibility for it, okay?
Hey! Why do I have to
hear this crap because of you?
You don't even
deserve to sleep, you punk.
Don't even eat.
The surgery went very well.
Don't worry.
Thank you, Doctor. Thank you.
How old are you?
Don't worry.
She'll be moved to a room soon.
Let's go.
Go on in.
You don't love with the heart.
You love with the brain.
Thank you, young lady. Thank you so much.
No, it was my teacher who did everything.
- What is your name?
- What?
I want to name my daughter after you.
I want her to grow up
and help others like you.
Welcome.
Welcome...
I'm sorry. This is 10,000 won for the CD.
I'm trying to live differently now.
I didn't think I could
until I paid you back.
I can't accept this.
Is it not enough?
Give it to Teacher Hong Ji Hong at
South Yangju Girls High School.
He came back that day
with the CD and the money.
He said he found it on the street.
Oh my!
What is it?
- I have something to say.
- Say it.
Can't I come in?
No, it's too messy.
Oh, it's a total mess.
What are you doing?
I'm cleaning.
Put that back down!
It may look like a mess to you,
but there is an order to it all.
I hate it when people
touch my belongings.
Good.
So, what brings you to my room?
Do you want to become friendly with me?
Yes, I think you are kind of cool.
You tend to say things suddenly
without any warning.
Doctors make more money than teachers
and get more recognition.
Yet, you gave up on being a doctor
and became a teacher.
Why did you do that?
"Why did you do that?"
Why do you think I did that?
I thought about it
and I can't figure it out.
All the books on your floor
are all medical books.
It seems like you still have an
attachment to being a doctor.
Ah! Were you kicked out?
I left on my own.
Why?
I didn't give up on being a doctor.
I consider being a teacher
an extension of being a doctor.
Okay, I understand that,
but let's say that's true.
That saying about
brains having feelings...
Where did you hear that?
I thought that up.
Oh, that is great.
You were talking about
all that other stuff.
You sounded very smart.
I see you have completely fallen for me.
You'll end writing
a biography on my great life.
I'm 18 years old.
I can't live like this forever.
I'm tired of it.
Even I wanted to change before,
I had no reason to change.
Now, I have a reason.
What's that reason?
I want my grandma to live in comfort.
Oh, live in comfort.
That's a very old word
for such a young girl to use.
Be serious, please.
This is about my life.
So, why are you telling me about this?
I want to start living differently,
but I don't know how to.
Sorry to say this from the beginning,
but you can't live a different way.
You know how people say that
you have to fail in order to succeed?
That's all a big lie.
If you continue to fail,
you will never succeed.
Only people who succeed will succeed.
The only thing you learn from failure is
how to feel bad about yourself
and feel small.
I can succeed if I put my mind to it.
Try it. We'll talk after you succeed.
What can I succeed with right now?
What can a student succeed with?
Do you really not know?
Studying... how do I do it?
I'm a teacher.
Your homeroom teacher, at that.
I can't teach you how to study.
Go on, now.
Thank you.
I went to the CD store.
Ji Hong!
Yeah.
Who was that?
Landlady's granddaughter.
Oh, I'm glad you called.
What? What's going on?
Who's the smartest kid in our class?
Over here! Seo Woo, here!
Hurry, hurry.
Sit, sit, sit.
You know Hye Jung, right?
I do.
Hye Jung, this is Seo Woo.
Why did you ask me to come?
Here. This is the fish burger
that you like.
Tell me what you wanted
instead of dragging it out.
Hye Jung wants to start studying.
She has no knowledge of the basics,
so she needs a teacher.
Don't you have a mouth?
Why is Soon Hee asking for your favor?
Can you help me with my studies?
I'm busy with my own studies.
You can go to an academy.
We have our midterms in one week.
I have to show our
homeroom teacher my report card.
Why do you have to show it to him?
Are you going to teach me?
I don't really want to tell you
if you're not going to help me.
You're kind of testy for someone
asking for a favor.
We're seeing each other often.
It must be fate.
Oh, it's a new face.
Nice atmosphere here.
Oh! You're Jin Seo Woo, right?
Best face at
South Yangju Girls High School.
She's really smart
and her dad's a doctor.
She's on a different level than us.
She doesn't seem that great. Right?
Don't touch me.
I told you she's on a different level.
"Don't touch me!"
She told you not to touch her.
Don't you understand Korean?
Seriously, you girls...
Get over here.
Enough.
She's mine, so don't touch her.
You must be kidding me.
Why am I yours? I belong to me.
No one can own me.
These girls are with me.
Don't mess with them.
Let's go.
Look at that rude arrogant thing.
Hey, does that girl
have something on you?
Why can't you take any action?
Are they following us?
They're following us!
Run!
Ah! Run!
Get them!
Hurry up!
Run faster!
That way.
They're not coming anymore!
Oh my gosh, seriously!
Why are you guys so fast?
I thought you were only good at studying.
Really...
- I'll help you study.
- Really?
I want to check something with the
homeroom teacher first.
Yeah!
Are those medical papers?
Academic journal. I was bored.
What is it?
I'm going to tutor Hye Jung.
I know it won't really do much good,
but I'll do it for you.
For me?
You always make me do chores,
but never the other kids.
I know you're doing it on my behalf.
Because all I do is study and
don't get any exercise besides breathing.
You think I won't understand
so you reply, "Just because."
You tailor your teaching to the students
based on their home environments.
Hey, what are you doing now?
I like you, like a woman and a man.
I'm not asking to date you now.
Wait two years for me.
Don't marry In Joo.
I'm going to go to medical school
and I can marry once I graduate.
I won't make you an old bachelor.
Jin Seo Woo, you've gone too far.
I've told you my feelings.
You said confessing your feelings is
better than not saying anything at all.
I take that back.
It's not so great from this position.
Teacher...
Also, it's your choice whether
you teach Hye Jung or not.
Are you making a deal with it?
You like warm people.
I wanted to let you know that
I'm becoming someone you like.
Don't try to become
someone that others want.
Become someone that you can like.
Also, how can you confess
without even bringing chocolates?
What is this?
Grandma, you should've come earlier.
You've been getting worse.
Is it very bad?
The only good news is that you're old.
How is being old good news?
The cancer will progress slowly too.
It matches the speed of your body.
You have to let life
push you down sometimes.
That way I can avoid a bigger calamity
and live another 10 years.
I have enough for
the surgery in my account.
Oh my goodness.
Grandma, you need to stop
talking to yourself.
What are you always saying?
Where are you going?
To study.
Hey, let's not go around lying like that.
- I really am.
- Really?
If you really are,
I have nothing more to wish for.
What would you want me
to become, Grandma?
Will you do it if I say so?
I could.
Then, become a doctor.
You could wear a white gown, be called
Doctor, and people would bow to you.
You'd make good money. I like that.
You have big dreams.
Can just anyone become a doctor?
Tell me something more realistic.
Forget it. You can't even dream big.
You were born into this world,
so why not live a special life?
Shouldn't you show me
something like that before I die?
People keep asking me
to show them something these days.
What do you want to see, Grandma?
Becoming a doctor? I'll do it, okay?
That's fine.
I'll be happy if you do chores
in the hospital.
I'll be back.
Transpose the next one.
X plus 2y squared minus 5x plus 2y.
What is transposing?
To replace it.
It's a basic in factorization.
How do I do it?
Oh, this is frustrating.
I didn't realize you wouldn't know this.
How long have you not been studying for?
I can do well if you teach me...
just the beginning.
Kids, have some snacks while you study.
Thank you so much!
Eat lots. Studying takes up
a lot of energy.
Wow, you made this all yourself.
You're so lucky, Seo Woo.
If I tell my mom that I'm hungry,
she orders take-out.
Hye Jung, hurry up and eat.
Seo Woo, can I talk to you for a moment?
Gosh, I am so upset!
Why are you so upset
after taking up the snacks?
There is nothing to be gained from
giving them snacks.
They are still here. Let's talk later.
What do you mean later?
Are you protecting them because
you consider them friends?
What's wrong with Soon Hee?
Why is a principal's daughter like that?
Her book is full of
nothing but scribbles.
She's a nice girl.
If she's nice, that's halfway there.
As long as your friends don't betray you,
that's the most important thing.
Your expectations of people are so low.
You should tell her to meet people
she can benefit from.
We are quite well-off.
It's enough to meet people
who don't take from us.
Seo Woo, your dad trusts you.
Stay healthy and study hard.
You're always the good guy
in front of our daughter.
Besides Soon Hee, who's the other girl?
Just stop it. Don't you have any manners?
We can talk about this once they leave.
Why can't I even speak in my own home?
All your competitors
are in Gangnam right now.
If you end up at a bad college,
who will end up being blamed?
It's me.
So, this isn't for me.
It's all for you.
The house is nice,
but it's not very soundproof.
Yeah, we should go.
- We should go.
- Let's.
We'll get going.
Take this.
Just memorize it if you don't know it.
Math is memorization.
These are questions my tutor gave me.
How can you give me this?
Do you think it's my only copy?
I have other copies.
Thank you.
When it's meal time, just eat.
- Hey, seriously?
- What?
- Hello.
- Hello!
Hello!
You're doing all sorts of things now.
What kind of grade is a success?
If you're ranked within 30,
it's a success.
It it going well?
I will only beat up one person. Math.
Oh... thank you.
Do you have a straw?
You don't have much sense.
You can't take it back
after giving it to me.
Teacher!
Let's stop now.
Collect it starting from the back.
It's not that one.
Our marks are coming out today.
I'm so dead!
You scared me!
You didn't scare me.
I guess Seo Woo's in a good mood
because she did well on the test.
You're probably in first place.
It was so hard this time, right?
You can't give up on studying
even if you didn't do well, okay?
Studying is about keeping
your butt in the seat, not your brain.
I will keep that in mind, Teacher.
- Let's go.
- Let's go!
I was really shocked
after I saw the test results.
- Yoo Hye Jung.
- Yes?
Did you do anything wrong?
You did something very wrong.
Think about it.
I heard the math test was very hard.
Yes, it was so hard!
The number one for math is in our class.
Yoo Hye Jung.
Do you still not know what you did wrong?
No.
You did too well, that's what.
You are in first place.
That's so awesome!
At first, even I couldn't believe it.
Everyone was suspicious, but not me.
I saw how hard you studied.
Congratulations.
Studying is something
you have to be born with.
I heard that Hye Jung from your class
placed first for this math test.
- Yes.
- Didn't you tutor her in math?
- That's right.
- Looks like you raised a tiger.
I heard that her IQ is 156.
What did you get this time?
You stay up all night
taking pills to study.
Yes?
Thank you.
What are you thanking me for?
It was your hard work that did it.
So, you've succeeded now.
Are you here to ask me how
you should live your life differently?
No, I already am.
I teach you one thing and you learn two.
What are you doing?
Preparing for the juniors' class.
- Us?
- Yes.
What's your blood type?
It's probably O.
What do you mean "probably"?
It either is or it isn't.
Sit down.
Sterilize your fingertip.
Then get a drop of blood.
Put it on these two spots.
I'll let you know
what your blood type is.
It stings.
Okay.
You're type A.
If your blood forms a cohesion with this
A antiserum, you're type A.
Look.
It's not the same on this one.
Wow, really.
That's really simple.
Do you want to see
your red blood cells too?
How?
What's your blood type?
B.
Look.
You have to put your eyes like this.
Oh.
Do you see it?
Can you not see it?
I can see it.
Fun, right? You want to learn about it.
Yes.
What is this?
- Grandma.
- What?
- Grandma!
- What is it?
I got first place in math.
Really?
Really! Really, really.
Oh, good job, my child.
I'm so proud of you.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy so why do I keep crying?
You should laugh if you're happy.
Why are you crying?
That's not good.
Don't do that. Don't.
Why are you crying, Grandma?
Because I'm happy.
Oh, my child! Oh dear!
My granddaughter is number one!
[HYE JUNG]
Hello?
Thank you, Teacher.
- This...
- I don't need it.
I don't need it anymore either.
I memorized it all like you said.
Thank you.
I won't forget the warmth
you showed me and I'll repay you.
Do you like our homeroom teacher?
Why aren't you answering?
I'll put it another way.
Does our homeroom teacher like you?
I don't think Teacher and I can be
put into a category like that.
Category?
You know terms like that?
You lied to me, right?
- About what?
- Being bad at studying.
You fooled me, right?
There's no other way you'd
suddenly be so good at it.
I never lied to you.
I've never studied before.
So, that means you're just really smart.
I don't understand why
you're getting so angry.
Yeah, I don't know why I'm
getting so angry either.
Hey, do you know how to ride a bike?
Ready, go!
It's dangerous!
Do you want to win?
- Yes!
- Then, win.
Yoo Hye Jung wins!
It's raining.
It's like a movie.
Here.
How did you...
I've become friendly with
the owner of the CD store.
He got that for me.
Grandma gave me money for getting
first place so I bought that.
Thank you.
You have good sense.
I was really envious of you that day.
You should do it too if you're envious.
I need to have really top grades
to become a doctor.
How can I do that?
I was just lucky this time.
That's true.
Things don't always work out
just because you work hard.
You were just lucky.
I was by my mom's side
when she was dying.
How nice would it have been
if I were a doctor back then?
Then she could have lived
like that pregnant woman.
Or it would have been really great
if you had been there.
People who are meant to die will die
even if doctors are there.
Otherwise, everyone would live
if they went to the hospital.
That's true.
It stopped raining.
Let's go to school. We'll be late.
Okay.
They're coming to school together again.
Look at the chemistry between them.
Are the two of them dating or something?
No, why would you imagine such a thing?
We're still just teenagers.
It's the most innocent time in our lives.
Why are you denying something
right in front of our eyes?
Yes, we are teenagers.
Biologically, we are at
our peak physical state.
- What are you doing?
- I'm going to post it online.
I'll take that temporarily.
Hey!
What are you doing all the way here?
It's been decided.
Am I going up to Seoul? Starting when?
- Next month.
- That soon?
Meet with people before you come
and get in favor with them.
I've set things up for you,
so it's up to you now.
Father!
What are you doing?
I will get it done!
I won't let you down.
Let's have a nice dinner tonight.
- Bring Seo Woo and your wife.
- Yes.
We're done for the day.
Tell the kids to go home.
Teacher.
I heard a strange rumor and
wanted to confirm it with you.
Yeah, what is it?
People say that you and Hye Jung
are in a special relationship.
- Did you start the rumor?
- What?
You come to me with something ridiculous.
What do you want to confirm?
Just tell me you're jealous of her.
Then I'll understand.
Why would I be jealous
of someone like her?
I have everything that she doesn't have.
That's right. You have everything.
She doesn't have anything,
but just managed to grab a thin string.
You even want that string.
You're too greedy.
Whose side are you on?
Don't make me into a teacher who has
to take sides with his students.
Send the kids home and go study.
Meet your goal of getting into college
and meeting your parents' expectations.
Do you think it's my goal
to meet my parents' expectations?
I am not a machine.
I have feelings and they are very hurt.
I am very upset and in pain.
I am in pain too.
Everyone lives with their pain.
Do you know what?
You are always cold to me,
but always smiling when you see her.
[CLASS 2-4 TEACHER HONG JI HONG
AND YOO HYE JUNG]
[AN UNBELIEVABLE REALITY HAS OCCURRED.]
[IT IS TRULY UNIMAGINABLE...]
An unbelievable reality has occurred.
It is truly unimaginable.
A teacher and a student.
To think that it is Teacher Hong Ji Hong,
whom I trusted so much.
I cannot believe it.
Are you happy now?
Do my words mean nothing to you now?
I asked if you're happy now.
Do whatever you want.
You and our homeroom teacher
are done now.
Why are you doing this?
You disgust me, so get lost.
Let's talk.
Don't grab me.
I'm on the verge of exploding.
What should I do?
What do you want me to do?
What should I do for you to cancel it?
I don't care what you do
because I'm already at the bottom.
But, Teacher Hong is different.
You liked Teacher Hong too!
You're not at the bottom yet.
You have something to protect.
Teacher Hong Ji Hong.
Hye Jung.
Our teacher might get fired.
They're having school administration
board meeting.
Seo Woo's mom is the president.
Let's go.
Hold on.
It's okay. It's just a secret hideout.
There it is. There's the light.
What did you want to talk about that
we had to come all the way here?
It's a little creepy. It's exciting.
It's not dangerous.
I came with Mi Ra before.
Isn't Mi Ra, herself, dangerous?
You didn't say we'd be meeting Hye Jung.
Seo Woo, why don't we just talk?
We can resolve things by talking.
How can we talk in this dirty place?
Maybe it's a place for threatening.
Hye Jung, talk.
Oh, I'm so cold.
I'll do whatever you tell me to.
Just say you were mistaken
on what you posted.
How would I look if
I took back what I said?
It can't be stopped.
Seo Woo, why are you being like this?
If you keep acting like this,
I don't know what I'll do either.
Thank you.
You gave me more to post online.
I'll add what happened today
to it, as well.
You're not only talented at seducing men.
You're a coward who uses your friends
to accomplish your goals.
Hey, you're the one who doesn't
treat friends like real friends.
You've never once treated me
on an equal level.
How could you do this to me?
If I didn't trust you as a friend,
I wouldn't have followed you here.
I'm like an accessory to you.
This is all because of you.
She never acted like this
before she met you!
- Seo Woo.
- Let go.
Let go of me!
Hye Jung!
Hey...
Do you think I'm not fighting back
because I don't know how to?
What are you going to do, then?
Are you going to beat me up?
Do it! Yeah, that's more like you.
Do what you always do.
Do what you always do! Do it!
- Seo Woo!
- Let go of me!
Stop it, you guys!
Seo Woo!
What do we do?
We have to get out of here.
Seo Woo!
Seo Woo, wake up.
We have to get out of here.
Seo Woo!
What are we going to do?
Seo Woo, please wake up.
Seo Woo!
My goal of living differently...
was taken from me
after one sweet success.
I had overlooked the fact that the
environment surrounding me was the same.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor's Crush]
Are you saying you're going
to protect Hye Jung?
Teacher and student.
Woman and man.
Who do you think will get hurt
when these issues arise?
Why is it that
I'm more worried about you?
Stay away from Hye Jung.
She's a really charming girl.
I can help you.
I don't want to see you again, Teacher.
Should I really leave?