[DOCTOR CRUSH]
Is it really okay for me to leave?
I don't ever want to see you again.
I met him again.
I didn't know I would
meet him like this again.
If you think about it,
it was like this from the beginning.
It started out as a coincidence,
and then became inevitable.
Then it became fate.
[FINAL EPISODE]
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
I'm so embarrassed because of your mom.
So why don't you just admit yourself
into the hospital like I told you to?
If you had admitted yourself already,
this wouldn't have happened.
Let me take a look.
Forget it. Do it later.
Oh my! Teacher!
Hello.
What's going on here?
What are you doing here?
- Do you know her?
- Of course, I know her.
She's the one who
did that to our Seo Woo--
She's my friend.
What?
I said that she's my friend.
We should move him into a room.
Let's do that.
We'll move him into a VIP room.
Gosh, what is going on here?
This is the hospital.
Dad and I work here.
I wish you would keep
proper etiquette around here.
We'll move you into a patient room.
I'm going to walk.
- Get me my shoes.
- You have none.
- Go find me some slippers.
- Yes, I will.
Does your head hurt, Honey?
What should we do?
How is it?
The tumor on his spine
is the same as before.
His brain is fine, as well.
So it was just the sleeping pills, then.
I'm not even his doctor,
so why was I called?
I thought you would be
best suited for this.
Wouldn't Doctor Jung Yoon Do
be better for this?
Director Jin ordered you back to work
in Neurosurgery yesterday.
Well, he never spoke to me about it.
He spoke to me.
Keep him hydrated for now.
Okay.
I'm opposed to Doctor Hong
operating on your dad.
Are there no other doctors?
Why does it have to be him?
There's always Yoon Do,
or let's just go to the U.S.
Getting the surgery from
Doctor Hong Ji Hong is our best option.
What do you mean, "best option"?
We brought him from the US
because he was good.
Why would I go to the US?
It hurts my pride.
Is your pride more important to you
than Dad's surgery?
I never thought I'd live to see the day.
How could we meet him like this again?
We looked at your CT and MRI,
and it hasn't changed from before.
Why are you here, Professor Kim?
Why isn't Professor Hong here?
Will you allow Professor Hong Ji Hong
to operate on you?
Then, who else will operate?
Why did you call me to the ER?
Did you know that I was working again?
No, it's because you're the best.
That's why I called you.
That makes me feel good.
Did you know about Director Jin?
No, I just found out when I saw.
It looks very bad.
Yes, even with the surgery,
he won't be like he was before.
Why don't you want to operate on him?
We went head-to-head recently.
The patient probably doesn't
feel comfortable with me.
It isn't right to operate on someone
just because I can operate well.
[DOCTOR KIM TAE HO]
Yes, Doctor.
Come in.
You two should talk now.
Stay here with us.
You two can either build trust
or build a wall with blocks.
It's up to you.
Let's have coffee once you're done.
Thanks.
For what?
For calling Professor Hong.
I was just making a
judgment call as a doctor.
You hate my dad, though.
I don't like him, but he's a patient.
I can't let my emotions get in the way.
I can't be objective
when it comes to my dad.
That's why he's my dad.
I know that he hurt you.
But he is my father,
whom I cherish very much.
You have a tumor on your third
and fourth cervical vertebrae.
We'll have to perform
a biopsy to be certain.
However, I believe it's an ependymoma.
An ependymoma is usually
from the cerebrospinal fluid cells.
It's usually in the
ventricle of the brain.
It can also be found in the spinal cord.
In your case, it is in a
very dangerous location.
I see.
Director, we need to
operate before it grows.
What happens if it grows?
It is very dangerous, even to your life.
How are you going to operate?
The tumor is inside your spinal cord.
I'm going to open
the back of your spinal cord.
There will be damage once you do that.
Even if it is a success
you'll likely have
issues with your senses.
Your ability to control your muscles
and movement will be affected.
There is also the chance that you
may become a quadriplegic.
Let's just do the surgery quickly.
Are you really okay with me doing it?
Yes.
I trust you as a doctor.
There is a problem, though.
What is it?
I need Doctor Yoo Hye Jung to assist me.
I can't do this surgery without her.
Are you doing this to spite me
due to personal feelings?
It's a dangerous surgery.
Doctor Yoo and I have
worked together a lot recently.
Our rate of success is high.
As a doctor,
I want to save every patient.
Yoo Min Ho? Please come in.
Yes.
I was glad to hear from you first.
I went to see Grandma recently.
Oh, did you? I should go too.
I haven't been able to go lately.
Should we go together next time?
Why did you accept a settlement for
Grandma's medical accident?
Did you move her to a better memorial
because you felt guilty?
I didn't know what to do back then.
I didn't know where to start.
I asked for a copy of the medical record.
So, I looked at it. I did.
But what was I supposed to do with it?
I didn't know what I was looking at.
Going down a legal path
would've taken a long time.
Then you shouldn't have
accepted the settlement money.
For whose sake?
Only the hospital would gain from that.
What could I have done in that situation?
I need to make a living and
take care of things too.
I was so angry too.
Yet, that was all I could manage to do.
What could I do?
I don't have any pity for your life.
You know, most parents
and children are not objective
when it comes to one another.
But I can't think of a
single good memory with you
no matter how hard I try.
It's strange, though.
I don't like you.
Yet my heart hurt
when I heard you were sick.
If you're sick or having a hard time,
I will want to help you.
But if not...
I think it's best that we don't meet.
I want to start a family.
If I didn't talk with you first...
I didn't think I could start properly.
That's why I wanted to meet.
Are you getting married?
I will be, someday.
I probably won't be contacting you.
Live well and healthily.
I'm sorry.
I wasn't there for you as a father.
I made life hard for you.
Thank you for your apology.
I'll do my best not to get sick.
Live your life happily.
Go outside. I need to meet someone.
Go ahead. I'm not stopping you.
Who can't you meet
just because I'm around?
I was totally embarrassed because of you.
I could have come in quietly once I
had a surgery date, and now look.
Come in.
You told me to leave to meet her?
You always leave me out.
Why didn't you tell me that
Doctor Hong and that girl work here?
I'm a patient here.
You've moved up in the world.
How did you become a doctor, at that?
I told you to stop.
Okay!
You heard from Professor Hong, right?
I don't know what you're referring to.
He has to operate on me.
He's being stubborn and insisting
that you have to assist him.
I won't do it.
I agree with you.
If that happens,
I'll be too worried to get the surgery.
Go and tell that to Professor Hong.
I will.
I will switch the doctor in charge to
Chief Kang Kyung Joon, as well.
You do that.
[JUNG YOON DO]
Why aren't you picking up?
Do I have to?
You don't have to.
Have you prepared
Kim Ji Young for surgery?
Yes, I just need to go in.
- Your father...
- He has a nasty tumor.
It's in such a dangerous location.
How can it be right on the neck?
I heard Professor Hong is operating.
No, it hasn't been decided yet.
I don't know why.
All the nerves in the body
pass through the neck.
If something goes wrong...
I have a bad feeling.
I can't live without my dad.
My grandpa is going through a trial.
What do I do?
It'll all work out.
I'll help you.
You were in here, Doctor Jung.
See you later.
What are your feelings for Seo Woo?
Why do I need to tell you that?
I'm Seo Woo's friend.
I was by her side when she was going
through a hard time because of you.
I think that gives me a right to know.
You're being really polite, aren't you?
Have you liked Seo Woo
since you two were in school?
Is that why you've always
kept your distance from me?
I liked her as a friend.
Though, not anymore.
I'm no more than a brother to Seo Woo.
If you end up dating Seo Woo,
I'm all for it.
Be good to her.
Tell me if you're having a hard time.
Aren't you just too cool?
What's so cool about me?
You found a person you love.
You're trying to protect that love.
You're the cool one here.
I'm sure you know this already.
Seo Woo's a bit mentally weak.
I'll be going now.
Wow! This looks just like them.
"As usual, this is the best."
KJ says, "It's boring. Get lost."
This crazy punk.
People don't seem to like it.
KJ says it's boring.
I think I know this KJ.
He keeps coming around
and posting this nonsense.
Is it you, Chief? KJ.
- Kyung Joon.
- No.
It really isn't me.
Am I the only KJ?
Kwang Joo, Kyung Joo, Kook Ja,
or like Kyung Joon...
Oh! Kyung Joon.
Wow, you just outed yourself.
Fine, it was me.
How did you know?
Is it very obvious?
Seriously, why are you doing that?
You're just doing so well.
I'm worried you'll become a writer.
Gosh, really.
I like webtoons. They're a hobby.
My dream is to be a surgeon.
Stop worrying about useless things
and don't do things like this.
Okay, okay.
Okay!
Kang Soo.
What about the seizures?
They are...
gone now that I took medication.
- What a relief.
- You're checking diligently.
Are you doing that for all patients?
Yes, I am.
You know that the director
is in the VIP room, right?
Yes, I made the call from the ER.
You sure are good at answering.
Will the director be able
to stay in his position?
He'll probably get fired
once there is a new board director.
He doesn't have that connection anymore.
Hello.
What? Were you gossiping again?
You went quiet when I came in,
so I guess you were.
No, we weren't.
Where's Young Gook?
He's in the on-call room.
Young Gook.
Yeah.
I'm hungry.
So why would you come looking for me?
You should go eat.
You're right.
Why did I come to you when I'm hungry?
What is it?
Stay put. I'm not going to attack you.
You're barely even eating.
Why did you say you were hungry?
Why did you just leave earlier?
It seemed like you were
talking with Senior Yoon Do.
He was just returning the favor.
- When he used to get dumped--
- You don't need to explain.
Is there anything about you
that I don't know?
Let's get out of here.
Seo Woo.
As I've always been, I'm by your side.
Right?
That's right.
I think you've always been
there by my side.
But what do I do now?
I've changed now.
I think it was ever since then.
When I first did that bad thing to you...
Since then...
you came rushing into my heart.
I don't really know
when you came into my heart.
But when I heard about my dad...
the first thing I thought was that
I wanted to be comforted by you.
Everything...
will be okay.
I know it's late, but congratulations
on coming back to work.
What is all of this?
I bought them at the hospital store.
Take them home with you.
I'm usually single-minded.
I've decided to change that.
I'm going to do multiple things at once.
- You're testing it out on me?
- Yes.
Taking care of you and being a surgeon.
Being a great friend to Soon Hee.
Being a good senior
to the department people.
Can you do all of that?
I won't be doing Director Jin's surgery.
To summarize,
Director Jin's surgery is on your mind.
All your thoughts are on that,
so you want to keep yourself busy.
How did you know?
Because I'm your man.
You say all the answers I want to hear.
If you don't go in,
I can't do that surgery either.
Why?
I don't have the confidence.
You have things
you're not confident about?
Yes, it's a very difficult surgery.
It's emotionally burdensome and risky.
I'm worried that the patient
will suffer from that risk.
I haven't been able to
forgive Director Jin.
That's why I can't do it.
I need to go to the ICU. I'm sorry.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
How is she?
Her BST was 250, so I gave her insulin.
Her cortisol levels are a little high.
What do the obstetricians say?
They say it could be temporary,
so we should just check on her.
Okay.
I'm very sorry.
I made this decision for
your benefit, not for mine.
How can not operating on me
be for my benefit?
Do you think I asked you to
operate on me because I like you?
I know that.
We are looking into other surgeons.
You can't come in this month?
It won't be good to delay this.
Okay, then.
Then find out when Professor Song
is coming back from the U.S.
Okay.
Professor Lee Sung Min can't do it?
No, and Professor Song Man Soo
is off studying right now.
Professor Song Hye Jin.
She got into a fight with Director Jin
and left the hospital.
That won't work either.
What should we do?
Can't you do it, Doctor?
I have to perform the duties
of the director right now.
And I've been handling management duties
so my hands are not what they used to be.
Gosh...
Does it make sense that he can't operate
because Hye Jung won't do it?
He can just say he doesn't want to do it.
What kind of excuse is that?
It's not like that.
The two of them have rarely
failed in surgery together.
Hye Jung is a skilled surgeon.
Why do you care who is assisting?
It's the surgeon who's important.
The assisting surgeon is important.
No matter what the surgery,
a small mistake can make it go wrong.
She is really detailed about her work.
So is Doctor Hong.
Getting the two of them to operate
is the best thing for you, Dad.
Forget it. Kim Tae Ho is
looking into other surgeons.
I can get it from someone else.
What brings you by this late?
I wondered what you thought about
postponing the surgery date.
It's hard to find anyone who can
operate on your schedule.
Did you even look properly?
I understand you're feeling sensitive,
but please don't cross the line.
Perhaps you want me to die.
- Dad!
- It's all right.
We'll talk again later.
Do you need something to help you sleep?
I'm fine. I can sleep well.
This is so upsetting.
How did things get this way?
Why do bad things happen all at once?
Father-in-law has to be questioned by
the prosecutors the day after tomorrow.
Why do you keep talking? It's noisy.
Go home if you're
going to be bothersome.
Can't I even talk?
You get annoyed whenever I talk.
Can't you stay quiet?
Does it hurt?
What can I do?
[JIN SEO WOO]
Hello?
Where are you?
Can we meet now?
I'm sorry to come so late.
It's okay. Sit down.
So, you live here with Soon Hee.
- Where's Soon Hee?
- She'll be here soon.
- Are you okay with herbal tea?
- Yes.
Hye Jung.
About my dad's surgery,
can you come in and assist?
Doctor Hong says he won't do it,
so we're looking for another doctor.
It's not working out well.
Your father won't like it.
I can persuade my dad.
You should try talking to Doctor Hong.
Kyung Joon or Young Gook can assist.
Can you do it?
I feel like that's what would
make me feel at ease.
I'm sorry.
Please, I'm asking you.
Why are you alone?
I sent them all away
because they were irritating me.
Don't be like that.
This is when you need
your family more than anything.
Why are you here so late?
I kept trying to come.
My heart felt weak and my
body felt weak. I couldn't come.
My child is sick. How could I be okay?
I can't sleep.
Dad...
How did such an awful thing
grow inside of you?
Even if I get surgery,
I won't be able to live like before.
I might not be able to walk and
I might not be able to talk.
I'm scared to death.
You just need to live.
You can become used to
the other discomforts.
Don't think about that stuff.
I keep thinking I'm going to die!
I think I'm going to die during surgery.
I don't want to die, Dad!
You're not going to die!
How can you say that
in front of your father?
You... will not die.
Your dad will not let you die!
My doctor knows what he is doing.
My doctor is good looking and smart.
I trust my doctor.
Yes, Kyung Joon.
Director Jin Myung Hoon is
complaining about headaches.
Okay.
He didn't take any medication
or food that would cause this.
Where and how severe is the head pain?
It's everywhere and I feel like
my head is going to explode.
Just in case, let's take another CT.
Give him some painkillers quickly.
Okay.
Tell me if there's anything else wrong.
You're not even going to do my surgery.
Tell Yoon Do to take charge
until I get a surgery date.
We can't do that according
to the hospital rules.
I will take responsibility for you
until your surgery.
Stop dangling a mouse
in front a cat and just leave.
You're just leaving me to die.
Gosh.
Oh! Pretty Doctor Yoo, whom I respect.
- Hello, there.
- Coming from somewhere?
Running errands.
Just doing my job as secretary.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Which floor? The station?
- No, the VIP floor.
- Okay.
Why are you going there?
Do I have to report that to you?
No, have a good visit there.
What brings you up here?
I'm here to see the director.
If the director wants it,
I will assist you in the surgery.
Why?
I'm a doctor.
I should do it if the patient wants it.
You made a good decision.
I might get rejected.
I made the decision to do it, though.
Director.
Why are you here?
I want to assist in your surgery.
What?
I will go into your surgery, do my best,
and help the lead surgeon.
Leave out the part about doing your best.
Don't make fun of me.
You're going to cut one of my
blood vessels during surgery, right?
Then say that you did your best?
Why would you think that?
I'm going crazy right now.
Do you think I'm getting what I deserve
because this happened?
Yes, I do think you are.
I haven't done anything wrong.
I looked at the MRI and CT again.
The tumor is inside the spinal cord
so we'll have to
open the posterior column.
I know that.
When we open it up...
I will do what I can to avoid
causing damage to the area.
You do seem to have skills.
I found that out...
when I was digging into your past.
Do you know what my grandma said
to me before she went into surgery?
"My doctor knows what he is doing."
"I trust my doctor."
I thought about it.
I think my grandma's last moments
were peaceful, at least.
Because she trusted you.
She trusted that she would wake up.
She thought she would
live a healthy life.
Before the surgery...
you made her feel she could trust you
and feel safe going into her surgery.
Thank you for that.
You were originally my patient.
You need this surgery
and I want to save you.
I want to save you.
And I want to hear you say "Thank you."
I will be going now.
You tell Professor Hong Ji Hong.
Schedule the surgery as soon as possible.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Self-retaining retractor.
This surgery requires the spinal cord
to be opened because the tumor is inside.
It is extremely difficult.
It's a dangerous surgery
that could cause paralysis, right?
Yes. Do you understand, Joong Dae?
I will study it.
Gown, please.
Cutter, please.
Let's get started.
Irrigation, please.
Rinse it here.
They've cut the backbone
of C2 to C5, right?
Yes.
Don't go near the inner part
of the vertebral artery.
Bipolars.
They're getting in okay.
They've barely touched it so far.
It's really stuck on there.
I see that.
The tumor is on the underside
of the spinal cord.
It looks like they will have to touch
the nerves to remove the tumor.
I don't know. I got Hong Ji Hong
to do this surgery to avoid that.
We're almost there.
They've removed it.
Yes, they've done it.
There's bleeding.
It was unavoidable because the tumor
was adhered so tightly to the spine.
They have to fix that.
Bring me cottonoid.
Doctor.
I see it. Let me finish this.
Biopsy.
The bleeding isn't stopping.
His nerves are getting damaged.
Cottonoid.
What if he wakes up and can't move?
Why isn't the bleeding stopping?
Let's just watch, kids.
Doctor, the signal is strange.
We have to do something.
I have to stop the bleeding.
I got it.
Good work.
They got it.
They finished a very hard surgery.
Good work, Doctor Yoo.
Thanks.
The director lived. Let's finish up.
The surgery went well.
The tumor was removed.
There was damage to some nerves.
We won't know anything for sure
until he wakes up.
We'll move him into his room.
Thanks. Thank you, Doctor.
You're welcome.
Bye, then.
He survived.
Let's go see your dad.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
The coffee has arrived!
Thank you, Doctor Choi!
- No, wait. Secretary Choi.
- Secretary Choi.
What's going on here?
- Doctor! Have this.
- What's this?
Iced Americano. Kang Soo bought it.
Doctor, it really feels like our
department again because you're back.
Now that the director's surgery went well
let's go out for welcome-back drinks!
It's not like
I just started working here.
Professor, we're all feeling down lately.
Let's just have a beer.
Ah! Doctor Yoo can come too.
Yeah, we can all go if she comes, right?
We can all go if I go? Where?
We all want to go for a beer.
- Chief, you can't go.
- Why?
You're on-call.
Gosh, no!
- Then, should we go for a drink?
- Yes!
Gosh...
Here, have this Americano.
Thank you.
I'm on-call tonight.
Let's work hard!
Doctor!
This is called a one, two,
upper backspin, and elbow.
And this?
That's a high kick.
Yoon Do, your uncle is here.
Gosh...
What are you doing here alone?
I like being alone.
Are you an outcast?
Ji Hong went out to drink with people
from your department.
They didn't even invite you, did they?
They did. I just didn't go.
How can I watch her with Professor Hong?
I'm human too.
What about Doctor Yoo
do you like so much?
It's not one thing in particular.
I like everything.
It doesn't make me lonely to like her.
It makes me lonelier to meet other women
and then think about Doctor Yoo.
How is it love if you like her
but she doesn't like you?
Don't look down on one-sided love.
To find love in this world...
is better than not loving at all.
Let's toast.
What should we toast to?
To Hong Ji Hong's return.
- Good.
- I like that.
Let's toast and then
play a game of truth.
Man, that is so old. When were you born?
Old?
What kind of game is that?
Professor, when did you start
dating Doctor Yoo?
- Are you drunk?
- I'm sorry.
- Hello?
- Doctor!
Lee Hee Young's water broke.
How long has it been?
Call her obstetrician now.
I'll be right there.
- Lee Hee Young?
- Yes.
Wait, Doctor!
What are they doing? Are they leaving?
You could say they are perfectly matched
when it comes to work and love.
It's Jin Jin!
You're right. Jin Jin's coming.
Hurry. Let's go.
Stop eating, would you? Hurry up.
How can you just leave like that?
Joong Dae, Joong Dae. Ahn Joong Dae!
You guys didn't even pay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This is Yoo Hye Jung.
Yes, Doctor.
Your wife's water broke and the baby
will be delivered by C-section.
It's Jin Jin!
So cute!
Jin Jin.
Round face three!
That hurts.
So cute.
Don't you want to have babies?
Are you crazy?
We should move the patient into the ICU.
Okay.
[BABY LEE]
[KANG KYUNG JOON]
Yes?
Doctor, Hee Young's vitals are dropping.
Okay.
Kim Woo Jin, there isn't much time.
- Did you call?
- Yes.
Why isn't he coming?
What if he doesn't get to
see her before she goes?
I love you, Hee Young.
Time of death, 2:25 a.m.
Lee Hee Young has died.
I believe Hee Young saw Woo Jin
in her last moments.
Maybe I imagined it.
I saw Hee Young smiling.
I am Kim Tae Ho, who has been
voted to be the next director.
I believe Gookil is at a fork in the road
between growth or taking a pause.
We have been running until now.
So, I would like to take a pause.
We need to know where we stand
and where we are headed.
Why does a hospital exist?
Who does it exist for
and who should we work for?
How should we solve these problems?
I would like to ponder these issues
with all of you here.
I will become a director who will
resolve these issues together with you.
Thank you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Why isn't he waking up?
Hello.
I checked his motor response starting
from his limbs and didn't get much.
Honey.
- Dad!
- Myung Hoon.
His hand is moving.
He will need to do rehab now.
Honey.
He's alive.
This week was so long. I'm tired.
Are you taking the vitamins I got you?
I shouldn't have said anything.
You shouldn't think of it as nagging.
Your health is very important.
What are you doing this weekend?
It's obvious, really.
Should we go fishing?
I can just imagine what Father would say.
"You said no when I asked you."
"Now that I can't go with you,
you're finally going fishing."
Father... Father.
Yes, Father.
I will catch all of the fish
on his behalf.
Okay.
[DIRECTOR JIN MYUNG HOON]
I'm on my way.
You go on without me.
I have to drop by somewhere.
Where?
To see Director Jin Myung Hoon.
I'll wait.
Sit down.
It's all right.
You're doing well with rehab?
Yes, I am.
Thank you.
I want to thank you, too.
For surviving the surgery and recovering.
Oh, what is all of this?
Will you marry me?
I should be the one to put it on for you.
It's mine, so I'll put it on.
It's not romantic though.
You told me to be romantic.
That's why I did all of this.
I love you.
Ah... really.
I wanted to create a nice atmosphere
and leave you with good memories.
Call me right now.
Call you now?
[HONG HONG HONG]
"Hong Hong Hong." That's me?
Yes.
Why?
Whenever I see you,
I end up going "Hong Hong Hong."
What is "Hong Hong Hong"?
Just like I said, "Hong Hong Hong."
That's weird. "Hong Hong Hong."
It makes you laugh when you do it, right?
Yes.
Oh, I feel shy.
I don't know when I started to love.
I may not know when I started to love,
but I had been loving the whole time.
It was a once in a lifetime love
and I don't know when it started.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever