Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 3
The feelings associated with like and dislike...
are produced by the amygdaloid nucleus in cerebrum.
The Amygdaloid nucleus is also responsible...
for the fight-or-flight response and aggressive behaviour.
Falling in love causes people...
to become simultaneously more combative.
Hello. I tried to come on time.
Please sit.
- I ordered my drink already.
- Yes.
- I'll have a soda.
- Okay.
I guess you can't judge a book
by its cover.
Who knew you would be caught up in
a messy scandal like this, Teacher?
I believe it's basic manners to respect
the other person when conversing.
And I respect you.
Seo Woo misunderstood things and
that's why there was a messy scandal.
I don't want anyone to
get hurt by what happened.
I'm willing to accept getting hurt.
What you're saying is that
you will protect Hye Jung?
That child will most likely be expelled.
You will have to take some
responsibility for this too.
If that's the case
I will have to sue Seo Woo
and the school for defamation.
Teacher!
If this issue gets any bigger,
it won't be good for Seo Woo either.
It won't matter if you do so.
I cannot accept you and Hye Jung
in the same school.
Teacher Hong.
I really liked you.
You're a doctor who became a teacher.
It's a nice title.
Why throw that away?
Please get the temporary English teacher
to take over my class.
What is it?
What are we going to do?
We should go to the hospital.
It's okay.
Don't tell the homeroom teacher
why we met up.
He ought to know what you did
on his behalf.
- Soon Hee.
- Yes?
My friend, Soon Hee.
I want to become a good person.
I want to live a good life.
I don't want our teacher to get
involved in this with me.
Same goes for you, as well.
You should run far away from me, quickly.
Give me your parents' number
instead of your grandma's.
I don't have any.
She attends our school
and she's a nuisance.
Arson is a crime.
Then, what's going to happen?
What do you think? She'll go to prison.
You're over the age of 14,
so you'll get a prison sentence.
Even if it was an accident?
Some container of gas fell over, is all.
Did that container fall over on its own?
Someone set a fire and made it fall.
Can I take my daughter home now?
Yes, you can take her home.
What about Hye Jung?
She has no guardian.
I will have to charge her
for the crime of arson.
No! I'll stay here with her.
Stop saying nonsense. Come on.
Hye Jung!
Go home with your dad.
I'm the one who started it.
I should be the one to end it.
No, I did it. Hye Jung didn't do it!
Kids this age will do anything
for their friends.
She's still very clueless.
- Let's get going!
- No, Hye Jung! Hye Jung!
Dad, Dad! Hye Jung!
Hye Jung! I'll be back. Dad...
You must think you're cool
to take all the blame.
But... the reality is that
it's like a deep ditch.
Hey.
Welcome to my home!
Gosh, be quiet! You'll wake everyone.
Stop barking.
This second year resident with
not much to do is here to visit you.
Don't do that.
Why am I so happy to hear
that you quit school?
Did you quit to go to the US
with the director?
Have you eaten yet?
Are you going to cook for me?
I'm going to give you
food from the fridge.
That's the same thing.
Oh, hey!
Be mine. I'll be good to you.
Who is that? I'll kill her.
Hello?
Teacher Hong. It's Soon Hee.
Yeah, why are you calling so late?
Sorry, it's urgent.
Hye Jung is at the police station.
What happened?
Hello, Doctor. Hello, ma'am.
What, exactly, happened?
What did Hye Jung say?
I came to you first.
She tried to kill me.
- Seo Woo--
- I liked you, Teacher.
I respected you.
Because someone like you was there,
I actually enjoyed going to school.
Why did you have to disappoint me?
What did you like and
what disappointed you?
Why can't it be me?
Why is Hye Jung okay, but not me?
Why do you like her and not me?
You know that you're
pretty and smart, right?
Rest up and get better,
both your heart and body.
Yoo Hye Jung, come on out.
Give me your arm.
No.
There you go, not listening again.
You never did listen very well.
Seo Woo can't be the only one injured.
You were both in the same place.
People with backgrounds like yours can
get treated unfairly by the police.
Why would you want that?
Just because.
You are an odd one.
Sign it for me.
Lee Ji Hong? Hong Ji Hong?
Oh, that? I was an orphan
until junior high.
What's that look?
Do I suddenly look pitiful to you?
Ah, so that's how people feel
when they look at me.
When I tell them I don't have a mom...
Here.
I'm looking at you because
I have nowhere else to look.
Seo Woo's okay. I just saw her.
I'm sorry.
I've been avoiding you since
that post went online.
Me too.
It's just so strange, you and I...
I didn't imagine it could be possible.
I heard that you resigned
because of me--
Teacher and student. Woman and man.
In a society like ours,
who would end up suffering more?
So, why am I more worried about you?
Teacher.
Thank you for everything.
Why are you suddenly doing this?
I have a feeling I might not
see you anymore.
Don't come to visit me anymore.
It's better if we don't see each other.
Take care of your injury.
You don't need to put gauze on it.
Put this on it.
I'll drive you home.
It's getting late. Just go home.
No, I want to drive you home.
In Joo, isn't your uncle a lawyer?
All right, I'll get her a lawyer.
I'll take care of everything for her,
so I want you to back out.
I don't need to do that.
If there is a scandal,
the weakest person will suffer most.
I know that.
I know that Hye Jung will suffer most
because of this lie.
You should leave Granny's house.
It looks worse because you live there.
People who think that way
are the strange ones.
I don't need to hear this kind of
criticism from you.
It's not criticism. It's jealousy.
- In Joo!
- Stay away from Hye Jung.
She's a really charming girl.
You're going too far. She's my student.
Yes, she's a minor.
She should be protected,
so you need to act properly.
I don't want to drive you.
I changed my mind.
It's okay.
Nothing will be resolved if I do nothing.
-
- Is that you, son?
You need to come here.
If this is about Hye Jung,
don't talk to me about it.
She's your daughter so
who else should I talk to?
She got into some trouble
and she might go to prison.
Whether she goes to prison
or emigrates to
I don't need to know.
Then you should come
because I have cancer.
Stop putting on a show.
I'm crazy for expecting anything.
You have to do something, Kang Mal Soon.
Be strong. Be strong.
Will this heal properly?
Don't worry, ma'am.
We don't need to do a skin graft
for a burn this minor.
Hel...
Oh, Doctor! What are you...
What are you doing here, Grandma?
That young lady in bed is my daughter.
Oh no, what do I do?
I'm so sorry, Doctor.
My granddaughter did a great wrong
against your daughter.
I'm sorry. Are you very hurt?
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- What do you mean you're okay?
Leave!
Can anyone enter VIP rooms like this?
Sorry. Grandma, please leave.
I'm sorry.
There is nothing I can say
to make this better.
Sorry.
Here you go.
Take this thing out of here!
It's 100 percent juice. Try it.
Let's go together.
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh, seriously!
Come and eat rice.
Does someone like me even have
any right to eat rice?
What right does anyone need to eat rice?
Any breathing person can eat.
Here, eat.
I don't want to. I have no appetite.
Have some soup, at least.
It's bone broth so
it should give you strength.
Don't come here anymore.
It'll only upset you to come.
From now on, you live your own life
and I'll live my own life.
You think you can say whatever you want
because you have a mouth?
How can I live off on my own
and you on your own?
You would toss me away if
you were embarrassed of me.
Who says I would?
I'm telling you to live comfortably
and run far away from me.
I'm just a pain so I'm giving you
an opportunity to go.
Even if you don't give me an opportunity,
I can run off whenever I want.
I may have lived a reckless life,
but I've never run away from anything.
Give that to me if you're not
going to eat it, you wench.
It's good.
Whoever made it is a great cook.
You made it for me
so why are you eating it?
Are you hurt at all?
I'm not hurt.
How could you not be hurt?
Are you all right?
Sorry.
I'm so happy.
I'm happy so why do I keep crying?
You should laugh if you're happy.
Why are you crying?
Why are you crying, Grandma?
Because I'm happy.
Oh, my child! Oh dear!
Dad.
You're here.
In Joo was here waiting,
but she got a call and left.
She butts into everything.
I like her. She's very bright.
Did you finish up at school?
I just need to say
goodbye to the students.
How is your health?
Don't treat me like an old senior.
One surgery isn't going to change much.
Apply at Johns Hopkins and Mayo
before going to the US.
Prepare all of the documents.
You have lots to do. You'll be busy.
- Are you happy?
- I am.
- How about you?
- I'm happy too.
What is it? What's wrong with you?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I'm embarrassed to look at you.
I was really petty last time.
What you said did make me
come to my senses.
Can you look after Hye Jung?
- Do you trust me?
- I have to. You're my friend.
You sure are smart.
You get what you want out of this
and draw a clear line between us.
You hit two birds with one stone.
You're home?
Why are you out here?
Did you meet the lawyer?
Yes.
He was very kind, likely because
it was a favor you requested.
I think it will work out.
I hate to bring this up now...
but, I'm moving out.
You went through a lot
because of my granddaughter.
Thank you, Teacher Hong.
You can give me my deposit later.
I'm the one breaking our lease.
Give it to me when our lease is up.
Make sure to contact me when
you get settled in somewhere.
Of course, I will.
- I'm hungry. Give me rice.
- Yeah, okay.
I won't be able to come for a few days.
I told you that you don't
have to come at all.
Stop saying things that you don't mean.
Are you so great?
When you do bad things,
you're just saying...
"Please look at me. Look at me."
Do you think I don't know that?
You're so great,
yet you run a restaurant.
Why not become President of Korea?
You seem lively now that you've had food.
Anyway, I can't come next week.
Aren't you even going to ask me
why I can't come?
What an odd thing to demand.
You could just tell me.
Why can't you come?
I'm getting surgery.
It's stomach cancer and they say
I'll be okay after surgery.
I didn't want you to worry
and that's why I didn't tell you.
I was going to tell you when
I was going into surgery.
Since you're bored in jail,
you might as well worry about me.
That's why I'm telling you.
I thought about waiting for you to
come out before doing my surgery.
But, I wanted to show you.
This is how much your grandma
loves her life.
This is how badly I want to live.
The doctor says that it hasn't spread,
so I should be okay after surgery.
Still, they're cutting up my body and
internal organs so how could it be okay?
- I could die.
- Grandma!
You're just sitting in there.
Not even thinking of coming out,
worrying, and if you end up in prison...
you might not be there when I die.
You won't die. Don't worry.
I know that.
So, you have to live too.
I'll do whatever it takes to save you.
You have to do something
for yourself too.
You didn't start that fire, did you?
Don't take all the blame and speak up.
You should go now.
Get surgery and come back healthy.
Grandma.
Grandma...
Let's go.
I did it.
If you look at Jin Seo Woo's statement
"Cheon Soon Hee lured me to a place
and Yoo Hye Jung was there."
"Yoo Hye Jung wanted revenge for the
post I put up on the school site."
"Yoo Hye Jung demanded that I
delete my post and we fought."
Seo Woo doesn't know
how the fire started.
They were arguing so she doesn't know.
If you did it,
you realize that a person was injured.
It's a minimum of five years in a
Youth Detention Center.
Are you still saying you did it?
I will take her with me.
I'm afraid you can't.
We're re-writing the report.
You crazy girl.
Even if you like your friend,
do you want to become a criminal?
Why do you like someone like that?
You have your parents and siblings.
Do you like her more than them?
I like her more!
Since the day I was born until now,
only Hye Jung treated me with sincerity.
What?
You and Mom always say so.
That you suffer so much
for having a child later in life
and shouldn't have had me.
Our whole family is embarrassed of me.
All my brothers and sister-in-laws.
Hye Jung actually likes me.
She's not embarrassed of me.
I won't leave her alone and leave.
All right... do whatever you please.
I don't know how I had a child like this
who's brought such shame to our family.
Yoo Hye Jung, get out.
Get out of there.
You. Get inside.
Why would you?
I did it.
Don't do this. You can't survive in here.
If you can do it, so can I.
Please let her go. She can't be here.
I asked her to call Seo Woo for me and
she got mixed up in it because of that.
Are you two dating?
You're just full of affection
for each other.
You two can figure out
the love issues, okay?
Dummy, tell them now that it wasn't you.
This isn't going to change anything.
I'm just an unlucky girl
and that's why this happened.
I... didn't leave you and run away.
Just remember that.
Hye Jung or whoever she is...
has been expelled.
What about my homeroom teacher?
Don't even think about
that school anymore.
You should transfer.
That place is not up to our standard.
Go to school near
your grandfather's house.
Here. Eat this.
I feel stuffy in here.
I'm going to step outside.
Where would you go at this hour?
Never mind.
Seo Woo, wake up! Seo Woo, Seo Woo!
Seo Woo, Seo Woo! Wake up!
- Get her on my back. Hurry!
- Okay.
Hurry! Let's get out of here.
Did you escape from the police station?
You know the fire wasn't set on purpose.
It was an accident.
If you told the truth,
it could end without anyone getting hurt.
The important point is that
you called me to that place.
You called me to that place because
you had intent to threaten me.
It's the same thing as setting the fire.
Soon Hee came to the police station
and told them she started the fire.
Seriously, that girl can't be stopped.
Is she crazy?
Why are you doing this?
Things were good with us.
You helped me with my studies--
I get angry... whenever I see you.
I don't know why either.
I start to feel very angry.
What can I do, then?
Should I beg,
though I doubt it will work?
You need try it to see
if it works or not.
Now I know.
It doesn't work.
I was worried I wouldn't be there
for your surgery.
Oh, you scared me!
I was sleeping.
Hey, when did you get out?
How did you get out, huh?
I'm sleepy.
Wait a minute.
I can't be sitting around like this.
This isn't it.
She needs to eat something else.
Hye Jung, eat this. Come on.
Later.
You have to eat it now. Just chew.
You're being admitted into
the hospital today.
You have a good memory.
My child.
- Thank you, Lawyer.
- Your welcome.
Thank you.
Dad!
Thank you, Dad.
Just being in the jail cell one day
was so scary.
Do you think I did it for you?
You brought such shame to our family!
Still, thank you for getting me out.
Once this whole mess is over,
I'm sending you to your aunt in Canada.
I'm prepared for that.
You must be so embarrassed right now
because of a daughter like me.
Dad! Dad, Dad...
I have no excuses.
However, I am sorry I couldn't stay with
you all until the end of this semester.
I trust that you will all
make the right judgments.
Once time has passed,
let's meet again.
Class President.
Attention.
No matter where I end up,
I will remember all of you.
Thank you.
Salute.
What are you doing?
I guess you're worried
about your grandma.
Who says I'm worried?
You've survived all these years.
Cancer's not going to kill you.
You said the doctor told you not to
worry either.
You got expelled from school.
What are you going to do?
I'll tell you my plans once
you're out of surgery.
What kind of trouble are you
going to cause?
Don't you trust me?
You have to act trustworthy
for me to trust you.
Even if I wanted to die,
I can't die because of you.
I'd better keep causing trouble, then.
You'll live a long life.
Stop saying nonsense.
- "Stop saying nonsense."
- Oh my.
Oh, Grandma...
I'll be out soon.
Don't sit around crying or anything.
Go get something to eat.
Mind your own business and just be well.
My doctor is very good at what he does.
My doctor is good looking and smart.
I trust my doctor.
Since when did he become "my doctor"?
He's that girl Seo Woo's father.
You'll be indebted to her for life.
We're heading in now.
Yes, I know. 5:00 p.m.
I'm in surgery now.
I'll finish up quickly.
Wow, it's wider than
I originally thought.
Suction!
Blood pressure is dropping.
Get more blood now!
She's in arrest!
I did my best but it didn't go very well.
What do you mean when you say
it didn't go very well?
Like I said, it didn't go very well.
You should prepare for her funeral
with your parents.
That makes no sense...
My grandma is Kang Mal Soon.
Kang Mal Soon.
Kang Mal Soon would never die.
I'll talk to the adults about this.
Why can't you talk to me?
Why do you need to talk to adults?
My grandma was the closest to me.
Instead of speaking to the person closest
to her, why would you speak to others?
Because adults have common sense.
Our family is all gathered together.
Today is a turning point for our family.
Let's drink to it.
- Enjoy your dinner, Father.
- I will.
The fragrance is lovely.
Tastes great.
Honey, eat lots.
You were born into this world,
so why not live a special life?
Shouldn't you show me something
like that before I die?
This is all your fault.
Why are you even crying?
We shouldn't have left you
with your grandmother.
Right, Honey?
In the end, you managed to
gobble her up too.
You've been expelled from school too.
What are you going to do?
You received money from
the hospital, didn't you?
What money?
Ah, money for the funeral?
Why would you concern yourself with that?
I told you something went wrong
with the surgery.
How could someone who went in
laughing come out dead?
I know they did something wrong!
Stop causing such a fuss.
Since when have you cared
so much about your grandma?
She was an old lady.
Surgery is hard for young people,
let alone a senior.
There can be complications during
surgery and it's possible to die.
"It's possible to die"?
"It's possible to die"!
How could you say that?
Would you say that if your daughter died?
Why would you say that about my Yoo Na?
What about you, Dad?
Don't you have anything to say?
Let's go quietly.
"Quietly," you have to be kidding me.
You killed my grandma, right?
You killed her?
You said she'd live
if you removed the cancer.
Seriously, what's with this girl?
Move aside.
Go on!
You think this hospital will do well?
I won't let you get away with this!
Let her go.
Exactly, what is it that you can do?
I already spoke to your parents.
We've come to an agreement
and they even accepted payment.
I find this regrettable.
I have nothing to feel guilty about
because I did my best.
I took care of things afterward, as well.
If you did your best and a person died,
you should be embarrassed.
Can you forgive yourself
just because you did your best?
If you can find something
showing that I didn't do my best
then I will be punished
however you see fit.
However, I cannot forgive
this kind of reckless behavior.
If you cause a disturbance
in the hospital
I won't let it go next time.
Of course, purely as a student.
I've always helped out Hong Ji Hong,
so I agreed to help you.
I can take care of myself.
It's a school you can go to.
It's in Gangwon-do.
They have dorms there.
I'm going to take my GED exam.
I don't want to be apart from my grandma.
You like Ji Hong, right?
Birds of a feather flock together.
You and Ji Hong live in different worlds.
Ji Hong and I run in the same circles.
When we are together,
it's a win-win situation for both of us.
To get straight to the point,
you'd be a hindrance in Ji Hong's life.
Yoo Hye Jung.
Why didn't you call me?
Why did I have to hear about Granny
from someone else?
Why do I have to tell you
about my grandma?
Of course you should tell me.
What are you planning on doing?
Why do you care what I plan on doing?
Of course I care. You're my student.
Do you care this much about
all of your students?
I'm sorry.
I don't think this is
the right time to talk.
Goodbye.
Should I really go?
Yes.
I don't think I want to see you again.
I can help you.
No.
Go back to the place where you live.
I will go back to where I live.
Do you want to get away from here?
Doctor, here!
We need an MRI so get it ready now.
Good work.
Where is the doctor?
Call the doctor! Call a doctor!
Our boss is here.
Is this the best you can do?
You do it.
You said that neurosurgery is
the most important in the ER.
You said you guys have to look at
all of the patients first.
Is it you? Get over here.
So... what brings you here today?
We're here because he's hurt.
Stop being scared! Stop!
We're people too. Come here.
He's bleeding here.
Hey! What do you think you're doing?
I... I was just nervous.
- What is it?
- Oh, Doctor!
He's the one in charge here. Go on.
Yes, I am in charge.
- You're a doctor?
- Yes.
Hurry up and look.
Let me take a look.
First, let's do an AGAB and routine.
- Then do a CT and and MRI.
- Okay.
Do you think I'm a fool?
You think I don't know that you're trying
to make money off me with useless exams?
Hey! Can't you even do that properly?
Boss is talking to you right now.
Why are you yelling at him
instead of responding?
Should I fold you in half
like an accordion?
No.
You're taking out your anger
on him, right?
No... of course not.
- Clench your jaw.
- No.
Clench your jaw.
Who are you?
A medic?
Can't you tell by looking? I'm a doctor.
This is a place for patients
to receive treatment.
If you're not a patient, please leave.
Who are you to
speak that way to our boss?
I'm the person who will be
treating this patient.
It's my job to create the optimal
environment to treat this patient.
I won't receive treatment from a woman.
Bring a man.
Hey, take her outside.
Yes, Boss.
Hey, just go outside.
Come on, Doctor.
Why not go and take a break?
Senior, I've liked for a long time.
No, that's not it.
Isn't there something fresher?
I have to get that animal
to feel something.
Yoon Do, I've been watching over you
since our hospital training days.
"Watching over"?
I sound like a stalker.
No, let's keep it simple.
It won't work with him if I try too hard.
Jung Yoon Do, you're mine.
Couldn't you wait a bit?
You started eating without me.
You're acting like a girl now?
Ask your boyfriend to do that
when you get one.
I don't think I can eat.
Why would you buy me a meal
in a place like this?
There are lots of nicer places.
There are places that are nicer,
more expensive, and have bad food.
Do you know how famous
and good the food here is?
You wear 20,000 won socks
and you're so thrifty with food.
I've told you before.
The completion of an interior
is the finishing materials.
The completion of an outfit is socks.
Just hurry up and eat.
I said I'm not eating.
Then let's go in.
I have to go to the hospital.
I have something to say.
Then say it.
I know if I try to put it into
pretty words it won't work on you.
So I will give you facts.
Hey, ma'am.
- Me?
- Who else am I looking at?
I'm looking at you, ma'am.
I'm not a "ma'am."
You have very bad eyes.
Sorry, I thought you two were married.
Senior, people must think
we look very good together.
That's not why I thought that.
The guy is treating you with
such disinterest.
A boyfriend wouldn't do that.
Gosh, this woman is really playing
around with my emotions.
By the way, miss,
you sure are very strong.
I'll pay for it.
Why don't you try apologizing first?
Who asked you for money?
I'm sorry. I am sorry.
You did something wrong too.
That was on the verge of falling off.
What would you have done
if someone got injured?
Senior... are you leaving?
Senior, haven't you ever seen a drama?
A man should save the woman,
speak up, and offer money here.
Clean up your own poop, okay?
- Senior!
- Where are you going?
Gosh! How much is it? I can pay for it.
- Are you all right, Ma'am?
- Oh no!
- Oh no.
- What do I do?
Ma'am!
What are you doing? Call an ambulance!
- What do I do?
- Ma'am!
Is the operating room ready?
Yes, room 1.
Why is it room 1 and not 2?
Room 2 is being used by the new fellow.
It was an emergency epidural hemorrhage.
Why is a surgery I don't
know about in progress?
I'm on duty today.
I'm responsible for all
of the surgeries today.
Yes, I know! I told her that
she can't, but she just--
You should have called me.
What the hell are you doing?
I let you have some freedom
and this is what you do?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
You'll take responsibility
for what you're sorry for.
Subtitles by DramaFever