Success comes with a lot of perks.
The way people view you changes.
I'd like to see that one, please.
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
I found out after I succeeded.
Success is meaningful...
only when you have someone to share it with.
I lost the only family I had.
I lost the desire to make another too.
So...
I chose a car over a home.
Still there are things you lose...
but you can never forget.
(Gukil Medical Center)
What do you see?
Isn't it a cerebral edema?
Are you sure?
Be confident. There's swelling. What else?
Subdural hemorrhage.
- Are you sure?
-  Yes.
You're sure about what isn't definitive,
and you aren't sure about what you should be sure about.
You don't know anything.
A 4th-year resident shouldn't confuse...
an extradural and subdural hemorrhage.
You should be embarrassed.
- Prepare for emergency surgery.
-  We can't.
The doctor on call...
We might lose the patient.
We have order and protocol.
This will only get me in trouble.
Are you risking a life to stay out of trouble?
It won't be just me. You'll get chewed out too.
Don't worry about me. Prepare for surgery.
But...
Darn it.
Why is she here when it isn't even her shift?
It's her first day. She should just go home and go to bed.
- Right?
-  You're right.
I just have to do what I'm told.
And why is she so strong?
Did you see her earlier? She could kill an ox.
She flew, tossed a few guys around and kicked them left and right.
Did you see that?
They let her off lightly because she's a woman.
Shouldn't you secure an operating room?
If I do, Dr Jung will kill me.
If I don't, Dr Yoo will kill me.
If I want to stay alive now,
I should obey Dr Yoo.
You were a mess.
What kind of doctor are you? Can you hold a scalpel?
I just gave you a reason to tease me for another year.
Do you like poking wounds?
- Wounds?
-  In high school...
I almost burned in a building a bully dragged me into.
It traumatised me.
This lady collapsed after I touched her.
I'm scared of threatening someone...
just as much as being threatened.
I didn't know someone so cheerful like you had such a past.
You're the first one I told.
I used to have a burn scar here.
It's gone now.
It aches when it rains.
Girls play too rough.
Are you sure you weren't just being intolerable?
I fought her in the name of justice.
I bet she's going in and out of prison.
(Operating Room)
I'll do it.
This is my job.
Hand it over.
You're so fast.
Don't overreact.
I think it's Dr Jung.
(Dr Jung)
Doctor, I...
- You're done here.
-  Okay.
Hello.
Is there an operation room ready?
Yes, room one.
What about room two?
The new fellow's operating right now.
It's an emergency surgery for extradural haemorrhage.
Why is there a surgery I don't know about?
I told her she couldn't do it, but she wouldn't budge and...
Then you should've called me! What were you thinking?
- I apologise.
-  It's fine.
Just take responsibility later.
Why cause trouble for yourself?
He's the only one with a horrible temper.
Can't you play along?
You haven't met the new fellow, have you?
Why?
There will be war.
There can be only one sun.
What got into him?
Did you see the new fellow?
Is it true she beat up some mobsters in the emergency room?
Yes. I heard it was quite the sight.
Game over.
Why didn't I notice such a character?
I never saw her at any conferences.
I should become her friend and make her my bodyguard.
Are you pretty enough to need one?
Someone might think we're friends.
We are friends.
I'm below you because it took me 10 years to graduate college,
but you have to be good to me.
Why are you here?
How did your confession go?
I didn't do it.
He went into emergency surgery.
Don't do it.
Dr Jung enjoys being in control.
He won't like being led in a relationship.
Don't tell him you like him. Make him tell to you first.
I prefer to stay in control...
of both relationships and work.
Don't you think it's the worst time for a confession of love?
I heard he's furious that the new fellow went against protocol.
There will be a showdown after surgery.
I want to be her friend,
but this is a bad start.
I think it'll be a bad everything.
You have to fight for a promotion.
How dare you compare me to someone from an unknown college?
That's why mentors dropped you and you're still a resident.
She won't be a pushover.
Our head hired her.
Doctor.
The surgery went well,
but we have to monitor him as he recovers.
He'll be in the intensive care unit, so wait until he comes round.
The ICU restricts visitors.
Any questions?
Are you married?
I won't answer personal questions.
She liked it.
Don't smile.
I'm worried.
- Pick up my coins.
-  Yes, Sir.
- I'm missing eight of them.
-  Let's hurry. Here's one.
Tell Dr Yoo to see me when she's done.
She's already done.
She was really fast.
She shaved the patient's head too.
I had nothing to do.
Is this how you mock me now?
Accuracy is more important than speed.
What's our priority?
Did she shave the patient?
That's because she doesn't trust others. I mean all of you.
She's your typical neurosurgery psycho.
I apologise.
Will you stop saying that?
Anyway,
tell her to wait.
You're on an extra shift for a week.
Gosh. I totally see a bumpy road ahead.
I can barely handle him,
and we have one more like him now.
Why is my life so messed up?
Stop Dr Yoo from leaving, or I'll kill you.
Oh my goodness.
Where are your manners?
Don't you see I'm changing?
Dr Jung wants you to wait...
until his surgery is over.
Why?
He's very angry.
He is the one who's on call today.
Tell him I'll see him in the morning.
Dr Jung hates it when someone doesn't follow the rules.
What surgery is he on?
A subarachnoid haemorrhage due to a ruptured cerebral aneurysm.
I just hate having to wait.
She smells nice.
(Operating Room, Restricted Zone)
I'm Yoo Hye Jung.
I'll be at Sooni Hawaii right by the hospital.
This girl really has no common sense.
Sorry I didn't pick up earlier
Shy, shy, shy
Cheer up, baby, cheer up, baby
Be a little
It's you.
I was testing you to see if you remember what I taught you.
Did I do a good job?
You did a great job!
You should've just gone home. Why did you come here?
I wanted to go home with you.
Here's a gift for you.
I guess you thought of your grandma again.
Whenever you miss your grandma a lot, I get a gift like this.
This is what I've wanted to have.
- Gosh, stop it.
-  You're the best!
You're amazing. I wish you were a guy.
Then I could've married a doctor.
Gosh, it's too bad.
Didn't people ask you why you were leaving again at midnight?
No one asked me anything, but someone wants to meet me.
Seo Woo?
Why are you talking about Seo Woo?
Her father owns the hospital you're at now.
I heard that she also became a doctor.
You said that you saw her at school too.
How would she feel if she finds out that you've become a doctor?
Gosh, just the thought of it thrills me.
Just the thought of it stresses me out.
What's the best stress reliever?
Eating something sweet is the best!
It's the best indeed!
No matter how much I think about it, I can't understand why.
You mean why I joined Gukil Medical Center?
- We're on the same wavelength.
-  We're meant to be together.
It must be that cranky guy, the one who told you to wait.
Why is he texting you instead of showing up?
Run over here right now.
What did he say? When is he coming?
(Run over here right now.)
Finish this drink and get going.
Poor thing.
(Daejeon Hospital Yoo Hye Jung)
(Dr Yoo Hye Jung, the Department of Neurosurgery at Daejeon Hospital)
She was famous in that area.
I see. This is why the division head recruited her.
A coiling procedure?
"Ligation of a cerebral aneurysm through cranioplasty".
Gosh, this means she and Dr Jung Yoon Do won't get along.
By the way, why did she come here as a fellow?
Goodness, the story isn't coming together.
She's totally my type, though. I love tough women.
Hey, did you finish organising the charts?
It hurts! Yes, I finished it.
What about dressing?
- Well, it has been...
-  Oh, Dr Ahn Joong Dae!
Oh, my! Hello!
- How are things in the ward?
-  Everything is okay.
By the way, why do we always work night shifts?
We should get at least one day off.
- Doing it for the entire week is...
-  Shut it!
Shut it! Of course.
I'll train him again. Be quiet, will you?
Who wants to eat jokbal?
- Me!
-  Me too.
- Let's figure out who'll pay.
-  Shall we?
Chief. Would you like to join us too?
You guys drive me crazy.
You're all old enough. I'd spank you if you were kids.
- So he won't spank us, right?
-  Of course not.
- Thank goodness.
-  I know, right?
You little...
You're adding fuel to the fire.
How are you friends with the fellow when you're one year my junior?
I won't be easy on you any more.
Thank you for being easy on me so far.
- Wake up, guys. Choi Kang Soo.
-  Yes.
Are you checking Mr Lee's vitals on a regular basis?
Yes! Everything is normal!
Ahn Joong Dae!
The same goes for you.
You're in your 2nd year, but you're not any better than 1st years.
Joong Dae, Ahn Joong Dae!
Even your name sounds ridiculous.
Don't act recklessly just because Dr Jin Seo Woo got your backs.
I'm going to head to ICU to make rounds.
I'm giving up sleep to work hard. Learn from me, all right?
Learn!
Jokbal? Goodness.
- Count me in too.
-  See you later!
See you soon.
(Nurse Hyun)
Hello?
I see. Okay.
(Jung Yun Tae)
- I need to go to the ward quickly.
-  See you later.
See you!
Gosh, what now!
(Jung Yoon Do)
(Neurosurgery Specialist, Jung Yoon Do)
Come in.
You walked. I told you to run here immediately.
Didn't you hear that I wanted you to wait?
I did.
And you still left?
Is that your way of insulting me?
- I sent you a message.
-  That you'd wait at a cafe.
Why do I have to meet with you one-on-one outside of the hospital?
I didn't think that far. I guess you could see it that way.
- I apologise.
-  This one is apologising too.
I hate those people who do what they have to apologise for later.
No more talks about you not waiting.
Why did you perform the emergency surgery?
Coming to the emergency room when you're off is a type of ceremony.
It's just what I always do on the first day of work.
I'm not talking about you coming to the emergency room.
Why are you babbling away about your personal stuff no one wants to know?
I couldn't wait. You'll know when you see the record.
You didn't jump on it because you wanted to show off?
I guess you gained a bit of fame by doing whatever you wanted to do...
at the other hospital, but it's different here.
- You sound so sure of it.
-  It's because of the way you act!
I don't really like people with showmanship.
Let's find out at the conference.
Whether the patient actually needed an emergency surgery...
or you just jumped on it to show off.
Please decide whether you'll use honorifics or not and stick to it.
I guess you can't let things slide if they bother you even just a bit.
That's like me.
Honorifics or not.
I'll be mixing it up.
Let's stick to that.
If you performed the surgery when there was enough time to wait,
you'll have to take responsibility that comes with it.
Okay.
If it gets proven that the emergency surgery was necessary,
you'll have to apologise to me.
Are you making a deal with me now?
I'm not under your guidance, and I also apologised to you.
I think you're out of line.
You said you hate people who do things they have to apologise for,
but it looks like you'll have to apologise if that happens.
The fact that you're behaving this way...
shows that you're not interested in becoming a staff member here.
Why did you come here if that is the case?
You said that you don't want to know anything about my personal stuff.
I did,
but I changed my mind because I'm capricious.
Let's hear it.
Tell me why you're here if you don't want to become a staff member.
I don't want to tell anyone who isn't close to me...
about my personal stuff and the way I feel.
Then I won't be able to find out for the rest of my life...
because you and I will never become close.
Your door is open. You didn't go the night duty room...
I'll see you tomorrow then.
Sorry, I didn't know you had a guest.
It's okay. We're done now.
Wait.
We've met before, haven't we?
You two should introduce yourselves.
This is the new fellow, Dr Yoo Hye Jung.
- This is...
-  Yoo Hye Jung?
You're the Yoo Hye Jung I know?
Yes. It's me, Yoo Hye Jung.
You're a doctor now?
Does seeing me still anger you?
Do you know each other?
Wait.
What's your intention for coming here?
Many doctors want to work at Gukil Medical Center.
That fact alone is enough to explain why I'm here.
I can't believe this. How can you be a doctor?
How can you work at the same hospital as me? Well...
How can someone like you be at the same level as me?
So is the fact that I've become successful making you livid?
Then did you expect me to congratulate you?
Do people here know that you used to be a bully?
Did your co-workers at the other hospital know?
I neither advertise nor hide it.
Why? Are you going to post about it on social media this time?
That's your specialty.
You excel in ruining people's lives by using the invisible majority.
Hadn't I done what I did,
Mr Hong's life would've been doomed because of you.
Don't you agree?
You're right.
I wouldn't have come this far if it weren't for you.
Anger was my motivation for success.
All right. Let me ask you one thing then.
Do you still talk to Mr Hong?
I've been too busy to be able to reminisce people in my past.
You're lying again.
You used to lie to me and fool me, telling me you didn't study at all.
How can you believe whatever you're thinking as facts?
Is everything a lie when you can't understand it?
You know that Mr Hong will start working here next week, don't you?
You must've come here knowing that.
No matter what I tell you, you won't believe me.
Leave this hospital.
Then I'll believe you.
I will walk out whenever I choose.
Mr Hong married In Joo.
He's a married man now. Don't even think about it.
What's wrong with my wrist?
Have you been checked?
Stop flirting.
I'm aware that you've been staring for a while.
You're both overly aggressive...
and more defensive than necessary.
How long has your hand shaken like that?
Why do you want to know?
Are you a doctor or something?
Yes, I am.
So what?
Peripheral nerves can be temporarily stimulated...
to cause the hands to tremble.
But brain malfunctions can also be the cause.
I am only 25 years old.
I'm too young for brain malfunctions.
I know you're a doctor, but aren't you overstepping your boundary?
You're right.
I think it's a basic trait that all doctors need to possess.
You're a smooth talker, aren't you?
I think you would've made a great news anchor too.
I'm sorry if I offended you.
Miss!
I need a cushion.
Are you a doctor?
Yes. I'm a licensed neurosurgeon.
- Do you have a first-aid kit?
-  Yes.
There should be Lorazepam inside. I need it quickly, please.
Okay.
Please hold her down.
When will we be landing?
She doesn't have much time.
Have you contacted the emergency centre at Gukil Medical Center?
Yes, emergency response will be waiting at arrival.
She needs to be on the operating table within four and a half hours.
Otherwise, she'll die.
How do you feel?
Please talk to me. How do you feel?
Of course I don't feel good.
I don't know why I'm here.
Based on your statements, the surgery seems to be a success.
How could "not feeling good" be a success?
You are a whiner, aren't you?
It's funny to hear someone who lives off bothering others whine.
Are you trying to kill me by making my brain rupture with anger?
Even if the surgery goes well, the surgical site can bleed out.
You can fall unconscious, develop a speech impediment,
become paralysed or have a seizure. Those are the risks.
But since I can see you whining,
I'm happy that you're okay.
Why didn't you tell me that from the get-go?
Observe him a bit longer and get a CT scan if there are anomalies.
If his status doesn't fluctuate, move him to a room.
Will do.
Get some rest, Boss. I have to run along.
Thank you.
What did you say?
I said thank you.
I couldn't hear him. What did he say?
He said thank you.
I see.
Thank you for waking up.
You pretended not to hear what I said, didn't you?
Of course, it took a lot of effort to earn that.
Do you not remember how you behaved last night?
Gosh, you hold grudges, don't you?
Yes, I'm quite good at it.
So from now on, I hope you will follow all my medical advice.
Rest well.
(Flight Emergency)
Yes?
Doctor.
A patient was discovered with a cerebral haemorrhage...
during a flight. She's on-route in a helicopter.
One of our doctors diagnosed her.
She needs an operation immediately.
They need a neurological fellow to wait by the helipad...
so the patient can be transferred for surgery immediately.
When will the patient be arriving?
She'll be here soon.
Go prepare the operating room.
- Tell Yeong Gook to come up.
-  Okay, Doctor.
25 years old, female. Mental stupor.
Pupils are 5mm and 3mm.
There's no pupillary reflex on the right eye.
What is the presumed diagnosis?
It's suspected to be cerebral haemorrhage.
She's showing signs of status epilepticus.
The patient is intubated, and her vitals are unstable.
What is the time of the first visible symptoms?
- That's...
-  What time?
Doctor, I am friends with Dr Jin Seo Woo.
Dr Pi Yeong Gook.
Are you saying you want to be friends?
The hospital is not a place to make friends.
Are you trying to get away with not knowing the patient's condition?
- I am sorry.
-  If you're going to work with me,
- you'd better come to your senses.
-  Okay.
He said they'll be here soon.
(Gukil Medical Center)
- You're a resident, right?
-  Yes.
I've heard a lot about you.
- Take a CT scan right away.
-  Okay.
How long has it been since she went unconscious?
It's been 4 hours and 45 minutes.
Have you been well?
Are you married yet?
No.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Then we're set.
80cc is confirmed for the right brain.
Will you be performing a navigated aspiration?
(Navigation equipment assists with checking the bleeding spot.)
I'll be performing a freehand aspiration.
- What?
-  Doctor.
She's been unconscious for five hours.
It takes more than an hour to prepare for aspiration.
The patient will die.
- That's too dangerous.
-  That's why I'm doing it.
Contact the Department of Anaesthesiology and prepare the OR.
It's already prepared.
You're coming in?
What are you? You don't seem like a resident.
Your gown pockets are empty.
Are you trying to catch up with me right now?
Yes. I can't?
Is it necessary? I mean the freehand aspiration.
- We can drop the blood pressure...
-  Hye Jung.
I looked for you whenever I came to Korea.
Is In Joo well?
Why are you asking me about In Joo?
You married her.
I'm married? Since when?
- Thank you.
-  You're welcome.
How are you feeling, Sir?
Why are you asking, you imbecile!
Has he been like this?
Yes.
Consult the Department of Psychiatry.
What's wrong with your attire?
I told you not to walk around in an operating gown.
I told you not to degrade the Department of Neurosurgery.
I am sorry, Sir.
Your hair...
What do you need? You must be here for a reason.
Prof. Hong, the new doctor,
will be performing aspiration without navigation.
So what? You want everyone to go watch?
Is that why you're making a fuss?
Which operating room is he in?
How will he know where to place the catheter without navigation?
Have you seen anyone do this?
That's what doctors did before navigation was invented.
Place the monitor on my left, please.
Scalpel.
Over here.
What happens if the catheter is placed on the wrong location?
Don't mention it.
I don't even want to think about it.
The patient came in too late. She's dead regardless.
- Is the blood extracted yet?
-  They haven't inserted it yet.
Please work.
Pull it.
Prepare the syringe.
They failed.
He's so talented!
He's impressive. I bet women are lining up.
He married to his school colleague.
He's not married. Stop assuming that the fine man is taken.
I heard he was married.
You heard that too, right?
You were the one who told me.
That's right. I did.
You should check your sources.
Don't be doubting everything I tell you because I'm wrong once.
He's not married, but he could be a womaniser.
- Bingo.
-  Maybe he lives with his partner.
Are you boys having fun?
Don't you have a conference to prepare for?
That's right.
Those two seem to know each other.
Do you know them too?
- Should I close her up?
-  Can you?
Yes.
- It's what I always do.
-  I've never seen you do it.
I only believe what I see.
Then you can do it.
I'll trust you. Go for it.
Good job, Doctor.
Good job, everyone.
Dr Kim.
You certainly made a grand entrance.
This is awkward.
Why don't you meet everyone and begin work today?
Are you a cruel employer? I'm taking my vacation days off.
Whatever you want.
Say hello to everyone at the conference.
All right. I'll see you then.
- Where are you going?
-  I have to check on something.
Why are you back?
I'm here to check if you're doing a good job.
I have to confirm your skills before I trust you completely.
Your suspicion fits the neurosurgeon stereotype perfectly.
Are you laughing?
You should laugh when it's funny.
You're good.
You're very good.
Cut.
Teach me how to insert a catheter without navigation.
Your enthusiasm to learn is nice,
but you've become a brat.
Is asking for something the first thing you do after our reunion?
You sound like you consumed a truckload of cheese.
Are you calling me cheesy?
Stop laughing.
You're acting a bit distant.
What's the matter?
You did that during high school. You rejected my helping hand...
and disappeared on a motorcycle with some sleaze.
How is he doing?
Did you look for me to ask me that?
I wanted to know how you were doing.
Look. I've been working for a while now.
I understand why you're doing this.
I've never been married,
but I've seen many male doctors volunteering for night duty...
to avoid going home to their wives.
I've also witnessed many affairs.
Why are you telling me this?
Please be kind to In Joo.
Why are you bringing her up?
Marriage is sacred.
Yes, you're right.
What's wrong with her?
So if I marry In Joo,
our vows should be considered sacred.
But why does she insist on marrying me off?
Why do I keep talking to myself?
(President Jin Myung Hoon)
- Good morning.
-  Good morning.
I'll take that.
Consider this place your home.
Would you leave trash on the floor of your own home?
- Warn the cleaning manager.
-  Yes, Sir.
President Jin.
Good morning, Sir.
Are you ready for the meeting?
- I'll escort him from here.
-  Okay, Sir.
Do you have the votes of the board of directors?
Yes, I have more than half.
They promised to vote for you, but you never know.
Not even 40 years of friendship amounts of much.
I'm not sure how they he can treat you like this despite my goodwill.
I've respected him as the founder, but not any more.
I'm preparing for his impeachment.
We need to be quick.
People trust Chairman Hong, and the odds are against us.
They're trying to oust me by attacking you.
They want both of us out.
Since my appointment, the hospital has been seeing profit.
Under what pretences can they oust me?
They're against the Senior Citizens' Health Centre...
and accusing us of trying to turn this into a family-run enterprise.
There's plenty of nonsense.
All the profit will be coming from senior citizens soon.
They'll realise that I'm right after some time.
The doors are opening.
(The 2016 56th Directors' Meeting)
I'm here to ask for your consent for the Senior Citizens' Centre.
People now enjoy 100-year lifespans.
The Senior Citizens' Centre will be at the core of our business.
I admire your passion...
to personally make the presentation.
There are plenty of local health centres for the elderly.
Why must we expand in that direction?
Also, what's the point in building a health centre...
for VVIP senior citizens?
Frankly, it's to make profits.
The government won't approve the medical fees we ask for.
If we keep pestering the public,
people will neglect our institution due to the infighting.
Should doctors starve to death?
Your line of thinking is extreme.
We're bringing in profit outside of medical treatments.
They're also being generated from business incidentals.
Building a health centre for senior citizens...
simply for profit...
Is something that businessmen do.
Managing hospitals nowadays is a downhill enterprise.
If we stop now, we'll fall.
We'll lose everything unless we expand.
Hospitals are not corporations.
Making money is nice, but we must give things up...
for the interest of the public.
I know I'm being direct. But doesn't the word "bankruptcy"...
faze you at all?
That's why we cut the budget of the Burn Centre by half.
Are you planning to divert...
the budget cut into building a geriatric centre?
President Jin, do you run your hospital with that mindset?
Are you planning to close every department that is unprofitable?
We are doctors first and foremost.
If we lose our dignity as physicians,
then it's better for our hospital to shut its doors.
Let's calm down. We need to continue the conference.
Let's vote.
(Kim Tae Ho)
Until when must we accommodate for his every whim?
We only lost by a small margin.
He should just relax if he doesn't understand business.
Why does that old man have to be so ridiculously stubborn?
So are you going to give up the Senior Centre?
I'll never give up.
Doctors these days are so pathetic,
especially the ones who attended top schools.
They studied their whole life under parental guidance,
so they don't have a mindset to take risks.
That's precisely why I prefer third-rate graduates.
They understand life.
They know what being trampled on is like.
They say every man has his own trade.
Who knew that you'd have such great business acumen?
Everything you touch becomes profitable. No one can follow you.
We should mobilise quickly...
and oust that old geezer.
I realised the urgency at the conference.
It won't be easy though.
As you know, Doo Sik even brought Ji Hong on board.
What have you been doing, Father?
Why are you letting Chairman Hong win?
What do you lack?
You little... How dare you!
I'm not letting him win!
I'm showing him my respect since we've been friends for life.
You don't even know what you're talking about.
I couldn't even take a day off.
I know.
It'd be great...
to build an organ transplantation centre here.
Our future. In other words, life extension and the quality of life...
will be decided by organ transplantation.
President Jin wants to build a geriatric centre.
We already have one.
He wants to make more money.
He does know how to run a business,
but he's tacky.
Father, stop thinking about the hospital and hang out with me.
How about we have dinner together?
I'll say goodbye to my co-workers quickly...
and head home to unpack and make something delicious.
Shall we?
This breeze feels nice.
(Neurosurgery Conference, Gukil Medical Center)
(Gong Byeong Doo, 32, Dr Yoo Hye Jung)
This 32 year old male patient was assaulted...
and rushed to the emergency room with scalp lacerations.
He arrived conscious with a normal mental state.
The CT scan indicated...
an acute extradural haemorrhage the width of a bone.
An emergency operation was performed immediately.
It didn't look like his extradural haemorrhage required surgery.
Why was the operation rushed?
He was convulsing...
You mentioned that he was young with a stable mental state.
If he regained consciousness after his convulsions,
shouldn't you have waited to observe his condition?
Those moments of recovery were lucid intervals.
I decided on surgery after the patient fell into stupor again.
According to the CT scan,
the haematoma shouldn't have affected his mental state.
Maybe there was an error with his mental assessment.
There was no mistake.
Then the cause of the patient's stupor must be something else.
The scans should've been consulted if his condition was worsening.
The operating field revealed a continual haemorrhage...
from a ruptured middle meningeal artery.
The extracted haematoma exceeded 50cc.
The operating field is a surgeon's discretionary domain.
If your suspicions continue,
I cannot no longer reveal the details behind my decision.
That is correct, the operating field is under a surgeon's discretion.
If we don't respect our professional boundaries,
no one else will.
Let's wrap it up now.
I'd like to introduce someone to you.
Professor Hong Ji Hong.
Come on out.
He's joining our department as a staff member.
I'm sure all of you have heard about Prof. Hong.
He's a world-renowned intracranial tumour expert.
I went through hoops to bring him on board.
I am Hong Ji Hong. It's very nice to meet you all.
Dr Jin Seo Woo.
- Yes.
-  Whose guidance are you under now?
Dr Jung Yoon Do.
Prof. Hong and Dr Jung.
Decide whom you'd like for your assistant...
between the two fellows, Dr Yoo and Dr Jin, and let me know.
Dr Yoo and Dr Jin.
If you'd like to be trained by a specific staff member,
score some brownie points so that you can be chosen.
Gosh, I'm hungry.
- Is this usually on Mondays?
-  Yes, usually.
- Unless anything special comes up.
-  I see.
Mr Hong!
Oh, yes. It's been a long time.
I saw Hye Jung too. What's going on?
I was very impressed by your thesis on "Neurosurgery".
Come on.
Seeing you guys is making me reminisce the old days.
Do you two know each other?
She was my student. Dr Yoo too.
Seriously?
So you taught two neurosurgeons?
They're making me so proud as their teacher.
I look forward to working with you.
Likewise.
Dr Jin. Are you trying to lobby him...
so that you can work under him?
She doesn't even need to because I already know her.
Tell me if you want to work under me.
I still have a lot to learn from Dr Jung.
All right, then.
Let's have fun working together.
That'd be great.
You have to maintain a good relationship with Prof. Hong.
I know that you have good rapports with everyone,
but there's something I'm planning that involves him.
Yes.
Dr Kim.
I'd like to talk to you about something.
(Office of Vice President)
I'd like to know why you recruited Dr Yoo Hye Jung.
I don't want to be biased against her education,
but she went to a third-rate university and...
You shouldn't criticise her based on her education.
As you know, your father Dr Jin Myung Hoon...
is running Gukil Medical Center despite graduating...
from a university outside of Seoul.
When we hire fellows here, we strictly look at...
their talent as doctors.
And that makes Dr Yoo a good fit for the role.
She was already working as a staff member at another hospital.
She must have an ulterior motive for choosing to come here.
I'm curious about it as well.
Why did Dr Yoo follow me?
Being a successful staff member at that age isn't an easy thing.
She'll also make a lot less here.
Dr Yoo. You're not seeing any outpatients today, right?
No, I just need to make rounds at the ICU.
Whom would you like to be trained by first?
I'll just let them choose. I don't want to think about it.
You're cool.
What's cool?
Nothing. You're just cool.
You're making me think of the old days.
I think I treated my teacher in high school...
like how you're treating me now.
I hope you're not still thinking that I made a wrong decision.
I didn't see the operation field with my own eyes.
Hence, I can't really apologise.
I thought you'd be difficult, but you're actually not.
Are you insulting me right now?
Being persistent like that makes you look so childish.
I was nervous thinking that you'd be difficult,
but it looks like I can relax a little.
- I beg your pardon?
-  Even if you didn't witness it,
you should still trust people more.
What you just did made you look so lame.
She called him lame.
Who are you really?
You beat up that gangsters. Do you think you're one of them?
Why are you speaking so harshly?
Why are you so rude to me?
You were rude to me first.
I always give back what I get.
Dr Yoo.
I'm sorry about the extradural haemorrhage surgery.
Now we're equal.
For your information,
I also always make sure to give back what I get.
What if it's because of Prof. Hong?
Prof. Hong?
I can't tell you any more because it concerns her privacy.
However, I trust that letting Dr Yoo go...
would be the best thing for the Department of Neurosurgery.
Are you intimidated by Dr Yoo?
Are you scared?
Why would I be?
The girl who comes from poor family and some unknown college...
is now at the same position as you.
You come from the family of three-generation-long doctors.
So relax.
People can't grow alone.
Dr Yoo will become a good competitor.
You are aware that they are hiring professors next year, right?
There's only one spot.
You made Dr Yoo my rival.
I will show you that you've made a mistake.
Saying that you have private matters you can't talk about is...
much more of a personal attack than saying that there are private...
matters you can talk about.
I didn't know you had that side.
(Access Denied)
(You do not have the credentials to access the patient's information.)
Doctor.
Aren't you going to make your round?
Can't we check all the records of our hospital patients?
I could in the previous hospital.
The information about VIPs or celebrities...
is not open to us doctors.
Whose records are you trying to look up?
My grandmother's.
Why?
What do I have to do to check the medical records?
Go and ask the Administrative Office.
There has to be something.
What happened to her grandmother?
(Gukil Medical Center)
You can't check the record of Ms Kang Mal Soon.
It's high security level information.
In order to check it, you need to fill out the form first.
But we can't guarantee it.
Your collar is rolled.
Will I get arrested for sexually harassing her if I do this?
It is sexual molestation. If you do with words, it's harassment.
Is that right?
Let's trust each other.
We shouldn't make the world such a cruel place.
I won't accuse you.
You're an interesting young lady.
Is Gukil Medical School your alma mater?
No, I attended a provincial school.
Good luck.
Our hospital is the land of opportunity for doctors like you.
It may be a small thing, but it can still show...
if you are a good doctor material or not.
- Good luck.
-  Thank you.
Thank you.
Doctor.
By any chance, didn't you leave with Dr Yoo awhile ago?
I didn't get the numbers of the doctors yet.
Do you want me to give it to you?
- What's your name?
-  I am Choi Kang Soo.
Kang Soo. I like you.
Tell me if you have any further questions.
When it comes to Dr Yoo,
I am the one who knows the most in the Department of Neurosurgery.
I am sorry it happened.
But I did everything I could, so I have no guilt.
I think I dealt with it well too.
If you prove that I didn't really do my best,
then I will get punished the way you want.
Dad, it's done. Come.
Aren't we supposed to eat jjajangmyeon on first day of moving?
Pasta is much easier to make.
- I'll make that next time.
-  No. No. I love pasta.
It feels awkward because it's just us two guys.
What's awkward about it? Why can't you be happy with me?
Do you still talk to In Joo?
No.
I heard she's divorced.
I feel sorry to In Joo.
It would've been so nice if you two had gotten married.
You would've been very understanding to each other.
You are immoral.
In Joo!
In Joo! Gosh!
Let's go in. You will catch a cold.
I thought it would work if I try hard.
I tried so hard, and all you say is...
that it's not going to work?
I am sorry.
You don't say it,
but I know who you like.
Do you want me to say who it is?
(Yoo Hye Jung)
I heard you still beat up people.
I heard everything from Kang Soo.
Why did you ask me to meet up? I see you at the hospital.
There's something that's been bothering me.
I had to get it over with.
What is it?
Why do you keep making me a married man?
I didn't make you a married man. It was your choice.
You've changed.
Why do you listen to other people?
I am not married.
Okay. You're not married.
- I'm going now.
-  Gosh.
I had made my mind after I got beaten up by you.
I made my mind that I won't get beaten up by you again.
I give up!
The unresolved past always finds you again,
whether it's love or hatred.
(Doctors)
You have access to all the medical records of the hospital, right?
I need to know everything that happened during the surgery.
I need to send Doo Sik home now.
I saw a strange person.
Call Dr Yoo.
She's not answering. Should I go and check?
You realise how precious things are only after losing them.
Are you okay?