(Episode 5)
I heard you still beat up people.
I heard everything from Kang Soo.
Why did you ask me to meet up? I see you at the hospital.
There's something that's been bothering me.
I had to get it over with.
What is it?
Why do you keep making me a married man?
I didn't make you a married man. It was your choice.
You've changed.
Why do you listen to other people?
I am not married.
Okay. You aren't married.
I'll get going now.
Gosh.
I had made up my mind after I got beaten up by you.
I made my mind that I won't get beaten up by you again.
You body moves on reflex when you're in danger...
in a way you learned and practised or you are used to.
We learn the habits we need your body to know when we are young.
Once your childhood passes,
nothing can take its place.
I give up!
Is this a mount?
Yes.
Can you get off of me?
What?
Yes, of course.
I'm sorry.
Oh gosh.
I was too focused on winning.
Did I hurt you?
- No, I'm fine. - That's a relief.
It would've been nice...
if you hadn't fought back.
I'm never going to fight against you again.
Me, neither.
- Why won't you fight me? - No reason.
Gosh...
Are you okay?
You're too strong.
Do you hear me?
I got rid of the tube as soon as she regained consciousness.
What brings you here?
I feel responsible for her.
- What is your name? - That witch...
Do you understand me? What's your name?
That witch...
Please state your name first.
Woo... Myung... Mn.
It's okay. She just has mental drowsiness.
Please lift your right arm.
Please lift your leg.
She's following your instructions.
You have to get plenty of rest.
Give her 100cc of mannitol every six hours.
She could get worse if her blood pressure drops.
Aim her systolic pressure to be between 160 and 180.
- Okay. - Her artery won't burst again.
So don't worry and keep the nimodipine.
If she has a severe headache, give her acetaminophen.
If it doesn't improve, give her half a bottle of ample morphine.
I like you.
- What? - I didn't know I'd do it like this.
I lost my momentum, but I want to say it.
What is it?
I liked you when you liked someone else,
and even after you broke up.
It wasn't love at first sight, though.
- You silly thing. - What?
You know the type of women I like.
I do.
It's time you stop getting fooled.
I don't think I was fooled.
I grew up as much as I loved and was hurt by those women.
You grew up? Nonsense.
Who put up with all your drunken whining?
- Why do you like women with a past? - I wonder myself.
Why do I like such women?
I'm cheerful, come from a nice family...
did well in school,
- and I'm pretty... - Gosh. That's enough.
Find someone else.
You have weird taste.
Yes, I do.
Why do you care what woman I pick?
Is it about Hye Jung?
Why are you mentioning her?
She bothers you.
You met in school. Were you rivals?
- Why would I be her rival? - See?
She seems to be someone with a past, but...
- Do you care about her? - Of course I do.
Is this love at first sight?
- Do you know what she's like? - You hate her, don't you?
I can't let you be my girlfriend,
but I can send her away.
- For my sake? - Why would it be that?
It's for my sake. I don't like having her around.
She lacks skill and shows off. And she's rude.
And she talks back, too.
You can't kick her out. Our head likes her.
A cerebral aneurysm case is all I need.
Have you seen...
reality that goes beyond imagination?
I have.
In you.
I thought you'd be fine,
but I didn't imagine you'd be a doctor.
The world's still a decent place.
I climbed society's ladder by studying.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Shall I teach you how to insert a catheter without navigation?
Then work for me starting next week.
I'll come in tomorrow, but it's not an official work day.
I just have to make rounds to see my patients.
Okay.
Go on inside.
You can leave. I can manage now.
Do you know what you must learn before you insert a catheter?
What?
Learn to accept protection.
It seems like nothing,
because you can do everything.
I can protect myself.
People who grew up in a protective environment...
trust themselves and society, and that's the basis of life.
It can protect you...
when your life's in turmoil.
Only children needs protection.
You can't change or compensate for the past.
You just accept it.
You still don't listen.
I paid a huge price to learn that lesson.
Incidents can't be changed,
but your heart can.
I don't know where to start and how much to teach you.
I need to write up a whole curriculum.
- What for? - For no reason.
Go on inside. I'll watch you go upstairs.
Don't turn around.
You never listen.
Mr Hong.
Soon Hee.
Congratulations on your marriage.
No. No.
No?
Oh dear.
Sorry. Are you divorced, then?
I said no.
You've changed.
She gossips.
You don't know her, then.
She never keeps anything from her best friend.
Right?
Yes.
How was your day?
- Shoot. - Hurry up.
It always falls out.
I didn't tell you to sit.
Did you just wake up?
No.
Come closer.
Why did you lie?
You just woke up.
I didn't.
Look at your shirt.
Anyone can miss a few buttons.
This doesn't prove that I just woke up.
Look at you. Do you think I'm an idiot?
I told you. If you make a mistake, admit to it.
I woke up, dozed off,
and then woke again when you called.
Why did you doze off? Why?
Where's Yeong Gook?
(Neurosurgery's Dog)
Mr Lee Ki Cheol's lab results are normal,
and we switched to oral medication.
Good. How's the hematoma?
Down to 20cc.
Am I your alarm clock?
- Were you asleep? - No.
I checked on Ms Do Yun Gyeong before Prof. Hong's rounds.
How could you?
I covered for you so you wouldn't...
Okay. I give you that.
You, scan this.
You borrowed this from me yesterday.
I'm so poor that I can't afford to buy the book, okay?
Okay. I'll scan it for you.
You go onto the National Weather Service site...
and download the weather for the past few years.
Is it for your thesis?
Why do you ask such obvious questions?
-Joong Dae, Joong Dae, Joong Dae. - What?
He's asking stupid questions because you used to.
Well...
It's not that.
I asked because I have a lot to do already...
without having to help with your thesis.
You need to show by example.
Okay.
He ignores anything he can't deny.
- Is Ms Hwang Jeong your patient? - Yes.
She had a cerebral aneurysm.
It was small and not a risk,
but it ruptured on a cold day three months ago.
Ask if I can mention her in my thesis.
Chief.
Why can't Yeong Gook compile the data for you?
Why are you dragging little innocent me into this?
I have too much to do.
And I don't?
You jerk.
How come all that beating hasn't tamed you one bit?
Are you a stallion?
Just do as you're told.
I'll do it.
I'll get the data you need.
Did you see that? Be more like him.
This comes from experience.
- I'll do my best. - Good.
This is how I survive.
Point taken.
Keep me out of it.
What are you talking about?
Are you ready for the rounds?
Don't let me hear that the professors found fault in you.
Prof. Hong,
Ms Do Yun Gyeong's hematoma is a bit bigger.
Not by too much. Try the urokinase irrigation every six hours.
- Okay. - Don't extract too much.
Close it if you see any cerebrospinal fluid.
Okay.
You're here.
- I'll leave soon. - The afternoon rounds?
I'll be here for that.
Why don't you just stay?
I'm going to enjoy my rare and valuable holiday.
Doctor Yoo decided to work with me.
When did you two agree on that?
Are you sure you're on holiday?
I didn't want to lose her to Doctor Jung.
I like that attitude.
Giving and losing are two very different things.
- Shall we have tea? - I have a meeting.
We have too many of them.
Wait, have you seen your office?
I'll take you there.
Bye.
(Gukil Medical Centre June Revenue Report)
General Surgery made the most this month.
Well done, Professor Baek.
I'll increase the limit on your company card.
The more you make, the more you deserve.
Isn't that the advantage of capitalism?
Thank you, Sir.
Professor Kim, our vice president.
General Surgery made 10 billion,
and Neurosurgery only made 4.6 million.
So what if you're famous?
How will you increase the revenue of your department?
I hired one more doctor.
Prof. Hong's back from Johns Hopkins. Things will improve.
Will one more doctor increase sales?
What vice president argues with how the hospital is run?
Why are you against a centre for the elderly?
In the long run, I think...
an organ transplantation centre...
If you keep talking that gibberish, hand over your vice presidency.
We need to survive to develop.
We lost 23.5 million last year.
We earned 100 million through other activities.
That's what putting the cart before the horse means.
Our main source of income should be the hospital, not the cafeteria.
I'm cancelling all of your staffs' holidays for this month.
See more patients and do more surgeries.
Forget about holidays.
Nice putting!
Are you not feeling your best today or are you just getting old?
I'm not feeling the greatest today.
We feel this way often because we're ageing.
Shouldn't we start thinking about retiring soon?
We should. Let's solidify the foundation...
and hand it down to our children.
Myung Hoon impresses me. I'm not saying this because he's my son.
He's very good at running the hospital.
He's good, but let's change it up.
Why do we need a change when he's doing a good job?
We need to develop talent.
Organisational decay is inevitable when we rely on one person.
Are you thinking the vice president of Neurosurgery, Kim Tae Ho?
Or Ji Hong?
You already made him a foundation director.
Don't shake up the top. The ones below them will keep them in check.
Myung Hoon owns the subsidiary.
He probably won't even have to work with the money it earns him.
He loves money, right?
Let's not talk about this any more.
We do need a change.
Did you just belittle my son?
Are you saying that my son is an incompetent doctor...
who is just greedy for money?
(Gukil Medical Centre June Revenue Report)
(Department of Neurosurgery)
- Father, you're here. - Yes.
General Surgery's revenue is the highest.
Why is the patient turnover rate so low for Neurosurgery?
I actually gave them a hard time about it today.
Good.
Give this to President Jung when you see him later.
What's this?
It's about Doo Sik.
I think now is time to send him home.
Hey, don't pick them up yet!
Wait, 1, 2, 3, 4...
Darn it!
- Hello, Doctor. - Hello, Doctor.
Gosh, please don't do that.
People will think that I'm your boss.
- Would you like some? - No, thank you.
It's grape flavour.
Do not let your guard down.
- Lay low and don't cause trouble. - Yes, Boss.
How do you feel?
- I'm all right. - You must rest.
Also, do you really need all those guys out there?
I have a lot of enemies.
If words spread about my condition,
many of them will come find me here.
Avoiding those situations would be the best if it is possible,
but I've learned that what's bound to happen will eventually do.
- You checked his vitals, right? - Yes, everything is normal.
Get some rest.
Rest well, Boss.
Well then. Have a great day, Doctor.
- Have a great day! - Have a great day!
- Do we have canned peaches left? - We finished it.
Keep checking to make sure that his surgical wound is healing well.
- Shall I keep dressing it too? - Of course.
We'll see how he recovers for a week and discharge him next week.
- Where are you headed now? - ICU. What about you?
Just a moment.
(General Surgery, Tae Yang)
Eun Ho!
Wake up, Eun Ho!
- Please take him to the CT room. - Sure.
Where's the patient in semicoma?
Eun Ho, open your eyes.
- Eun Ho. - I'll take a look at him.
He left to school and fainted all of a sudden.
Please save him, Doctor.
Ma'am, please calm down. Let me have a look at him.
- You can take him now. - Okay.
Eun Ho. Eun Ho!
Gosh, this is annoying.
Hey!
It's stupor, not semicoma!
Neurosurgery would have to take care of him either way.
I was so worried!
Goodness, I must've been out of my mind.
I have no idea why I believed that idiot in General Surgery...
who can't even do a proper mental assessment.
Hey, where are you going now?
You said the emergency room can't function without you neurosurgeons.
So just stay here, you kid!
- Let go. Let go of me. - I don't want to.
- You better let go of me now. - You better treat me respectfully.
- Be polite, will you? - Let go!
Do you know today's date?
I miss that witch.
Who is she?
She misses her terribly. Why aren't you guys bringing her here?
You'll meet her when you go down to your room.
It doesn't sound like you have fond memories of her.
You should see her when you feel better.
You're a smart young lady. I mean Doctor.
You're doing well,
so we should be able to move you to your room soon.
Ma'am, please cheer up.
It looks like you really care about that patient.
You always come with me when I check on her.
You must have a lot of time on your hands.
- I should give you more work. - You're crazy.
You just can't bear to watch anyone relaxing.
(Choi Kang Soo)
Yes, what is it?
It's a 15-year-old boy. He fainted on his way to school.
His right pupil is dilated by 4mm. His motor response is a bit slow.
I'll be right there.
What's going on?
- Kyung Joon, come with me. - Yes, Sir.
His daughter sac is ruptured. It'll be a complicated case.
Prepare the surgery, and call Dr Yoo.
Pardon? Not Dr Jin?
I want Dr Yoo to assist me in all of my surgeries from now on.
Why? Why is that?
War has finally begun.
- Where are you going? - Hello.
I need to prepare for Dr Jung's cerebral aneurysm surgery.
Really? Why didn't you report to me about it?
It looks like Dr Jung has a new assistant now.
The war between the two of them has finally begun.
War?
I'll cast my vote on Dr Yoo's leaving.
What about you?
Didn't you hear that I want you to get ready for the surgery?
Yes, I heard.
Then why are you still dressed like that?
As far as I know, Dr Jin is your assistant.
From today, you'll be assisting me directly as my trainee.
What do I need to be trained on by you?
I'm not interested in ligation...
of a cerebral aneurysm through cranioplasty.
I have enough experience with it.
You're going to only use the coiling procedure?
You can't do that as long as I'm here.
As I told you previously, I'm not under your guidance.
So you refuse to work under me.
Then you should operate on him yourself.
Then I'll approve you.
What if my surgery is a success?
I'll do whatever you want.
I'll do it.
If you fail, you might get expelled from this hospital.
I have a lot of respect for Dr Kim, so I was going to let it slide.
But you act like a punk.
You neither understand nor respect the hierarchy here.
If you have an attitude problem when you're incompetent as a doctor,
it only makes sense that you leave.
How is it going?
Oh, it's you. It's going great.
Is there a gym here?
Yes. President Jin thinks that those things are important.
The amenities here are great.
You sound cynical about it though.
Those amenities aren't free.
Nothing comes free in life.
Are they picking at you about your performance?
They peck at me like birds.
- They're pressuring me so much. - Goodness.
I should give him some credit though.
He makes practical choices as a president.
He understand what people want in this age.
When others are fighting about old values,
he goes after money.
That's normal. The situation in the States isn't any different.
Exactly.
No one in Neurosurgery is allowed to take time off this month.
Our revenue is lower than that of General Surgery's.
We have to increase the patient turnover rate by discharging...
patients quickly in order to boost our revenue.
I really don't want to pressure my doctors about it.
Then just deal with it yourself and don't vent to us.
I can't be the only one stressing out. At least you should know.
You once told me...
that life would be easy if people could be categorised as good or bad.
You said no values can beat our desire for sustenance.
We're all humans after all.
Some people must do what they want even though it could kill them.
Both you and I belong to that category. Aren't I right?
Are you teasing me now or what?
Just a second.
(Neurosurgery, Jin Seo Woo)
Yes, Seo Woo.
I'm here.
What's up?
Do you think a fellow can do this surgery?
This condition is quite critical.
A regular cerebral aneurysm surgery is complicated enough.
But this case has a ruptured daughter sac.
This surgery can't be carried out by a fellow. Are you doing it?
No, Hye Jung is doing it.
Who decided that?
Who decides who gets to perform a surgery like this?
I'm supposed to train Dr Yoo.
You can't take her without my permission.
I'm aware that your work starts next week.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Isn't that when it starts?
Here's the update.
My work starts today.
So your fellowship arrangement is void.
Dr Yoo is not going to assist me. She will be performing the surgery.
So it doesn't have anything to do with the fellowship.
Then I am going in.
A fellow cannot handle this surgery.
It's my patient.
Didn't you just say it was Dr Yoo's surgery?
Then it must be Dr Yoo's patient.
It is my patient.
- I can't allow this. - Our training starts next week.
I am still free. I will do what I want.
What's wrong with you? Don't be reckless.
I am confident about this.
She's out of her bounds like this.
Still, nothing changes. I'm going in.
Suit yourself then.
I will be the judge.
- I will do it. - It's my fight.
I don't avoid it when someone initiates it.
Don't worry. I only fight when I know I will win.
Just don't forget that I got your back.
Also don't forget that I'm always ready to help you.
- I will assist. Move. - Yes.
Irrigation.
Give me a dissector.
Bipolar forceps.
Give me a cottonoid.
She must've found it.
It wouldn't be that easy to find.
Clip.
She found it.
It ruptured.
Suction.
- I'll do it. - I can do it.
Dr Yoo, let Prof. Hong take over.
Hye Jung.
The blood pressure is dropping. Bring more blood.
Are you going to kill the patient, Dr Yoo?
Prof. Hong!
Concentrate.
Clip.
I got it.
Thank goodness!
Do you want to take over?
It's your surgery. Finish it.
- Suction. - Suction.
Dr Yoo.
I am sorry.
If you apologise this easily,
I will lose the fighting spirit.
When I lose, I admit it fast.
I will respect your decision now.
No matter what you do.
I act like a gangster. I am rude.
And I know nothing.
I don't even try hard to learn. What could I do?
Well... I apologised just a second ago.
You're still holding grudges.
You're very strange.
- I am a little strange. - You admit things fast.
I like that you're simple.
My granny used to be like that too.
Even when she was scolding me,
she suddenly became happy when I gave her what she wanted.
That's a compliment, isn't it?
I am rather simple.
You're still happy.
I think Prof. Hong loves his student too much.
I guess he liked you even more than Seo Woo when he was a teacher.
No.
He must be feeling like a parent who favour their weakest child.
I got expelled from high school.
Aren't you scared? I was bad.
Gosh, what's so scary about that?
I was pretty bad too when I was in school.
I'm sure you were when you were in arcades.
I'll get going then.
What?
What are you doing?
Hey, Uncle.
It's good that I ran into you.
Let me sleep at your place tonight.
Why would you sleep at my place? You have a house with a model.
I don't want to go home because of that model.
- You were so in love with her. - She wants to get married.
I asked her to break up,
and now she won't leave the house.
Just settle down.
You know my father. He's your grandfather.
He was married three times, and he had girlfriends when he wasn't.
Even during the marriage, he secretly met girls.
And your father, who is my elder brother,
swore that he will never be like father,
but he's preparing for his second divorce now.
Nobody settles down in my family.
I am going to change the DNA.
I thought like that too when I first got married.
But no matter what you do, your genes never change.
Will you let me stay or not?
I can't tell you the password.
Why are you so inflexible?
You can just change the password.
That's right. That's true.
What's wrong with you? You seem dazed.
By any chance, do you like the girl who just passed by?
- What are you talking about? - I'm just kidding.
Prof. Hong will be joining your department next week, right?
Be nice to him. He's my best mate.
I already blew that.
What? You already met him?
I bought yours too. Do you want some coffee?
I want to drink water.
I'll give you water then.
Here.
I want to drink coffee too.
I'll give you that too.
Did you meet the guardian?
Yes. I comforted him.
You're treating me nicely because I assisted your surgery, right?
This is nothing.
Hye Jung.
Will you continue to live like this?
How do I live right now?
You are too competitive.
You're successful now. So you should enjoy your life.
How much sleep do you get everyday?
I get 10 hours of sleep a week. It became a habit.
I wouldn't have been where I am now...
had I been living like everyone else.
Are you happy now?
There's no way I'd be happy.
Why not?
When I first told you I wanted to live my life differently...
You said you wanted to give your grandma a better life.
Yes, I lived a different life and became a success.
But she's gone.
That's not something I can help you with.
Accept it.
Why do you always want to help me?
Do you still see me as your student?
I may seem like the 18-year-old that always gets in trouble...
Do you think...
that I'm acting like this because I'm your teacher?
You're a fool if you think so.
Should I be happy...
that you became a doctor without dating any guys...
and you don't know what attraction feels like?
Don't you notice the way I look at you?
Whenever I think of you,
I remember the last time I saw you.
I shouldn't have let you go.
- Oh no! - Gosh, it's cold!
- Is this your way of saying no? - No.
Then will you go out with me?
- No. - Are you turning me down?
No.
Why are you saying no to both questions?
Do you habitually say no when you answer a question?
No.
I am right.
I'll ask you again later.
It's because I feel awkward.
It's weird...
how we always start out talking about serious things,
but end up in a comical situation. Whose fault is this?
What's with the face?
You're odd. You've become odd.
You mean girl.
I'm going to ask you again later.
I want you to answer yes no matter what I ask you.
Thank you for coming all this way despite your busy schedule.
I am sorry I wasn't in touch.
Could I see my son since I'm here?
I heard Yoon Do is in surgery.
I get to barely see him ever since he moved out.
I have to come searching for him.
Children don't know how parents feel until they get married.
Can I at least see Seo Woo?
She's also in surgery.
Fine, I love that they are working together.
Let's go in.
Although Chairman Hong has a lot of shares...
in medical care companies,
is this enough for the impeachment?
It'll be a different story if I say that it was to make a profit.
He thinks of his honour dearly.
Are you saying that he'll back out on his own?
I hope so, but we'll have to wait and see.
What did the Ministry of Health and Welfare say?
Will the Parliament pass the bill?
People are much against the idea...
of a for-profit hospital.
Non-governmental organisations are also opposing against it.
Until when do doctors have to be used by them?
We have to privatise hospitals like America...
and compete in a fair battle as an enterprise.
We should allow patients to get treated as they want.
A for-profit hospital opened in Jeju Island, so it's a matter of time.
There's no other option than to become industrialised.
I'm scheduled to meet Congressman Nam next week.
You should join us.
(President's Office)
Tell the media to write an article...
that he is bent solely upon profit for the hospital.
Yes, sir.
(Ahn Joong Dae)
What?
Mr Lee Ki Cheol says he can't sleep at night.
Should I give him sleeping pills or not?
He is clearly sane.
What's the problem if he's sane?
We never know what will happen to him later.
You idiot!
How are we supposed to prescribe medication, thinking about later?
Goodness. What did I tell you?
- Give Lee Ki Cheol sleeping pills. - Okay.
I hate you more.
How can you be this slow?
Why do you have to keep asking about everything?
It's not like I want to.
Who was the one that said I'm dead if I don't notify him?
You're supposed to notify him precisely, not often.
He's right.
Dr Jin was looking for you.
She is always looking for me.
I don't answer all the time.
- I'm not that easy. - What is he saying?
You! Do you want to die?
What are you doing?
(Missed calls, Prof. Hong)
(Neurosurgery, Ahn Joong Dae)
- What is it? - Dr Jin!
Mr Jin Min Ki is yelling.
Why are you notifying me of this? Is it serious?
Oh my, oh my, oh my.
Doctor.
I tied him down because he kept trying to jump off the bed.
Didn't you get a prescription from the psychiatrist last time?
Yes, she gave me the same prescription this time.
Then why did you ask me to come?
I never did.
Bring Kyung Joon here now.
Where is he right now?
Yes, Dr Jin.
Who do you think you are?
Why did you have him notify me about these small details?
- I'm sorry. - Why is the system so messed up?
Go easy on him.
Where were you? Why didn't you answer my call earlier?
I didn't go anywhere. I was just busy.
Good for you.
Why won't you let him notify these things to you?
He called me, scared he'd get in trouble if he called you.
Why you...
I'm sorry.
I'll talk to Joong Dae and make sure this never happens again.
- Joong Dae? - Yes.
Come with me. I have to talk to you.
- Can't we talk here? - Of course not. Come with me.
- Please. - Go with him.
I'll see you later, Dr Jin.
Why did you call?
I didn't answer Prof. Hong's call.
- Why? - I don't know why.
- What should I do? - Did you do something wrong?
Never mind, you're not the type to do anything wrong.
Call him back.
It's better than wondering why he called and feeling anxious.
- Do I look anxious? - Call him.
That's my answer.
I thought...
we needed to clear things up about what happened today.
Clear what up?
We once... I mean 13 years ago,
we wasted so many emotions because of a misunderstanding.
I didn't want us to go through it again.
I don't think it was a misunderstanding.
Fine. If that's what you think, I respect that.
I'll change my words.
I have to make this clear...
so we don't have any misunderstanding in the future.
Is it because I told you about Hye Jung's surgery?
It includes that.
I like Hye Jung.
You should tell Hye Jung that, not me.
Do you think I told you without telling her first?
I'm happy for you.
I was nervous when she showed up in my life again.
I was scared what she would take away from me this time.
At least it won't be love.
I like Dr Jung Yoon Do.
We are alumni and our families are close, so I trust him.
I hope you two can get along.
Could I ask you to be nice to her?
I was never mean to her first.
It was always her.
She was the one who approached me to ask about tutoring her.
That's when my life started getting messed up.
I miss In Joo.
She's another victim.
I shouldn't have started this.
This just can't get sorted out, can it?
Ji Hong!
Uncle.
Do you guys know each other?
Do you two know each other?
I asked you first, but I'll go ahead and answer your question.
Of course I know him. We're best friends.
Ji Hong, In Joo and I hung out all the time in university.
Right?
Why do you have to ask me?
It looks like I have to.
Goodness, you fool.
You should've come to me first as soon as you got here.
You always make me find you first.
I'll get going now. You two should catch up.
Bye. We will just go for drinks now. Right, Ji Hong?
Hey, do you even know what time it is now?
What's wrong? Drinking in broad daylight is the best.
Let's catch up later.
Hey, wait up!
- Are you married yet? - No.
- Do you have a boyfriend? - No.
Then we're set.
Do you know what you must learn before you insert a catheter?
What?
Learn to accept protection.
I will be done soon.
So don't be pathetic and cry.
Go grab some food.
(Hong Hong Hong)
Where are you now?
Hey, wait for me outside.
I need to talk to a fellow briefly.
Can I just stay here? I mean, you're just talking to a fellow.
Gosh, just wait outside. Oh, there she is.
Oh, I saw her earlier.
Introduce me to her. This is the second time.
I told you to wait outside.
- Hello. - Yes, hello.
Don't you remember me? I remember you.
Gosh, seriously.
We'll meet again.
We'll start going out the next time we cross paths.
- Who is he? - A total lunatic.
He's my friend, a staff member in General Surgery.
What did you want to talk about?
Do you want the second question already?
No, don't do that. Not yet.
You just had such a serious face. I didn't mean to scare you.
I'm sorry.
I have a favour to ask you.
Sure. What is it?
You're the chairman's son as well as the foundation's director.
That means you have access to all the medical records here, right?
You mean high-level information?
Here, the level of access varies according to your employee level.
I'm not a permanent employee, so...
Your access to medical records is restricted because of that reason?
What are you asking? So do you want me to get...
- information you can't access? - Prof. Hong. Let's talk later.
- Why? What's wrong? - I saw a suspicious-looking guy.
What? Wait...
Gosh, you startled me.
You walked in so quietly, Doctor.
Where did all of your people go?
I sent them all home.
Why?
You told me to let them go.
So you listened to me?
Do you actually want me to believe that?
Well... I'd like to start...
listening to women's advices.
Why are you here by the way?
Doctors don't need specific reasons to visit their patients.
Please get some rest now.
- Yes, what's up? - The patient...
with cerebral aneurysm. His blood pressure is under 90.
It's not going up even with an IV treatment and dopamine.
What should I do?
I'll come now.
Door is closing.
- Have you eaten yet? - No.
The emergency centre was swamped with patients,
so I haven't even sat down all day.
Go and eat something.
I have so much to do.
I need to prepare for the Ms Kim Mal Joo's surgery.
I have to dress that gangster boss' wound too.
I'll take care of the latter for you.
That will give you time to eat, right?
- You look thrilled. - Thank you.
By the way, why are you so nice to me?
- Do you like me? - Don't be cheeky. Get out.
- What about you? - I'll go back up to the Boss.
Thank you again.
Shall I...
thrust this right here?
You rat.
Go and save my brother.
Then I'll let you live too.
Her vitals are stabilising.
Dr Yoo is on night duty today, right?
- Yes. - Call her.
Well, she's not answering.
Does that mean I have to leave her in your hand?
Can I trust you?
You can.
All right then. I'll trust you.
What happened?
Here's your drink!
I hope you enjoy it.
Excuse me. Where shall I put this?
Oh, well...
You can put it in the kitchen.
My gosh. Oh my goodness.
Gosh, it's summer again. Hey, by the way,
was her name Soo Jin? Are you still seeing her?
Kang Soo Jin? Park Soo Jin? Which one?
- Kim Soo Jin, you womaniser. - Whatever.
Hang on. Yes, Soon Hee.
I'm on my way to your bar to grab a drink.
Mr Hong, Hye Jung is not answering her phone.
I have to tell her something urgently.
She's probably busy. Try calling her in a bit.
You're saying that because you don't know her well.
She always calls me back no matter how busy she is.
She texts me when she absolutely can't answer my calls!
I've never delivered to your bar before.
Please check this.
Anyway, find out where she is now.
I'll run to the hospital otherwise.
Oh, I guess you're new.
Yes.
Well... Haven't we met before?
Do you know me?
No. No, no.
How much is my bill?
She's not answering?
That's odd. You said she's on night duty, right?
Prof. Hong. Let's talk later.
I saw a suspicious-looking guy.
I'll meet you at the bar.
Hey! Wait!
Gosh.
Hello.
Where is Dr Yoo?
She went to dress the Boss.
Why would Dr Yoo do that?
She told me to get some food.
You haven't eaten yet?
You know a competent doctor always finds time to eat.
- Up your game, Doctor. - Okay.
- Call Dr Yoo. - I...
I can't leave my patients in your hands.
The person you're calling is currently...
She's not answering. Should I go find her?
Tell her to check on the patient with the cerebral aneurysm issue.
Okay.
Never mind. Just go and eat.
- No, I will go and check. - I said, go and eat.
- Don't make me say things twice. - Okay. Thank you.
Do you know who he is?
If you find out, you will regret saving him.
He's an evil.
Do you want to know how he killed my little brother?
Do you want to know how he destroyed my family?
Do you want to know what he did to me?
Let me show you.
I've been waiting...
for this day.
You can't be lucky forever.
What? Is there something you want to say to me?
Your little brother came to me.
He's the one who came to me first.
So?
You acted like a respectable big brother,
and you buried him when he became useless!
- Don't hit his head. - Sit down.
Or I will kill him.
If I can't hit his head, can I hit this part?
Don't do that.
He just got a surgery. Things can go wrong.
If something goes wrong with him, you have to be punished for it.
Don't you dare try to persuade me.
Why do you suffer because of that rubbish man?
If you get charged with murder, you'll be locked in prison for life.
And his men in jail will not...
forgive you.
Threatening him is enough.
He's terrified.
He's scared that he might die.
As long as he's alive,
people like you will keep coming.
Don't get his blood on your hands. Give me...
the knife.
It's a little complicated here, isn't it?
I don't want to interfere, so I will be outside.
Stop.
Come stand next to her.
Or this guy will die.
Take him out.
I will deal with him. You take him out.
Get out!
Mr Gong. Mr Gong!
People say that...
forgiveness is not for the person you're forgiving but for yourself.
It's not right to give such an advice.
Forgiveness is not as easy as you think.
(Doctors)
Dr Jung.
This is called "upper backspin elbow".
Is there anything you want to ask me?
What?
You are Hye Jung.
- Are they your family? - I wish.
So are you in love with her now? Stay out of her business.
When will you open up to me?
Right now, I am going to do something to you.
I will do something to you as a man.