(Episode 6)
You don't know...
how dear something is to you until you lose it.
- Good morning. - Good morning.
I love you, son.
I had no idea that...
the little things in life are what really mattered.
Doctor, doctor. Please take a look at my parents.
Please, Mum.
- Mum. - I lost her before my eyes...
without being able to do a thing.
Patient Lee Se Joon, time of death 1am,
September 11, 1986.
Patient So Hyeon Hui, time of death 1am,
I detest anything that destroys...
my everyday life.
- Are you okay? - I'm fine.
- Look carefully. - My goodness.
Pain is felt, not seen.
Dr Jung.
How did you let the situation slip like this?
Why are you yelling at me? What did I do?
I'm yelling because you haven't done anything.
I was helping, but it still turned out like this.
Do you think I just sat idly by?
Are you proud of underachieving?
I am!
Take him to the ICU.
Dr Jung.
Darn it.
"Darn it?" Hey, you.
Who was that directed to?
I was muttering to myself. Is that not allowed too?
Do you really think I'm that incompetent?
Take care of Boss!
Professor, please call General Surgery.
He's bleeding badly. I think his liver has been punctured.
Move it.
Hey.
You're always getting in trouble.
That hurts. You're so childish.
Sorry for ruining your evening.
Do you know that this is the third time for us to meet?
You're rambling again. Just go perform your surgery.
If we meet again, I'll consider us in a relationship.
That will never happen, so get lost.
Don't you dare...
He's a funny character.
Was that funny?
His pickup lines are exactly the same since college.
I'd get bored of repeating the same thing.
What's that look for?
- Where are you going? - To see Boss at the ICU.
I'll accompany you.
I'm only alive because the attacker...
tripped over Dr Jung's foot and missed.
Are you trying to say that I was too harsh on him?
I've never seen you get that angry.
I surprised myself with my own irrationality too.
You should go rest at home.
That's what I'd like.
Okay. Let me just drop you off.
Hye Jung.
What I'm about to do...
is pure humanity from one person to another.
What are you planning to do?
Thank you.
For what?
You sure are a fool.
You should get going.
(Patient Record)
Dr Jung said this patient doesn't show extra haemorrhage.
I've been instructed to give him mannitol and perform a CT scan.
Are the results in?
Yes, the results should be in.
Just a moment.
It's up.
He's haemorrhaging more blood, but not enough for a surgery.
Send him back to the ward. Let's monitor his status.
Okay.
I heard Dr Jung saved you.
Is it true?
- Who told you that? - He did.
It's a lie, right?
I witnessed your fight in the emergency room.
You subdued off 16 gangsters. There's no way...
How's your thesis coming along?
I'm still gathering data.
Your thesis is all about the data.
Shouldn't you work a bit harder?
How will you write three before the year ends?
Sorry.
You're short on time because you're always distracted.
If I were you, I'd focus on gathering more cases.
That spotted witch.
I was wondering when she'd lash out.
Dr Jung.
Dr Jung, hold on.
Why did you come looking for me?
That...
I don't need you any more.
Thank you.
Are you mocking me?
Why would I mock you?
I was so incompetent.
I should've kicked the knife away,
and I should've...
been the one to get stabbed.
I feel embarrassed.
Dr Jung.
That's called a 1-2-upper backspin elbow cut.
And this...
is a high-kick.
They're all martial arts moves.
I'm a professional female fighter.
Did I frighten you?
Are you trying to comfort me?
Since you're a professional female fighter,
I don't have to feel bad for getting roughed up?
Yes, your intelligence serves you well.
One more thing. I want to return the favour...
for how you thanked me.
- Thank you. If you hadn't... - Stop.
That's enough.
It's embarrassing.
Bye, then.
I have to wait until Boss wakes up.
I'm also on duty.
(Neurosurgery, Jin Seo Woo)
(Gukil Medical Center, Neurosurgery, Yoo Hye Jung)
Shall I join you when you meet Congressman Nam?
It would be nice if you could.
They're your connections after all.
What's the difference?
My connections are yours.
How are you proceeding with Doo Sik?
We're trying to figure out the best time.
Gukil just needs to become a for-profit enterprise.
The bill was proposed.
People tried to stop it, but it was proposed anyway.
When will Gukil Medical Center become Gukil Medical Corporation?
Not long from now.
The law won't be enforced right away.
I might not see it happen,
but Seo Woo will benefit the most.
Don't say such a thing, Father.
Once Doo Sik goes home,
I'll help Seo Woo settle down and retire myself.
You're the best.
That's obvious, so don't mention it.
Welcome home.
Did you two leave to play golf at the break of dawn?
He keeps calling you since we live in the same block.
You're ignoring me again.
I know you're an important man now,
but at home, you're my husband.
Talk respectfully, will you?
You're a wife to a man like me.
Have dignity that befits such privilege.
Gosh, since when were you so high and mighty?
Goodness gracious.
Hey.
Get married quickly.
I'm going to divorce your dad as soon as you get married.
Just get divorced now if you'd like. Don't use me as an excuse.
Even my one and only daughter gets on my nerve more and more.
You're becoming more like your dad.
You're never affectionate towards me.
Stop whining like a baby.
Dad and I are stressed from work.
Am I supposed to understand everything alone?
Yes. That'd be great.
You and Dad aren't a good match.
You'll never get divorced though. Just enjoy spending his money.
If only you weren't my daughter...
Gosh.
Are you mad? Mum, wait.
Bring Yoon Do home. Let's decide the specifics about your wedding.
Wedding? We aren't even going out yet.
You act like you're the smartest person in the world.
Why can't you win his heart?
I don't like easy guys. A bit of chasing makes them more special.
Women are at their happiest when they marry men who like them.
So are you happy?
You said you married Dad because he chased you so desperately.
That's right.
I married him because he chased me like there's no tomorrow,
but now he thinks he's too good for me.
They say that animals who think and speak will return evil for good.
Did you just call me an animal?
This is precisely why I don't like talking to your mum.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to say that.
Continue your conversation. You'll decide on the wedding date?
She's not there yet.
Set a date.
I'll never get locked into a marriage without love.
You do love him.
How many times do I have to tell you? Yoon Do doesn't love me.
We can't leave this in her hands. Please take care of this, Ji Young.
Dad, please.
Love? It's not that important in life.
Why would you let such ephemeral feelings decide your life?
Men aren't anything special either. Yoon Do?
If you want him, do whatever it takes to make him yours.
You'll get sick of him once he becomes yours. That's love.
Something you want to discard once it's in your hands.
What a great lesson.
She can have a loving marriage and become a great mum too.
Marriage can give women so much happiness.
Women like your mum is suited for that kind of joy.
You should see a bigger picture.
Don't forget what I told you previously.
Hey, can I move into your place tomorrow?
Two men over 30 living together is just wrong.
Yoon Do!
Hi, Uncle.
- What's the matter with him? - Is he really your nephew?
Is there such thing as a fake nephew?
He might be upset because I spent time with you instead.
He's a bit simple-minded.
He's being rude, not simple-minded.
You didn't have to say it like that.
Yoon Do! Do you love me that much?
Gosh, get off of me! This smell! How much did you drink?
You still reek of alcohol.
- Look at you nagging me. - What is wrong with you?
Ji Hong!
Let's get a ride from him.
Why would you tag along? Where's your car?
I don't have mine. I drank until I dropped last night.
No, I don't want to. I don't like him.
Ji Hong, he just told me that he doesn't like you.
Gosh, seriously!
Let's take a taxi if you feel the same way.
Why should we take a cab when there's a car right here?
It kills the environment.
Why? Don't you have your own car?
I need to go pick up my car when it arrives from the US.
Since when did we become so familiar?
Aren't you his nephew?
I'm his friend!
If you're his nephew, that means you're my nephew as well.
Aren't I right, mate?
Of course. You're not wrong. Let's go.
Okay.
Uncle. Prof. Hong!
My uncle? That's so old-fashioned.
Goodness.
How much did he drink?
Why is my uncle so hungover when you're completely fine?
Are you complaining or what?
Your logic makes no sense.
You're his friend, but that doesn't make me your nephew.
You're right.
Right? Then let's go back to before...
I found out that you two are friends.
I should get some sleep. Drive carefully.
And I was too harsh on you yesterday.
Gosh, what does that make me then?
It makes you a narrow-minded fool.
Please, Prof. Hong.
How's the patient's oedema?
It looks a bit smaller on the CT scan, but it's still quite swollen.
We're giving the patient 100cc of mannitol divided into 6 doses.
- What about pain management? - We're using acetaminophen.
If the pain seems to be intolerable, use NSAID or ample morphine.
Notify me when the cerebral oedema goes down a bit.
It looks like you can reduce the amount of mannitol as well.
- Yes, Doctor. - Where's the guardian?
I think they stepped out.
The patient is in mental stupor. Make sure they don't worry too much.
- Yes, Dr Kim. - Good.
(Neurosurgery, Hong Ji Hong)
Prof. Hong will get here after his rounds.
How do you know that?
Well, I just happened to know.
Are you waiting for him without telling him?
- Yes. - You're just waiting for him.
- Where did you get that plant? - A flower shop downstairs.
I see. I didn't know that there's a flower shop downstairs.
By the way, aren't you curious about me at all?
Do I have to be curious?
Well, that's how people converse. If I ask you questions,
you should reciprocate out of courtesy.
Why?
You're right. I don't know why.
The patient has oedema in the head. We left the head exposed...
because we have to do decompression.
The car accident affected the brain's midline as well.
She may not be able to live like before even if she wakes up.
What is oedema?
Oh, oedema is...
- It means swelling. - So her brain has swelled up?
Yes, that's correct.
You're saying that we should wait and see how she recovers, right?
- Yes, that's right. - Okay.
- Thank you, Doctor. - My pleasure.
- All residents to the meeting room. - Yes, Dr Kim.
Did something happen? Why does Dr Kim want to meet with all of us?
My gut feeling tells me that he's furious right now.
Would it be because of Boss' injury?
It's almost as if blood finds Dr Yoo wherever she goes.
I follow her around too because I'm a dutiful resident.
Right.
Is everyone here?
Yes!
- Kyung Joon. - Yes?
Repeat what you said to the patient Lee Soo Jin's guardian.
Sure. The patient has oedema in the head.
We have to do decompression,
- so we left her head exposed. - Enough.
What's problematic about what he said, Yeong Gook?
I know what the problem is, but I cannot say it.
Unbelievable.
Are you guys trying to defend each other...
and forming cliques here now?
How many times did I tell you guys to explain medical terms...
in Korean when you speak to patients?
As long as I'm the head of Neurosurgery here,
that is the rule. That's how I taught you all!
How dare you proudly say those terms right in front of my eyes?
Being able talk in medical jargons...
doesn't give you any privilege over patients or their guardians.
I apologise.
All of you are residents.
In other words, you're doctors who are still on training.
You must learn the right attitude along with the right knowledge.
- Yes, Dr Kim! - Yes, Dr Kim!
- When did you get here? - A little while ago.
Had you messaged me, I would've rushed here.
Go in.
Goodness.
I haven't organized it, so there isn't even anywhere to sit.
Sorry, my term hasn't begun officially.
Congratulations on joining Gukil Medical Center.
Thanks. I didn't know you could do these things.
What does this flower mean?
Does it symbolize pure love by any chance?
I don't know. I just bought it for no reason because it's pretty.
No reason.
That's my phrase, but it looks like you use it more often now.
I'm bribing you.
You have to help me.
What are these numbers?
It's my grandma's patient number, but I can't access her records...
because I'm not a permanent employee.
You're a staff member, so you should have the access.
Show me the power of a permanent employee.
Why do you want to see her records?
Please find her file and print all of her records for me.
Please also let me know which residents were in her surgery.
Is this why you refused the position at Daejeon Hospital and came here?
I thought I'd be able to view all the records as an employee here.
I must say that the president is quite remarkable.
This hospital has a great information security system.
Forget it all now, Hye Jung.
How can I forget?
Let's be objective. You're a surgeon too.
None of us are free from medical accidents.
I thought I would understand him if I became a doctor.
But now that I'm a doctor, I don't understand him even more.
"We did everything possible." "There are limitations."
"We paid, so don't cause any more trouble."
Is that the right attitude to deal with a person's death?
My grandmother...
trusted the doctor until the moment she went inside the OR.
I need to know everything that happened in that OR.
Once you find out, what will you do then?
I will decide once I find out.
The statute of limitations for medical accidents is 10 years.
You said accidents can't be restored and amended,
but the heart can.
How could you tear that note?
I'm sorry about that.
I just felt bad for you.
You've become a doctor now,
and people respect you.
Can't you just enjoy your life like everyone else now?
I had never had the privilege to be normal.
Never mind.
If you won't do it, I will find someone else.
Otherwise, I'll just hack in.
Are you crying?
Gosh, my awareness is a bit slow,
but you're worse.
It's normal to turn a blind eye when you see a sight like me.
At least you are not crying.
Why did it seem like you were crying?
The police is asking us to come and testify.
They want both of us.
Prof. Hong already did it.
He's speedy with everything.
Shall we go?
(Search Patient)
(Access Denied)
(You do not have the credentials to access the patient's information.)
Hye Jung caused more trouble, didn't she?
She didn't cause trouble. She's in trouble.
If it weren't for Hye Jung, he would've been long dead.
- Why are you here together? - We got investigated together.
It must me upsetting to get caught up in such a mess.
Something bad always happens when you're beside her.
I hope she gets kicked out like you wanted.
I no longer wish that.
Dr Yoo is a good person.
She turned out to be a decent person.
What made you change your mind?
If you want specific details, I don't have any for you.
What is this strange feeling?
Did you fall for her?
Why are you...
so hostile towards Dr Yoo?
I told you. I'm traumatized.
It's all her fault.
She was a gangster in high school.
She couldn't graduate since she was expelled.
I kept the details from you...
because I respected her.
That was unnecessary.
I personally heard from Dr Yoo.
This is where I get curious.
Did you really let Dr Yoo bully you?
I bet my car that you didn't.
I think something happened in Boss' room.
I'm sure he got blindsided.
There are many rumors, but when they're pieced together,
we can infer that Dr Yoo saved Dr Jung...
from getting beaten up to death.
Which animal do you like?
Dog.
I love them because they don't betray you.
Move her to the ward.
Okay, Doctor.
Hello.
The pretty doctor is here.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
You keep coming back.
As someone who was there when it happened, I feel responsible.
You came because you have something to tell my doctor.
I'm just an excuse.
Nobody can fool you!
Your car is mine now.
What? - How on earth do you think of me?
What makes you think that I didn't just get bullied?
- Let's talk somewhere else. - Let's talk here. Don't mind her.
She has already seen me making a fuss.
That's true.
Do you not understand what you've done wrong?
I'm sorry. All right?
Can you just omit the "All right?"
Right.
It's not an apology otherwise.
Gosh, you two are like best friends.
I'll take that part back.
All right?
You're not superior because I like you.
I have the upper hand.
I like you, Doctor.
I should've lived like you from the start.
You're just as hot-tempered as I am.
Will you do me a favour?
Please tell my son...
to bring the witch here.
He wouldn't listen to me.
Yes, Father.
Why are you so busy?
I know.
Isn't he still on vacation?
Why are you giving my son a hard time?
I wasn't, Sir.
I told him not to come, but he keeps insisting.
Gosh, that's not true, Doctor.
Okay. Okay. Rest until the end of this week.
That's good.
Let's go fishing.
I really dislike fishing though.
It gets fun once you're there.
But you've been fishing for more than 10 years.
I should've liked it by now.
I assure you. Within a year,
you will learn to like it.
I really don't like fishing.
Hello, here's an invite.
We opened a new cafe. Please visit.
Hello. I just opened...
a new cafe. Please visit.
It's a Gukil Medical Center 20 percent discount.
Anyway...
Watch where you're going!
How about you?
I am sorry.
Gosh...
Mum, let's hurry on up.
If we turn this in earlier, we might see a doctor faster.
- Oh... - Don't.
If your grades were just a little better, you could've been a doctor.
Mum, isn't it too late to say that now?
I am already on my third year.
I just feel bad. That's all.
You can't compare grade requirement standards...
between medical school and education school.
- Gosh. - Please stop the delusion.
My grades weren't good enough for medical school.
Gosh, you are too humble, Darling.
Let's go.
Hye Jung!
My proud doctor friend!
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Hey, Hye Jung!
- Lower your voice! - Hye Jung!
Where is she? Where did she go?
Who?
Gosh, there is this lady...
who always brags about her daughter becoming a teacher.
My friend is a doctor!
I would slap her if she wasn't ill.
You do your own marketing now.
Of course. Now I'm all energized.
I will be fine.
Here are your clothes.
You didn't have time to stop by at home.
Thank you.
Cheers, Dear.
Let's go.
Hello.
I'm from Sooni Hawaii, a new cafe that just opened...
across the street. I am the owner, Soon Hee.
We have an opening promotion.
I'm offering a 20 percent discount for employees at Gukil Hospital.
Please come.
Please go.
Pedlars are not allowed in the hospital premise.
What are the guards doing?
I don't think you heard my introduction properly.
I'm a CEO. I'm not a peddler.
I own a cafe called Sooni Hawaii.
So get out.
Since when were cafe owners referred to as CEOs?
My friend is a doctor here.
I see.
I'm not someone you can just treat with contempt.
My eldest brother is a Seoul District judge.
My other brother is a CEO of a well-known venture company.
My father dedicated his whole life to education.
And you're not leaving.
Ma'am, he has quite a personality.
Please, come here.
Gosh...
I can't believe it.
I am pretty, aren't I?
How can he treat a pretty girl like me so badly?
By the way, how old are you?
I don't look at girls who are older than 30.
I am 26.
That's perfect. 26 is perfect.
So your friend is a resident here?
- What? - Which department?
Anyway, please visit my cafe, Doctor.
I have to hand out flyers to the rest of the people here.
We're having a company dinner soon. I'll make sure we go there.
Thank you.
Good-looking people tend to have good personalities.
Look how messed up his face is.
Hey. Go get her.
Hey!
Hi.
- Lee Ga Jin. - Yes.
Let's go, Mum.
What brought you to the hospital?
As you can see...
- Oh. - What is it?
How is this possible?
What's wrong, Mum? You're embarrassing me.
Long time no see.
Mum.
This is your sister Hye Jung.
Let's do an MRI scan first.
Go with the nurse. She'll tell you where to go.
- Okay. - Come with me, please.
Is that really Hye Jung?
Why is she pretending not to know you?
She was always that rude.
- Mr Kim Gyeong Ho? - Yes.
Mum!
What are you doing?
Didn't you hear it? I'm her mum.
Wait a second.
- Hold on. - You!
Are you ignoring your own mum? You're Hye Jung, aren't you?
Since when were you my mum?
How could you say that in front of all these people?
Aren't you embarrassed to be a doctor and treat your mum like this?
I won't admit to anything that isn't true because people are watching.
There's no way you will be my mum.
Wake up if you think you can use people against me.
You're right. I'm Hye Jung.
I knew it was you. Then I won't let you treat me.
I want a different doctor.
I was very worried.
You never get old.
That isn't true. I'm getting so old that it makes me sad.
Come closer.
What do you think you're doing?
Don't cry. It's okay.
That temper is what made her brain burst.
Let's leave.
I feel so good.
I gave him a clean divorce...
when he cheated on me because he was low and dirty.
I didn't get a penny from that divorce.
So I worked hard to raise my children.
I worked day and night and am finally almost settled.
What did I do wrong?
Things will end well? Nonsense.
While I'm in a hospital bed,
her face is glowing from whatever she's taking.
You have to get plenty of rest.
If I hadn't divorced my husband,
she would've been living under my shadow.
But she has a good life.
You can date and have fun when you get better.
How would I date anyone at this age with this sick body?
You're still pretty.
You must feel bad for me.
You can't actually mean that.
Yes, I do.
Don't let anyone take him from you.
Nice people don't have happy endings.
That's how the world works. They stand up for the bad guy.
She gets to enjoy all the glory, and I'm just an old hag.
That's what the world is like.
I'll come to see you again. What do you like?
(Hong Hong Hong)
Why do you enjoy fishing?
We didn't catch a single fish all day.
There aren't any fish here, Father.
Look. There it is.
It's a carp. We can have steamed carp.
You don't like fishing, but you like to eat.
(Yoo Hye Jung)
Hi, Hye Jung.
Are you outside?
I came fishing with my father for a change. What is it?
- It's nothing. - Why?
It's okay. Have fun.
- Who is Hye Jung? - A doctor at the hospital.
- She must be pretty. - How did you know that?
I could hear it in your voice.
You don't sound like that when you talk to me on the phone.
That's nonsense.
- Father, can I ask you a favour? - What is it?
Find me this patient's medical records.
(Kang Mal Soon)
Do you have time?
The offender is the right PICA.
You'll have to do a microvascular decompression surgery.
I wanted to ask...
if you could do it.
Why would I do it when it isn't my patient?
Could you do it without asking for a reason?
No I can't.
If we start switching patients because we don't like them,
it could lead to chaos.
The hospital regulations won't allow it either.
Regulations are important to model doctors like you.
Thank you for your time.
Is she your family member?
I wish she was.
What are you doing here?
I was taking a look at a patient's MRI scan.
- Is it a rare case? - No.
Why would she bring you all the way here for nothing rare?
She didn't bring me. I came on my own will.
Do you feel inferior to Dr Yoo?
Why would I?
Exactly. Why would you be conscious of her?
You've been showing me different sides of you I've never seen.
This hospital is so nice.
It must be because it's one of the best hospitals in Seoul.
Even the food is luxurious.
Am I embarrassing you?
Why are you eating even without looking at me once?
- I met that woman. - Who?
My mum on paper and my biological dad's wife.
Where?
She came to the hospital with a facial spasm.
That's unbelievable. You finally got back at her.
What did her face look like?
Never mind. I bet she looked like she wanted to bite her own tongue.
She's broke, old and sick.
She got punished.
So what happened?
She didn't look broke, and she came with her daughter.
Is she your sister?
We share the same dad, so I guess she's my half-sister.
What's the problem?
If she doesn't look poor, she can get it treated.
I can't treat her.
Transfer her to a different doctor.
The different doctor said he won't do it.
He's weird. Why won't he do it?
The hospital regulations...
don't allow patients to switch doctors as they please.
Gosh.
Are you standing up for him because you're both doctors?
Aren't there any single men here?
I want squid and pork bulgogi.
Those two still stick around together.
What's wrong?
What is it? Whom did you see?
- Stop that. - Who is it?
I don't want to eat here.
Hey.
Come on. What's wrong with you?
The cafeteria food looked good.
The girl sitting across Hye Jung used to be my friend.
She dumped me after meeting Hye Jung.
There shouldn't be ownership between friends.
That comes from lack of affection.
That's why you identify with Ms Oh Yeong Mi.
What about her?
She said, "Bring me that witch" as soon as she woke up.
Her husband betrayed her and divorced her.
Why are you criticizing the victim?
A strong rapport with a patient is dangerous.
You worry too much.
I saw Yoon Do talking to Hye Jung in the fellow room.
Why did they have to discuss there?
Dr Yoo's mum came and turned the outpatient clinic upside down.
It must have something to do with that.
- Why? - What kind of mum acts like that?
Yelling and causing a commotion at her daughter's work would...
would obviously humiliate her daughter so much.
She must be her stepmother.
She lived only with her grandmother in high school.
I'm hungry. Don't forget that you already dragged me out.
Dr Yoo!
We want a party to welcome you and to celebrate me becoming...
a resident as well as Yeong Gook's first surgery.
We're thinking this Friday. You can make it, right?
There're so many reasons to party, aren't there?
- Yes, I'll be there. - Where are you guys going?
There's a place we usually go to.
By the way, who are you...
We opened a month ago. I'm here to promote my cafe.
Oh, Sooni Hawaii.
- You know? - I've been there once.
I knew it! I thought you looked familiar.
You're cute!
I'll take care of it if it's a welcome party for Hye Jung.
That way, she'll be able to win brownie points with her co-workers.
He's should try to score brownie points with me.
Oh, is that right?
Gosh, then I can't take care of the entire bill.
I'll give you a 50 percent discount.
- Let's do it. - Yes! Let's do it!
Get changed. Shall I wait for you outside?
It's okay. I'll get changed later.
Your life is so exhausting.
One day, it's the gangster boss. Then your stepmother shows up.
Why did you get Yoon Do involved in it?
I do not appreciate how you worded it.
I'm trying to make things better here.
Am I supposed to thank you for trying to make such effort?
We work in the same space.
Being on bad terms like this is uncomfortable,
so I'm reaching out to you first.
I was going to ask Dr Jung to take care of my female patient.
I'm telling you so that you don't get a wrong idea.
Do you think that I've been misled by wrong ideas all along?
You said five minutes ago that you're trying to make things better.
- Send me the organized charts. - Sure.
- Have a great day. - You, too.
Dr Yoo looks like...
she grew up in a rich family without having to lift a finger.
That's why I like her. She always surprises you.
You have such obscure taste in women.
What do you like about that spotted witch?
Why is she "spotted witch"?
She has a mole right here.
A witch with a spot.
How childish. You definitely lack creativity.
Gosh, don't hit my head.
Do you guys have nothing to do or what?
No, we were working.
Give me the chart for Dr Yoo's patient with facial spasm.
Are you going to take that patient?
That's awesome!
I'm so glad that you made this decision.
Why do you say that?
Don't you know that the patient is Dr Yoo's stepmother?
It looks like she has a complicated family problem.
Cranial nerve 7 and 8...
which emerges from the brainstem...
are located near the cerebral artery.
Arteries move every time the heart beats due to the pulsation.
It stimulates cranial nerve seven...
and causes facial spasm.
She's been going to a doctor in my neighbourhood...
and has been taking medication.
She's also tried getting Botox to alleviate it.
I only found out that her brain could be the cause...
after looking it up online.
However, the doctor she's been seeing can't help me with it.
Most patients take about 4 to 5 years to find out what causes it.
The brain surgery also scares them.
Then how could we treat it?
We could try the microvascular decompression surgery.
We'll get into where the nerve is...
and separate the facial nerve from the artery.
Then we'll insert a Teflon sponge...
between the nerve and the blood vessel...
to relieve and prevent the pressure.
It has a success rate of 96 percent.
When can I get the surgery?
Could you go to a different hospital?
I'll give you a referral and send your MRI scan to the doctor.
I don't want to go to a different hospital.
We could use your employee discount, right?
I heard that the discount is 30 percent.
You've done nothing for our family.
It's not like you'll pay my bill.
It won't inconvenience you in any way.
Do you know what I've been through while living with your dad?
I ended up with a condition like this because of all the stress.
I cut all ties with him 13 years ago.
A parent-and-child relationship doesn't end that easily.
It'd be so great if you could visit him and apologise to him.
I cannot do your surgery.
Why not?
Are you scared that you'd end up killing me?
I'll stay at this hospital regardless of what you say.
Knowing someone at a hospital makes a world of difference.
Plus, you're a doctor.
Why do I have to go to a different hospital when you're a doctor here?
People obviously don't change.
What about you then? Do you think you've changed?
You're just wrapped around in a fancy shell.
You come from the same place as us even though you sit there now.
Mum, stop it.
When can I get the surgery? Let's do it as soon as possible.
I have nothing to say. Please wait outside.
Hye Jung!
This is our restaurant.
(Grandma's Diner)
We're doing okay financially.
We won't burden you.
(Grandma's Diner)
The number you have dialed cannot be reached.
Please leave a message after the tone.
This is Jung Yoon Do.
I'll take care of the patient Ms Lee Ga Jin's surgery.
Who were you talking to?
Gosh, you startled me.
When did you get here?
A little while ago. I was quiet because you were on the phone.
The surgery for Dr Yoo's mother.
I'm going to do it. She won't be comfortable enough to do it.
Since when were you this considerate of others?
Was I inconsiderate?
I guess I'll try to change now.
Prof. Hong will take care of it even if you don't do it.
Stay out of everything related to Hye Jung.
Didn't you say you wanted her out? You're so capricious.
The human mind is a capricious thing. Don't let it bother you.
What brings you here anyway?
Let's eat together.
I can't. I have plans.
It's you.
I guess you're happy to see me.
I brought sandwiches. Let's eat together.
You're the only one who checks in on me nowadays.
- Why? - I threw a tantrum the other day.
I guess throwing tantrums is for those who are good at it.
No one cares because people are not used to seeing me like that.
Please eat.
It's delicious.
I have no appetite.
You're very pretty.
I'm angry.
I'm so livid!
Gosh, why did I live like a total fool?
I should've learned to express my anger sooner and...
Please don't think like that.
You should live happily to show everyone.
I'm frustrated. I should go for a walk to get some fresh air.
Please stay in bed.
You should still be resting.
I'm fine. I'm invincible.
Unlucky ones live long lives.
I survived like this because I met you and came here early enough.
Look at me. I can jump too.
- One, two... - No, you can't do that now.
- Gosh. - Three...
- Four. - Ma'am, please lie down.
I told you not to do it!
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Ma'am!
One, two, three, shock.
Up it to 200.
One, two, three, shock!
Ma'am. Ma'am! Ma'am!
Please wake up! Ma'am!
- Patient's time of death... - No!
Ma'am, please wake up...
Ma'am, please!
Open your eyes, please...
That's enough.
Ma'am! Ma'am!
Don't go...
Ma'am.
- Seo Woo. - Let go.
- Don't go! - Calm down.
Let go of me!
Patient Oh Yeong Mi. Time of death,
5:10pm, July 5, 2016.
She's gone.
Ma'am.
No! Ma'am!
(Grandma's Diner)
I love that.
I like something small and beautiful.
- I like the other one better. - Just get that.
- I'm buying it for you. - I'm going to be wearing it.
But I'm going to look at it.
- It's pretty. - It's pretty.
(Hong Hong Hong)
- Yes, Mr Hong. - Where are you?
I will call you back.
(Gukil Medical Center)
Sir, there is a cafe called Sooni Hawaii...
near Gukil Medical Center. Please go there.
(Grandma's Diner)
You're leaving!
- Thank you. - Thank you for coming.
You have great food, and you are great.
You will do even better in the future.
- Go, Hong! - Go, me!
- Bye. - Bye.
I will call you later!
Girls have to be pretty in any moment.
How do I look? Aren't I pretty?
Yes, you're pretty.
- Grandma, should I remove this? - Don't.
A mole between the eyes will bring you love from your elders.
Is that right?
But Dad doesn't like me.
No parents hate their children,
it's because they don't behave.
But I still can't tell you to understand him.
- Why? - It's parental love.
Parents love their children first.
Grandma, if you know so much, how did you end up this way?
Why are you ruining the conversation?
How about you? You always ruin it with your foul mouth.
I am sorry.
Don't be discouraged because you got expelled.
You can take a qualification exam and go to college.
You used to have the highest score on mathematics test.
- Gosh, you did it again. - Gosh.
My granddaughter is such a bully.
Hello.
Why do you look so depressed?
I will make you excited.
- What's this? - It's what you wanted.
Even I couldn't reach that data.
So I had to ask someone for it.
Thank you.
I got a copy of it too.
I'm going to ask my friend in general surgery to go over it.
If truth is what you're looking for,
and if truth can make you happy, I will help you.
Why aren't you answering me?
When will you start confiding in me?
It's late. Let's go. I'll walk you home.
It's raining. Is it supposed to rain today?
Yes. It's supposed to rain tonight.
These days, weather casts are so precise.
Let's go.
(Boarding)
Someone told me.
Life is...
not about waiting for a storm to pass...
but learning to dance in the rain.
Mr Hong!
Shall we dance?
Oh dear!
Turn!
I want to give you something special,
from one man to a woman.
Life is worth living.
I also have the chance to savor the little things in life.