Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor Crush]
Do you think I don't know you
were with that woman last night?
[Episode 7]
Here you go again!
Why can't you just trust me?
Where do you think you're going?
You can't go!
Let go of me!
I'll die you if you leave!
Fine! Do whatever you want.
Die or not. It's up to you!
To me, love between a man and woman
means fighting until one ends up dying.
Oh, it's cold! It's cold!
I don't know how to love a man.
As a woman...
Are we dating now?
I don't know how to receive love.
I'm going to do something right now.
Man to woman.
He's going to kiss me.
I have to avoid it.
Turn away. Hurry.
I'm not going to die because of
a man's love like Mom did.
Hye Jung!
At first, I ran away like you did.
I'm not going to ask you
that question a second time.
Why not?
You don't need to move.
I'm going to come to you.
The person who knows love
has to make the first move.
You don't have to move.
If you don't know,
just stay put until you know.
Thanks for caring so much
about my patient.
It's so unfair.
What good did it do to live her whole
life being good and working hard?
This is unexpected.
I didn't know you could feel this way.
Why is it unexpected?
I thought you wouldn't know
what unfairness was like.
That's not true.
I've been holding a lot in, as well.
Though, I'll explode and
let everything out one day.
It doesn't seem like you're holding back.
I love you.
I told you I liked you before, right?
Well, I was lying.
I guess you did explode, after all.
This is what I was planning on
telling you at the restaurant that day.
I didn't want to hear this from you.
I'm a bad guy.
If a guy tells you himself that he's bad,
that means he's a really bad guy.
You knew how I felt.
You just pretended not to know.
I didn't want to torture you
with false hope.
I don't care about torturing myself
if there is a small hint of hope.
You're being stubborn.
This is why I tried to stop you from
telling me your feelings.
Then, promise me something.
Don't like anyone else
for another six months.
Since you rejected me,
that's the least you can do for me.
I've already started...
What?
Who? When?
You haven't had time to meet women.
Is it Hye Jung, by any chance?
I'm getting goosebumps.
You girls and your intuition, seriously.
Why does it have to be her?
How would I know why it's her?
How can I control who I like?
I want to throw this right now.
That must be Young Gook.
I called him to watch over you.
Where are you going?
Something unfortunate
happened to my patient.
I'm not in a position to
comfort anyone right now.
Does he have to be a show-off
like that all the time?
What's the matter?
Why do bad things happen
all at once like this?
Do you want to go for a drink?
Was this taken after
Oh Young Mi passed out?
Yes, after intubation.
But, why do you need her angiography now?
I need to know what went wrong!
There was nothing we could do
after the examination.
There's a blood clot in the lungs.
It's pulmonary thrombosis.
Did she have any symptoms after
she was moved to her room?
No, we didn't see anything
in her CT either.
- Contact the guardian.
- Yes.
Here you go.
Enjoy your food.
Is this the only place to drink?
This is the new, hot place for our
hospital employees to go.
Hey, Seo Woo!
Hey!
Oh my, look at that girl.
How could she do that to a friend
she hasn't seen in so long?
I thought you were 26 years old.
You must have started school
at the age of three.
- I'll give you free appetizers.
- Deal.
What's the other bad thing
that happened besides Oh Young Mi?
Did Jung Yoon Do do something again?
I'll tell you once I've cleared my mind.
I can't tell you now
because my pride is too hurt.
Why are you drinking so much?
Oh, it's our CEO.
I noticed you're still Hye Jung's lackey.
Come on, now...
She had a bad day,
so she's not in a very good state.
I know her very well too.
I don't pay attention to
what she says. Don't worry.
- Good.
- Hey!
Pour me a drink.
Hey, what do you take me for?
Straight?
It's very strong.
Goodness...
He must have a very weak tolerance.
He's weak to everything.
How long have you been with Hye Jung?
We moved in together right after
I graduated high school.
My dad tried to send me off to Canada.
What did Hye Jung do all that time?
She studied and passed her GED.
We came up to Seoul with the money
that her grandma left her.
I heard that her grandma passed away.
Then she left with some gangster guy.
Didn't they live together?
No! I told you she lived with me.
There was a time before
she lived with you.
What are you talking about? I...
Oh, thank you. Bye.
Oh! Isn't that him?
It is him.
But he doesn't recognize me at all.
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Hey, don't do it.
- Stop right there!
Hey, stop that! Don't do it.
Don't you know me?
I'm Hye Jung's friend.
- I know.
- See, he knows.
Should I give you Hye Jung's number?
Forget it.
I'm sure you'll see her anyway if you
continue delivering to this store.
Did you know Hye Jung became a doctor?
You seem very drunk right now.
You picked the wrong guy to
start something with.
Are you looking down on me
just because I live this way?
What? Who does he think he is? Hey!
Gosh, what do you mean?
Look who's talking.
You must be going in early tomorrow.
Is that why you're washing your hair now?
Yes. Why are you home so late?
Seo Woo showed up and
was being such a nuisance.
I guess something bad happened
because she drank a lot.
Hey, I'll do it for you.
- It's okay. I'll do it.
- No!
I was going to wash my hands anyway.
We can save soap.
Goodness...
Make sure to dry your hair thoroughly.
If you don't dry it before sleeping,
it will fall out.
I'm sure I dried it.
I will be responsible for your beauty.
Come here.
All right, come here.
Your hair can be a sign of aging.
You often like to
pretend that I'm your doll.
That's not what I'm doing.
I'm rehearsing.
Once I get married...
I have to do these things for my husband.
You're so lucky.
Someone confessed his feelings for you.
How far have you two gone?
- What is that?
- What?
Have you... have you kissed him?
- No!
- You did.
I did.
No, it was just a light kiss.
Hey, I don't need all the details.
It's making me jealous.
I'm so jealous.
Seriously, Teacher Hong is so funny.
Though, I understand he must be
in a rush at his age.
He should be in a big rush.
He should move faster.
Hey.
Oh you, what a relief.
I thought I might have to be old and
alone forever because of you.
Why?
I'd feel too bad getting married
and leaving you alone.
You don't live the way
a person should live.
What's wrong with the way I live?
I thought you could relax
after medical school.
But you chose a difficult specialty.
I thought maybe you could
relax after that.
Being a staff surgeon was even harder.
What is that?
I can't remember the last time you
dressed up and went out.
You've had a lot to be upset at me about
all this time, haven't you?
It's not that I'm upset.
I'm worried.
Did you meet your dad?
No, I just saw him from afar.
You should get married too.
Why are you suddenly saying that?
Just make sure you marry Teacher Hong.
You like him too.
You were willing to throw away
everything for him.
You know I have to achieve a goal
once I set it.
That's why I'm telling you to love.
Walk down the flowery path,
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
There are priorities in life,
Cheon Soon Hee.
Yes, and what is more
important than love?
You are so bad at listening, really!
Come here.
[Surgery Records]
Okay, I won't ride in your car today.
What is this? Playing hard to get?
Doctor!
Can I turn on some music?
It's a bit awkward.
It's up to you.
If I read this,
it won't be awkward not to talk.
That's not right.
You're studying and I'm driving.
That doesn't seem right.
Let's turn on the news instead.
Large hospitals are
in urgent need of money
and are now turning to stock markets.
Reporter Lee Dae Hyun.
Major hospitals in Seoul are now...
Looks like things will be noisy.
You should just study.
I think that'll be better than the news.
I absolutely hate politics.
They make issues out of nothing
because they have nothing to do.
We can't let these issues created from
nothing violate our lives, though.
That's a political issue.
It's reality.
Director, is it true that
the hospital invested in stocks?
A hospital is not a business.
You received incorrect information.
Do you not hold those stocks?
We will put out a
press release later on.
Director! Sir!
- Doctor?
- Yes.
It's a busy morning with this news item.
Dad says not to worry,
but is it really okay?
How could it be okay?
The war is starting now.
Have you eaten yet?
Anyway, you have to face this thing now.
I'm a doctor.
My job is to treat patients and
that's what I'm best at.
You should deal with the politics
and I'll just support you.
This is an implicit
understanding between us.
Why are you being so serious?
I'm trying to give you a task
that you're good at.
Lee Soo Jung, the gold medalist for
archery in the 2011 London Olympics.
Do you know her?
Yes, I was a fan.
Is she still doing archery?
She got punished for drinking
before a match, right?
She's been suspended from
representing Korea for two years.
Then she can't go to the Olympics.
Do you think the hand trembling is
a sign of alcoholism?
I would have to examine her to know,
but it looks like an action tremor.
There are so many different reasons
why hands could tremble.
It isn't so easy to diagnose.
I want you to take care of Lee Soo Jung.
She visited many hospitals.
She's quietly looking for
a doctor to help her out.
I have no problem with that.
What does Lee Soo Jung have to do
with my dad's problem?
After I was berated by Jin Myung Hoon,
I got angry and learned a lesson.
Jin Myung Hoon is doing well.
Oh, Doctor...
So, I got the motivation
to fight and win.
Jin Myung Hoon's good management sense
is also a good sense of reality.
If I become the hospital director and
we continue to see losses
the hospital will eventually close.
Then who would listen to
what I have to say?
You've changed a lot.
To put it another way,
you must feel very troubled.
But, I'm glad that you've changed.
I like power now.
I'm so glad to have you back.
I have someone to talk to now.
So, my plan is for you to treat
Lee Soo Jung and get your name known.
Your name will be a source of strength.
That strength will be helpful to us.
[Jin Myung Hoon]
Let's go.
Why aren't you picking up the phone?
It's another meeting.
He's always calling me.
He doesn't like me but always calls.
Isn't that weird?
What if I can't treat Lee Soo Jung?
Oh, please don't
say that to me, Ji Hong.
I'll pay.
Anyway, I'm depending on you.
The amount of strength you get
will determine what we do.
Are you getting old?
Stop repeating yourself.
That's how important it is.
You've reached your credit limit.
There's no way.
Hey, do you see? Look!
Our revenue went down a bit last month.
They lowered the credit limit
on my corporate credit card.
I'll pay for it.
It's been 90 days since the surgery
and the patient is in a mental stupor.
The films are normal.
Doctor, I'm returning your message now.
Thank you.
What? This is it?
What is it?
He went into a drowsy stupor
not long ago...
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung!
Goodbye...
Isn't this too much?
You're just going to send me a text?
You left me a voicemail,
so I left you a text message.
Is something wrong with that?
It's not that it's wrong,
but it's not very grateful.
You gave your patient to another doctor.
How can you have no sincerity?
Doctor Yoo!
I don't think they're going to fight.
You don't know what Yoon Knife is like.
Yoon Knife will suddenly lose it.
- Like this?
- You scared me, you crazy punk.
My head...
Where are you going?
To Professor Hong Ji Hong's lab.
What about you?
Me? I'm going up to my lab too.
Why did you change your mind?
You said you wouldn't
take on that patient.
Of course, I am thankful.
I heard that she's family.
It would have been simple if you told me.
Why make it harder?
It isn't so simple to me.
I've had stepmothers too.
Not just one, but two.
I have no interest in
either of them, of course.
She's only your legal mother,
so why let it bother you?
You haven't been mistreated, have you?
- Oh, it's just coming at me again.
- What?
You should wait until I'm ready.
You just keep coming at me.
I'm taken aback.
What are you talking about?
It's just something...
I'll be seeing patient Lee Ga Jin today.
I'll try to book her surgery date
as soon as possible.
Okay.
Is that all you have to say?
If someone is showing you goodwill,
shouldn't you show some back?
What kind of curt response is that?
I don't feel bad for that person.
I don't wish for her
to get better either.
I couldn't resolve those feelings and
that's why I wanted you to take over.
It's a low point as a doctor.
The only thing that
makes me feel better
is that she's still
the same awful person.
Still, it doesn't change the fact that
I'm at my lowest point as a doctor.
That's why it's not so simple.
Is this a response that satisfies you?
Well, I suppose...
I'm on my way!
What... what are you doing?
Who is protecting whom?
I should be doing this.
Yoon Do!
Gosh, that kid.
Hey, Yoon...
Hello.
- You look more beautiful every time--
- Be quiet and come inside.
- Hey, hey.
- You come in too.
What about me?
What about you?
Shouldn't I go in?
Why would you come in?
We have something to discuss.
- Just you guys?
- Yes, just us.
Gosh, they shouldn't
have cliques like that.
"Just us"? Whatever.
[Kang Kyung Joon]
Yeah.
Oh, it's time for me
to see out-patients.
I'll be there.
I'm so busy.
There's not much in these records.
What do you mean by that?
Do you mean there were no issues or
that you can't tell by looking at this?
The latter.
The surgery procedure records are
not detailed and only show the results.
Cut the abdomen, died of heart failure
during removal of tumor.
The end.
So, we can't find out
what really happened
in the operating room with these files.
But there are original scans
of the surgery notes.
Doesn't that mean things went okay?
You can make it appear like
nothing's wrong if you want to.
You can hide it when you
make the initial notes.
If I really want to know what happened--
Anesthesia records.
Isn't that what we need?
Bingo! You couldn't find the
anesthesia files?
That's what was missing.
This was everything on the patient.
Then that's the end of that.
The records for anesthesia could be
saved in the medical records department.
The surgery wasn't done here at
headquarters, so would they have it?
- I know.
- What do you know?
It's probably at that local branch
hospital since that's where they did it.
I think I can get it from the
records department at that branch.
I'll talk to that medical records
department for you.
You've done enough now.
I understand that you want to help,
but this is my homework.
It's something I have to do by myself,
like writing my journal.
Aren't you supposed to be
seeing out-patients?
How did you know my schedule?
Did you look it up?
I'm your fellow who's
getting trained by you.
Of course, I should know.
I got excited for no reason.
I got excited for nothing!
Excuse me.
When can I get my surgery?
Most people have to wait six months
to get surgery from me.
As a favor to Doctor Yoo Hye Jung,
I'll do it for you earlier.
Doctor, will I be able to get better?
You can go now.
- I'll take you where you need to go.
- Thank you.
Please sit.
Are you here alone?
Yes.
My parents are suffering more than I am.
I don't want them to get their hopes up.
When did the trembling start?
It started last year
and has continued since.
At first, my hand would stop trembling
whenever I drank alcohol.
So, I drank before a competition.
After that... everything was ruined.
And alcohol? Are you still drinking?
I'm not that weak of a person, Doctor.
I'm from a wealthy family.
I've worked hard my entire life.
I've made it this far
by working hard, but now...
Can you fix it?
I'm willing try anything to stop
my hand from trembling.
Why don't we do some tests for now?
There could be many reasons for
the tremor in your hand.
It's difficult to diagnose.
Forget it, then.
Even doctors who promised they'd fix it
couldn't fix it for me.
I don't want to trust a doctor who
doesn't have the confidence to do it.
You're too impatient.
You make quick judgments too.
You weren't like that before, right?
Back when you won the
gold medal in the Olympics?
You can trust me because I'm not sure.
People who are good at what they do
will always doubt and question.
That way, they won't make mistakes.
You will have to get many tests done
before the surgery.
Blood tests, stool tests...
we have to do them all.
You have to do them within
one month of the surgery.
You should get them done again
a month after surgery, as well.
Are you saying I have to wait
one month to get the surgery?
But, Yoo Hye Jung is my daughter.
Ma'am, you are so impatient.
I was just telling you
how things normally work.
Since you're Doctor Yoo Hye Jung's mother
you're totally a VIP.
You can get surgery in two days.
That's Doctor Jung Yoon Do's
favor to you.
Is Hye Jung really that great?
She's the best.
What good is that?
She should be a good human being.
Her mother is here and
she isn't even showing up.
I'm letting it go
because I am her mother.
If I told people how she was
when she was younger
does she think she'd be able to work
or live out in society?
Mom.
When should we do the tests?
You can do them today since you're here.
Do family members
get discounts on just surgery
or on medical exams, as well?
- You get it on medical exams, as well.
- Then why didn't I get it?
Doctor Yoo needs to
submit the documents to HR
and tell them the dates of your visit.
It's just one thing after another.
There are no free things in life.
How will I stand having her
hold that against me?
- Doctor?
- Yes.
Can you give me my sister's number?
My dad wants to see her.
What do you think it is?
She's not even 30 yet,
so it doesn't seem degenerative.
Is it a resting tremor or action tremor?
Action tremor?
Intention or essential?
At first, it was intention that only
happened when she did archery.
Now, it happens all the time,
except in her sleep.
What are the causes for an
intention tremor and essential tremor?
An intention tremor occurs usually when
there is something wrong with the hand.
With essential tremors,
the causes are unknown.
Treatment?
Drug therapy is most common.
Propranolol or primidone.
Give a neurosurgeon's answer.
- DBS?
- That's right.
- You're going to do an awake surgery?
- Yes.
And I'm going to assist you?
Of course.
Oh, I'm so happy!
I've never done an awake surgery before.
I've seen videos and I've thought about
the day I might finally do one.
It's finally coming.
Thank you, Doctor!
- So, this is what you like.
- Yes!
Gosh, Doctor...
Yes!
What are you so happy about?
Have you done a DBS,
awake surgery before?
No, I wouldn't have, obviously.
Even in a big hospital like Gookil,
you haven't had that chance?
It's so obvious that
you're a small town girl.
A fellow can't do a surgery like that.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
You're not doing one, are you?
Doctor Hong is doing it
and I'm assisting.
Yes!
Come in.
Hi. Have you eaten?
I want to do the Lee Soo Jung surgery.
You said you wanted to work with
Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
I changed my mind.
Just because you change your mind,
it doesn't change anything.
It's not fair.
You're giving better opportunities
to the woman you like.
- Hey...
- Let me in on it, then.
Gosh, this isn't something
I can decide on my own.
Then, let's hold a meeting.
We are all here because
Doctor Jin Seo Woo has an objection.
I want to learn from
Professor Hong Ji Hong.
Okay, I'll go with Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
So, it's enough for
the two of you to agree?
Honestly, Jin Seo Woo and I
have been together for a very long time
so change is good.
- What do you mean "Change is good"?
- You wanted to switch first.
Do you have to put it that way?
Stop it. Are you in high school
or something?
What do you think, Doctor Yoo Hye Jung?
I received an offer from you
and I accepted.
I don't want to change that.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung, you are very good
at operating on aneurysms for a fellow.
It made me want to work with you.
We should work together.
You will learn a lot from me.
To summarize,
Jin Seo Woo and Yoo Hye Jung
want to work with Hong Ji Hong.
Hong Ji Hong wants Yoo Hye Jung and
Yoo Hye Jung wants Hong Ji Hong too.
There is no other match, so Hong Ji Hong
and Yoo Hye Jung will be a team.
Then let me in on this surgery, at least.
What do you think, Doctor Jung?
Since she wants to do it so much,
let her do so.
In return, the fellows can be
passed back and forth
to be trained on different cases.
Passed back and forth?
What a cheap way to talk.
Why are you getting angry
at everything I say?
So, let's summarize again.
I will accept
Doctor Jung Yoon Do's proposal.
We will train the fellows
based on the situation.
Are you okay with that?
Do you still not get it?
- What?
- Can't you see they like each other?
That's them liking each other?
I'm sure they're close
since he was her teacher.
He's known her since she was young.
- You should go through it too.
- What?
The pain of seeing the person you like
looking at someone else.
You know me.
I can maintain love,
but I'm great at starting it.
I haven't even started yet.
If there's a competitor,
I feel even more motivated.
Yeah, me too.
I don't know about anyone else,
but I'll never let you go to Hye Jung.
I'll lose to her once, but not twice.
Hey, why are you acting like this to me?
I waited for you for this long
and this is how you repay me?
I will get you no matter what I do.
You'd better prepare for it.
Why is she acting like that? It's scary.
Oh, we're not open yet...
Are you disappointed?
I turned up in this state.
Did you pretend not to know me
even though you knew?
No, I didn't recognize you
because you got so pretty.
You're all doing so well.
I hear Hye Jung is the most successful.
Is she really a doctor?
Yes, she was always smart.
I guess she always read books,
even while rebelling.
She's a really smart girl.
I came to say goodbye.
- I won't be delivering beer anymore.
- Why?
I got fired this morning.
I heard about you guys, felt ashamed,
got drunk, and made a mess of things.
You must be a bad drunk. Oh no!
Wow, you must have a lot of money.
How much do you need
for a place like this?
I told Hye Jung about you.
What did she say?
Do you still like Hye Jung?
You followed her around a lot back then.
Hey, did she say that?
Did she say I followed her around?
Anyway, don't hang around her.
She's going through a lot right now.
Why? Is she embarrassed of me?
I should just throw this right over!
President Jung, it's been a long time.
I was glad to hear you'd be coming.
That's why I made time today.
Old friends are the best kind.
How have you all been?
Congressman Na, you look good.
Gosh, I think my liver is failing.
I'm so tired.
You should drink less.
When we first started this,
we wondered if it would be possible.
People eventually end up on
the side that makes them money.
This is the way this generation
is moving, President.
Congressman Na is an expert on
how this generation thinks.
These days, politics are similar
to being a celebrity.
Once you lose your popularity,
you lose all support.
Oh, stop your complaining now.
No one has to look over their shoulders
as much as hospitals.
We even have to pretend
that we are kind.
Once hospitals become private companies
what will Director Jin
complain about then?
If that happens, no more complaints.
Only happiness!
Well... we are trying.
The public is the problem.
Don't worry. It will happen.
We will pass the new revision
to the health bill.
They said Jeju Island's private hospital
wouldn't happen, and it did.
You are all truly the best.
I feel very supported.
What's going on with Board Director Hong?
You don't need to worry.
I'll take care of him.
Today, let's go all the way!
Yes, let's do that!
Where is the
Neurosurgery Department here?
- How do you feel?
- Good.
The surgery went well
and there are no issues yet.
- You can be discharged tomorrow.
- Thank you.
When can I take a shower?
It's best to wait one day
after being discharged.
I'm dying to shower.
- I guess it hasn't arrived yet.
- What?
I thought I would be discharged tomorrow,
so I prepared a present.
- Is it a rice cake?
- Yes!
Everyone's eating it
at the nurse's station.
You should go out and eat it.
It's made with special rice grain,
so it's really good.
Yes, I'll make sure to eat it.
Wow, I've never had a cake
made out of rice before.
It's really good.
Leave some for Chief Kyung Joon.
He'll be like...
"Where's mine!"
Should we give some to
the staff surgeons too?
I'll give some to Chief Kyung Joon.
You have a really good personality.
He hits you all the time.
He has no clue that he's an outcast.
I pity him.
Go on, then.
- Are the professors still around?
- Yes.
Professor Hong is here and
Professor Jung is in the ICU.
Is Yoo Hye Jung around, by chance?
What is this about?
I don't think I need to tell you that.
Is she here?
She's not here.
If you leave me your number,
I'll call you when she comes.
That means she is coming. I'll wait.
What's going on?
Call Doctor Yoo and tell her not to come.
Call her now.
It's too late.
Doctor, eat this.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Oh, this is good.
Do you even know who bought this cake?
What are you doing?
Well... Doctor.
You're in my way. Move.
Okay.
Do you know him?
Yes, he's my friend.
What is this? What's going on?
What brings you by?
You're not embarrassed of me?
Why would I be? We're friends.
I heard about you from Soon Hee
but I'm so busy
and don't have any days off.
I'm sure you're busy being a doctor
in a big hospital like this.
- You've gotten better looking.
- Really?
You have facial hair.
You look like Wolverine! Wolverine.
Wolverine, no.
Why is that kid here?
Do you know him?
How would I know that?
Why are you getting mad at me?
Aren't you acting too friendly with me?
Well, can't I?
You can.
Let's go somewhere else and talk.
How have you been?
Not that well.
Then I heard about you and
it really made me think.
I thought to myself that
Hye Jung actually did it.
I did do it.
Thank you for being good to me
when things were tough.
I never did anything for you.
Let's see each other often now.
I'll buy drinks.
Thanks.
I thought you might pretend
not to know me
now that you're so successful.
What's wrong with you,
Kim Soo Chul?
What happened to that
"live or die" attitude you used to have?
I came to say farewell.
I guess it's a farewell
as soon as we met up again.
Are you going somewhere?
I'm going to where my son is.
Son? Are you married?
I'm divorced.
Hey, do you want to see him?
He looks like me, so he's good looking.
Show me.
Who's raising your son?
His mom.
I have to send her money.
Oh, he's so cute!
Right, he's so cute?
He looks just like me.
I'm going to work really hard now too.
Seeing how your life turned out,
I think I can make it work too.
Is it too late?
It's never too late.
You're still a strong and cool guy.
This is what I wanted to hear from you.
I think I can do it now.
Ah, do you still ride a motorcycle?
Every now and then.
You were so cool on your motorcycle.
I wish I could see it again.
Hold on.
- Hello.
- It's Dad.
Excuse me?
I said it's Dad.
What's wrong?
Where are you right now? Let's meet.
All right.
I'm sorry but I think I have to go.
You have to see me before you leave.
You have to.
Okay, let's get up.
This is where your grandma is.
Why did you move her?
The 10 year contract ended.
I wanted to move her to a better place.
You look like you've been good.
I've been running a restaurant.
Granny's Rice Soup.
I got your grandma's cooking skills,
though I didn't know it before.
The restaurant is doing pretty well
and we're okay.
You should come by.
Yes, you should come with the
hospital people.
I'll treat you all.
I'll get going now.
Why... you still have tea left.
I'm an adult who no longer
needs my parents.
Hye Jung.
You can't live like that.
How can you live happily with
a grudge against your dad?
Don't worry.
I don't hold a grudge against you.
Just like I said, I'm no longer young,
so I don't need you.
I'm used to living on my own.
Let's live apart like we've been doing.
Who will walk you down the aisle
when you get married?
You need your dad.
Because I might need you,
I decided not to get married.
- Hello.
- Oh Cho Ah, you're here.
Okay, let's start in five minutes.
Come in. Sit down.
All right...
I'm going to give you your diagnosis
for your illness.
You will need to make a choice on whether
you will follow
my treatment advice or not.
[In surgery: Lee Ga Jin, Go Ah Shin]
[In recovery: Choi Jung Hoon,
Jin Seo Joo]
Please count down from 10.
Ten, nine...
eight, seven, six...
Please intubate.
Cotton.
Dissector.
Do you see the lateral spread?
Yes, I see it.
Teflon.
Do you still see the lateral spread?
No.
- Is it gone?
- Yes.
Teflon.
The reason your hand shakes
is called an essential tremor.
Your hand has tremors
for no specific reason.
How can you diagnose it
without knowing the cause?
My diagnosis is that your hand
has tremors from an unknown cause.
The important part is the treatment.
DBS is deep brain stimulation surgery.
Take a look.
We use electrical stimulation
in the brain
to find the area that stops the tremors.
We keep you awake for the surgery.
You will be conscious for the surgery.
I think I've seen it in a movie.
Doesn't it hurt?
Not at all. The brain doesn't feel pain.
We will provide anesthesia
when we open up the skull.
What if you stimulate the brain,
but the tremor doesn't go away?
Could that happen?
Yes, that could happen.
Side effects include paralysis, coma,
hemorrhage, and seizures.
You could also end up with
temporary damage to your nerves.
Well, what is the success rate?
About 90 percent.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
- Oh no.
Please don't thank me until you win
at the Asian Games of Tokyo Olympics.
- So, I can continue with archery?
- Of course.
Is it possible to take a video of
my surgery and put it online?
Why?
I want to restore my honor.
I didn't have a tremor
because I was an alcoholic.
I was trying to be a great athlete
even with an illness like this.
Even if this surgery fails...
I want to show people I tried my best.
I'm rooting for you, Lee Soo Jung.
I'll do whatever you wish.
Come in.
Oh, Doctor.
You may not be curious,
but the surgery went very well.
Oh, thank you.
- Are you really thankful?
- Yes, of course.
Then, let's go for a meal together.
Okay, let's meet in the
hospital cafeteria later.
Not the cafeteria.
Isn't that being cheap?
Who says thanks by buying cafeteria food?
Honestly, I'm not so thankful that
I want to buy you a meal.
Then, I will buy the meal.
You can buy coffee, can't you?
I'm not thankful enough
to buy coffee either.
Then I will buy the food
and coffee, okay?
I'm sorry about both.
I don't think we're close enough
to go out to eat together.
How close do we have to become
for you to eat with me?
People usually become closer
by eating together.
Do you not want to be close to me?
Why did you stop talking
as soon as I walked in?
You walked in as soon as
I stopped talking.
Then it's her turn to respond.
Why aren't you responding?
It's not that. Let's do it later.
- Do what later?
- Why are asking so many questions?
Did you get rejected after
asking to go out to eat?
Your methods are so old.
Hey! Are you going to be like this?
We may be friendly,
but this is work and I'm your boss.
Have some etiquette.
What a joke.
Come to my office.
It's about Lee Soo Jung.
He texted you first.
She's making me angrier.
I'm already holding in
my anger as it is.
Sorry, I ran into the section chief
on my way here.
Sit down, sit down.
Put the box over there.
Did you book Lee Soo Jung's surgery date?
- Yes, tomorrow.
- That quickly?
Everything is ready to go.
I've been practicing it in my head.
Honey is just dripping from their eyes,
right in front of me.
Come out early tomorrow to get ready.
Two of you are enough, right?
Yes.
Just love each other blatantly,
why don't you?
I'll get going, then.
Okay.
Aren't you going?
I'll leave in a bit.
That's good. Help me move this box.
It's so heavy.
Seo Woo, hurry up. Come on.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
There's no need for that.
The surgery went well, so don't worry.
Yes, we heard from Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
He said he inserted some material
between the artery and nerve.
It must be because you're
Doctor Yoo's father.
You understand things very quickly
and speak eloquently.
Ah, there's Doctor Yoo now.
Thanks to you, the surgery went great.
Yes. Did you do the dressing on
Hwang Jung Hwa?
- Yes.
- Let's check on her.
Yes.
Is there anything to eat?
There's still some rice cake left.
Do you want some?
- Yes.
- Yes, sir!
- I will carry out your command.
- Stop playing around.
- Can I sit down?
- Sit.
Dad wanted me to bring you
our family documents.
Sis, do you hate me too?
No, I don't have ill will towards you.
I'm so glad I have a sister.
I've been so lonely.
This may come off cold to you,
but I like things the way they are.
I don't want to get
mixed up with your family.
I'll take care of this for you.
You can tell your parents.
[Proof of Familial Relations]
[Yoo Hye Jung, Yoo Yoo Na]
[Soo Chul]
Yes, Soo Chul?
I'm leaving Seoul tomorrow.
I want to say goodbye and
walk away looking very cool.
What do you say?
Sounds good.
Okay, great!
Our carpool is done now.
- Why? Are you disappointed?
- No.
If your car didn't come today
I would've gotten a girlfriend
and had her sleep over
just to come in the car with us.
Why isn't this opening?
Cute kid.
Girlfriend?
Sounds nice.
Oh, you look like your old self.
After I ride it today, I'm selling it.
You made the right decision.
Where should we eat? My treat.
You're buying?
Of course.
You became a doctor.
How can I not buy you a meal?
Then, let's go to my hospital cafeteria.
It's cheap and so good.
Hey, cheap and good...
that's totally my style!
Let's go!
[Yoo Hye Jung]
[Hong Hong Hong]
Yes, Doctor.
You sound happy.
I'm going to work with my friend.
- Soon Hee?
- No.
Soo Chul, my friend from
when I was a bit rebellious.
Hey, don't hang out with him.
Hey, you can't tell me not to
hang out with a friend.
Gosh... you're kind of...
Do you like him that much?
What is it? What's wrong?
Hye Jung!
It has always been this way.
Love brings fear.
And fear has taken over me.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Doctor Crush]
- The signal is strange.
- Why is her hand shaking?
Something is wrong, right?
I can't see anything.
If you come into surgery and things go
wrong, you won't be able to handle it.
Make a choice. Are you coming in or not?
I am thinking of you as a woman.
Let's eat together and go into surgery.
31 year old man,
motorcycle accident.
Neurosurgery is going to
do surgery first.
- Blood pressure is dropping.
- Suction.