Subtitles by DramaFever
- You've gotten better looking.
- Really?
[Episode 8]
You have facial hair.
You look like Wolverine! Wolverine.
Wolverine, no.
When a man and woman were in love,
the thing I envied the most
was when a man met someone that made
him behave in an immature manner.
I am very manly.
It's okay! They're just friends.
This immature behavior between
a man and a woman is healthy.
It's the best gift I can
show the other person.
Yes, Doctor.
You sound happy.
I'm going to work with my friend.
- Soon Hee?
- No.
Soo Chul, my friend from
when I was a bit rebellious.
Hey, don't hang out with him.
Hey, you can't tell me not to
hang out with a friend.
Gosh... you're kind of...
Do you like him that much?
What is it? What's wrong?
Hye Jung!
Where are you right now?
Call an ambulance!
Can you recognize me?
Don't move your neck.
Can you move your arms and legs?
No, I can't put any strength in them.
What about your fingers?
Move your fingers.
No!
This can't happen.
Are you okay?
- Doctor!
- What happened here?
He has damage to his cervical vertebrae.
I don't think his nerves are
completely damaged.
What about the ambulance?
They've been called already.
Good.
I've just been holding his hand.
You did well.
You're a doctor.
Don't lose yourself here.
Your friend will be in danger
if you do, Hye Jung.
We have to be very careful moving him.
Get a neck brace.
Can you help me?
Be careful. Even one wrong move
could make things go very wrong.
A little bit, just a bit.
Do you have him? Got him?
Good. Put him down slowly.
I'm putting you down slowly.
He's not breathing.
Get me a stethoscope! A stethoscope!
We need to get to the hospital now.
He'll be in real danger if we don't
stabilize his breathing
within 30 minutes.
Get a gurney.
He's been in a
motorcycle traffic accident.
Put him in the ER.
His rib is broken.
It must be piercing his lung.
His diaphragm might have a tear, as well.
There is blood in the lungs.
Get me a 28 French chest tube.
Hold on to to him, Hye Jung.
Hold on to the patient.
Give me the tube.
Cut.
We took care of that.
Let's get a CT done.
31-year-old man,
motorcycle TA (TRAFFIC ACCIDENT).
His BP was over 120 but he got
a chest tube and is now at 92.
The CT showed a bleeding spleen,
so we will need to do a surgery for that.
- What about hemorrhage?
- It's grade two but they're using drugs.
Get an operating room now.
He could suffer paralysis due to
a fracture in the vertebrae.
The Neurosurgery team is
going into surgery first.
- Who is? Ji Hong?
- Yes.
Take an MRI of the vertebrae and
get an anesthesiologist right away.
Call General Surgery and
ask them to come in right after us.
You don't need to call us.
I'm here already.
Good timing. Come take a look at this.
The bleeding is not too bad.
But it could get worse while
you're doing the surgery.
He could go into shock.
I need you to work fast. Quickly.
I'll prepare for surgery now.
- Okay, hurry.
- Yes.
Now, make a choice.
Do you want to come in or not?
You've done a good job up until now.
You don't need to do anymore.
If you come in and something goes wrong,
it will be extremely difficult for you.
If I go in and things go well,
will I become stronger?
Please stop becoming stronger.
How can I live in this world
without being strong?
Being weak isn't a bad thing.
It's okay to be weak.
I don't want to go in.
Okay.
Doctor Hong is going to do the surgery.
If you get the surgery,
you can ride your motorcycle like before.
I don't want another doctor.
Doctor Hong is a really good doctor.
I'm scared.
But if you were to do it,
I wouldn't be scared.
If there's anything I know about you,
it's that you can do anything.
You'll do it, right?
Doctor, the operating room is ready.
They want you to send the patient up.
I'll do it.
I'll be by your side.
I'm going in too.
Okay.
Yes?
Oh, what brings you by?
You ignore my calls,
so I came in person.
I was watching a new surgery.
I meant to call you back.
Did you know Director Hong is
giving a press conference today?
No, he doesn't report his
every action to me.
He caused trouble for the hospital
with this stock scandal.
He ought to just stay quiet.
Do you know how worried I am for him
because of that?
Director, let's not be fake
to one another.
You and I have been battling
for a long time now.
Let's have some respect for each other.
Should I be honest, then?
Stop stepping where you don't belong.
I'm the owner of this hospital
and you're just an employee.
As long as you make a good living,
why do you care who the owner is?
This is why I don't like you.
Can't you have some dignity?
Do you have to be so tactless and rude?
Go on and look for dignity.
Once Director Hong is gone,
you won't have any connections.
But I was born with a
golden spoon in my mouth.
Director Hong can try to take this
all the way with his press conference.
He needs to do that in order to
realize where his boundaries are.
Aren't the Medical Care stocks
essentially owned by Gookil Hospital?
The Medical Care stocks
are my own personal stocks.
They have no connection to the hospital.
However, I do apologize for tarnishing
the image of the hospital.
Is it true they're actually hospital
assets disguised as personal assets?
People say you will give them to
the hospital in the form of a donation.
Who said such a thing?
Would I, Hong Doo Shik,
do such a shameful deed?
You call yourselves reporters.
How can you all spread such nonsense?
You're here?
What will change if you hold a
press conference?
People believe what they want to believe.
There's someone behind this.
I have never run away
from something like this.
I will find out the truth.
I'll have to clean out the entire board.
Doo Shik, why do you do things
all on your own?
Shouldn't you discuss things with me?
You want to change out the board
without consulting me?
Aren't you and I on the same page?
I'm being falsely accused here
and you're okay with it?
If this were happening to you,
I'd find them all and get rid of them.
So, let me take care of it and just rest.
You too much of a perfectionist.
You do everything by yourself.
About Myung Hoon...
He hasn't given up on
the senior home, has he?
The Senior Health Center.
Why are you suddenly curious about that?
The person who would want to put me
in a difficult position...
is Myung Hoon.
Myung Hoon would never do
something like that.
He only lives to help this hospital grow.
All of you, leave.
Don't take Doo Shik too lightly.
I thought he would back off
once his name was disgraced.
- I was wrong.
- We need to see some blood too, then.
I guess we'll have to
use that move, after all.
[LEE GA JIN]
- Are you feeling okay?
- Yes.
You can be discharged tomorrow.
Thank you, Doctor.
You can come back to see me
on Wednesday, two weeks from now.
You could relapse.
Don't miss any appointments and make
sure to come in for all of the tests.
Bye, then.
You did well.
Hold on. Doctor!
I brought this for you to say thank you.
Oh, uh...
It's really not much.
You're my Hye Jung's co-workers and I
haven't been able to do anything for you.
I feel like I owe you.
Yes, thank you. We'll enjoy eating it.
By the way, where is Hye Jung right now?
He could bleed a lot and go into shock.
Please keep an eye on his vitals.
Scalpel, please.
Septum elevator.
Gown, please.
I'll change positions.
- Doctor, please raise the bed.
- Yes.
- Stop.
- Okay.
Suction on the right.
Suction!
Bring more blood. Forceps.
- Pressure's dropping.
- Bring more blood!
Who told you to sleep? Who?
I'm just so curious? Who?
I haven't been able to sleep at all.
A first year resident
shouldn't be able to sleep.
I stayed up for one whole week once.
It's the ones who are bad at work
who make excuses.
Kang Soo's not bad at his job though.
Look at that guy. He is so dense.
Why are you butting in?
What are you doing?
You must have so much time to kill,
Joong Dae, Ahn Joong Dae.
I have something for you.
I scanned my book for you.
It's my book.
You said you didn't have money to buy it.
All right! Thank you.
Joong Dae, can you give me one?
- No, I can't.
- You're bad. You're mean.
Your first year party is coming up.
Section Chief will give you
one as a gift. Don't worry.
Why doesn't the chief have one?
Didn't he get one from Section Chief Kim?
He gave something else back then.
- Eat this.
- What is it?
Doctor Yoo's father gave it to us to eat.
Wow, what is this?
You are amazingly good
at sniffing out food.
Aren't you in surgery?
I was, but Senior Hye Jung said
she'd assist so I had nothing to do.
Nothing to do?
Watching the surgery is work.
That's why you're always falling behind.
Do you enjoy being old and left behind
with younger kids?
- I like it.
- Oh my gosh!
- Should we eat this now?
- Gosh, seriously.
Let's put this in the fridge and eat it
when we're hungry. It's soup.
Let's freeze some of it too.
Should we do that?
I've been to this restaurant,
Granny's Rice Soup.
- It is really good.
- Oh, really?
Kang Soo, you should put it on your blog.
Doctor Yoo will like you for
advertising the restaurant.
Do you think so?
As soon you do that,
you'll be on the outs with Doctor Yoo.
They don't have a normal relationship.
But he's her real father.
Why are we even spending precious time
talking about her personal life?
Get back to work!
You're the one who brought it up.
- I hate you.
- Hate me? Are you crazy...
- Aren't you going to work?
- I scanned the book!
- Okay, that is true.
- Thank you.
I am going to put these in the fridge.
Gosh, I think I'm going to explode.
What would happen if you really exploded?
This is what would happen.
I hate you.
My dad and grandfather want to
have dinner with you.
The welcome party is tonight.
We can go a little later.
The adults are requesting it.
Do I have to say yes just because
adults requested it?
I told them the welcome party was tonight
and they told me to just come for dinner.
I'll tell them you don't want to go,
but I bet my dad will call you.
Where are we supposed to meet them?
More, please.
Good.
Take out the root.
Take it out.
Get ready for suture.
Give me some cottonoid. Thank you.
I think he had damage to his artery.
Will he get a cerebral infarction?
Don't make rash conclusions.
Do an angiography as soon as
surgery is complete.
It could be his non-dominant artery.
His blood pressure is dropping again.
Are you giving him blood?
It's done.
Do you want to finish up?
Yes.
Call General Surgery.
Hey.
Please, I'm asking you to do a good job.
I'll do a good job even if
no one requests it.
- Let's get ready.
- Okay.
We should get going too.
Good luck.
Doctor.
Where's Ji Hong?
He has an awake surgery
in the afternoon.
Ah, that's a really important surgery.
He has to succeed
on behalf of the hospital.
How did it go?
We should get a meal sometime.
Doctor!
Doctor, you must think of me too lightly.
I don't kill patients.
Of course, this time...
it was a success.
Doctor, Kim Soo Chul is out of surgery.
I have him ready for his angiography.
Let's go.
Doctor.
We've sent Kim Soo Chul up to the ICU.
His vitals are normal and I've told them
to call once he wakes up.
Good job.
It's a relief that the bleeding was
from his non-dominant artery.
Yeah, the other side is doing well.
Doctor.
You should be preparing for surgery.
What about you?
You're supposed to be assisting me.
- Doctor.
- What?
I'm going to do something right now.
Human to human.
Oh, it was wrinkled.
What were you imagining?
What do you mean
I was imagining something?
Seriously, I just saved your friend
and you're teasing me?
- Thank you.
- For what?
For everything.
What is she doing right now?
Is she playing me?
You can't move your arms and legs
very well, right?
No.
I told you before the surgery.
It's your first and second vertebrae.
So, it's the first and second vertebrae
in your neck that are broken.
That's where all the nerves that connect
to your body run through.
You said you'd screw on the broken bones.
The surgery was a success
and I've done my part.
It's your turn now.
Will I not be able to walk now?
You were by my side
when I wanted to die.
You didn't give me any advice.
You left me alone and let me
make my own choice.
Even though you were so young,
you had that kind of consideration.
I am sort of cool like that.
No, you are really cool.
Will my body and mind
be disconnected from now on?
If you're saying this to comfort me,
you can stop now.
Move your finger.
I can't move my arms and legs,
so how can I move my fingers?
I can't do it.
You did it.
I did. I did it.
Yeah... it's my turn now.
I will show you just how awesome
this Kim Soo Chul is.
You've always been awesome.
You don't need to show me anymore.
Find a nice woman.
Hey, you're the one who should
meet a nice guy.
Isn't the doctor who did surgery on me
your high school teacher?
You're right.
- He's married, right?
- No.
Don't date some old guy.
Even if you dated a billionaire,
you'd be too good for him.
Maybe if you were with me...
Kim Soo Chul, I see you are alive.
DBS needs to be micro-recorded.
Why is that?
- To find the spot causing tremors.
- Yes.
Once we find the area
to stop the tremors
how will we confirm that
she can do archery?
She'll have to shoot an arrow.
- During surgery?
- Of course.
I want you to monitor and
find the source of the tremor.
- Hye Jung, you watch over the patient.
- Okay.
Let's go.
Look, here's the tremor cello.
It's in the ventral intermediate
thalamic nucleus.
It's strange.
I can't feel anything.
Is something wrong?
The brain can't feel anything.
Don't worry.
You've reached the target.
We're almost there. Talk to the patient.
How do you feel?
My head feels empty.
I feel like the star of a movie,
like "The Matrix."
What about the tremors?
They're still there.
Okay...
The amp charges are at 131 to 135, right?
- Charge her with one volt.
- Okay.
The tremors are still there.
Has something gone wrong?
I can't see.
I can't see very well.
The patient is losing her eyesight.
The signal is off.
She's bleeding.
We could take the probe out and
continue once the bleeding stops.
Don't do that. Stop the bleeding now.
Use the biopsy needle
and use suction until you find it.
Give me the biopsy needle.
I can't see. I can't see a thing!
Something's wrong, isn't it?
Why is her hand shaking?
Something must be wrong.
Stop making a fuss, all of you.
You are bleeding a bit in your brain.
Doctor Hong will find it,
so don't worry.
What if my eyes stay like this?
Trust us, as well the choice
you made to have this surgery.
We could still wait...
We made the decision. Let's do it.
Vision issues during surgery
are only temporary.
You will see again soon.
Okay, wait just a moment.
- Doctor!
- He said to wait.
I've stopped the bleeding.
Let's continue.
I can see now.
Can you see your hand?
There are no more tremors!
Try grabbing my hand.
Oh! This is amazing.
It is amazing, right?
Put it down slowly.
Lift your right hand again and
move it back and forth slowly.
Slowly. That's good.
Put your finger on your nose.
Make a "V" with your fingers.
Thank you!
I'll bring in a bow and arrow.
Hey, where are the bow and arrow?
Bring it in now.
Take this and try it out.
Okay.
Okay, Olympic gold medalist
Lee Soo Jung will now shoot an arrow.
10 points!
You've gone through a lot.
All right, let's finish up now.
So exciting! Lee Soo Jung, Lee Soo Jung!
This is so exciting!
What was that earlier?
- What?
- "He said to wait."
Did you have to say that?
Do you want to look good to
Doctor Hong that badly?
What about you?
How can you act that way during surgery?
What did I do?
We could have taken out the probe and
waited for the bleeding to stop.
She had bled too much to wait.
Why do you think she couldn't see?
The blood was pressuring
her optic nerves.
Still, did you have to show off
and call me out like that?
It's important to calm the patient down.
If we start arguing over opinions,
the patient will become very anxious.
[PROFESSOR HONG JI HONG]
Yes?
Sit down.
Seo Woo.
As for your behavior today,
I can't just let it go.
It showed a lack of skills as a doctor.
It was the worst thing to do
within a team, as well.
Do you think what I'm saying is unfair?
I think you're going too far.
I see you haven't grasped the situation.
This was an awake surgery.
The patient was wide awake.
How would you feel if you were awake and
had people doing things to your brain?
Is telling you my opinion so wrong that
you question my skills as a doctor?
I'm not talking about your opinion.
Why are you pretending not to know?
Or are you really that ignorant?
If we agreed to be in this together,
we should all stick to a decision.
The decision was made
to stop the bleeding.
How can you keep saying to wait?
The patient will start to
doubt my choice.
Then what could happen?
Would you say this same thing if
Hye Jung acted the way I did?
Of course! This is about
your behavior at work.
How long are you going to compare
the way I treat you and Hye Jung?
Until I die.
Seo Woo.
I won't be talking to you
about these matters anymore.
Now I know there's
no point in talking to you.
Don't come into my surgeries
for the time being.
You can leave.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Hye Jung.
Hello, sir.
I really enjoyed the food you gave us.
- Thank you.
- No need to thank me.
If you want to eat more,
come by anytime.
This is my store.
She's being discharged tomorrow.
Okay.
How are you feeling?
I'm sure Hye Jung told you.
Why would you assume
I heard from Hye Jung?
Aren't you two dating?
- Does it seem that way?
- Oh, you're not.
I heard you're not married yet.
- So what? Did you get married?
- Yes.
You got married?
That's great.
People should get married early.
We'll move you into the
rehab facility in a week.
If you work hard on rehab,
you'll be back to your former self.
What a liar.
It's a little lie, not a big one.
You're a very cool guy,
getting married and all.
When I first saw you,
I thought you were a very cool guy.
You're very good looking too.
Tell me if you ever need anything.
Okay.
All right, rest up.
He's been in a mental stupor
for 14 days since surgery.
Motor function is normal.
- Have you followed up with a CT?
- Yes, nothing's wrong.
He's older, so he doesn't have
as much energy.
Check on his nutrition and
change his position often.
Yes, I will.
Don't worry. He will wake up soon.
Thank you, Doctor.
Why did you ask to see me?
What did I do so wrong?
You're the one who left.
Before you left, you tore up my heart.
I haven't had one night of good sleep
since the day you left.
Is she eating properly...
I won't be able to hold in my anger
if you keep this up.
What did I do?
What did I do to you?
Is it so wrong to try and
get closer to you?
Why are you suddenly trying
to be close to me?
We suddenly met up, didn't we?
You're my daughter.
A child may forget her parents...
but a parent never forgets a child.
A relationship between parents
and children is like any other.
We have never been close,
so how can we be now?
"Let's be close now."
You say that and now we are?
We've never spent time together.
We have no shared feelings or emotions.
[KANG KYUNG JOON]
Yes, Kyung Joon.
I should try to look stylish tonight.
Joong Dae, why are you taking that?
For these welcome parties,
they're going to make you drink a lot.
If you pass out and faint,
you will need this.
No, I don't need that stuff.
- I have a high tolerance.
- Oh, really?
I am no longer alienated.
I will finally get to lead a surgery.
Young Gook, have you been
dropped from residency before?
I can see why Chief Kyung Joon
always wants to hit you.
Ah, is that an old wound for you?
Yes, it is a wound and
you poured salt all over it.
- What is it?
- Oh, hi.
It's about Kim Jin Han with glioblastoma.
The 27-year-old grad student who
came into the ER with head pain.
She's Doctor Jung Yoon Do's patient.
She's getting surgery tomorrow afternoon.
You're amazing.
You know about all the patients
that are admitted?
Stop going overboard and sucking up.
Doctor Jung Yoon Do told me to
tell you to get ready for surgery.
Where is Doctor Jung?
Why would I attend the board meeting?
Secretary Kim,
I know my father ordered you to do this.
Don't do it.
I have no interest in
any sort of management.
When did you get here?
About Kim Jin Han's surgery...
With a glioblastoma surgery
fast judgment is
more important than technique.
You know that, right?
Why don't you do it with
Doctor Jin Seo Woo?
- Why?
- That's how it's always been.
If that's how it's always been,
do I have to keep doing it?
Do I only have to be close to
and date people I always have?
You're making a leap there.
We made a decision at that meeting.
The fellows will do surgeries according
to where the staff surgeons see fit.
I'm following that decision and
telling you to do the surgery.
You're telling me to do
what I usually do.
I got annoyed.
It's nice to see you smile.
Did you know your father
gave me stew to thank me?
I didn't know.
You should know that stuff.
It would be nice if you also knew
that it was really good.
You don't like hearing this.
- What?
- I didn't make you smile.
I like that look you have now.
What are you doing? It's so cheesy.
Women like it when guys act like this.
They start to complain that it's cheesy,
but they're eventually won over.
People get addicted to
these cheesy lines.
Oh... Doctor!
I am thinking of you as a woman.
Let's eat that cafeteria food tomorrow.
Let's eat together and then
go into surgery.
Your answer is "Yes."
One, two. One, two.
Mic test, mic test.
- Can you all hear me?
- Yes!
Thank you.
Gookil Hospital's
Neurosurgery Department.
Now, let's welcome Choi Kang Soo
and Pi Young Gook's first lead surgery!
Yes, thank you.
I am your MC for the night,
Gookil's eternal cutie...
Kang Kyung Joon! Hello, everyone!
Joong Dae, stop eating and clap.
First, Neurosurgery's captain and leader.
Let's hear a toast from
Section Chief Kim Tae Ho.
Kim Tae Ho, Kim Tae Ho,
Kim Tae Ho, Kim Tae Ho!
It's best to keep things simple
on days like this.
The Neurosurgery Department
deals with the brain.
The brain controls the human body.
Therefore, the Neurosurgery Department
controls everything!
- Welcome!
- Grandpa.
We live in the same building,
but why is it that I rarely see you?
- I'm sorry.
- Sit down.
Yes.
We kept saying that we would have dinner,
but it took so long to happen.
I'm sorry. I've been negligent.
We ordered already.
I have an appointment and
have to leave in two hours.
I see.
I met your father and
he's hurt that you don't ever call.
- You should call him.
- Yes, I will.
Seeing the two of you sitting there,
you two look alike.
You're right.
- Yoon Do?
- Yes, sir.
We have so much work to do.
We need the right person.
The hospital will grow many times larger.
Once our health care becomes privatized
and we become a company
in the stock market
it will open up a
whole new world to us doctors.
We have a lot of expectations
for the two of you.
Seo Woo will do a good job.
You will too, Senior.
I won't be involved in management.
If I were interested in that,
I would be working at my dad's company.
I became a doctor to
free myself from that.
Then let your in-laws take over.
Seo Woo will do it.
Excuse me a moment.
Excuse me.
Senior... Senior!
Are you feeling uncomfortable?
- I'm leaving.
- What?
It's boring and uncomfortable.
Still, how can you leave in
the middle of a dinner with elders?
You're not that kind of person.
We haven't started eating yet.
- You should speak to them for me.
- Why should I?
It's less embarrassing for you that way.
I'm a bit confused lately.
I'm seeing things about myself
that weren't there before.
Is having dinner with my family
that unpleasant?
Enough so that you would do this to me?
We've known each other for 10 years
and there are no sparks.
- Sparks on one side are still sparks.
- You can't start a fire with that.
I will guarantee you this.
Something bad will
happen to you. I know it.
Bad things happen to anyone
who loves Hye Jung.
That's the jinx she has.
Then... I'll just fall into bad luck.
Nice shot! That was great.
One for Chief, one for Professor Hong.
One for the pretty Doctor Yoo.
I'll have two.
Over there.
Oh, Doctor Jung Yoon Do is finally here!
Oh, you can't just sit down
when you just got here.
Since you're late,
you have to drink this.
That punk.
One shot.
One more time, one more time,
one more time!
One more time!
Also, you cannot forget the last step.
Bowing and drinking.
First, Doctor Hong Ji Hong!
What? How do you do it?
I'll do it first.
Please wish me luck!
How can I do that?
Oh my! A man should be able to do it.
Even she can do it.
- She's not a regular girl.
- Doctor!
I'll be his black rose.
Doctor Hong is kind of bad at this stuff.
Give it to me. I can do it.
It doesn't look so hard.
Just put it here like this and do it.
Ouch!
Oh no! Look, it's red here. Does it hurt?
- It doesn't hurt.
- It looks like it hurts.
- I'll do it again.
- No, don't do it.
Doctor Hong is bad at this kind of thing.
Doctor Yoo, why don't you
be his black rose?
Doctor, I said I would do it.
Why are you saying that?
It's just your forehead...
Okay, I just have to knock it in.
Wish me luck!
Eat.
I'm sorry.
He must think very lowly of you to leave
without even saying goodbye to us.
It's not like that.
Then is it because he looks down on me?
Relationships between men and women
are no different from any other.
The stronger one calls the shots.
You can't take charge
in one relationship.
Can you really handle Gookil Hospital?
Why would I trust you
and give you this hospital?
Stop, let her eat.
Dad!
This is what we're up to.
When are you coming?
Jung Yoon Do, that bastard.
This is not too bad.
You awful people.
Give it to me.
You want me to do it too? It's okay.
Just give it to me now.
- This is nothing for me.
- Okay!
First year resident Choi Kang Soo.
I will work very hard!
One shot, one shot, one shot!
- Hey, Kang Soo.
- Choi Kang Soo!
Hey, Choi Kang Soo!
Wake up, Choi Kang Soo. Choi Kang Soo!
He's not breathing.
- Intubate him.
- Here?
- We don't have the instruments.
- Oh, you can't do it without them.
Senior.
Shall we intubate him?
Joong Dae, you really are so giving!
What did you want to talk about?
You were my black rose,
so I should do something for you too.
- What could it be?
There was a place like this?
There was.
- Have you tried shooting?
- No.
Watch me do it. You hold it like this.
It's not working very well.
It must be the gun.
You give it a try.
I think something's wrong with the gun.
Wow! You really are something.
What, Doctor...
Two points! Two points!
Three points! Three points!
Two points!
[YOO HYE JUNG 735]
735!
Write mine down too.
[HONG JI HONG 386]
386 points.
Let's play another game!
Can you get it?
Got it.
Here.
Thank you.
Should I get another one for you?
This is so fun. I feel like a kid again.
- You like competing, don't you?
- Yes.
We're doing everything you like today.
- Let's go!
So, the person who makes it to
the goal post first wins.
One... two, three!
I won!
- Are you that happy?
- Yes.
Should we do it one more time?
Okay.
I'll lose for you this time.
It was the first time a woman
grabbed on to my hand first.
Subtitles by DramaFever