Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 9]
Three!
I can't do it anymore.
Look at the stars.
They're so beautiful.
- Hye Jung.
- Yes?
My arm is long, right?
You can use my arm.
That line gave me goosebumps.
If you get revenge,
you can find peace from hurt and anger.
Revenge helps you to find peace
and strength to move forward.
I cannot rest until I achieve my goal.
However, when I'm next to this man,
I find myself falling asleep.
Open this for me.
That's enough drinking.
- Open it for me.
- Stop drinking. You've had enough.
Hey, aren't you going to leave?
I have to close up now.
You came here so late and
now you won't go.
This is all because of you.
All right. I'm sorry.
What's with you?
Are you being sarcastic right now?
She's making sarcastic remarks at me.
Hey, be careful.
Will you please do something about her?
I've never seen her so drunk before,
so I don't know what to do.
- Oh, my head.
- Here.
Okay, let's get going now.
- Let's go.
- No, I'm not leaving.
I'm going to blow this place up.
Why are you doing this to me?
This is all your fault.
If you hadn't brought Hye Jung around
this wouldn't have happened in my life.
Put this down and let's go now.
If you want blow this place up,
do it tomorrow.
Let's get going, okay?
You have to buy some bombs too.
- This is all your fault.
- Let's go.
Go to the hardware store
and buy some bombs.
Bye.
Gosh, that girl is such a nuisance.
- Seriously...
- 22!
Oh, you scared me!
Who are you, Mister?
I'm Ahn Joong Dae.
Seriously. what are you saying
you're going to "give me"?
Is everyone gone?
Yes, they're gone. Now, go!
Why was I the only one left behind?
Excuse me. Do you have ramen here?
I'm hungry after taking a nap.
I'm not giving you any, Ahn Joong Dae!
You little punk, seriously.
Do you know what you put us through?
What is this?
What do you think it is?
It's glucose. What do you think?
You said you had a
high alcohol tolerance.
Why did you lie?
- Oh, did I pass out?
- We're talking about your life here.
It only ended well because Joong Dae
brought the intubation kit.
If he didn't, who knows...
- What do you think you're doing?
- I'm sick.
Let me sleep when I'm sick.
- Gosh, you punk!
- Wait, look.
All right, rest.
Why is he suddenly acting that way?
Your arm hurts because of me,
doesn't it?
No, I'm just rotating it.
Is your arm really okay?
My head was really heavy, right?
Was that your head?
I thought it was a feather.
Thank you, Doctor.
I haven't slept so well in a long time.
Are you just getting home now?
Aren't you getting in too late?
You sounds like the
school principal or something.
Teacher, I am her guardian.
There are many weird people these days.
When it was raining last time
I heard a crazy girl and guy
were dancing in the park.
What if our Hye Jung happens to run into
one of those strange people?
That's true.
I'll get going.
Bye.
- Bye!
- Yeah, bye.
I suppose anyone who runs into
Hye Jung would be unlucky.
Hey, wait for me!
Ah, I'm so tired.
How come you finished up so late today?
It's way past the store's closing time.
Seo Woo showed up
and caused a scene again.
She didn't show up for the party.
I guess she came late.
She got very drunk and left.
That doctor Young Gook took her.
He seems very nice.
He's tall and good looking.
Young Gook is your type, isn't he?
Did you notice?
Yes, I noticed.
You should bring him by often.
You're not going be the
only one dating, are you?
Now that you're dating,
I want to date too.
Is this what dating is?
Oh, you know that tall guy
who came at the end?
You know that guy who looks sort of
like a Siberian husky dog?
Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
His name is Jung Yoon Do?
He was a little bit strange.
He was staring at you and
Teacher Hong the entire time.
Which of you does he like?
I'm going to bet 500 won
that he likes you.
You're just getting back now?
You seem upset that I'm coming back now.
What are you doing this late
instead of sleeping?
I had some things to think about.
- So, are you done thinking?
- Yes.
Doctor, I like Doctor Yoo Hye Jung.
Why are you telling me that?
I heard that you and Doctor Yoo Hye Jung
have a special relationship.
Though a special relationship is
different than being in love.
I've heard that you've only recently been
in a relationship as a man and woman.
And?
Maybe I'm overthinking things.
You two are not married yet.
So, I believe I still have
a right to pursue Hye Jung.
- Does Hye Jung know this too?
- Of course, she knows.
Would I tell you first without
telling the woman I like?
That's true.
So, why are you telling me all of this?
I really hate to stab people in the back.
Since I know you two have
some sort of relationship
I don't want to be the kind of person
to scheme and take her away.
How do you plan on taking her away?
Did I say I'd let you?
- What?
- I like it.
You're very manly.
A man should be this way.
But, just so you know...
I've never lost something
I've wanted before.
I'm happy you recognize all of
Hye Jung's charms.
I'm glad Hye Jung knows just
how popular she is with men.
Wait...
Aren't you worried about me at all?
Why would I be?
You're going to help Hye Jung and me
realize how strong our relationship is.
Doctor!
Good luck with the fight.
Wow, he puts up a good front.
What's with that overconfidence?
You never know with men and women
until they enter the wedding hall!
What is this? I feel like I've lost
when it hasn't started yet.
That's so cute.
How do you get emoticons like this?
This is all I have.
What are you doing tomorrow
on your day off?
I'm very busy. I'm not telling you.
Then, what about the next day?
I was going to study.
Can you leave the morning empty for me?
Okay.
[KIM CHI HYUN]
[SOUTH YANGJU GOOKIL HOSPITAL]
I'm sorry. I can't give you
the records for Kang Mal Soon.
Why is that?
We destroy files that are
over 10 years old.
It's gone now.
This is Gookil Hospital admissions.
Do you know where Doctor Kim Chi Hyun,
who was a resident 13 years ago, is now?
Do you mean Section Chief Kim Chi Hyun?
We're not seeing patients yet.
I'm a junior of Doctor Kim Chi Hyun.
I wanted to drop by.
Who are you?
You were a surgical resident 13 years ago
at this hospital, right?
Has it been 13 years already?
How did you know that?
I was a patient's guardian back then.
But it wouldn't have been me back then.
The section chief would've been
the one giving treatment.
It was you who filled out
the paperwork, wasn't it?
Who, exactly, are you?
Why are you being so sensitive?
If you wanted to ask this,
you should've put in an official request.
What the heck is this?
If I put in an official request,
would you have even met me?
I did not lead that surgery.
Why are you coming to me about this?
You were a physician
and you filled out her chart.
I want to know everything that happened
that day in the operating room.
How can I remember something
that happened 13 years ago?
I performed so many surgeries.
Many patients die during surgery.
Even if you can't remember,
force yourself to remember.
This surgery from 13 years ago
may have been insignificant to you.
But some people have thought about it
every single day since.
You can't sue even if you find anything.
The statute of limitations on this
is 10 years and it's too late.
I know.
Even if there was an error,
a legal punishment is difficult.
However, legal punishments are not
the only kind of punishment.
What is it that you want?
An apology, the truth...
To make people pay.
These are the rules that any
healthy society should abide by.
Anyway, I have nothing to do
with this surgery.
I was not the lead.
Sorry. I'm busy.
I'll leave this here.
Think about it carefully.
Call me.
Hello.
I want to look more bright.
Can you choose a color for me?
Sure, I'll pick out some tints for you.
You must be going to meet your boyfriend.
Oh, no.
Then a person you're flirting with?
I'm meeting my grandma.
She likes pretty things.
I envy you. My grandma passed away.
I'll give you lots of samples.
Give them to your grandmother.
Grandma, do you like the flowers?
You like small and pretty things.
I'm sure you'd like these.
Well, I suppose it's okay
as long as I like them.
When you bought me my necklace...
you said you'd be
the one looking at it.
Grandma, I haven't forgotten.
That life of yours that you loved
until the very end...
I won't ever forget your life.
Why do I keep talking to myself?
Just like you always did.
I really miss you.
Don't get hung up on a guy.
No one will love you
as much as your dad.
Yoon Do has no manners
to treat elders like that.
If it weren't for his father,
I wouldn't have let him be.
Don't drive him away though.
Men are weak to women who wait for them.
Pretend to wait for him.
How can I pretend?
Business is about moving
people's hearts by pretending.
I'm a doctor.
You're a doctor who knows business.
Don't focus only on one thing
and be more flexible.
Hi. Morning.
How much do you hate fishing
that you need my help?
I don't hate it. It's just boring.
I do want to spend time
with my dad though.
If you're with me, the problem is solved.
My dad must be here.
- Should we get out?
- Yes.
Dad.
This is my junior.
Hello, my name is Yoo Hye Jung.
Yoo Hye Jung?
Hye Jung? I think I've heard that name.
Is she that person who called
when we were fishing before?
Wow, you remember that?
Come this way. Let's walk together.
Yes, okay.
What do you like about my Ji Hong?
- Pardon me?
- Dad, why are you saying that?
I'll say whatever I want.
- Grandpa!
- Hello.
Dad, you're here early.
Oh, I finished golfing early.
I wanted to show you
something great, Seo Woo.
This is the place our dreams will start.
Gookil Medical Corporation.
We still have a long way to go.
No, starting it up is half of it.
Your father and I are on it.
You only need to
reap the fruits, all right?
Okay.
I will live for the three of us
and our dream from now on.
Yes.
It's today, right?
Yes, I should head back in.
I should take a look to see
how it's playing out.
What's going on?
It says National Tax Administration
on the boxes.
I didn't think it would get this big.
It's suffering a big loss
to gain a small profit.
If you consider what we
could lose later, this is nothing.
Board Director Hong is done now.
Are both of your parents alive?
You're still young.
I'm sure they are alive.
Why did I even ask that?
My mother passed away.
It must be because I'm getting closer
to the age where people die.
When did you first become
close to Ji Hong?
Spicy fish stew is the best
when you catch the fish yourself.
Enough with the questions.
You're making her nervous.
Were you nervous?
No.
- I'll do it.
- No, it's okay.
Yes, it's okay.
It's fine for you to just sit here.
Do you know how to cook?
No, I'm not very good.
That's good too.
It's fine for you to just sit here.
Dad, you're being very cheesy.
Okay, let's eat now.
Be careful. It's hot.
Thank you.
- Bon appetit.
- Enjoy.
[DOCTOR KIM TAE HO]
Hold on, Dad. I need to take this.
We have a problem.
The National Tax Administration is here.
Your father's stocks
became a bigger issue.
I'm with him right now.
I'll call you back in a moment.
Yes.
- Eat some of this.
- Thank you.
I want to look bolder.
What do I need for a smokey look?
I'll help you out.
Miss, the color of your eyes
is so beautiful.
Brown eyeshadow looks good
with light eyes like yours.
How about some black eyeliner, as well?
- I'll take them.
- I'll wrap them up for you.
My dad's driver will take you
to the hospital.
I can take a taxi.
I'm sorry I can't drive you myself.
It's okay.
Should I ask him what's wrong?
Hye Jung, thank you.
My dad seemed so happy.
I don't think I was a dutiful son,
so I feel a bit bad.
Don't ask.
- Did you send her off well?
- Yes.
This is all so absurd.
How could I be harming the hospital?
That's just unbelievable.
I spent my entire life working for
the hospital and the patients.
I think someone planned this.
Otherwise, there's no way everything
would work out so negatively.
I'll call a board meeting.
It's time for a decision.
Are you going to quit?
I should quit.
I'm sure they will be very happy,
the people who planned this.
What is this?
Are you a food fighter or something?
You're eating quite a variety of food.
Hey, this is all mine.
Young Gook!
Joong Dae, is our hospital
going to fall into ruin?
If the government is coming
to investigate and all...
It will be in the news too.
What if this hospital closes down
and we all become unemployed?
That won't happen.
Our hospital will never close down.
We could get fired.
- How do you know?
- I studied business.
There's definitely a
hidden plot behind this.
The National Tax Administration
doesn't usually visit hospitals.
Someone made it happen.
Right, this guy took a different path
through medical school.
So, who do you think it was?
There's Board Director Hong
and Director Jin.
It's a power struggle.
Wow, Joong Dae!
This is the most intelligent
I've ever seen you look.
He knows that's an insult.
Go on and eat a lot.
Who is calling me now?
[SEO WOO]
Young Gook, you chose to
side with the right person.
You'll make it to professor level,
Professor Pi.
- Professor Pi, Professor Pi.
- You'll be Professor Dae.
Professor Pig.
Professor Pig!
That's a bit harsh.
Hey... what's with you?
I'm going to study.
- Going around like that?
- Yes.
This is a hospital.
The way you look right now is not
how a doctor should look.
Are you rebelling against Doctor Jung?
Who is he that I would rebel against him?
- Then, what?
- I'm going to live recklessly.
I lived my life as a good person
and what did I get in return?
I'm always on your side
because we are friends.
Why bother stating something so obvious?
Why are you so startled?
I'm just coming into my room.
I was on my way out.
Let's talk.
You and I can't continue on like this.
You've seen me before at a neurosurgery
academic conference, right?
And you avoided me?
Otherwise, how could we never have met?
There aren't many women in neurosurgery.
Yes, I have seen you before.
You're right that I avoided you.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
I might be a traumatic memory to you,
but you are to me, as well.
- Why would I be?
- Because I liked you.
I envied you, too.
I was happy when you
accepted me as a friend.
Then things went wrong between us.
I found out you were at this hospital.
I prepared myself to meet you.
Even so, it was difficult
when I did meet you.
You didn't get to prepare yourself,
so it must've been harder for you.
I knew you planned it.
You came to this hospital in order to
take everything that is mine.
Why? Was Doctor Hong not enough?
You knew back then, too,
that I liked him as more than a teacher.
You won't believe me,
but I didn't know.
Why do you say I wouldn't believe you?
You assume I'm talking to you
but won't believe anything you say?
My reason for coming here
has nothing to do with you.
So who does it have to do with?
I'm certain you came here
because you have a goal.
If I can understand that goal,
I'll believe everything you say.
I can't tell you.
Are you saying you're giving up on
improving relations with me?
Should I take your silence
to mean "yes"?
Let's be clear about this.
You're the one who just rejected me.
Boss!
You suffered a lot!
Do you still think I'm trash?
Do me one favor.
What is it?
Please don't harm that man.
He's already been hurt.
Who?
I don't know who you're talking about.
Don't come back hurt again.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung of Neurosurgery.
Please come to the parking lot.
I repeat.
Doctor Yoo Hye Jung of Neurosurgery.
Please come to the parking lot.
Adios.
I'll listen to what women
tell me to do every now and then.
Thank you.
Wait!
What is it?
You must be so happy, Doctor.
Give me ride in it sometime.
Give me Boss's personal information file.
Why? Do you want to thank him?
Doctor, did you see the car?
We should all go look at it.
I know it's a capitalistic society.
Let's consider the
integrity of capitalism.
I wouldn't even accept it.
I wouldn't accept it either.
This number doesn't exist.
Give me the second number listed.
The guardian's number.
That's probably a fake number too.
He wouldn't leave a trace behind.
What should I do?
Give it to me.
You shouldn't have brought up
capitalism and integrity.
What's so funny over there?
Doctor! Doctor Yoo got a sports car gift
from one of the patients.
It's a foreign car, at that.
Where is Doctor Jung Yoon Do?
You only care about Doctor Jung Yoon Do.
He'll be here.
Here comes the tiger...
Is Kim Jin Han's surgery prep going well?
Yes.
- What about lunch in the cafeteria?
- Later, I have something to do.
You like her that much?
What?
You want to hear it here or outside?
Shouldn't you be seeing out-patients?
Are you worrying about me?
I'm not worrying--
Let go.
Why are you acting like I'm a
crazy person who liked you by myself?
You knew exactly how I felt.
You knew how I felt and told me to go,
but your eyes told me to stay.
Was I imagining that?
Yeah, I was attracted to you for a
moment but it was a brief moment.
The unfair thing about this is...
you didn't always only have eyes for me.
I can endure it if you insult me
because I love you.
But I can't stand by and
watch you insult my family.
Fine, you felt insulted by me
all that time.
Let's call it even since you slapped me.
I had felt sorry towards you,
but now that burden is gone.
My love wasn't so light that
we can call it even with this.
Then what do you want?
You're always attracted to damaged women
who have a strong nature.
You say you love Hye Jung?
That's not love.
That's your emotional complex.
I'm going to get rid of your complex.
- You're doing psych analysis now?
- I'm going to live crookedly now.
People who really want to live crookedly
don't announce it to the world.
This world is all wrong.
In order to live in this world,
I have to live crookedly.
How can a person like Hye Jung be loved
and live proudly in this world?
You're the one who needs to get rid of
your complex about her.
Even you see her appeal.
You're busy making excuses
and being afraid to do anything.
But she does it all.
And she's pretty.
She's pretty?
You must be really blinded by her.
She's pretty. Prettier than you.
It drives you insane to hear me
talk this way, doesn't it?
I know you very well.
I know how to hurt you too.
Don't try your awkward psych analysis
on me and apply it to your own life.
I'm not interested in you as a woman,
but I do see you as a sibling.
That's it.
I'll accept your anger
until you've cooled down.
Just like you said, I'm partly
to blame for mistaken feelings.
But don't slap me next time.
It feels like crap.
She's here. She's here.
- Do it.
- Okay, okay.
- Doctor.
- What is it?
About the car...
you know, the one from Boss.
Yeah, I don't know what to do with it.
I don't know how to return it.
Should I donate it to the hospital?
What would the hospital do
with a sports car?
You should just drive it.
I believe there are no free things
in life, so I don't want it.
I believe there are many
free things in life.
I won't ask you for the car.
Can we ride in it just once?
Doctor, me too.
I have never been in
a foreign car before.
I don't think it's right
to be born female
and never get to ride a car like that.
Since you said "never"...
I said it's okay.
It's not okay with me.
Let's just say that I drank it.
I'm not the only one who
doesn't like free things.
I'm going to buy you that
fresh kiwi juice you like so much.
Yes.
Section Chief Kim Chi Hyun is here
from South Yangju.
I said we could talk on the phone.
Why did you insist on meeting?
It's this.
What is this?
It's a surgery you led when
you were in South Yangju.
The patient's guardian came to see me.
She was a young woman.
It's been over 10 years.
What does she want to do?
She wants to know everything that
happened in the operating room.
She says she wants us to
pay for what we did.
It's too late, legally.
Does she know me?
You're famous, so all she'd have to do
is search on the internet.
She knows me, but went to you first.
It's a scheme for money.
It didn't seem that way.
What else could it be?
How can you still be so naive
about the world?
I'm sorry.
Show me this time that you
really are one of my people.
Then when will you bring me
up to Seoul headquarters?
You killed my grandmother, right?
Did you kill her?
You said you'd remove the cancer.
What is going on with our security?
A patient file that could not
be accessed was leaked.
Find out who accessed it.
Yes, sir.
Aren't you going to the board meeting?
I am.
Doo Shik will announce his retirement.
He won't stay because of his honor.
Some of you here...
Some of you here today
may believe that our hospital's troubles
have been brought on by me.
Personally, I have learned a lot
from this incident.
If I were to think about my own dignity,
I'd give up being director of the board.
I want to show people that I am innocent.
I realized that stepping down
is not the answer.
I promise to take responsibility for
what has happened...
and finish things up.
You've changed.
You're not like you were before.
This is why people should leave politics
when they get old.
What is it that you want to say?
I feel bad seeing you
turn into a greedy, old man.
Do you think I'm staying on
because of greed?
Is it not that?
Then, was it Ji Hong who
coached you into doing this?
Since when did you have to concern
yourself with what he thinks?
He's not even your son.
He's not your blood.
Why, you!
Don't you dare talk about
Ji Hong in that way.
I won't let you get away with this.
It's because of you that
our taxes are being investigated.
How will you take responsibility?
If you had something to say,
you should've said it then.
You said nothing then,
so why say something now?
I assumed you would retire.
Who knew you'd insist on staying on?
Someone planned this whole thing
and leaked it.
I'm looking into it.
If it was someone in the hospital,
I need to find out why.
My judgment is not dead yet.
So don't get in my way.
Don't worry about he said.
- What?
- Before...
He said you're not my son or whatever.
What are you doing?
I stopped caring about
that stuff long ago.
You're like a boy going through puberty
getting in fights over that.
Are you making fun of me too?
Dad!
- Are you all right?
- I'm fine, I'm fine.
Tripping is not a big deal.
You don't need to worry.
How long has it been since
your last physical exam?
Why do you ask?
You've been going for check-ups
and following up, right?
I'm all better now.
Why would I bother?
Dad!
I'm going to lose my hearing.
Get some tests done while you're here.
Later, it's such a pain to do it.
That's why you should do it.
If I do that now
there will be rumors that I'm dying
even though there is nothing wrong.
In a situation like this,
I can't do it based on just your feeling.
You misspoke twice during
the board meeting.
Your face muscles twisted too.
I think it's facial numbness.
No, no. It's not.
I just pronounced it wrong.
Your facial muscles changed.
You're just too sensitive.
Your body tilted a bit.
I think it's ataxia.
It could be the
Vestibular Schwannoma again.
Get a medical exam, Dad.
Looks normal.
Why would you let him hit you?
What happened with Director Hong?
Does he know you did it?
He wouldn't stay put if he knew.
What if he finds out about the slush fund
in the hospital foundation?
That won't happen.
That will never happen, Dad.
What were you doing
letting it get this bad?
It's too big and it's
pressing on the brain stem.
Surgery will be hard.
It's all my fault.
No, it's my fault.
I call him my mentor and teacher,
but I didn't even follow up.
What do we do now?
What else can we do?
You need to do surgery.
How can I do this surgery on him?
If something goes wrong,
I won't be able to live.
Then, who will do it?
I can't do it.
Doctor Jung Yoon Do
will be better than me.
He has better hands than me and his
surgeries are the most successful lately.
No one can find out.
Even if the surgery is a success,
he needs to rest for several months.
Tell him to retire from his position as
director of the board.
Nothing is more important than life.
Please make sure no one finds out until
my dad makes his decision.
You're just an orphan.
You ought to know your place.
Why are you so good at studying?
You need to get beaten up.
Why do we need be stressed out
because of you?
You may be good at studying.
But you will always be at
the bottom your whole life.
It's you guys who will be
at the bottom all your lives.
You think I'm getting beaten up
because I'm not strong?
I'm letting you hit me
because I'm an orphan.
Stop showing off.
That's enough... for today.
Like you said, I'm not someone
for you to compete with.
You punk, are you crazy?
What are you kids doing there?
Let's stop.
Today's not the only day.
We always have tomorrow.
Are you okay?
I'm okay, Director.
You don't seem okay to me.
It will take two weeks to fully heal.
I'm okay because it will
be better in two weeks.
Aren't you overthinking things
too much for a man?
You must enjoy losing.
- Reality is not a movie.
- What?
Hitting people without thinking
about the consequences.
Getting overly emotional and
putting people in danger.
Do you like these types of things?
That's how junior high kids act.
Do you want to come with me?
No... do you want to live with me?
I'm saying no.
I'm going to marry a woman.
Did I ask to marry you?
How would you like to be my son?
I will accept your congrats and
congratulate you too.
Your dream of having the same job
as your son came true.
Why did you ask to see me here?
Are those mine?
It grew a lot in that time.
Gosh, life is a scary thing.
Even cancer cells are working away
so hard to try and live.
It is definitely the
Vestibular Schwannoma.
It really is strong.
You need to admit yourself.
I won't get surgery.
Nothing is more important
than your health.
It's already progressed this far.
We can't delay the surgery.
I can't do it now.
How can I with the way things are?
Dad.
Please...
I no longer want to send off
the people I love before me.
Wow!
Oh, this car is so beautiful.
Doctor, let's go to Gangbyeon.
We can go to this hotel there.
Hotel? Are you crazy?
We can't do that.
We're not in that kind of relationship.
Did I say I wanted to sleep with you?
I wanted to eat pizza.
There's a good pizza place
on the hill by that hotel.
Today, I'm pretending to be
from a wealthy family.
- What?
- You have to open the door for me.
Right.
Wow! This is so nice.
- What are you looking for?
- This.
Why don't you just drive?
If you act awkward like this,
you'll ruin my whole rich girl act.
Right now, I'm on a date with a guy who
has 20 foreign cars like this.
What's with her Cinderella fantasy?
Why did Cinderella have to
lose her glass slipper?
She made all the girls in the world
look for a prince.
Hurry. Let's go.
Oh my, oh my! Wow, it's amazing!
So amazing!
- Should we get going?
- Yes!
I'll drive around the parking lot once.
Why?
There's no insurance on this car,
so we can't get into an accident.
Why are you worrying suddenly?
Don't worry about it.
You're a great driver. What accident?
I am a good driver,
but I don't have a license.
What? What kind of guy doesn't have
a driver's license?
I've been so busy
that I couldn't get one.
I'll get it next year.
If you want to drive,
you can do it, Nurse Hyun.
What?
What was I thinking
pretending to be a rich girl?
Stop! I'll drive the car.
Okay, but why are you getting mad?
I'm in big trouble now.
What are we going to do now?
Hey, just focus on eating when we eat.
Oh, isn't that Doctor Yoo?
- Yes.
- Why are you drawing that?
Are you still dreaming of
being a comic book artist?
Joong Dae, you don't throw away dreams.
You should develop them.
This might be my last work
before I'm beaten to death.
Are you not going to eat?
Hello, what brings you by?
- Do you want some noodles?
- No, it's okay.
I can't live after doing wrong.
What are you doing there?
- Doctor.
- Are you hiding from me?
- No.
- Give me the car keys.
You look like you're about to cry.
I guess the car is very good because
I rammed into the other car very hard.
The damage wasn't too bad though.
How can you leave it like this?
I was going to take it to get fixed.
I was on duty the whole time,
so I didn't have time.
Get it fixed quickly.
- Is that it?
- Yes.
- It's not enough? Should I hit you?
- No.
It'll cost a lot to fix.
If you don't plan on driving it,
do I really need to fix it?
Okay.
Gosh...
Doctor, should I keep waiting here?
I have surgery soon.
Come in.
Both of you, come over here.
I want Doctor Jung Yoon Do
to do surgery on this patient.
I want Doctor Yoo Hye Jung to assist.
Who is it?
It's Director Hong Doo Shik.
I don't want to do it.
The entire hospital will be
paying very close attention.
I don't want the attention.
I don't want anyone but the three of us
to know about the surgery.
Don't ask me why.
It's large in size and pressing on the
brain stem, so it won't be easy.
Also, you say it's a relapse?
Rather than total removal,
I'd like you to use lateral SOC.
Then I want you to use
radiosurgery for the rest.
I think total removal is better.
It relapsed after he tried radiosurgery.
Total removal?
His facial paralysis is not bad,
so we save those nerves.
The trans-lab approach is best to
remove the cancer completely.
That surgery takes a long time.
No, take the safe route.
If you do not want total removal
there's no need for me
to do this surgery.
You know me. I'm all or nothing.
All or nothing.
Don't be overconfident.
Be humble with this surgery.
If you don't trust me,
you can ask someone else.
I'm not saying I don't trust you.
I'm asking you to be careful.
You're not being your normal self.
All surgeries have risk.
"Be careful" are words that mean fear.
It's over for a surgeon
if they feel fear.
Are you scaring me before
the surgery has even started?
Is it true you're going for
a total removal?
Don't remove it dangerously. Be safe.
There's that word "safe" again.
My principle is sub total clear.
Don't worry.
I'm making this request.
You're acting like the general public.
This pressure and request.
And you, Doctor Jung,
are speaking in a very improper tone.
Do you speak this way to
family members of other patients?
They don't treat doctors this way.
They trust the doctors.
Do you trust me?
I did not want this patient.
I can quit now if you want me to.
Well, I have another surgery to do.
Irrigation.
Doctor Hong is acting that way
because he's scared.
He's worried something could go wrong.
You're the same too.
What do you mean?
You're scared something could go wrong
and you'll get all the blame.
That's why you're acting tough.
Who says I'm scared?
Don't be scared. I'll be assisting you.
I'll be helping so you don't
have to be scared.
- You have an ego.
- Yes.
When you grow up in a poor environment,
it helps to have a healthy ego.
Should we cut this?
Yes, I think we should cut it.
Okay.
I searched your work history
before you came here.
Am I livestock for you to judge
or something?
You are very talented.
You asked me if I trust you?
I trust you as a doctor.
Should I bow down in thanks?
As a patient's guardian,
I don't trust you.
If this surgery goes wrong...
I will kill you.
When doctors become
guardians of a loved one...
they become weak people.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[DOCTOR CRUSH]
- Are you happy?
- I am happy.
I'm alive and I have a person I like.
Finally, we are eating
our cafeteria meal.
I hope the surgery goes badly.
I refuse to leave my position.
I heard that Doctor Yoo Hye Jung
received a car as a gift.
We're rivals over one woman.
Do you know how long I've known her?
We're still only flirting.
- Your hand is really big.
- Oh, yeah?
You still come at me suddenly,
just like before.