Did Han Gi Tak really have a younger sibling?
When should we meet?
Just a minute.
(Episode 11)
Did I startle you?
No, there's no reason to be.
Your friend is waiting for you.
I'll call you later.
Let's go home together.
"Bring Song Yi Yeon as the model."
That's what he said.
I had the same feeling about him since the fashion show.
The chairman is awesome.
Wouldn't that be too much for you, though?
What are you talking about?
I needed to make an extraordinary measure in order to save this store.
What's more extraordinary than this?
At any rate, I've got a great friend from up above.
Please do a good job, Young Soo.
You don't need to ask me that.
We're much closer than that.
Let's get Yi Yeon's signature on the paper...
and go for a drink tonight. How does that sound?
Perfect!
(Model Contract for Sunjin Department Store)
Why would I?
I'm on an upward trend but they're going downhill.
Why would I get myself involved with them again?
No, you won't be getting involved with them.
It's more like facing-off with Cha Jae Gook.
Well... From their point of view,
the store will improve their image with me as their model.
However,
if something unpleasant breaks out again...
and my reputation is trashed, who'll be responsible for it?
It'll never be trashed.
I'm not like Cha Jae Gook who only cares about the exterior.
I'm renovating the store from inside-out.
Hey, Yi Yeon! Do you know what it took to make this happen?
Don't get personal feelings involved in business. Just get lost!
I used to be the top Korean star.
So I only work with the experts in the field.
You're right. You should make your choices carefully.
Plus, did I ever ask you to help me?
Are you going to be like this? You just need to follow along.
Stop giving yourself credits for it!
I never asked you to do any of this. You shouldn't flaunt!
Please, don't raise your temper.
Let's just talk over...
What, then? Do I look like I'm doing this for myself?
Gosh, this is lame.
- Lame?
I'm not lame.
I'm Lee Hae Joon!
Why didn't you pick up your phone?
I told you we could come home together.
I thought this over...
but I think it's best for you to leave after two months.
Come on.
You can't even look straight at my eyes.
I guess I'm on your mind.
Yes, you get in my way.
I'll be leaving in a month and I'm not coming back.
I'm just someone you bumped into.
You can tell me about the things...
you can't tell anybody else as if I'm the flowing wind.
And if you are tired,
you can lean by my side.
I'm also fine with you yelling at me or complaining.
I'll let you be.
You'll never get a better offer than this.
Mr Lee, why would you...
I'll do everything that Young Soo couldn't do before he left.
You can consider it that way.
I just want to...
protect your family.
Oh, you can go.
So what if he's tall and got a sweet voice?
He can't keep playing with me.
How annoying.
Don't worry about it. I won't let him have me.
- Oh, dear.
- Da Hye, I haven't heard anything.
Nothing at all.
Da Hye!
Can you make us something?
This is not the bar.
Hey!
Wait until you finish this.
So you decided to run away from home?
That girl would only miss me once I'm not there.
I'm not a saint.
I can't take her any more!
Thank you.
Wait, Ms Shin! You should join us.
No, I'll pass.
Come on. You can sit down.
I felt bad we couldn't do this last time.
Come on.
I can't drink.
That's one-to-one.
The golden ratio.
Next...
You pop a tissue on top.
- Like that!
Shake it...
like a tornado.
Like that!
What are you teaching her?
She deserves to know how satisfying it is when the world becomes one.
Your mind becomes clear...
and you can be honest about anything.
Your can be truthful with your entire being. That's how it feels!
It's so tasty.
Make more.
I'll try this time.
Like that!
There. That's gone.
I was wondering... Why would a cute lady like you meet this...
I mean why did you marry Young Soo?
In the beginning,
I didn't want to marry Young Soo.
- What?
He was too nice.
I was lonely growing up...
so I wanted to marry him and...
have a lot of babies.
That's why we bought a house with a big front yard.
It's so hard to mow the lawn.
Then, what about a man like him?
Mr Lee is so handsome.
He is handsome.
But...
this guy...
He is so strange.
He's very strange.
- What about him?
- At times,
he's so similar to Young Soo.
He keeps on confusing me.
I talked too much today, didn't I?
She could do better.
She could do better than him.
What are you doing?
Hey.
Come over here.
I'll take care of her.
What are you... Come over here.
Oh goodness. It's so warm. This is nice.
Mum.
What do I do? I'm in trouble.
Han Na.
Han Na, I can't breathe.
- Mum.
- No.
Han Na.
Mum, hug me.
- You little monkey.
- Mum, I love you.
I thought I was going to suffocate.
No. Hug me, hug me.
Han Na, you may well misunderstand this.
Daddy, no, I...
I went to your mum's room because...
It is... It's...
It's a homing instinct. Which is like...
the instinct of an animal to go back to where it came from.
I used to live on the first floor.
I was drunk. And I was sleepwalking.
Gosh.
I wanted to have your mum's hairpin.
This is just what I like.
If Mum finds out,
you'll get kicked out.
Don't do that.
What shall I do?
- Give me your number.
- My number?
This girl, she's so small-minded.
Hey. Don't you know where Hong Nan went?
You don't know.
Well, I have another way.
Tell Yi Yeon...
to live happily without me.
That was so close.
How could she be so good at negotiating?
I can't believe she asked for my number.
Hey. Song Yi Yeon...
What is it?
Is Yi Yeon really coming?
She'll sign a modelling contract with Mr Lee.
Then I should send my regards.
Send my attorney to Yi Yeon.
She can't live without her kid. She'll know how she should behave.
Yes, Sir.
Get out of my way.
Those idiots.
Is the air dry?
- Gosh!
- It's Song Yi Yeon!
- You're so pretty.
- Can I have your autograph?
- My gosh.
- You're so beautiful.
Me disappearing worked like a charm.
I know.
This is preposterous.
- Hey.
- Don't push.
Ms Song Yi Yeon.
We need to talk.
I can't believe this.
Let me hear what you have to say.
What are the terms?
First,
treat me like when I was a top star. Like the top celebrity.
I think you've lost your senses since you haven't been...
- working for so long.
- Okay, it's a deal.
We will treat you like we would top celebrities.
You bluff too much, Mr Lee.
- Are you in your right mind?
- Yes, I am.
Ms Song Yi Yeon is well worth it.
Second,
I only deal with the best.
Raise the value of the department store...
so it deserves me as its model.
I'll decided after seeing...
which one of you makes that happen.
Raising the value means...
What on earth are you talking about?
- Give us a clue.
- No.
I only ask questions. You should come up with the answer.
This conversation is over.
Go home and take care of the child.
I will take that challenge.
I'll raise the value of the department store.
By the way,
I'm asking this because I really have no idea.
They say this contract will be the deciding factor...
in choosing the successor of Sunjin Group.
- Is that true?
- Yes, very much so.
You sent...
a custody petition.
Well.
You'll have to try harder.
I'll wait and see.
You should've just signed the contract with Lee Hae Joon.
Why did you provoke Cha Jae Gook?
Come on.
You're ruining the mood.
Why did you give him a chance?
Did you do that because you still have feelings for him?
He's my kid's father.
He should at least show my son that he's trying.
So that's why you used the chance like that?
Don't you know what he's like?
Hey, doesn't she look like she's jealous?
Jealous?
I should just keep quiet.
You're not that hot just yet. Don't go ahead of yourself.
- Where are you going?
- It's none of your business.
- Are you going to sleep out again?
- Yes.
What's gotten into her?
Why are you following me?
You can't stay out all night.
I used to stay out all night all the time...
Were you worried?
I'm sure Na Suk Chul is having you watched.
Don't go around alone.
(Han Gi Tak, died in car accident)
(Song Yi Yeon)
She's Hong Nan.
She says she's Han Gi Tak's sister. She showed up a month after he died.
She is working as Song Yi Yeon's manager...
and won over all of the people who worked for him.
You're Han Gi Tak's sister?
(Han Gi Tak, died in car accident, restaurant owner)
I don't think I put you there...
so that I'd have to see Yi Yeon's arrogant face.
Pick your side properly!
Don't you worry.
Her glory days are over.
I know this industry well.
I'm sorry I'm late.
(Na Suk Chul)
What did you find out about that manager girl?
Well,
she's obsessed with becoming famous.
You don't need to worry at all.
I see.
You tell me not to worry about anything at all.
How can I trust you?
How could you say that?
I doubt Song Yi Yeon came to the department store to shop.
I thought she'd easily hand over the victory to the other side,
but she gave you a chance, which means we may win.
Are you telling me to put her face on my department store?
It's better than Lee Hae Joon winning the contract, is it not?
What if we approach the manager?
Yes. I agree.
- I think...
- I want...
Mr Jung to handle this one.
Pardon?
I heard Sunjin is digging into Han Gi Tak's accident.
Sunjin?
His name is Jung Ji Hoon. I think he's one of Cha Jae Gook's men.
Shoot.
You said you'd teach me Gi Tak's secret method. What is this about?
Hey.
I almost died after eating your pasta, you punk.
You can't create that flavour unless you have no sense of taste.
Salt, sugar, MSG.
Pick.
Come on now.
Of all the...
Sugar.
Salt.
MSG.
Sugar.
Suk Chul, that jerk.
What did he feed you?
- You've lost all sense of taste.
- Sugar.
Salt.
Stop it! They are all salt!
Hi, pretty girl.
Some jerk is digging into your brother's past.
- What do you think about that?
- What are you saying?
Sunjin Department Store's Jung Ji Hoon.
Jung Ji Hoon?
I have a feeling he'll catch you...
before I reap my benefit.
I worked hard to get where I am, but I'm about to lose it...
because I was too nice to Yi Yeon.
So you need to step up, don't you think?
I'm sorry, but we're closed.
Hong Nan?
Jung Ji Hoon?
What brings you here?
Did Cha Jae Gook send you?
Who is he? He's annoyingly clean cut.
I'm sure I've seen him before.
You aren't 100 percent on Lee Hae Joon's side, are you?
Help us out, too.
Song Yi Yeon's mission is way too difficult.
I'm sure it is.
I may have lost my sense of taste,
but my vision is top rate.
If the pretty girl meets Jung Ji Hoon,
tell me what they talk about.
Excuse me. Is the owner of this restaurant...
Han Gi Tak?
Yes, he is.
Thank you.
Ji Hoon is digging into your past?
- What for?
- It's obvious.
Jae Gook is probably looking for something to use against Yi Yeon.
Would he do personal errands for him on top of his job?
What is that punk after?
He asked for a hint in getting Yi Yeon's contract.
What?
Not a chance!
When I see him tomorrow,
I will torture him.
How's your back?
It's fine.
How about your neck? Did you sleep well?
Yes.
What are you doing?
Stay still. I need you right now.
How is it? Is it comfortable?
This is the latest pillow. It puts you right to sleep.
Good morning.
I think she likes the pillow.
Loser.
Shoot.
She definitely liked it.
Calm down.
You're a married woman.
Han Na. Give me strength.
- Recharge!
- Mummy!
I can't breathe!
- Father.
- What?
What's wrong?
I need strength.
This is your favourite wine,
right?
Here.
I didn't think you'd remember things like this.
You must not know it,
but I'm very interested in you.
That sounds frightening.
Get to the point.
If you're going to work with Sunjin, enter into the contract with me.
That looks better...
Working with you looks the worst.
I'll treat you like a top star as you want.
Really?
- What about the value of the store?
- What?
How will you make it worthy of my image?
You're the company president.
You must have something in mind.
What? Shall I put gold flakes and ribbons on the storefront?
You'll have to try harder.
Darn it!
I'm Lee Hae Joon.
I'm the genius Lee Hae Joon.
For goodness' sake! How do I raise the price of the department store?
This is so frustrating. I can't think.
He must have a lot of time to kill.
He's fighting with the president to sign Song Yi Yeon, right?
I bet he bluffed about the employee benefit he promised us about.
I know, right?
Oh, I almost forgot.
It'll be good for you to get to know him. Take good care of him.
- Yes, Sir.
- He'll give us the push we need...
to sell off our department store.
Hello, Mr Lee.
Hey.
Who are you to tell me what to do?
Sir, this area is designated for female...
I ended up here because you couldn't even direct cars in the parking lot.
I wasted 10 minutes on the road because of you.
I make 100,000 dollars per minute.
How much do you make?
You must be better than me to dare block my way!
Hello, Chairman Jang.
Yes, President Cha. You better train your employees well.
Yes, I'll keep that in mind.
Hey, you there. You can go home.
Pardon?
Hold on, Sir.
I didn't do anything wrong.
What do you think you are doing?
You couldn't even follow the manual. You have no reason to be here.
Why are you watching?
Wait, Sir. Sir...
He was signalling just fine.
He always fires people whenever there's a complaint.
He's so annoying.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I'm sorry.
My apologies, Sir.
You should have done this from the beginning without talking back.
Don't make me cringe my face.
- What are you doing? Remove him.
- Yes, Sir.
Just a moment.
There's Robin Hood.
What is it now, Mr Lee?
It looked like my employee was having a problem.
I can't let this slip.
What now? Are they both going to insult him?
This is big. Let me film this.
Mr Lee Gi Sang.
You weren't given your tag so that people can insult you.
- Don't put yourself down.
- Yes.
Your store manager is so arrogant.
Mr Lee, stop causing a commotion. Let's quit it.
Do you even know who that gentleman is?
Our department store sells products, not attitudes.
Paying money for goods is a fair trade.
We don't need to treat customers with bad attitude well...
if they consider themselves to be above our employees.
We are not obligated to do that.
The owner's words are the manual.
Don't you get it?
- Have you heard me?
- Yes, Mr Lee.
- Mr Lee!
- And while I am at it,
let's change that manual.
You should familiarise yourself with the updated manual.
Mr Ko.
You should take good care of him.
So that he doesn't get humiliated again.
Well, then. I'll be on my way to meet my VIP customer.
Take care.
He's so cool.
Han Na!
I thought you weren't coming.
Come on, Daddy promised to teach you how to ride a bike.
I'll teach you on behalf of him.
Let's get started.
- You're so good!
- Like this?
Yes, go left. This way.
It's working.
This way.
I'll try on my own.
Sure, you're so good.
Han Na, you're good at riding the bike.
- Don't let go.
- I won't.
- I know.
I didn't know the strategy department researched...
such things as the model's favourite food and music.
Of course. Since she'll be the model of Sunjin Department Store.
Yi Yeon has great discernment in things.
In her choice of men as well.
By the way,
are you a close friend of hers?
We met in the States.
Did you meet Lee Hae Joon in the States, too?
You're not a reporter.
But you seem to have a lot of questions.
I saw you at the fashion show.
You seem like a very charming person.
You'd be a good actress.
People say that a lot.
Isn't it hard to live...
someone else's life?
I know your brother very well.
I mean, Han Gi Tak.
My brother probably doesn't know you.
You say that you're Han Gi Tak's sister.
You're lying, Hong Nan.
He knows that I'm fake.
Who is it? Cha Jae Gook? Na Suk Chul?
Why do you think I'm lying, Mr Jung Ji Hoon?
If you want to hear my answer, have dinner with me tomorrow.
Explain.
I changed everything.
If Cha Jae Gook knew that I was Han Gi Tak's sister,
he wouldn't stay put like that.
There's no reason for Jung Ji Hoon to come and ask me,
"Are you fake?"
I can't figure him out.
I'll have to meet him tomorrow to find out.
What's this?
What is that?
"I'm waiting for your reply. From X."
Who is X?
Whose heart did you steal this time?
My popularity is soaring.
It's not like I can put up a sign that says "I'm taken."
Right?
I don't know what to do.
Our department store sells products, not attitudes.
- My gosh.
- Oh, dear.
Mr Lee is so awesome.
- I was mistaken.
- I knew it.
- We were mistaken.
- I trusted him.
- What?
- Come on.
- Let's watch it again.
- Play it again.
Our department store sells products, not attitudes.
- He's so hot.
- He is, right?
I knew it.
Did you want to see me?
Mr Jung.
You know how important Yi Yeon's modelling contract is, don't you?
Of course, Sir.
I heard that you met with Yi Yeon's manager, Hong Nan...
and accused of her for being fake.
Why did you do that?
- You two are so well connected.
- Just answer my question.
Is using a dead person your speciality?
- What?
- She's pretending to be...
Gi Tak's sister in order to use Yi Yeon, isn't she?
So I made up Gi Tak's sister in order to beat Cha Jae Gook?
- That's right.
- What's your reasoning?
You'll soon find out.
What are you waiting for?
Here's a list of the new products.
Leave it there.
I didn't want to say this because it hurts my pride.
Why Lee Hae Joon and not me?
- Sir.
- Is it because we were together...
on the night Young Soo died?
I feel the same.
Young Soo's death pained me so much.
For that reason, I hesitated numerous times.
But I can't just sit back and watch...
because I'm worried that you might get hurt.
That's right.
I hate myself for being with you that night.
I want to erase that time if I could.
- Da Hye.
- It's true that I was upset...
because Young Soo always put work first.
You showed up and...
I was able to smile for a short while.
And Young Soo died then.
So every time I see you, I'm reminded of that day.
It really hurts me.
Us meeting that night, do you think it was a coincidence?
- I had something to tell you.
- I don't want to hear it.
Da Hye.
I'm sorry.
I was an idiot to have doubted you.
I never once celebrated...
our anniversary or took you out for dinner.
I left you all by yourself.
I'm sorry for asking you to be understanding all the time.
I'm sorry that...
all I can say is "I'm sorry."
Since when were you there?
Always.
I've always been beside you.
You just didn't know.
Is that right?
I won't say that I'm sorry like an idiot.
So that I don't have any regrets...
when I leave.
Isn't it hard to...
live someone else's life?
You say that you're Han Gi Tak's sister.
You're lying, Hong Nan.
Jung Ji Hoon.
What does he know?
Wait.
Does he know who it is?
So what did Jung Ji Hoon say?
He knew Hong Nan was Gi Tak's sister.
Well.
He's pretty good.
We should take care of it before Cha Jae Gook finds out.
You're right.
If Mr Cha finds out,
he'll be upset.
Don't you think so?
- Gosh.
- Sir.
How did you know where I was?
I told you not to scare me like that.
I'm sorry, Sir.
It's something urgent. I was in a hurry. I'm sorry, Sir.
What is it?
Do you remember Yi Yeon's manager,
Hong Nan?
I know her real identity.
She is Gi Tak's sister.
Also,
the place Yi Yeon is staying is...
Hello, this is the store manager.
This is an announcement for the customers and...
employees of Sunjin Department Store .
We have designated two Family Days...
- per month.
- What is he talking about?
We are offering special promotions to customers.
The employees will be dismissed an hour early...
- from work.
- No way.
- I don't believe it.
- Today is Family Day.
- You'll be off work at seven.
- Is he joking?
Please note that the lights will go out at 7:30pm.
Gosh.
Don't think about working overtime. Go home early.
What was that?
- No way.
Valued customers, it's time to return to your families.
Have a nice day.
Oh my gosh! Did they really turn off the power?
- What's going on?
- Oh my goodness.
This is so exciting!
Wait for me!
What are you doing?
We're going on a date.
Try it on. It's for you.
Mr Lee.
You need to put that on, so we can go eat.
Will you...
trust me one more time?
- Hi.
- Mummy!
What is it?
Are you disappointed that we're home?
Doesn't it look good?
Grill it up.
I'll cook it well.
It looks good.
Doesn't it smell good?
Aren't you all so happy spending time with family like this?
Mummy, I'm starving.
Yes. Let's eat.
Yes.
The meat doesn't seem to be cooking well.
Are you sure it's working?
Is the flame out?
Wait a little bit. They're almost done.
Wait just a little while longer. I'm almost done.
We'll be up all night.
- Should I help?
- No, no!
The man should cook when you're outdoors.
- Sit still.
- Da Hye.
Let's just make instant noodles.
Shall we?
Han Na, you must be hungry.
- Noodles.
- Yes.
Isn't that better?
Yes.
Goodness.
Oh my.
What's this?
- Mummy.
- The house is going to fly away!
- Han Na.
- Are you okay?
Da Hye!
Have you lost your mind?
You shouldn't push someone who's trying to help you.
I'll be on TV a lot from now on.
I'm a total hit.
You'll probably spend all day long looking at my face.
Is Daddy good to you?
He made me fried rice and kicked a ball around with me.
- He did?
- He said to make sure to tell you.
I see.
You must have been happy.
Where are Auntie and Uncle?
I don't know. They both must be busy today.
I'll bring them next time.
(Final Goodbye)
Quick feet...
and expert moves.
Did you finally realise my worth?
President Cha, you cute punk.
The game is going to get more interesting.
I can't wait to see it!
Come in.
Miss "Not Han Gi Tak's Sister".
Would you like a beer?
Why did you want to see me at home?
To tell you why you're fake.
Was Gi Tak insufficient?
Did he tell you to wipe out everyone in his vicinity?
Is that what Cha Jae Gook told you to do?
Is it dangerous if he finds out?
You know that and yet you pretend to be Han Gi Tak's sister.
Is it for money or loyalty?
- What?
- It's incredible whatever it is.
But I'd like you to stop.
I think that person would be very sad if she found out.
Whom do you mean?
Han Gi Tak's real sister.
- What?
- I know the real sister.
The real sister?
What do you mean?
(A man of justice)
His real sister is looking for her family.
I can finally keep a promise I made long ago.
I won't let you and Lee Hae Joon mess that up.
Who is it?
She's close.
Where is she?
Where are you going?
Is it good? Here you go.
For you.
Yes!
Enjoy.
I'll cut this for you.
Hi!
Hong Nan! I'm glad you're here.
Join us!
Come in.
Punk.
It's been a while.
Han Hong Nan.
Five cargo ships, three cruise ships...
and three planes passed by.
But...
there is the 12th ship.
(Come Back Alive)
Hong Nan. She looked.
Do you know why I can't get over Gi Tak?
Why were you so arrogant?
How dare you covet something that is mine?
I want to play with you,
but I don't have much time left.
Are you going somewhere?
Don't make things harder for Da Hye.
I will protect her.
Leave a little place in your memory for me.
- What...
- What did you say to Han Na?
She's missing.
- She disappeared.
- Where are you?