Why are you standing there?
Do you remember what I said about my sister?
She cried so much as a baby...
so I used to call her a crybaby.
Every time I called her a crybaby,
she used to cry even more. I found that cute...
so I always made fun of her for it.
I did.
I found out where she lives.
My sister.
Really?
Where does she live?
Gi Tak.
I'm your brother-in-law from now on.
Are you saying...
that Da Hye is...
Han Hong Nan.
Her real name is...
Although we'll never call her by that name.
What...
What kind of a sad fate is this?
Now I know...
why we had to return...
together.
And why...
I came back in a woman's body.
Now I know.
Hong Nan, why don't you join us already?
Sir, here we meet again.
Hello, welcome.
Have a seat.
Hi.
Hong Nan, try this.
(Heemang Orphanage)
Now that your mother's passed away, how do you plan to raise her?
If you don't want her to live within thugs, send her to us.
Don't even think twice.
Once she gets adopted overseas, she'll meet nice foster parents...
and won't even want to come back to Korea.
Where are we going?
Why are you about to cry again?
People will call you a crybaby if you start crying.
If someone harasses you, what do you do?
One, two.
Good job.
That's my sister.
Are we going off to see Mum?
Look. There's a car.
Should we take a picture in front of it?
Yes.
Here we go.
In 1, 2, 3!
Hong Nan.
Why are you staring at me?
I missed you.
Me, too.
You should have come earlier. We're almost done eating.
I should have.
I came too late.
- Give me some.
- Open your mouth.
Open.
This one's good.
Do you want more?
Hey, you should try some meat.
It's quite good.
Yes, Sir.
I was getting hungry.
It's tasty.
- Is it tasty?
- Yes.
It's because I cooked it.
Don't worry about it. I can do it.
I always wanted to do this.
Acting like a family.
How many siblings do you have?
I have an older brother.
He used to...
call me a crybaby. That's my brother.
I envy you. You feel protected when you have an older brother.
I'm here.
Crybaby.
Sir, you should rest inside.
Sure. We shouldn't have a guest cleaning up after us.
It's all right.
She wants to get to know Da Hye.
Okay, very well.
Da Hye does need a friend.
Da Hye, how were you as a child?
Did you have a happy childhood?
I think I was happy.
Actually,
I don't remember my childhood.
I had an accident when I was about Han Na's age.
I don't remember clearly, but I think I was...
running around to find my dad or brother.
Then I got hit by a truck.
My current mum hit me.
She lied to the hospital saying that I was her daughter...
because of the insurance benefit.
You can guess what happened, can't you?
Since then I grew up delivering meals at a market.
This is strange. I've never told this story...
to people other than Young Soo.
I guess I feel comfortable around you.
Han Na, can I ask you something?
What is it?
Did your mum say anything to you...
when your dad wasn't around?
About having a hard time...
or having a secret she couldn't tell.
If I tell it, then it's not a secret.
Right. That's true.
There's nobody without a secret.
Even I have one.
- What?
- I have to do homework.
Do you want me to help you?
No, it's okay. I can do it by myself.
Okay.
I'll leave you to it then.
We need to talk. Can I come see you now?
I didn't think you'd come right away.
Is this what you meant by doing what Da Hye wants the most?
A long time ago, I promised her that I'd find her family.
I finally kept that promise.
Stop trying to use Han Gi Tak.
And leave Da Hye.
Kim Young Soo.
What had he been doing...
as her husband?
How could he not know...
what you know?
It was her choice.
I went back to give her the gloves and picture after we parted.
She told me to throw them out.
She said she had Kim Young Soo, a new family.
He had such huge responsibilities,
but he neglected his duties.
Kim Young Soo did.
Hong Nan, did something happen today?
Do you want to try punching my hands?
I think that'll make me cheer up.
Like this?
Tightly clench your fists and...
punch my hands. One, two.
One, two.
My brother taught me...
never to be weak wherever I was.
You introduced her to Gi Tak's pub.
Did you already know then?
I wanted Da Hye to meet her brother casually.
It was difficult for me to tell her.
But Young Soo took her...
He took her to a funeral and made her do chores.
He broke his promise again...
the next day.
I got so angry. I went there to tell her that...
she had a real family beside Young Soo.
I couldn't, though.
She was left there alone...
and Young Soo died.
Da Hye got hurt too much...
because of that.
So...
Will you tell her...
about Gi Tak?
I wasn't going to tell her...
since she lost her husband and her brother.
So I thought I was the only one to protect Da Hye...
before you came along.
Jung Ji Hoon.
Young Soo must be grateful.
Since you found Da Hye's family.
But...
don't tell her.
Let's not make her cry again.
Losing Young Soo was enough.
That's interesting.
Hong Nan said differently.
I am Gi Tak's real sister.
Don't tell her.
You'll make the wrong person get hurt.
Or was she saying the same thing?
Anyway, don't make Da Hye get hurt.
I will protect her.
Where did Mr Lee go?
Did he go to bed?
It's okay. I'll see him again.
For once.
Can...
I give you a hug?
Of course.
Who told you to die so soon?
Look who's talking.
You had an untimely death.
You idiot.
Who told you to die from working excessively?
Are you proud of dying at the age of 40 because of work?
If you left her, you should be alive at least.
Why did you make her become an orphan, you jerk?
What did you say?
- Why you...
- You jerk.
What? Did I say something wrong?
What if it was with thugs?
You should've raised her.
Why did you leave her? Tell me why!
You jerk.
You promised to make her happy. You should've kept the promise.
Why did you make her even lonelier?
I'm going to kill you.
- Got it?
- I'm already dead.
Why don't you just cease to exist?
- Take this!
- Die!
Die!
- You jerk.
- Take that.
- Shoot.
- You jerk.
What do you take me for?
You punk.
- Let go.
- Look at you.
You said you wouldn't. Let go.
Stop it.
Did you think I'd fall for it twice?
- You jerk.
- You need a beating.
- Do you think I can't do it?
- You jerk.
You need a beating.
What are you doing?
Where did you go...
after creating the mess?
Did you get into a fight?
Your face...
How did you fall on your face without even drinking?
My legs are too long, so they got tangled.
You're so silly.
You're the one who is hurting the most.
Once again, I'm the one receiving.
All done.
Put some more on, please.
It hurts a lot.
Don't tell Yi Yeon.
It was just a little squabble.
How did you know I was there anyway?
Did you follow me in case I stayed out all night again?
You're Han Gi Tak's sister?
You're lying, Hong Nan.
I trust you.
Trust me. I'll stay home.
Yi...
Yi Yeon.
This punk ripped them real good.
I'm sorry.
These are your brother's only photos.
- Was it Cha Jae Gook's doing?
- Well.
I left home a while ago. It would be weird if he didn't know.
As long as he doesn't know you're Gi Tak's sister, it's fine.
You must have been frightened.
It's fine. This is fine.
He swore he'd never let me go.
I don't know...
when it will ever end.
One, two.
Good job.
Hi.
I wonder just how many scary dreams...
you would have had all by yourself.
Your brother had something scary happen today, too.
For us, nothing is more frightening...
than you not remembering.
Leave a little place in your memory for me.
And fill the rest...
with happy and nice memories.
Okay?
What are you doing?
I couldn't sleep.
Are you thinking about Gi Tak?
I love these pictures.
I can feel...
the life that he led...
that I couldn't see for myself.
I'm sure he thought it was for the best.
But when you think about it,
it was a cruddy life.
I'm sure he didn't know...
that doing something for someone...
may hurt them the most.
That idiot.
Did something happen?
No. I'm just drunk.
I'm sorry for drinking alone.
Let it slide just this once.
I'm happy I got to know a little more about you.
Hello, my brother-in-law.
Is your face okay?
And are you okay?
Call me "Brother", won't you?
- Brother?
- Yes.
How pretty was my little sister this morning?
All the flowers at the store wilted in her presence.
Those flowers won't come back to life.
Our family genes are quite superior.
I didn't know your real sister's name was Hong Nan.
What were you thinking?
If she were alive somewhere...
If we could meet again...
I wanted her to look back...
if she heard her own name.
Hong Nan. Han Hong Nan.
She looked. She looked.
She looked.
I'll call you when I'm done.
Okay.
You startled me.
Mr Ma. It's been a while.
Did you miss me?
I was bored.
Like I wanted to chew on something, but had nothing to chew on.
Thank you for the vacation.
Thanks to you,
my family was able to spend a great time in the Philippines.
It was the first time since I started working here.
I'm glad. Submit the receipts.
The company will pay for the family outing.
You do mean it?
I don't say things I don't mean.
Just a minute.
What are you doing?
I am looking for your wings.
I thought you must be an angel.
You're not entirely wrong.
You're the first man...
to shake my heart.
The first...
Even the sky is wishing you a successful photo shoot.
What a great weather!
I knew this day would come.
Why isn't anyone here?
Have we come too early?
I'll look into it.
What? Why would it get cancelled? Why?
I don't know why. We were told from the organisers.
Look, is this Yi Yeon?
You are stunning.
What now? You got them for nothing.
It was him, wasn't he?
His way of doing things never change.
I guess robbing my house yesterday...
wasn't enough for him, then?
Come on, that's not enough to dissolve his anger.
You live in Gi Tak's house with his sister.
Don't get her involved.
That would depend entirely on you.
You are acting too smart with me. You're trying to fly all over me.
You've gone too far.
Besides this, you have three more contract cancellations.
I can't pay any fees to the contractors.
So that means you'll have to pay them yourself.
Hey.
How long do you think you'll be on the rise?
You know as well as I do who has you by the collar.
Why would you act so arrogant?
Why don't you go to Cha Jae Gook...
and wag your tail for him?
I told you to watch your mouth.
I'll bite you for real next time.
Oh, dear.
There you go again. Stop acting.
Yi Yeon!
Hey, pretty girl!
- Weren't we in this together?
- You're so naive.
I don't have any patience.
Call me when the pretty girl comes out of the water.
Tell her to bring the money.
That's my last warning.
Song Yi Yeon!
Gi Tak.
Yi Yeon!
Open your eyes, Yi Yeon!
Why is there no movement on Yi Yeon's side?
It's only normal for her crazy manager to barge in here.
Was it Han Hong Nan?
How did your meeting with her go?
I didn't get much out of her except that she's close to Mr Lee.
You haven't gained much.
What have you done for me recently?
Shin Da Hye hasn't signed the agreement paper either.
I'm sorry, Sir.
I don't like too many things in this world.
Don't disappoint me.
Ms Song fell in the water due to an accident in the dock...
but her manager saved her.
Han Gi Tak's...
sister.
Yi Yeon.
You grew a thick skin.
You are not crying after being insulted.
That's my girl.
I can do it.
I saw Gi Tak in the water.
I must have been close to death.
But...
I was happy seeing him nonetheless.
You keep talking about Gi Tak!
Look what happened to you because of that punk. Aren't you fed up?
What is he to you?
Do you know why that punk abandoned me?
He couldn't let me live with the thugs.
He said he won't look for me if I died...
and not to look for him once he died. He betrayed me.
He's a coward and a jerk.
- Hong Nan.
- You said...
you ruined his life, right?
Don't be mistaken.
10 years ago,
he brought you in front of Jae Gook.
He's the one who called your manager!
So forget about that coward!
How can we end this?
What do I have to do...
to end...
this nightmare?
Mum.
I found Hong Nan.
But after I...
I came back here, everything turned into a mess.
Mum.
I'm sorry.
I'll do it.
Let's do it. The modelling contract.
Really?
She'll sign the contract. Give me high five.
You made the right decision.
Sunjin Department Store's model, Song Yi Yeon,
welcome.
Can you carry out the conditions right away?
Of course. The modelling fee...
will cover the current agency contract cancellation fee.
Finally Na Suk Chul will be fired.
Until you find a new agency,
we will take care of your schedule.
Please...
carry out the last condition as well.
Ms Han Hong Nan.
You are fired from being her manager.
It won't cause any harm to reconcile with Yi Yeon.
You're right, Sir.
It surely is getting positive reviews.
That idiot.
I basically spoon-fed him, but he couldn't even take it.
What has Jae Gook been doing?
The two have different methods.
- Please look at this.
- Our store sells products...
Plutocrats' obnoxious behaviours are controversial issues.
Mr Lee's welfare and love-oriented management policy...
went well with what Yi Yeon expected from the department store.
We are not obligated to do that.
Was Hae Joon...
like that?
It's a bit different from his previous behaviours.
Did you come here to check how I'd look?
I...
I did give you a chance.
Don't think this is the end of it.
You said you won't let me go.
If making me miserable was what you were after...
Yes.
You used the best method.
Na Suk Chul.
You kept that horrible monster by my side.
Do you know why I can't forget Gi Tak?
He was the only one...
who saved me from that horrible monster.
Because of that,
Gi Tak ruined his life.
What are you doing?
I'm only trying to have a talk.
- Okay.
- My friend will be staying with me.
You know Hong Nan, don't you?
She's been fired. She has nowhere to go.
My gosh. How did that happen?
So please welcome her and treat her nicely.
Okay, I will.
Here.
- What are these?
- I keep getting those.
I'm too popular.
It's too much for me to handle.
Why are you giving these to me?
You eat them. Don't give them to Han Na.
It's fun to break these.
It has love messages inside too.
I'm not interested.
Of course you are.
(It's not what we planned. I'll be waiting for your reply.)
Wait for my reply?
You scared me.
What does it say?
Well...
Is this not a love letter?
Hello.
My name is Big Head.
That's not funny.
I'm the Big Head Monster then.
It's not funny.
- Han Na.
- Yes?
Shall I tell you a secret?
- A secret?
- But...
you have to tell me why you're feeling down.
I want to play with you more,
but I don't have...
much time left.
Are you...
going somewhere?
You tell me first.
What's your secret?
Well...
I love Han Na very much.
What was that?
Hello.
Hi, Han Na.
- You're home.
- Yes.
Why...
Why are you here without notice?
I was that close with the family. I would visit...
without notice.
I brought this on myself.
Jung Ji Hoon.
What brings you here?
Do I need to tell you?
Did you come here...
to tell them about that thing?
Da Hye and I will...
I'm sorry. This is all I can serve you.
- Sir, give it to me.
- What?
Give it to me.
Well, he came uninvited.
He should've brought his own refreshments.
We're family, aren't we?
Han Na, did something happen in school that upset you?
No.
Don't pretend you know things.
Are you hungry? Do you want to go out and eat something yummy?
- I'm not hungry.
- You know nothing.
Is it because you're bored?
Do you want to go out and play?
I don't think so.
You want to play inside, don't you?
He's wrong, isn't he?
Han Na,
did you enjoy the concert?
Those tickets were hard to get.
Do you even know how many members there are?
Well.
Do you think I don't know?
How many then?
Song Yi Yeon,
do you think I don't have a place to go?
I have a family too.
I'm not lonely at all.
That's funny.
Hey. Chef's assistant, Jegil.
Let's have a family meeting.
Mummy!
Hello.
Father, I'm home.
Hi.
Da Hye.
Han Na, I'm going to wash up, so wait in Grandpa's room.
Young Soo.
What are you doing in here?
Hi.
Thanks.
But...
what was that in the box?
Something your mum lost some time ago.
Why did you have it?
I thought she may look for it some day.
Why Lee Hae Joon and not me?
- I don't want to hear it.
- Da Hye.
Is it because we were together...
on the night Young Soo died?
Do you like my mum?
I do.
I like your mum and your dad,
and I like you, too.
(Kiwi Banana Juice)
Do you get itchy if you eat bananas, too?
What?
No, right?
I don't take after my dad at all.
I don't want to be like you.
What do you mean?
I hate that my dad was as smart as you,
and that he was as competitive as you.
I hate that my dad liked you.
That's right.
Are you getting ready for the test?
I've been too busy lately to...
- But how do you know that?
- Just because Gi Tak is gone,
did you stop studying altogether?
That's not what I mean.
I'm sorry.
Gi Tak told you to take the exam and go to college.
He said not to worry about tuition,
but that's gone now.
- Is that his fault?
- That's not what I mean.
That scum, Na Suk Chul.
Yes.
He's the one to blame.
What should we do?
Should we attack and reclaim the pub?
You punks!
Soak your bodies in hot water...
and draw out that thug nature. Got it?
How many times must I say it?
Legally! Fair and square!
We will reclaim our pub...
fair and square.
Got it?
- Yes, Boss!
- Yes, Boss'... sister.
Also,
let's go see the Big Boss.
You're home.
Yes.
Get lost.
- Your old personality is back.
- What?
You were as cold as ice before Hong Nan showed up.
What about you?
You changed the most after she came.
I... I did not.
Will you really not see her again?
I really don't want...
Hong Nan to become...
like Gi Tak.
If making me miserable was what you were after...
Yes.
You used the best method.
Na Suk Chul.
Hello.
I wondered if I'd ever get to see the inside of your office.
I'm so honoured to be here.
But why did you call for me in the middle of the night?
Have a seat.
Yes, Sir.
You were so useful when I first met you.
You are too kind.
You knew who Yi Yeon went to 10 years ago,
and to whom she'd run to first when the scandal came out.
Almost like a fortune teller.
I have a radar for things like that.
That's how I do what I do.
But...
who did this to you?
This?
Why do you care about my humble background?
Humble background? Still, I want to know.
Why? Is it difficult to say because it involves...
Yi Yeon and Gi Tak?
Sir. That is...
You rat.
How dare you...
use me?
You're mistaken. Please spare me.
How dare you covet my woman?
How dare you covet something that is mine?
Please stop, Sir.
No one would care if I kill a rat like you and dump you in the street.
Shall I try?
Sir!
No!
I told you not to eat bananas.
You should've been careful.
- Mummy.
- Yes?
Grandpa, you and dad aren't like this.
Why am I the only one?
Dad shakes whenever he has carrots.
What was that?
All done.
I'll call your teacher tomorrow. Take the day off.
I'll come home early, too.
Sleep tight.
I miss Daddy,
so I'm going to see him.
(My Love, Han Na)
Your call is being forwarded to voicemail.
Father, where are you?
How about Han Na? Aren't you with her?
No. I'm at the senior centre.
Why? Is something wrong?
No. I'll call you back later.
(My Love, Han Na)
Your call is being forwarded to voicemail.
Han Na, please pick up.
Hello?
How's Han Na?
They say seasonal foods are good for allergies.
So, for dinner...
Hello? Are you still there?
Are you there?
What's wrong? What is it?
Han Na...
Han Na is gone. She isn't answering her phone, either.
What? Where are you?
I'm home.
I'm home, but she left a note and she's gone.
Don't move. I'll be right there.
Han Na.
Why is this...
Mummy.
Yes?
Grandpa, you and dad aren't like this.
Why am I the only one?
What did you tell Han Na yesterday?
Da Hye, what do you...
What did you say to her?
Did something happen to her?
Han Na, where are you?
Daddy's coming.
- Yes!
- Hold on.
- What's wrong?
I don't think this is right.
You rat. You want to save it and eat it all by yourself!
Give it.
It doesn't taste good at all.
Daddy waited 10 years for Man Bong.
Tell him to wait a little longer.
I'll fly right over.
I love you.
I love you, got it?
Man Bong.
I need to go to my baby, Man Bong.
- No!
- Man Bong!
No! Stop!