[PLEASE COME BACK, MISTER]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Han Na, where are you?
Daddy's coming!
Yeah, Honey?
- Han Na's missing!
- What?
I'm sure Han Na's mom
is freaking out right now.
- Please go to her right away.
- Got it.
I'll head over there right away.
She won't pick up her phone, and none
of her friends know where she is.
Have you called her
school and the police?
- Yes.
- Good job.
Above all else though,
you need to calm down.
Don't worry. I'm sure that
our Han Na is just fine.
Ms. Da Hye! I've called my
entire crew. We'll find her soon.
But, um, if she went to
go look for her dad
maybe she went to the columbarium?
I'll give the security
staff over there a call.
All righty! All that's left for you
to do is not worry, and smile.
Thank you.
I haven't seen her.
- Have you seen this girl?
- You're Han Na's friend, right?
If you see her, call me right away.
- Okay?
- Yes, ma'am!
Two of you, this way.
Three of you, that way. Go!
I want to see Dad.
I'm going to go see him.
Han Na, where are you?
Oh, Father!
What's everybody fussing about?
Don't worry. I'm sure she's just
hanging out with her friends.
If she wanted to see her dad,
she probably went there.
What do you mean, "there?"
I think I know where she might be.
- Take me with you.
- I'll find her.
I promise.
Han Na, please be there!
[EPISODE 13]
I heard that the Branch Manager
told them to change
the main billboard to
Song Lee Yeon's photo today.
Wow, he's having a grand
old time, isn't he?
Whatever. He has a death wish, defying
me like this. What about the Chairman?
Didn't he say that he had an
important meeting today?
He told me that there's
no need for you to join him.
You should focus on saving the store.
So he doesn't want me to
sit next to him anymore, huh?
Did you hear that? Our Branch Manager
beat him and got a contract with Ms. Lee!
So the big shot around here
is Branch Manager Lee now!
Does this mean that we can finally escape
from the pressure from
the higher-ups to raise sales?
Yes!
Lee Hae Joon.
He's a real clever one.
He really knows how to piss someone off.
Does he think that I won't
be able to sell the store
if he tacks Song Lee Yeon's
face onto it, or something?
Continue with with the selling
of the department store.
Buy up all our stock, too.
I think Father wants me
to show him just how skilled I am.
So it's only fair that I show him.
- Um, yes, sir.
- Oh yeah, about Song Lee Yeon's manager.
That girl named Hong Nan, I mean.
Was there anything strange about her?
What do you mean exactly, sir?
Why do you think she
is hanging around Song Lee Yeon?
It's really getting to me.
Do you have a private
relationship with her, sir?
No. Leave.
- Section Chief Gu.
- Yes, sir?
Bring Na Suk Chul to me.
I need to ask him something.
About Han Gi Tak, that is.
I really don't have the right to try and
comfort her in a situation like this.
When you feel uneasy, here's something
you can do to help yourself calm down.
Pucker your mouth so it
looks like a butthole
and make a sound for
a long time, like this.
- Are you mad at me?
- No.
Did you come here because
you wanted to see your dad?
Dad said that we'd come here together.
Wow, it looks cool!
Do you want to ride it?
Mister. Will I be able to see
Dad if I get closer to the sky?
It's been so great lately.
Mom and Grandpa seem to like you, too
even though Dad's not here anymore.
If I start to like you, too,
I'll feel so bad for Dad.
Because I forgot
about Dad for a little bit.
And forgot about being sad.
He doesn't even come
visit me in my dreams anymore.
There are still so many things
I didn't tell him yet, though.
Should we go see Dad, then?
- It's so high up!
- Aren't you scared?
N-no.
I'm a bit scared, though.
Your hands are so big like Dad's,
and you smell just like Dad.
Really? Maybe it's because
we use the same lotion?
Mister... Dad sent you, right?
Figures.
Han Na. Can you tell me
what you wanted to tell your dad?
I like you, but you're not Dad.
Dad!
- Dad!
- Han Na!
Dad! Do you know how much I missed you?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Why did you just leave me behind?
Why did you do that?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, my baby. I'm sorry.
Dad! I'm sorry that I'm
not your daughter.
No. I was so happy to be your dad.
Thanks for being my daughter. Okay?
Dad! Dad!
- My daughter. My daughter.
- Dad! My dad!
It's okay, it's okay.
Ms. Da Hye!
- Why, all of the sudden...
- You're someone who doesn't suit me.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No.
I've just grown to dislike you.
Well, okay. Since that's how you feel,
I won't say another word.
But, my feelings are mine, so
don't tell me to forget about you.
If you get yourself another man, I'll do
my darndest to live a great life anyway.
So don't worry about me, and just
think about your own happiness.
Goodbye, then.
- Kim Han Na!
- Mom.
Are you going to keep
upsetting me like this?
Yeah, Han Na. You need to be scolded
a bit for scaring your mom like that.
Are you going to do that
to me again? Huh?
- Hurry up and apologize.
- I'm sorry, Mom!
Are you going to do that
to me again? Huh?
Do you known how upset I was?
That's enough. She apologized.
Mom, I'm sorry!
See, what did I tell you?
Hey, girl! How many times have
I told you to sit still while eating?
What a stubborn girl. How could she leave
like that and not contact me once?
Who does she take after that
she's so stubborn, Gi Tak?
I wonder if she takes after you?
No, not at all.
Even if I'm not here,
Seung Jae will protect you.
Tell Hong Nan not to even think
about coming near me again.
- I'll never take her back!
- Understood.
I don't want to hallucinate that
she's here, or anything like that!
So make sure that she never
comes close to me again! Got it?
Yes.
How did you end up
meeting up with Mister, anyway?
I don't know. He just came and found me.
I see.
Did you want to see Dad
that much, Han Na?
You know how much Dad loves you, right?
Even when you were still in my belly,
he'd call you his little blessing
and sing to you, and even
danced so that I'd laugh.
And when you heard his voice, you
were so happy that you'd kick a lot.
You two sleep in such a similar
way. You know that?
Both of you sleep with
your arms up, like this!
Oh yeah. Mom. I saw Dad.
What?
When I was on the ferris wheel with
Mister, I saw him in my dream.
He said "thank you" to me, and that
he was happy to be my dad.
Dad said that to you?
So I told him that I was
so happy to be his daughter.
I did well, right?
You must be so happy
that you got to see Dad.
Good night.
I want to see him, too.
You're probably still very dizzy,
so you shouldn't move around yet.
But, um, what am I doing here?
You passed on the street.
Did your guardian go somewhere?
- Guardian?
- The baby's dad!
I'm... I'm right here!
The baby's dad is right here.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
I'm in front of your house.
I don't know how to describe how I feel.
But I feel even more lonely
now that I've found my younger sister.
She's family, but we might
as well be strangers.
And there's nothing
that I can do for her.
And I can't even tell her
that I'm her older brother.
I know that feeling very well.
I felt that way myself.
You two look good together.
It'd be nice if the two of you
could live together like this.
Han Na told me, "I really
like you, but you're not Dad."
They said that this second shot at life
would jut get harder and harder.
I think I finally understand
what that means.
Is Han Na okay?
She's not hurt, is she?
Yes. I called you because I was
so flustered. Sorry about that.
- Ms. Da Hye.
- Also...
I'd like it if you didn't come
to our home anymore.
Is Han Na... my daughter?
I had my doubts before
but I thought it was impossible
since you two were married.
But I need to hear it from you now.
- Is she really not my daughter?
- What are you saying?
Han Na knew even before I did
that we are quite similar.
Why is that bastard here again?
I know I have no right to say this,
but you can tell me the truth now.
Manager Jung, you're too much.
- Shouldn't you have told me, at least?
- No. It's not true.
Han Na's dad is Kim Young Soo.
And the father she so dearly
MISSES IS JUST ONE MAN: Kim Young Soo.
This is how it has always been,
and this is how it will always be.
Have I answered your
question? Goodbye, then.
What the hell? What the hell
was Jung Ji Hoon talking about?
You heard. Han Na's my daughter.
Answer me properly.
What is it that I don't know?
Brother-in-law, why
are you acting this way?
You... knew this from the very beginning?
And that her child was
Jung Ji Hoon's, too?
No. I wasn't aware of that last part.
I only found out after I came back.
After I found out that they once dated.
How could you not know?
Jung Ji Hoon was right by your side!
And Da Hye didn't say anything, despite
the fact that he was always by your side?
When I married Da Hye, I promised her
that we wouldn't talk about it
and that Han Na was my daughter.
I thought that was the best way
to protect our family at the time.
But, it was Jung Ji Hoon, of all people.
I really feel like I'm going to go crazy.
I guess I'm really a shallow person.
After all, I assumed that they'd
been seeing each other secretly.
You idiot. Why are you
just telling me this now?
Were you planning to keep your mouth shut
about it until we went back to Heaven?
That was the plan, and it was really hard
for me, but I'm sure Da Hye felt worse.
After all, I'm the only one
she could've confided in.
I'm sure she felt terrible, seeing
you with Jung Ji Hoon all the time.
And she couldn't even tell you.
I was just being selfish.
I didn't even consider that.
I'm such an idiot.
I really did like Jung Ji Hoon,
and I envied him.
I didn't mean to, but I ended
up making her more miserable.
I don't know why I'm so foolish, even
when I was given another chance at life.
Han Na's dad is Kim Young Soo.
This is how it has always been,
and this is how it will always be.
Hey, Jung Ji Hoon!
Ms. Hong Nan?
You terrible bastard.
You call yourself a human being?
- Why are you doing this?
- You really don't know?
Is this because of the gloves?
I didn't say a word!
What are you talking about?
You blabbed to everyone.
You freaking blabbermouth.
You need a beating today.
Geez, look at the state you're in.
My little blessing, are you
comfortable in there?
If there's anything you want
to eat, let Mommy know!
I'm counting down the days
until I can finally meet you!
Oh, this is your Dad, by the way.
Be careful!
How long are you going to act like this?
I'll just give you this before I go.
It would be terrible
if you caught a cold!
It's so cold. Make sure to keep warm.
Also, here.
Here. It's cute, right?
It's Christmas, after all. Here.
I'll be going, then.
- Mr. Young Soo!
- Yes? Yes?
I have a request to make.
Buy me cake.
Oh geez! And here, I thought...
of course I can buy you cake!
It's not like it's a diamond ring.
If I ask you to buy me a diamond
ring, will you buy it for me?
Of course I will! A diamond or whatever!
Yes, of course! You want one? Let's go.
Oh, I thought of a name for the baby.
- How's "Little Blessing?"
- It's so tacky!
You're right. That is tacky.
Oh, why did I think of such a tacky name?
Thank you for making me a father.
Um, er, it's a Merry Christmas
indeed. Merry Christmas!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
How long did you say
Han Gi Tak lived here?
Ten years. Probably longer
than that, actually.
I see.
[HAPPY LIFE! SEEKING TO MAKE
OUR CUSTOMERS' LIVES BETTER!]
We meet the owner of
"Knulp", Han Gi Tak!
Wow, owner!
"We heard that
you're currently single."
"We feel that you will develop
a desire to eat delicious food"
"in a cool location with
someone you love."
I do feel that way a lot when I see
the people eating at my place.
However, seeing my customers
happy while they eat
gives me the greatest
amount of happiness.
Oh stop.
You sound so boring!
This is why you still
don't have a girlfriend.
"If there was one thing you wanted
to do on a date, what would it be?"
Hold hands and walk on Mapo Bridge.
So it's not me, huh?
This is obviously a non-celebrity
you're talking about.
Whatever. Next. "What's the most
delicious thing you've ever eaten?"
The fermented soybean stew and rice
that my deceased mother used to make.
Rice and fermented soybean stew, huh?
What's so hard about making that?
"They say that you named your pub
after a book by Herman Hesse."
"Is there any special...
meaning behind that?"
It was the first gift I ever received
from the woman I love.
It was written by a person who wandered
around all their life while writing it.
But I still haven't finished
reading it yet.
It's way too difficult!
What's wrong with you, Song Lee Yeon?
That girl is nothing to me, anyway.
Wow, it's been a while since we
were at a place like this together.
No, it's the first time.
Oh yeah.
You told me before that I could speak
to you freely about anything, right?
- Yes.
- I'll take you up on that offer, then.
I received such a tremendous
amount of love from Young Soo
so I thought that I didn't have
the right to complain to him.
So I couldn't be honest with him
and tell him I was having a hard time
and I couldn't show him my true self,
since I acclimated to him.
I regret all that now.
Maybe he could've changed
if I had been more honest with him.
I blamed myself so much
for not holding on to him.
Then you appeared and
saw the true nature of our family
and you were a great source
of comfort for all of us.
We came to depend on you a lot.
That's right.
I became attracted to you.
I don't know if it's because
you're so similar to Young Soo
or if I just fell for you because
of who you are, Lee Hae Joon.
It may be that I kept searching
for Young Soo in you.
When I see Young Soo again
I'll ask him to chide me
for falling for someone else.
I can't do this anymore, though.
Because I love Young Soo.
- Thank you for telling me that.
- You're thankful?
Yes. I'm satisfied with just this.
Don't be sad. I'm sure your
husband will understand, too.
I'm just a fleeting person passing
through your life, with no significance.
If I was able to comfort you a bit,
I'm satisfied with that.
What should I do? Should
I leave the house now?
If it's hard for you, I can do that.
You said that you'd be
leaving soon, right?
Yes.
Stay until then.
But in exchange, I'd like if if we
didn't see each other again afterward.
Don't you worry about that.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Ah, this feels so nice!
- When did you get here?
- Get over here.
- Why?
- Come close.
- More.
- Geez.
- Geez!
- My pretty little brother-in-law.
- What are you doing?
- I thought long and hard about it
but it's really because
you're so damn lovable.
Get over here. What, are you going
to give me another passionate kiss?
When did I ever kiss you?
Thanks for loving my
little sister so much.
No, it's me who should be
thanking you with a big bow.
I think one reason we were sent
back here is because the man upstairs
took pity on us and wanted
to make sure that we at least knew this.
I think one of those reasons for me
is you, Kim Young Soo.
What's with you?
You're embarrassing me.
I can't figure out
the rest of it, though.
I don't really feel like there's
much else beyond that.
You're lonely, aren't you,
Brother-in-law?
If, just if, you could be born again...
no, if you could turn back time
and start over with Ms. Lee Yeon,
what would you want to do?
What would I want to do?
I'd just... want to hold her hand
like this and walk with her.
Oh geez, I must be going crazy.
I'm even hallucinating now.
Hey there.
Who told you to show up
without my permission?
What?
I'm saying this because you made me
worry when you showed up all the time!
Sorry for bothering you, then.
I never said it bothered me!
- Hey!
- I'll disappear, like you want me to!
I'll disappear from your sight forever!
I won't ever show up again.
Happy now?
You haven't changed a single bit!
Piss off? You want me to piss off?
How is that such an easy thing
for you to say to people?
How far do you want me to go?
Do you want me to leave the planet?
Do I have to come and go as you wish?
- What did you say?
- You and that nasty temper of yours.
I don't want to piss off!
I'm not going to!
Are your own decisions and
deliberations the only ones that matter?
- Are you that great?
- That's...
Don't you dare say that it was for me.
All you do is blame yourself afterward.
You're just going to be
crying by yourself again.
Am I wrong?
I wish Gi Tak had gotten
mad at me like this.
I really wish he had scolded me,
and called me a bad person.
There you go on again,
about Han Gi Tak.
I guess I really do miss Gi Tak a lot.
It seems that way,
since I keep seeing him in you.
Forget about that dead guy.
Judging from the way you speak,
the world is really a cruel place.
Do you think I didn't know
what he did ten years ago?
I knew all about
how he called my manager.
I was afraid that Han Gi Tak would
die if Cha Jae Gook found him.
Or at least, maybe I kept telling
myself that to make myself feel better.
It feels great to hear
you curse me out.
I want to be by your side.
Even if it's just like this.
I really didn't want to acknowledge
this because it hurts my pride...
but I missed you, Han Hong Nan.
- What are you doing? Hurry over here.
- What the hell?
You told me to piss off!
Ta-da!
- How did you...
- I really wanted to make this for Gi Tak
so you have it, in his stead.
I'm sure it doesn't compare to
your mother's cooking, but...
eat up, okay?
What is it? Does it taste bad?
No. It's just hot, that's all.
It's just really hot.
If it's hot, eat the things
that aren't too hot first.
Hello? What is it?
Ms. Hong Nan. I'm thankful for last
time. Want to have dinner at our place?
Oh, sure! Let's eat together!
I'll head over there tomorrow.
- Who was that?
- Just someone.
- Someone I like.
- Who was it?
Don't worry about it.
Have a grand old time and stuff your
face there tomorrow. Give it back!
Stop it!
Jung Ji Hoon! You can't do this. How can
you face Da Hye and Han Na like this?
How low will you go?
What did you call me up here for?
What's your reason? You knew that
I made Mr. Kim's death look like suicide
and yet, you didn't tell
Ms. Da Hye. Why is that?
Just how much do you know, exactly?
Does that mean that you
already knew Mr. Kim?
That's not so important now.
Get your head on straight
and live a righteous life.
You may end up offering hope
to someone one day, after all.
About that woman, Ms. Han Hong Nan...
She is being watched closely
by Cha Jae Gook.
Why?
I think Na Suk Chul and Cha Jae Gook
are linked to Han Gi Tak's accident
and there's a suspicious
element to that accident.
Are you saying that
it may not have been an accident?
He has his suspicions.
That's all I know.
Did Cha Jae Gook
do that to Brother-in-law?
No way. What exactly is going on?
[IS THAT THE REAL YOU?]
Who put the fortune cookies in my office?
Chairman!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Chairman! Over here! Over here!
- Gi Tak's younger sister, eh?
- Yes.
But, Chairman... is Na Suk Chul really
not linked to the Boss's death?
You ended up this way not
long after the Boss's death...
Na Suk Chul discovered you
unconscious at the pool.
He shouldn't have done that.
If he was going to strangle me,
he should've made sure I died.
How sad.
So I survived, huh?
You're taking good care
of that money, right?
Excuse me?
Oh! Yes, sir. Of course.
- Um...
- Don't open your mouth carelessly.
I'm not that curious about it.
Don't worry, sir. I'm sure
nobody will be able to find it.
Oh, really?
Yes. After all, it's a place that only
my younger sibling and I know.
Let me meet Gi Tak's younger sibling.
No, even a phone call would be fine.
I have something that
I really must tell his sibling.
You're here?
There's something that
I entrusted to Gi Tak.
Only Gi Tak and his younger
sibling know where it is.
Find it before that bastard
Suk Chul does.
You have to.
It's the last thing you can do for him.
Please wait!
You're awake!
This patient needs to be examined
so take him to the examination room.
No need.
If his heart stops again, he won't be
able to be saved. Is that okay with you?
Big Boss. If you woke up
you should've contacted me.
I was so worried.
I'm very disappointed.
- I'm really...
- Disappointed?
- Are you, now?
- Yeah, asshole.
Where did you hide the money?
Fess up, already.
Where is it? Where is it?
Hurry up and tell me!
I don't know.
The only person who knows
is no longer in this world.
Aren't you the one who killed Gi Tak?
No. It wasn't me.
It was you, you old geezer!
I'm worn out, so hurry up
and take my place.
I'm the one who suffered so much
making the organization grow this big
and yet, he gets to reap
all the benefits?
What an unfair world, damn it!
I'll ask you this one last time.
Where did you hide that money?
Oh geez... did I sleep too much?
I really can't remember.
Oh, I see. You slept
way too freaking long, huh?
Got it.
You should've told me
you knew, you stupid old geezer!
Yeah. What about our little Pretty Lady?
Ms. Hong Nan went to the columbarium
with Choi Seung Jae recently.
Columbarium? Oh.
Big Boss.
Where are you right now?
Huh? I'm at that worthless... um, I
mean, Branch Manager's place.
Don't move a muscle. Stay there.
- Wow, I'm so touched!
- You said before
that you wanted to act
like we were family.
I wanted to make you a hot meal
as if you were family at least once.
When you saw me for the first time, you
said "Missus" and were so friendly to me.
I was really thankful for that.
I'm kind of an introvert, you see.
- Oh, I see.
- Oh yeah!
Oh no! I was making rice, but forgot it!
Just a moment. I'll be right back!
Slow down!
[VOICEMAIL. PRESS TO LISTEN]
Voice message.
Oh ho. Looky here.
So that's where it is.
The secret stash that
the old fogey was hiding.
Where did you say is was right now?
The Branch Manager's home.
What should we do, sir?
Run and hide. It's time
for hide and seek, Pretty Lady.
Ms. Hong Nan! It's a
pressure cooker, so it took...
What happened?
[IS THAT THE REAL YOU?]
- Ms. Hong Nan disappeared!
- What?
She disappeared, and I can't
get in touch with her!
No! Han!
Branch Manger Lee!
- It was you, wasn't it?
- You must be completely crazy.
It was you, wasn't it, Cha Jae Gook!
- Hi there, Pretty Lady.
- Na Suk Chul.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever