[PLEASE COME BACK MISTER]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Hi, you pretty thing.
Na Suk Chul.
What have you done to Hong Nan?
What is this rubbish?
Please let go of him.
Where's Hong Nan right now?
Why are you asking me for her?
Was it really not you?
What would I do with that crazy woman?
What's up with that punk?
Look into it.
Yes, Sir.
(EPISODE 14)
Seung Jae, it's Hae Joon.
What's the matter?
Hong Nan disappeared.
Can you guess where she could have gone?
Na Suk Chul.
I think I know where they are.
Where's that?
Hey, pretty thing.
A revenge on Yi Yeon?
This isn't a revenge.
When you were yelling her name...
and jumped into Han River,
I almost thought you were Han Gi Tak.
You're as lame as him. No wonder you guys are siblings.
What is it that you want?
What do I want?
It's simple.
Ta-da!
How's this?
You hid...
the photo frame here.
Right?
Hide what?
What are you talking about?
You know what it is.
The secret account.
The key for your brother's secret account...
in the Swiss bank.
Where is she?
I'm having quite a few rude guests today.
Where is Hong Nan?
You people must be crazy.
What did you do with Hong Nan?
Who would harass her if not you?
Are you...
doing this because of...
- Han Gi Tak's sister?
- If you dare...
touch one hair on her,
I'll never...
let you off the hook.
What would you...
do with me then?
What...
shall I do?
Should I...
cancel all the contracts I've signed already?
What...
What shall I do for you to let her go?
What is it?
Should I go on my knees in front of you?
Quit this nonsense!
Na Suk Chul kidnapped Hong Nan.
Na Suk Chul.
Bring him to me.
I have a feeling...
that you tricked me and hid it somewhere else.
What are you saying?
Is it so wrong to take the only photo I have of me and my brother?
I haven't found the money, yet.
I need to ask Big Boss.
Isn't this unfortunate?
Your boss went back to sleep.
For good. Forever.
No way.
The boss...
Find it...
before Suk Chul does. You must.
That's the last gift...
I can give your brother.
Na Suk Chul! What did you do?
Hey, pretty thing.
If you keep doing this,
you'll be stuck to me for life.
I'll neither kill you nor let you live.
I told you already.
Once I bite, I never let go.
What was that?
Hey, Choi Seung Jae.
- Na Suk Chul.
- Hey, Choi Seung Jae.
- Did you ride on your horse?
- Let go of her.
What a shame. I can't let go...
of you princess just yet.
You have no manners, you jerk.
Why are you standing around?
Seung Jae!
Sit still.
Catch her!
Oh, my head.
Yi Yeon.
It's me.
There's no word yet, right?
No, I'm not worried.
She'll...
come back for sure...
as her rowdy self.
Stay out of it.
Why?
I'm just warming up.
Let's do this!
Good job!
Go.
Who's that punk?
Are you okay?
What's going on?
I'm Lee Hae Joon. I called up some of Gi Tak's guys.
You went missing. This is nothing.
Isn't that punk...
the store manager of Sunjin Department Store?
Is that him? Is that Na Suk Chul?
- That punk, I'll see the end...
- Stop.
You can't even fight.
Aren't you going to tell me what that was about?
Na Suk Chul.
My old friend...
or more like...
someone who thinks of me as his enemy.
Big Boss was more fond of me...
than Na Suk Chul even after I quit,
and that became his venom.
Big Boss couldn't trust him,
so he left the funds to me.
He did this to you so he can find the money?
Where is that money?
Somewhere safe.
It's a secret account under Gi Tak's name at a Swiss bank.
You need to have the secret key to withdraw the money.
Gi Tak died...
so only the remaining family members can take over the account.
By family members,
do you mean Da Hye?
Then, she needs to know that she had a brother.
If in any case...
Na Suk Chul finds out that Da Hye is my real sister...
No way.
I think it's best if I don't see her for a while.
I can't...
let Da Hye get hurt.
Boss.
I'm saying this on behalf of Gi Tak.
Don't seek...
revenge on anyone.
I thought you were going to die.
Why would I die?
How could I die, leaving you behind?
Why are you back so late?
Did you wait for me? You put the lights out.
Is everything okay? You should have called.
We had a problem but it's all good now.
Hong Nan is back at Yi Yeon's.
I'm relieved.
Actually, there was a huge fight...
but I took a bunch of guys and set everything straight.
Like this!
You should have been there to see it.
Weren't you going to say it was 17 versus 1?
Pretty close actually.
Have you eaten?
I guess I haven't.
Are you keeping me company?
Nobody wants to eat alone.
Consider this a special service from your landlord.
You must be a kind landlord.
It tastes good.
Hey, Yi Yeon.
It's not like I have a serious illness.
Oh, goodness.
I know. I do.
I know exactly what you mean so just stay still.
I'll do everything for you today.
Gosh.
What will you do for me?
I get anxious whenever you say things like that.
You always protected me.
I'm glad.
You seem much better than you did back then.
Eat up.
Good girl.
(DA HYE)
Are you all right?
Yes.
I'm glad.
I was worried.
You're not hurt, are you?
Are you asleep?
No.
You weren't responding.
I was happy...
that you were worried about me.
Don't do that again.
Next time, tell me before you leave.
I waited for you. I was worried, too.
I'm sorry for making you wait.
I'm sorry, my baby sister.
- Have a seat.
- Okay.
Mr Lee.
When did you put all those grapes up?
I was so touched by you and your mum, so I put them up.
Do you want to leave soon?
No way.
I promised I'd leave once the grape is complete.
Mr Lee.
Didn't she prepare a total feast today?
- She won't get a grape then.
- You're right.
I can't give her one then.
Oh no. I made a mistake again.
Han Na, is there anything else you wanted to do with Daddy?
I'll do them all for you.
Are you upset that I said you're not my daddy?
Still, I don't dislike you.
Is that right? Is that right?
Should we expand the garden, Young Soo?
Yes, Father.
Father.
I meant you. It slipped out.
Why do you keep doing that? You scared me again.
I get names confused all the time.
I even call Kang Ja, Han Na at times.
Right, Kang Ja?
And you.
Why did you respond?
You're so silly.
Let's eat.
(APRIL 7, 2016)
(I CALLED HIM YOUNG SOO AGAIN.)
(APRIL 6, 2016)
(I CAN'T REMEMBER THE DATE QUICKLY.)
(I GOT LOST COMING HOME. I CAN'T REMEMBER THE PIN NUMBER.)
(CATCHING DEMENTIA EARLY IS KEY, HOW TO DIAGNOSE)
Give it back.
Do you have dementia?
- Keep it down.
- Who else knows?
How could you have dementia?
Watch it.
You need to come with me.
Come here.
I said I don't, so stop it.
How long has it been? Does Da Hye know?
It isn't dementia.
Everyone's memory fails when they get older.
I'm exercising and going to the doctor regularly.
You should've told your son and daughter-in-law.
Your son didn't know anything.
I'm not sick.
I can't get sick. If I do, who will protect my baby?
- Mr Kim.
- Also,
when Han Na left home because she missed her dad,
how did you find her?
That's because...
Young Soo told me before.
I don't know how much you know about our family,
but don't act like you know.
- Sorry?
- Thank you for staying here...
for Young Soo's sake, but if you're going to be obvious about it, leave.
What do you mean?
Don't make it so obvious in front of Da Hye and Han Na!
Mr Kim.
- Did you know?
- Don't say that, either!
How long have you known?
Before the wedding,
Da Hye said she couldn't marry Young Soo.
She said she wasn't worthy, and came crying.
I felt bad for her...
and since my son liked her,
I wanted to protect her.
Of course, it was tough, but it's all in the past.
Now, she's my daughter and my baby.
She was so good to me.
Mr Kim.
You must have made a lot of effort.
Making effort doesn't work. You become a family naturally.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Why are you crying?
No, I...
Never mind.
Anyway, don't you dare say anything about dementia.
I'll kick you out.
Yes, Sir.
Let's do this!
She was just like Gi Tak.
This...
is certain.
It's definitely loyalty.
Do you have a fever, too?
Did you overdo it last night?
Where's Yi Yeon? Why are you here alone?
She said to protect you.
I'm not a kid.
I'm going out.
No.
Na Suk Chul hasn't given up on you.
- You punk.
- He's behind Big Boss' death...
as well as Gi Tak's.
If you get hurt as well,
I can't face Gi Tak.
I won't get hurt.
I promise.
I'll call you first if anything happens.
Okay?
This is loyalty.
That's right!
How did you find me last night?
- What?
- It's not like you have a tracker.
I raised my boys well.
You're so smart.
Can you come here now?
I practised dozens of times, so that I can.
I'll get better.
When will I be better?
I won't ask anything else.
I know how you feel now,
so I don't want anything more.
But if you ever need my help,
let me know.
If you ever want to find your family again...
or anything else.
I'll help you.
Thank you.
If that happens,
I'll make sure to ask you, Sir.
I think the ball is in your court.
Can you protect Da Hye forever?
If you can't, back off now.
Don't hurt her like I did.
Have you...
moved on?
It's my burden.
I must make amends for the rest of my life.
I hope you'll be happy here...
even if I'm not here any more.
Thank you. Have a nice day.
This just came in.
- It's new?
- Yes.
I wish we had met sooner.
How can I leave you behind?
What are you doing there?
Sir.
Was it you?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Was it you all along?
No, it's the first time.
I just wanted to eat one.
Liar.
It's true. I sheepishly came...
to bring you some coffee,
and...
(WHY ARE YOU AVOIDING ME?)
Who are you?
How are the employees responding to the new facilities?
I'm embarrassed to say it,
but they've gone nuts.
(GAME ROOM)
- Oh my gosh!
- Goodness!
- Look at this.
- Gosh.
Oh my gosh!
(FEMALE MASSAGE ROOM)
(MUSIC AND DVD ROOM)
(RELAXATION CAFE, FEMALE)
So nice.
This is awesome.
Are we dreaming?
Is this a pre-school?
We must stop meeting like this.
Mr Lee.
Sales went up because of Yi Yeon and employee satisfaction,
is that it?
Yes, for the first time in six years.
That's great.
We'll get a great price for the department store, thanks to you.
We'll confirm our decision to sell at the shareholders' meeting...
next week.
I said you can't sell the store.
You act like you're the only one who cares about this company.
I have plans as well.
Do you think the chairman will just watch?
Even if he opposes, I have plans.
It's finally stabilising. Must you do this?
Yes. You keep raising its value.
Good work.
What's taking so long to catch Na Suk Chul?
He got himself in trouble.
The police are after him.
Well...
Murder charges?
If Na Suk Chul takes this secret account,
Da Hye will be in danger.
Yes. I agreed it was best not to tell her.
But...
is this the right thing,
hiding who her brother is forever?
I've already died.
I'll only hurt her.
That money...
will put her in danger as well.
Na Suk Chul will be caught soon.
And I'm not talking about the money, but about Han Gi Tak.
You can't tell her.
At first, it'll be hard to accept that her brother died as well.
But...
both Yi Yeon and Da Hye have become strong.
Even my elderly father and Han Na are strong.
Even if the two of us are gone,
they will carry on with their lives.
I want to tell Da Hye...
that she had a brother who loved her more than anyone.
Actually,
I want to, as well.
I want to tell her...
it wasn't because I didn't love her.
I want to tell her that.
Let's tell her...
all of that.
We have no time to fear.
Look at this.
(I CAN'T WAIT ANY LONGER. THE SALE IS IN PROGRESS, EXECUTE YOUR PLAN.)
What's this?
They aren't love notes.
Is it someone...
who knows...
the real Lee Hae Joon?
Don't you think so?
Should we ask Maya?
Yes.
It's a spy that the real Lee Hae Joon had planted.
Does he know I'm a fake?
I don't know.
You should figure that out yourself.
Our time is almost up. Can't you be generous?
You know you don't have much time left, don't you?
I need to become real in order to protect what I have created.
You are already...
more real than the real thing.
It'll help in saying goodbyes.
Come to think of it,
I've done nothing for my family.
Whatever.
Of course, you have.
This is where you wanted to eat?
Jae Gil's food is not fit for human consumption!
Let's eat at home! Come on!
Shoot.
Ta-da.
(KNULP)
My sign.
How is this...
It couldn't be.
He was drowning in debt,
so he put the restaurant up for sale.
So I bought it...
and put it under your boys' names.
Who asked you to do this?
I wanted...
to get it back for them.
It's not because of you.
It's for Da Hye.
What?
She has nowhere...
but the department store to remind her of her husband.
I don't want this pub to be a source of pain as well.
It's the only place where the three of us met while alive.
I want to replace the bad memories with good ones.
You fool.
Who else would've helped me, but you?
Right? Boss.
Welcome!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Welcome, our dear customer.
Sit here.
Can I make an order?
It finally feels like...
I'm back.
- Welcome to Han Gi Tak's Knulp!
You guys...
What? Were you moved to tears? Okay, fine.
Fine, I get it.
- Stop it.
- Fine.
What are you doing, Boss? Blow the candle.
I'm the owner?
Sure, let's blow it out!
Hold on, wait!
It's such a historic day. I need to take my camera out.
Okay. Wait, hold on.
Why is this so blurry?
Move.
Oh, that looks good.
You look so ugly!
- Hurrah!
- Cheers!
He's my type.
How cute. He's so cute. Look at him.
They look happy.
You rascals.
Do you think you can reopen the pub at this rate?
It's been merely a few months and you've lost your grip.
Get your mind back in the game.
Commence!
- Yes, Ma'am!
Don't be confused. Stay calm.
She has tendency to intimidate others.
No wonder you are related to Gi Tak.
You focus on your own job. Just do your job.
You're the most troublesome out of all of you.
Can you tell sugar, salt and artificial seasoning apart?
I cannot.
Just do your job and stop trying to discipline the guys.
Are you watching?
It feels like you are back.
The consignee is Lee Hae Joon,
the store manager of Sunjin Department Store.
Sunjin Department Store?
He's the one who brought Han Gi Tak's guys...
to rescue the girl.
So Lee Hae Joon and Han Gi Tak know each other.
I'm back.
You're back late.
Did you wait for me?
Yes, I did.
People usually stay up when their family hasn't returned home.
Family?
You should rest.
Do you want to have dinner...
with me tomorrow evening?
Let's eat together before I leave for good.
I hope you can make it.
Sure.
Han Na,
you can go to school on your own now, right?
Try to go with your friends and use the main roads.
When a stranger talks to you, ask for help from adults nearby.
And when you're going out, make sure you tell...
your mum and grandpa where you're going. Got it?
Fine, I get it.
Stop nagging me.
You're just like my daddy.
Fine, Kid.
You can go by yourself, right?
Why? Why do I have to go by myself?
I have to go to work.
- Okay, then.
- Hold on.
I walked you all the way here, so you have to pay for it.
You look like an octopus.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Go on.
Sir, do it like me!
Like this! It's good for preventing dementia.
- Like this?
- Good job.
- You're doing well.
- Like this!
Walking and exercising are good for preventing dementia.
Even when I'm gone, you should come out...
and meet your friends. Keep exercising, too.
Don't you worry.
I'm strong for my age.
My brain is functioning perfectly, too.
And my spine is also in good shape.
Look.
Oh, dear.
Father, when did you shrink?
You used to be so big.
I'm still in good condition.
Hello, ladies! Hello!
He just started working out here. Please treat him well.
- Sure.
- Hello.
He's so charming.
He's smart, too.
His hips are nice and his waist is strong, too.
Sir, show them.
What brings you here?
I wonder.
One of you fall into the river and the other gets kidnapped.
What a mess.
Why are you staying behind here for?
Anyone could drop by here.
And here's that random person dropping by here.
What is it now? What is it?
Young Chan is looking for you!
I'll come and get him!
He wants to eat with you.
The three of us.
It's not like I want to but I don't have a choice. That's what he wants.
For goodness' sake.
Why am I even wasting my precious time...
here to tell you this, anyway?
It's deserted here.
I don't know who he takes after, but he's eating well and growing fast.
Gosh, why is he acting like that? He's making me more anxious.
Don't get intimidated by him.
He can't get his hands on you now.
I wasn't intimidated.
I won't let him step all over me any more.
Yi Yeon.
I have a favour to ask of you.
Forget about Jae Gook and Gi Tak...
and you should enjoy your life.
Don't worry.
I've started the second phase of my life.
I hope you meet a good man next time.
Not like Gi Tak who loved but was a coward...
or Jae Gook who liked you but harassed you.
You should meet a man...
who'll love you for who you are.
No, actually,
you don't have to date anyone.
Just...
meet someone nice.
Someone who can...
stay by your side as a friend and as family.
That sounds like you.
Don't go anywhere and live here with me.
I want to live like this forever,
eating your food.
I'll watch you meet someone nice,
fall in love,
get married,
have kids...
and happily grow old.
I'll watch in your brother's place.
That is the future...
I dreamed of with you.
Oh, gosh.
Dol Sem, go with Da Hye and bring a new mannequin.
Sorry? It's so scary down there.
I'll get it myself. I'm strong.
- But...
- I'll be quick.
Couldn't you go with her? It's heavy.
She's too quick.
What do you mean you were lonely?
Are you saying you weren't happy?
- Mr Lee.
- Is that...
how you've felt all this time?
What a strange man.
(GOODBYE, MY LOVE, I WANT TO GO HOME.)
(STOP SQUAWKING ABOUT SALES!)
(DA HYE, YOU ARE...)
Da Hye, you are always pretty,
but you're the prettiest when you smile.
But don't smile in front of other guys. It makes me jealous.
There's so much abuse of power here.
When I'm tired, I get on the elevator.
Because the day you smiled at me for the first time comes to mind.
The egg attack. You are my vitamins.
My joy, Han Na.
She is the greatest gift you ever gave me.
Thank you.
I say this hundreds of times a day,
but I never said it to you.
Thank you for being my wife.
Da Hye, I love you.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you that I love you more.
And...
please be happy,
old lady.
(OLD LADY)
(WOULD YOU LIKE TO MEET ME? - X)
Your call is...
What is our cutie pie Mr Cha doing that he won't answer his phone?
Sir.
I'm sorry to call like this.
I'm in a bit of a pickle.
I know that already.
Your number showed up quite a lot on the call log.
Is that right?
Detective, what did you say you came to discuss?
I'm investigating on Na Suk Chul...
for the murder of Chairman Jang Jin Goo.
Is that right?
I need to take this.
Sir.
I won't go down that easily.
Help me, please.
I know you're in a jam,
but are you worth investing in?
You know I don't invest in something that won't pay off.
Bye.
Wait!
I have an important appointment.
- Bye, then.
- You rotten crap.
Then about Gi Tak...
Kill that piece of garbage!
Mr Cha Jae Gook, who hired me to kill Han Gi Tak.
What do you say?
Shall I go and introduce myself to your family?
Or shall I share this with the whole world?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Aren't you hungry?
No.
I'm starving.
Should we eat first?
Do you want to wait for Daddy and eat together?
Yes.
Do you like eating with Mummy and Daddy?
- Why?
- Because I like it.
Daddy!
Young Chan!
You waited for me.
My son is the absolute best.
Welcome, Ma'am!
Please follow me.
(PLEASE BE HAPPY, OLD LADY)
No one cares about a wound here.
You may not understand what I'm saying right now.
I take back the "shoot".
That one, too.
Good job.
(MR LEE)
Old Lady?
Hello?
Are you still there?
Of course.
- Where are you?
- I'm almost there.
You'll wait for me, right?
Yes.
I'll wait.
I'll keep my promise this time.
I've been on this deserted island for 51 days.
What's more frightening than hunger...
is despair.
It is that nobody is looking for me.
Father.
I can finally say it.
I've resented you...
for the past when you shunned me,
and now, for not searching for me.
I hate you for it.
But now,
I will forgive you.
It is too miserable...
to leave the world with hatred.
So I...
forgive you now.
And...
I love...