Subtitles by DramaFever
Want to have dinner with
me tomorrow evening?
Let's have dinner together
just once before I go.
It's the one place the three of us
met when we were alive.
I want her to think
fondly of that place.
I don't want this to be the source
of a painful memory for Da Hye.
So Lee Hae Joon and Han Gi Tak
knew each other, eh?
Mr. Cha Jae Gook, who wished
for the death of Han Gi Tak...
I won't go down so easily.
Are you all right?
- I'll help you up!
- Can you get up?
- Aren't you badly hurt?
- Are you going to be okay?
Just wait a bit longer.
I'll be right there.
[Become happy,
Middle-Aged Lady.]
Middle-aged lady!
You're still there, right?
I'm almost there.
I'll be there soon.
You'll wait for me, right?
I'm a bit late, aren't I?
These got all wet in the rain.
But will you still accept them?
[Episode 15]
Did something happen?
I ran over because
I was running late.
You could've taken your time.
I didn't want to be late this time.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, valued customer?
I already ordered for us in advance.
That's okay, right?
The chef's special
is ready for us, right?
Of course, sir.
- Hey, hey, be careful!
- Ooh, so much pressure!
Hey, make sure you take
good care of them.
Yes, chef!
- Please enjoy!
- Thank you.
Let's eat.
I heard the food here is great,
but I've never had a proper meal here.
Here.
It's okay. Give me mine
back. I'll be fine eating it.
I wanted to do that for you.
Go on and eat.
How is it?
Is it good?
You're not eating?
Go ahead and eat.
But, you know...
Why did you want to see
me here, of all places?
Because I was so thankful for the
warm meals that you made for me.
So I wanted to buy you a
delicious dinner, at least once.
Even though this is nothing compared
to all you've done for me.
Also, because you
became my family.
Thank you so much.
I wanted to be sure to tell you
these things, no matter what.
I... feel great.
I kept my promise this time.
- Um...
- Today, you...
look so beautiful.
Mr. Hae Joon!
Hey, Honey!
Hey, wake up!
What do we do,
Ms. Hong Nan?
- Call the ambulance, now!
- Yes, ma'am!
What?
I... got... hit by a car.
- Will he be okay?
- Is the patient okay?
Doctor!
- What happened to him?
- It was a hit-and-run.
Let's do a thorough
examination of him first.
Please stay here.
Why didn't he say something?
- He'll be okay.
- Why does he do this?
Why go through such great lengths?
Round up the kids and find out
what the license plate was first.
We're in a hurry,
so make sure you do it quickly.
And call me as soon
as you find it out.
Okay, got it.
Are you just going to
let him die like this?
It truly is a shame
but it seems that Mr. Kim Young Soo
will be returning earlier than expected.
What kind of bullshit is that?
It'll be hard for him
to live past two days.
Wait, you're not saying... that
he's going to die again, right?
It can't be helped, as he
brought this upon himself.
So you want him to
die like that, again?
You're the one who made
him into Lee Hae Joon!
Save him!
Now, damn it!
I cannot do anything that interferes
with the life and death of humans.
You should at least give them
time to say their goodbyes.
Bring him back to life!
What can I do?
I can't just let him die like this!
- There is one way, but...
- And what is that?
I'll do anything.
Mr. Han Gi Tak. Can you share the
time you have left with Kim Young Soo?
Please, please wake up already.
If you don't,
I'll get mad at you!
You said that you'd come
and go, like the wind.
You can't do this to me.
Hurry up and wake up,
and leave our house smiling!
Let's go home.
Are... are you okay?
I want to go home.
I want to lie on my own blanket
and listen to Han Na chatter on
and eat the food
you make for me.
Yes, let's go.
Where's the patient
that was just here?
- He was discharged.
- What?
- But he has a brain hemorrhage!
Geez... just what kind of trouble
did this guy cause this time?
- You're back?
- Yeah.
- Geez, makes me so worried!
- What is it now?
Cha Jae Gook!
He asked me to get dinner
with Young Chan and him
but he wouldn't smile
or even talk in front of her.
Geez, seriously.
Something's definitely off.
- Really?
- Gosh.
Oh my.
Oh my, this is me!
How long has it been?
I did this interview 10 years ago!
Wow. Your older brother sure
did collect peculiar things.
I don't know who
this lovely lady is
but she sure was pretty
10 years ago
and she still is now.
She's pretty, right?
She sure is.
Sheesh... it's been far too long.
I look so young here!
President Cha, it sure is a nice
change of pace to see you like this.
Meeting under a suspicious bridge.
How suitable, really.
I guess the thug life hasn't
been easy on you.
That's why you're going
to save me now.
We're on the same
boat, after all.
- Give me "that" first.
- Ah.
You mean, this?
Kill that piece of trash!
Oh my, how surprising!
Now you have to show me the funds.
That'll have to be the
original recording.
Of course it's the original.
Oh my. Looks like you've
gotten yourself new buddies.
An owner can't let
his crazy dog run amok.
Crazy dog, eh?
Oh, yeah.
Did you hear?
Here I was, doing
my crazy dog thing
but he kept getting in
my way, so I ran him over.
I'm talking about your rival,
Lee Hae Joon.
What?
Lee Hae Joon?
Why would I run him over,
you may ask.
Well, that's because
you ordered me to.
Just like how you told me
to kill Han Gi Tak.
So you killed him and you're
going to put the blame on me?
I've been taking your
crap this whole time
so I need some sort of insurance.
You were the one who told me to kill
Han Gi Tak and Lee Hae Joon.
You commanded me to
do all that. You did!
Because we're
in the same boat.
Wow, this son of a bitch.
You dare try and blackmail me?
You're laughing?
Oh, ouch.
That hurts.
You think I brought just that
without anything to defend myself with?
Surprise!
Just you wait for it.
Find him.
Find him!
Go after him.
Hurry and find him!
Damn this loach-ass bastard,
slipping away from me!
Hurry up and find him!
Find him!
[Hurry up and get better, Mister]
Oh no, that'll leave a scar.
Good morning,
Middle-Aged Lady.
- Are you all better now?
- Yep.
I feel like I've made
a complete recovery.
That's a relief.
Come downstairs and eat.
It felt like someone kept on taking
care of me in my dreams.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Did you hear me ask for a sticker?
Oh, Ms. Maya!
I think the watch is broken!
The time I have left here
decreased by a ton!
- It's not that it's broken.
- What? What do you mean?
It's not that your time has decreased.
It's actually increased.
That's all I'll say.
Say it in a way
that I'll understand!
You'll find out when
you come back.
Just make sure you take care
of everything you need to.
This isn't nearly enough time!
It's like that for everyone.
I'm curious what your plan was for
acting oblivious this whole time.
It was to the point where I wondered if
you really were the Lee Hae Joon I know.
I couldn't trust you completely.
I believe that you said something
similar before, as well.
I'm not exactly
a trusting person.
Lee Hae Joon, the leader of
the Sunjin revitalization project.
The Chairman was
your official guardian, but
the one who protected a motherless boy
like he was his own was someone else.
And that was the Chairman's executive
secretary, which was my father.
I didn't expect that at all.
I wanted to confirm the
results of his efforts
for the sake of Sunjin's
future, for myself.
Right now, there's a game going on that
is leaving you at a disadvantage.
May I help you now?
if I want to stop the department store
from being sold
I have to become the real Lee Hae Joon.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye!
- Oh, hello!
- Hey there, friend.
I came to raise
your sales for you!
Hello.
Ms. Hong Nan was at the pub.
She's not your manager anymore?
That pub was originally
her older brother's.
I've heard that, yes.
She said that she learned
from him when she was younger
and even taught me a few moves.
Her older brother was
originally the chef there
but he was a skilled
fighter back in the day, too.
You must have been
close with him, too.
Han Gi Tak.
That's his name.
Han... Gi Tak?
I really liked him a lot,
but he died.
And now, his men are protecting me.
They're so wonderful to me.
Are you all right,
Ms. Da Hye?
Yes.
I'm fine.
How strange.
Why am I reacting this way?
Branch Manager!
Have you seen this?
Oh my gosh.
Oh me, oh my!
Yes. The preparations to sell the
store are going well, correct?
Make sure you manage
the directors until the end
so that the sale can
be finalized this time.
Are you the one whose voice
was recorded and put online
where the person was ordering a murder?
What are you talking about?
Rumor says you're the one
that ordered a man named
Han Gi Tak killed.
Word is spreading fast.
Stop it with your nonsense.
Which bastard sullied my name when I
have such an important deal coming up?
The police are on the
move right now, too.
Big trouble, sir!
If this is true,
I can no longer help you.
What's wrong?
Did something happen?
Um... are you all right?
I think this voice file is
talking about our Boss Gi Tak!
What should I do,
President?
These nasty bastards.
Then, shall we do as we
planned, to Han Gi Tak, and--
Kill him! That piece
of human trash!
- Then, I'll do it, as planned.
- Oh my gosh!
You know, I saw that too.
Isn't that this store's President?
- Oh, no way!
- Kill him!
That piece of human trash!
- Oh my!
- Then, I'll do it, as planned.
Han Gi Tak.
Kill him!
That piece of human trash!
Cha Jae Gook.
- Oh my!
- The President? Really?
Um, Ms. Da Hye.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Are you all right,
Ms. Lee Yeon?
Of course. I'll be sure to
come back next time.
Kill him! That piece of
human trash!
You killed Han Gi Tak?
Just who is spreading
around this nonsense?
- Did you cause his death?
- I'm Cha Jae Gook.
Why would I be so afraid of
some thug that I'd kill him?
I'll kill everyone who goes around
spouting nonsense like that!
Yeah, it had better not be you.
Because if it is...
I'll destroy you.
Good. Now you're finally showing
your true colors, Lee Hae Joon.
I'll be sure to make you feel the pain
of the people you've trampled on.
- It can't be.
- Song Lee Yeon.
No matter what a terrible man he is...
he wouldn't have done this.
Hong Nan, I'm sorry. I have something
else I have to do today.
I'll be going now.
Did you hear it?
Cha Jae Gook and Na Suk Chul...
those bastards killed...
- Follow Song Lee Yeon.
- She's not important right now!
Your older brother
was murdered!
- I'm begging you.
- Han Hong Nan!
Think about what
Han Gi Tak would want.
Are you okay,
Ms. Hong Nan?
That's what I want to say.
Here.
Are you alright?
No. I'm not
alright at all.
I didn't exactly live as
a goody two-shoes
but I didn't live such a bad life
that someone would
want to kill me, right?
Geez, why are you
saying such things...
I cast my family aside and
hurt the woman I loved.
Is that why I was punished this way?
Don't worry. I'll be sure to uncover
who was responsible for sure, so--
No. Instead of doing that, stay by
my Hong Nan's side a bit longer.
She asked me if I was okay.
Even though I'm the one who's
so sorry for having died like that.
I can't be by her side, so be by her
and protect her in my stead.
Even if you have to do so for the
remainder of your time here.
I promise I will.
I'll use all the time I have
left to be by her side.
Han Gi Tak.
That's his name.
I told you that only crybabies cry
just about anywhere, right?
You're so cool,
my Little Sis.
- Where are you going?
- Ms. Da Hye.
Ms. Da Hye?
Um, did you have a bad
dream or something?
I guess I'm just
having a hard time.
It's so strange. Why do I feel like
something bad is going to happen?
- Can I ask you a favor?
- Go ahead.
Even if you leave, don't leave
without saying anything.
You have to say goodbye
before you leave, okay?
Okay.
I promise I will.
So you've finally made
your appearance.
Did you really...
do that?
Did you really tell him
to kill Han Gi Tak?
How many years has it been since
you've come into this room?
But this is what you came
in here to say, huh?
You didn't, right?
You didn't. You didn't, right?
Hurry up and tell me.
You didn't, right?
Hurry up and tell me
that you didn't do it!
You can't have done it!
No! No! No! No!
Yes, I killed him.
I was the one who had him killed.
I told them to shred him apart so that
there wasn't a piece of him left!
Happy?
- No... tell me it isn't true!
- No, no!
I killed him. Why, you ask?
Because of you, Song Lee Yeon...
because of you.
Where are you, punk? You don't
have time to be doing this to me.
Are you going to see
the prosecutors?
- Huh?
- President.
Wouldn't a more formal outfit
be better suited for this?
Why? It's not like
I did anything wrong.
Oh, come on in.
What is all this?
Cha Jae Gook is being investigated right
now as a potential perp for the crime.
But Jung Ji Hoon and
Choi Seung Jae both said
that there were many mysterious
aspects about your death.
So I decided to look
into it again, myself.
The truth behind
Han Gi Tak's death, huh?
All right, lay it on me.
Okay, first: the black box camera in your
car that should've been at the scene.
Secondly, the driving patterns of the
paparazzi and the truck driver.
They were both quite suspicious.
And thirdly, they did this
in a place where there were no CCTVs
to see what happened.
- So?
- So!
What is it that we need?
Our brains.
Let's go through the accident again,
using your memories of the night.
- Yes, Seung Jae. Let's talk later.
- What happened, sir?
The police are even at the
restaurant right now.
- What?
- They're making a fuss, looking for you.
What are they talking about?
Physical assault?
What, exactly, is--
So they're starting with me, eh?
All right, bring it on!
Han Gi Tak was in the middle of
chasing down a paparazzi's car
to clear Song Lee Yeon's name.
He also knew that there had been
an assault incident with Yoo Hyuk
and that he'd been
caught in someone's trap.
So he followed the paparazzi
who'd followed Song Lee Yeon
and then the first phase
of the accident happened.
And the second phase of the accident
was when the truck hit Han Gi Tak
and thus, ensuring that that he'd
be crossing over to the next world.
You don't remember anything about that?
Like, anything strange that stood out.
Well, I'm not sure.
Thinking about it...
What's this?
"Purgatory?"
There was a cigarette
in my pocket.
And just what
the hell is this?
Even though it'd been quite
a while since I'd quit smoking.
You okay, Mister?
Hey, Mister.
Is he dead or alive?
Hey, Mister!
Is he dead?
Here you are, sir.
Go on, now.
What should I do, sir?
- Disgusting scum.
- Then, shall we do as planned and kill--
Kill Han Gi Tak!
This piece of human trash!
Only do as we'd planned,
without any issues.
When he said "kill him,"
it was merely in a fit of anger.
His original plan was to lock
Song Lee Yeon up with the scandal.
Yes, I'll be sure to take care of
Han Gi Tak without any issues.
[Cha Jae Gook:
Recording]
Good work. Get some
good rest now. Later.
Na Suk Chul, that bastard.
He used Cha Jae Gook
to kill Han Gi Tak?
What a pitiful bastard.
He'll burn in the pits of hell.
The one who did the hit-and-run
was Na Suk Chul, too.
So it was Na Suk Chul, huh?
What does he want, exactly?
He killed the Big Boss, who was like
his parent, as well as his friend.
The only thing he cares
about is money.
Now, he has nothing
left to lose.
Cha Jae Gook ended up this way, too,
so Na Suk Chul's last hope is...
the secret funds?
Until Na Suk Chul is good and dead,
Han Gi Tak's little sister must be me.
No matter what.
Will they be okay?
If we go back like this,
will Da Hye and Lee Yeon be okay?
I have to hurry up and catch
Na Suk Chul while I'm still here.
What the heck?
Why is it different than mine?
- Why do you have so little time left?
- What are you talking about?
What did you do?
Your time hasn't decreased.
It has increased.
That's all I'll say.
Did you, by any chance,
give your time to me?
She said that you didn't
even have two days left.
It was for my little sister's sake.
Hey, come on, you.
I told you, be good to your wife
if you have time do be doing this.
- Hey!
- Geez, how pathetic.
- Pathetic?
I want to forget so badly, but I can't.
So what am I supposed to do?
I want to just rip it out of
my heart, but I can't!
And they keep wandering around me,
to the point I want to claw my eyes out.
You call that pathetic?
I'm the most pathetic
person in the world.
I wish you could've been
here with me too, Gi Tak.
Your younger sister grew up
to be so pretty and strong.
It would've been so nice if
we both could have seen her.
Gi Tak?
Oh my. Wow!
My wish came true.
And here I was, wishing I had
a photo that we'd taken together.
I'm sorry, Gi Tak.
I did whatever I wanted, and then
couldn't help but want to see you
and then went to seek you out,
like a selfish woman.
I'm sorry.
I knew that you'd never
be able to forget me
and yet I kept telling you to
forget me and to piss off.
I'm sorry for loving you.
I'm sorry.
Song Lee Yeon.
No, it's fine.
No need to be sorry.
Cha Jae Goo isn't the one
who did that to Han Gi Tak
so there's no need for
you to feel guilty.
I'm sure that Cha Jae Gook
feels totally drained right now.
So you have to take
good care of Young Chan.
Isn't that right?
That's what I came here to say.
I'll be going now, then.
Show me your face, won't you?
I have to leave soon.
I've done all I had to
do here, after all.
[The 15th Sunjin Shareholders' Meeting]
President!
Oh my. It's been a
while, directors.
I heard quite a strange thing
through the grapevine.
Apparently, one new topic up for
discussion has been added in.
Number One!
The termination of the President.
Number Two: Regarding the
selling of the department store...
Do you really think
Number One will happen?
But... I do wonder whose
bright idea this was?
Was it you? Or was it you?
Which bastard dared to try and fire me?
It was me.
I did it.
Lee Hae Joon.
What right do you have to--
Well, I'm only the
majority shareholder.
What?
I bought them out bit by bit
all thanks to you making the
stock worth next to nothing.
Wouldn't 4.9 percent
be sufficient?
Covering up an employee's death
from being overworked as suicide.
Trying to cover up
a bribery scheme.
Trying to cover up our decrease in
sales by renovating the store.
Using company funds to
fund private investments.
Ruining our image with
your dating scandal.
Having shown that you're a
risk to our company many times over
our Sunjin Department's
position is becoming quite shaky.
No matter the situation
the company and owner
must be separate entities, and
we must establish a firm foundation
so that Sunjin will no longer be shaky.
And with that in mind, I propose the
termination of President Cha.
Father. You sure did
raise a great son.
You must be real happy,
as one of the two ended up all right.
We'll now be discussing the
termination of President Cha.
Okay, we'll do it with
a show of hands.
Those in favor of terminating him,
please raise your hand.
Due to a unanimous vote,
President Cha has now been terminated.
For the time being, Lee Hae Joon will
take over the position of President.
What a great decision!
- It was for the sake of the company.
- Is this your way of comforting me?
I know that you didn't actually
intend to kill Han Gi Tak.
Piss off.
In the end, you managed to
acquire the department store.
- Yeah.
- But, um...
Why did you want to meet at a
place like this? It's so awkward.
- We're... going to see Da Hye.
- What?
Sit down.
I know you want to see her.
The one who wanted to meet
in the first place is Da Hye.
What?
Ms. Hong Nan!
I found these while I was cleaning
the Branch Manager's room.
This kid is definitely me.
But I don't understand any of this.
Please tell me...
how do you have this?
The truth is... we've found
your older brother.
But I can't tell you that person's name,
age, or even where they live.
He doesn't want that.
He can't appear before you
but one thing is for certain.
He loved you very much
and wanted to protect you,
which is why he left you behind.
Is my older brother...
Han Gi Tak?
[Epilogue]
It's too far.
Whatever.
No need to look.
Wait!
It's here!
- Over here!
- Please, save us!
Subtitles by DramaFever