Please help me.
My dad did not commit suicide.
Something went wrong.
He would never do that.
Please help me.
Let go.
- Please help me.
- Han Na.
You shouldn't do this.
I'm sorry, Sir.
Who is she?
She's the late Kim Young Soo's daughter.
I have proof right here.
He wouldn't have committed suicide after...
buying a gift for my mum!
Please help me.
Please help.
Please help, Sir.
Please.
Hello?
So it's you.
3747.
He is...
Cha Jae Gook, the president of Sunjin Department Store...
as you may know already.
Are you all right?
Stand up then.
Daddy told you to get back up even if you fall down.
I heard that's what he used to say.
Are you okay?
(Episode 4)
That morning, he made me teach him how to make cute faces...
to make Mum feel better.
He got the necklace a few days before to surprise her.
Why would he commit suicide all of a sudden?
You know exactly how I feel.
He wouldn't want his money to go to waste.
He wouldn't die.
But there may be something...
in the adult world that kids can't understand.
That can't be.
He was frugal but he wouldn't do anything bad.
He was a scaredy-cat.
Even if things were hard for him,
he wouldn't have left me and died.
That's my baby.
How could I leave you?
Your mum told you he died of a heart attack.
When did you find out?
I'm not a fool.
I just pretended I didn't know.
Can Dad...
I mean... Can I keep this and give it to Mum later?
If I give it to her now, she might get sad.
Why?
Are you going to deduct it from Mum's debt?
I wonder who you take after.
Gosh, seriously.
Are you really an important person?
Yes, I'm the most important person here.
I see.
No wonder you have enough money to loan to people.
No, I don't loan money.
Have you ever seen a loan shark this handsome?
My dad said the handsome ones cause more problems.
I'm sorry.
Why are you here?
- Why aren't you at school?
- Mum.
That's not the problem.
If that's not the problem, then what is?
Why are you here?
- What are you doing here?
- Why are you hitting her?
Mum,
I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Mum.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I got angry.
You're awesome.
I knew it.
Cha Jae Gook made up Yi Yeon's scandal.
You became the store manager overnight.
I sure am glad you're my friend.
This is the place.
It's where I took my last breath.
That must've hurt.
Actually, I don't remember...
whether I was hurt,
sad...
or scared.
I'm sure you were hurt, sad and scared...
just like me.
I feel that way now.
My daughter...
I'm afraid I might make her cry again.
It hurts me,
saddens me...
and scares me.
She's pretty...
like her mum.
I'll find out no matter what.
I'll never...
make my girls...
cry.
You and I both have a long way to go.
By the way,
was the world we lived in...
this lovely?
There.
Who are you?
Father,
he was here yesterday.
Who was here yesterday?
That's right.
Yesterday feels like the day before it.
And the day before yesterday feels like yesterday.
Have dinner before you go, Mr Moneylender.
Do you...
think the same way?
Do you think it was suicide?
Do you really believe that?
The circumstances were...
Do you believe it wasn't suicide or do you want to believe it wasn't?
What difference does it make?
A dead man tells no tales.
That's the funniest thing I've ever heard.
Hey, you.
You're blocking my way.
I have no place to sleep.
I'm asking to stay in your room not in Yi Yeon's room.
Why won't you let me stay?
Gosh.
Stop talking nonsense. You better go home...
before it gets ugly.
I am not talking nonsense.
You getting a circumcision in middle school was what got ugly.
Why would Boss...
Gi Tak said...
What else did he say?
He said you would never betray him...
even if everyone else in this world does.
"Today, I saw Song Yi Yeon in Sunjin Department Store."
"She was flirting with her ex-lover in front of her ex-husband."
"I think she is crazy."
"She's coming out with a movie. An erotic movie would be perfect."
"She can't live without men."
"Her poor son..."
Stop it.
Why? There are 600 more.
So please...
face the reality, Young Chan's mum.
Yi Yeon,
why did you act up?
He must have felt threatened.
I can see by the way his servant coming here...
And barking up.
What?
Shall I call you...
a slave instead?
I know you work for him.
That's right.
We get paid from the same man.
So let's be polite to each other.
Don't make me pop in and out. It's tiring.
You got this big house. You're fed well and dressed nicely.
Who'd put down...
that much money for a has-been actress?
- Then...
- The investor is...
very upset in many ways.
The dead man is dragging down a living person.
I'm so upset.
Send your son to his father.
- Live freely and act...
- Let me go.
Let this go or I'll kill you.
Who's that?
Na Suk Chul.
Why you...
I'm sorry, Sir.
This is my sister whom I told you about.
I told her now, but she begged to at least run errands.
- Let's go.
- Let go of me!
Are you the president...
Na Suk Chul?
I am.
Would you like some coffee?
Naturally.
These are the offers that came in.
One has a nude scene.
And the other is an adult movie.
Which one do you want?
You should be grateful...
and do as you're told, okay?
Stop being obvious that you're a thug...
and stay out of it.
I'll take care of my own business.
What will I ever do about that confidence of yours?
It tastes good.
I'll work like a dog and pay back your money...
and leave this dump.
Please do.
Gosh.
You drink...
way too much.
You're too weak.
There's a meeting with producers tomorrow.
They're working on something with Director Bong Soon Wook.
I'm not ready yet,
but they insist it must be me.
How do I look?
Am I a big mess?
Well,
not so much that you're unrecognisable.
I gained 5kg after having a kid.
I'll look huge on screen.
But...
what's your name again?
Hong...
Hong Nan.
Hong Nan?
Han Hong Nan.
What a pretty name.
That looks good on you.
You keep it.
Hong Nan.
Let's not meet again.
I...
want to forget the name...
Han Gi Tak.
As if...
he were never in my life to begin with.
I'll pay back all the debt I owe Gi Tak...
on my own later.
You may resent me,
but for now,
I want to live a quiet life.
What did that jerk Suk Chul say to you?
Please.
Get out of my face!
It's too late...
to repay that debt.
I shouldn't have...
come back.
Did you see?
That punk shook his body and completely ignored me.
He did this as his greeting.
Did you see that woman mock me?
And who was that kid?
They teamed up to insult me, Cha Jae Gook,
and in my own department store, too!
You too, punks.
You should respond when someone talks to you!
Shoot!
Don't be nervous just because he's the chairman.
Right now, he's my father.
Mr Chairman! It's an honour to meet you!
Mr President. I was out of it earlier.
I'm sorry!
"Increase Sunjin Department Store's sales by 130 percent in 2 months!"
"You'll be busy starting tomorrow, so get some rest!"
That is what he says.
Whatever it is,
don't do it.
- Sorry?
- You can't have it anyway.
What do you mean?
Drop the act.
What? Just because he called you into the department store,
do you think Father will accept you?
Absolutely not. Not a chance.
So don't even bother.
I see. Is that so?
If you return to the States now,
I'll make sure you go back with a lot.
The department store is closing down anyway.
The losses are multiplying as we speak.
The store is shutting down?
He was just yelling at me to increase sales.
I died for nothing.
I'm sure you understand what I mean.
You're smart, aren't you?
Yes, Sir.
You're smart, so you understand.
I'll try my best, and if I fail,
we can talk again then. Goodnight.
It's about to get interesting.
She wants to forget.
She wants to erase me,
is that it?
Go.
Don't go.
Gosh.
What am I doing here?
I have nowhere to go...
and there is nobody waiting for me.
Why did I even come back?
I'm so hungry.
Gosh.
If you need help or have any question,
press the star button.
It's a direct line to reach me.
What is it?
Would you like to return?
Goodness. I didn't press it. I really didn't!
Wait a minute. Were you watching me all this time?
- Are you a pervert?
- It's called monitoring.
You are not a prosecutor.
What you are doing is illegal.
Goodness.
Why are you insulting me? I'm just trying to do my job.
Don't. Stop working so hard!
- It's going down
- Gulp it down
- Stop right there.
Let's be cute and adorable.
- The rabbit descending from the sky
- Says carrot, carrot
Hong Nan.
Let's never meet again.
I...
want to forget the name...
Han Gi Tak.
As if...
he were never in my life to begin with.
I am back.
- I am trash.
- I am totally trash.
- I met her,
- loved her...
- and left her on her own.
- That's my biggest sin.
That was amazing.
It's a masterpiece. I could watch it again.
The rosy red wine
I signed another big contract today.
Han Gi Tak, are you watching?
I'm watching, you jerk.
You can't beat me
Even if you give your best
You are dead already, you punk.
I must sound crazy.
When...
did I put the light on?
What's going on?
What's wrong with it?
Shoot. Why is it not working?
Let go of me!
You brat.
It's not working again.
My punches are not working.
That hurts. Stop.
Just stay low, you stupid girl.
Girl? Did you call me a girl?
I bit him like a girl.
So unmanly.
Seriously...
What?
What are you doing here?
Do you even know what you are doing?
Why would you crawl in there?
Did you follow me?
Don't go.
Go.
Gosh.
I met her,
loved her...
When did I turn the light on?
I guess you were worried, then.
I am not interested in who you are.
If you were looking to dig up something,
you better go away before you get hurt.
You are trying to scare me away,
but I know exactly what you are thinking.
You are so cute.
How can I leave you behind?
What a man.
Didn't they teach you to respect others in the States?
What's wrong? Should I call you by your name?
You punk.
I... I warned you.
Get going.
Don't treat me like a woman.
Treat me like a boss.
Why do you keep appearing in front of Song Yi Yeon?
That's what I wanted to ask.
- I saw a ghost!
- That dude.
Why did he appear in front of Song Yi Yeon all of a sudden?
This is dangerous.
Follow me.
Hold on.
Oh my goodness!
You are doomed.
Say hi.
(Han Gi Tak)
He doesn't have a family that would hold memorials for him.
I was planning to throw away his ashes in the ocean,
but I was afraid it will make him lonely.
(Han Gi Tak)
Now that I see this,
it finally hit me.
Don't act up.
If you fall into danger,
I'll be too ashamed to speak to Gi Tak again.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
What happened that day...
was purely an accident.
You could have been hurt...
if you were there with him.
It's a relief that you are okay at least.
You were right.
That's why I am waiting for the right moment.
I have to wait until nobody pays attention.
I have to hold my breath...
and watch quietly.
You are not...
I will...
reveal the truth.
Gosh.
This is awesome.
It's nothing.
What you need is...
Enjoy your weekend!
Bye!
Yes!
It's awesome.
Yes, Gi Tak.
What's wrong with your voice?
What? You have no place to sleep?
Man, you stink.
How much did you drink?
Did you make a run without paying?
She wants to forget.
She wants to erase...
Han Gi Tak.
Did Yi Yeon say that?
But...
Seung Jae...
How could I forget him?
He's family.
What shall I do?
Shall I go or not?
I can't control my body.
These are my fists.
Why is it wet?
Is it raining?
Come on. A tough guy like you shouldn't cry.
Why are you crying?
It keeps...
raining.
Don't be like this.
Gi Tak. Gi Tak!
Gi Tak! Gi Tak!
Gi Tak!
You look handsome.
You look good even when you just woke up.
Good morning.
Hey!
- Hello.
- Hello, Mr Lee.
- Mr Lee.
- I love you.
- Oh my.
- Gosh.
- Goodness.
- He's so good looking.
The secretary's office is having crisis.
- Why?
- To be Mr Lee's secretary,
someone even cancelled her maternity leave.
Oh goodness.
There's someone already chosen to fill the position.
Aren't I too old to do this job?
Why am I shaking?
Get out of my way.
Come in.
Yes, Sir.
Mr Lee.
Here's your coffee. Did you have a good break?
Yes, thank you.
Well,
you're not upset about serving coffee, are you?
Not at all.
I am very honoured to serve you.
Please help me until I grasp my tasks here.
Yes, Sir. I'll do my best.
Stand aside.
Don't block the view.
They can't see me.
So...
you ordered the full glass walls for...
It's a work benefit.
- Hi.
- Gosh.
It's to cheer up the employees.
I see.
I'm cheered up as well.
Very much so.
When you receive new menswear products,
send them to my office first.
Pardon? What for?
I'll put them on and walk around. I'll be like a model roaming around.
The sales will shoot up, won't it?
I see, Sir.
It's more convincing because you said it yourself.
One's face completes one's look.
Face completes fashion.
You are complete.
You work in fashion. When will you complete your look?
Pardon?
Your eyelids are starting to sag. How about getting them lifted?
If you leave them like that,
they'll sag like this. You might not be able to see.
No, Sir. I can see very well.
All right. Let me know when you can't see.
Yes, Sir.
Okay.
Oh goodness.
What is it, Sir?
I want iced coffee all of a sudden.
On a cold day like this?
Shall I bring a new one?
- Yes.
- Sure. I'll bring a new one.
I'll bring iced coffee.
Hey.
Hey!
Did he bring a woman?
Yes, Sir. And...
Come on.
You whisper like a sad undertaker asking for payment.
Stop that.
Whisper of an undertaker?
Just say it out loud.
- Nobody is listening.
- Right, Sir.
I think she was the reason why he postponed coming to work.
He invited her to his house.
He spent many nights drinking with her in expensive bars.
He finally brought her to the department store...
and...
And...
they are shopping.
Bang!
These are just my taste.
Those are mine!
Buy me! Buy me!
Please...
Please buy me.
- Gosh.
- Oh my.
Hello, Mr Lee.
My friend wants to buy some clothes.
Then I will help...
Will you help, Ms Shin Da Hye?
Me, Sir?
Yes.
She...
is really my friend.
She has horrible taste.
Please recommend her some clothes.
Please help me.
Your wife is so pretty.
No wonder you insisted on coming back.
She's totally cute.
Would you like to try it on?
- You look beautiful.
Do I have to wear these stockings?
They're giving me a wedgie.
It's nice and elegant. We'll take this.
And that and that.
Ring up the bag and shoes, too.
All of them?
Yes.
I'll charge it.
The black card that only the top one percent uses.
Single payment please.
- How much is it?
- That will be 9,620 dollars.
Are you crazy? Don't do it.
When else would I do this?
- Single payment, please.
- Yes, Sir.
It's okay. I'm the store manager. It's okay. I'm the store manager.
That would be months of my salary.
Oh my goodness.
He has so much money already.
I see why women shop when they're depressed.
Hey.
What is that walk?
Women are all about attitude. Stand up straight. Chest...
Chest out.
Stick out your butt like this.
This is the most beautiful pose.
Like this?
Can't you do that right?
Is it hard?
- Put your hand on your waist and...
- Okay.
Press down and...
What a waste of expensive clothes.
But you know,
your wife seemed very familiar.
Where have I seen her before?
Where would you have seen her?
I'm sure I've seen her before.
Maybe she looks like Madam Bong from the club.
Do you want to die?
I've already died, punk.
By it for me.
Hey. Hey!
Do you have an appointment?
Someone else stood there and asked me the same question before.
I'm sure she was fired the next day.
Of course, that was long ago.
He's in a meeting right now.
They say that every time I call.
It's good to be busy.
As long as he doesn't forget who made this a major movie company.
I can't wait long.
You can't go in!
You came out.
Miss Song.
What brings you all the way here?
You seemed busy, so I came myself.
Did you talk to the director?
Oh, that.
I told him that you would be perfect for the role,
but he had a different image in mind.
Most actresses won't be able to pull off that role.
My sentiments exactly.
But you know how stubborn Director Bong is.
He's not a rookie, so I can't be too pushy.
I'm leaving.
- I'll see you at the shoot.
- Okay.
Miss Song.
I'll play a mum.
Aunt. Grandmother. That's fine.
Small roles are fine. Just give me something.
Yi Yeon.
For old times' sake.
Please.
I'm sorry,
but I have no choice. That was the investor's condition.
Sunjin Group has been pressuring everyone,
so you'll only be able to do indie films for a while.
Shoot.
You must be so upset.
That scum!
Shoot.
Director Bong is calling.
What?
Hello, Sir?
What? Today?
Do I have time? Of course...
I'll have to check.
How does my day look? I have a little time? Okay.
I have a little time.
I don't usually go to that part of town, but I'll go just for you.
Okay. I'll see you later.
He asks for hot coffee then iced coffee...
then honey water.
And...
he has a strange habit, too.
Let's work hard together.
Do you need help?
I guess I don't have to worry.
Punks like that are easy.
He's not as great as the rumours say he is.
I drank a lot last night.
You should all cut back too.
You'll get in trouble in your afterlife.
Mr Jung, what are you doing here?
He was recently promoted to manager.
You were? Manager?
Wow. Then you're the same as Mr Ma.
How impressive.
Ji... I mean, Mr Jung.
You saw Kim Young Soo on the way to work on the day he died, right?
Yes.
His daughter says...
he had a date with his wife that day.
And he asked you to cover for him at work, right?
Yes.
You're saying someone who asked you to cover for him and had a date...
committed suicide, is that it?
That is...
Why did you conclude it was suicide when there was no note?
Did you see him on camera?
We have a video of him getting into the elevator alone.
He took off his shoes and there was no sign of foul play.
Because of these and other reasons, the police concluded it was suicide.
I see. Circumstantial evidence.
I'm sorry,
but I don't understand why you keep asking about him.
Why am I here?
Because the chairman told you to increase sales.
Sale? Yes!
I need to increase sales.
But would you want to...
shop at a despicable store like this where an employee took bribes...
and killed himself?
That's why...
I want to clear this despicable store's name.
- Pardon?
I plan to expose why Mr Kim had to die here, to which...
he devoted himself for 15 years.
I'm sure the reason is right here.
Are you saying...
whether or not it was suicide,
the cause is within the company?
Exactly.
If something is rotten,
we must cut that out, must we not?
For the sake of our sales.
Don't you agree, Mr President?
- What was his problem?
- Exactly. I don't understand.
Mr Lee is very zealous.
Let's hear what you have to say.
These are people who saw Mr Kim...
on the day that he died.
That night,
he was very desperate and passionate.
He didn't look well.
He said it was his anniversary...
and that he hurt his family, and begged and begged...
for another chance.
To be honest,
he's the one that won the Lucia deal.
But...
he committed suicide that very night?
I can't believe it.
I was shocked when I saw the news.
I felt like I did something wrong.
I didn't smell any alcohol on him.
He rushed out of the car...
and suddenly threw up.
Did you see him jump?
I said no.
I heard a thump and looked down and...
he was already...
Wait, is that a camera?
Why you...
I have nothing to say. Just go.
I heard you quit the job the day after Mr Kim died.
Will you explain?
I have nothing to say!
Leave me alone!
We couldn't get anything else from him after this.
What was he so afraid of?
But you know...
we need to focus on what he did say.
I said no.
I heard a thump and looked down and...
he was already...
The camera is awesome.
Wow.
It smells all sorts of dirty.
He didn't see it.
He was on the roof for 1 to 2 minutes.
Unless he was hanging on somewhere where he couldn't see and fell,
it was enough time to witness someone trying to commit suicide.
Let's assume something.
Everyone said he looked ill that night.
What if he didn't jump voluntarily?
So what is that reason?
He isn't a window-washer.
Why did he go up there unless he meant to die?
It's not like we can ask a dead man.
Mr Lee.
So, are you saying it was or it was not suicide?
That's what I'd like to ask all of you.
There is a man.
He works himself to death during sales season...
to meet the target of 130 percent increase.
There are times when he sleeps 2 hours and eats twice in 2 days.
He eats kimbap, hamburgers and the like...
and downs it with soda.
He has no time to work out and goes to the gym twice in six months.
He takes diet pill because his boss tells him to lose weight.
And he drinks every day with clients.
If you add up all the alcohol he has drunk, it is 1/30,000 of...
the Pacific. Is this or is this not suicide?
Cerebral infarction, myocardial infarction, high blood pressure,
hyperlipidemia, diabetes!
There are 15 ailments!
(Physical Examination Result)
But he overworks and drinks every day.
His body probably sends him signals with constant pain,
but he ignores them and pushes onward.
Is this or is this not suicide?
A suicide without a doubt.
You work an average of 40 hours a week, correct?
With Mr Kim,
he worked on average 72 hours a week...
although he was paid for only 45.
He devoted more than half of his life to this place.
That's how most of the employees at the department store work.
Everyone who works with them can attest to that.
You pressure someone with unrealistic sales targets...
and yet, how can you say his death was not the company's fault?
If the company is even one percent responsible,
we must admit it and compensate him accordingly...
at least for the family...
who lost their only husband,
father and son.
That was very moving.
You have a point.
But...
you said the company is responsible for Mr Kim's death.
Then...
is that woman Shin Da Hye working at...
the company that killed her husband?
If she had any suspicion about her husband's death,
how could she work at this company?
Don't you agree, Ms Shin?
Hey.
Hey. Hey!
Is it hypothermia?
No! No! You can't die.
No! You can't leave me here and die!
No!
Who are you?
(Come Back Alive)
It is too painful for me to look at you.
Did you think you could keep hiding it?
Why did he have to die?
I'll give you that answer.
Please wait.