This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
[Episode 14]
Geez, you surprised me!
What are you doing here?
You scared me!
Why are you drinking?
You should study instead!
If you're not going to study,
wash up and go to bed!
Man, what a shock.
Did you get home okay?
Did you get a girlfriend, Big Bro?
What?
You just look like
you're in a good mood.
So I was wondering if you
got a girlfriend or something.
Yeah. I did get a girlfriend.
Who is it?
What?
Who's your girlfriend?
You don't need to know.
Stop thinking about nonsense
and focus on studying.
He's stupid when it comes to
studying, but he sure is perceptive.
Should I just tell him the truth?
No, they're just fleeting
unrequited feelings anyway
and he'll probably get over her
on his own soon enough.
There's no need for
me to get involved.
I don't want all of this
to become a huge headache.
The person who'll become my
girlfriend is Professor Park Ha Na.
Well, it's only unrequited
love for now, though.
I'm going to start dating her
after I pass the exam for sure.
Uurequited love?
If you have time to be thinking about
nonsense like that, study more.
He knew exactly how
I felt about her...
and yet he was doing that
behind my back?
Yeah, Gong Myung?
What are you doing?
Let's have a drink together.
Oh, we can just
drink that together.
What?
What's with you?
Why are you drinking alone?
Why else? It's because he's miserable
over Jung Chae Yeon, of course.
Because of Master?
Why?
Answer me!
Do you like Jin Gong Myung?
Yeah, I do.
Why do you care?
What is it?
Why do you feel miserable?
You don't need to know.
There's just something, all right?
Yeah, don't pry any further than that.
There's just something with him.
Hey, what's with you?
Things between Joo Yeon
and me are totally over.
What?
Why? I thought you two would get
back together after you passed.
What do you mean,
what am I talking about?
I'm saying that Joo Yeon
got herself a boyfriend!
Hey, it's only been two months
since we broke up, okay?
And yet you're already
seeing another guy?
I don't have a boyfriend, all right?
I thought you'd be studying
hard after we broke up.
You've been snooping around
on my social media site?
Don't call me again.
We're over.
Hey! I asked you why
you two are really over now!
Yeah, um, don't pry.
He has his own circumstances too.
What's with all three of us today?
What do you mean
all three of us?
I don't think that
I have a shot with Professor Park.
She got herself a boyfriend.
Geez.
What's with all of us today?
But... why'd you leave your house?
What? You left your house, man?
Why?
Don't pry.
Something just happened.
So let me sleep over at your place.
You room is bigger than
this guy's, after all.
No.
How could you even ask...
You can't sleep in my room tonight!
What's with him?
Hey, what did he mean by that?
He has his own circumstances.
Let's go to my room.
Where'd you put the TV remote--
Huh? Where did he go off to?
Looks like he ran out since
it's the weekend tomorrow.
I ought to rip him a new one.
[No Geu Rae]
Yes, Ms. No Geu Rae?
Yes. The weather
nowadays is so nice.
How about we walk
near the Han River tomorrow?
Yes, let's do that.
And how about we get lunch
at Kyungridan-gil?
Yes! What should we eat?
Anything is fine with me
as long as I'm eating with you!
Then what should
we do after lunch?
I'm fine with anything
as long as it's with you!
Me too. I'm fine with anything!
Yes, see you tomorrow, then. Yes.
Oh wow, did you have a party, Miss?
Looks like you had
tons of people over!
Huh? Oh... yes.
Man, I need to cut
back on my drinking.
Oh, is that Professor Jin?
No way. We talked on
the phone for so long too!
Let's all go hiking as a team-building
activity since it's been a while.
Okay, buddies?
What? Why hiking?
I want to rest tomorrow!
Why hiking?
Damn it!
But he'll be really peeved
if I don't show up.
Wow! I'd love to go hiking! Whoo!
I'm fine with hiking.
I was feeling depressed,
so I should get some air anyway.
What? It looks like
everyone is going!
Oh well, it can't be helped.
This is my first weekend date
with Professor Jin after all.
I have important plans
tomorrow, so--
Why aren't you responding,
Professor Park?
You're not going to say that you have
important plans and not come, are you?
I really hate it when people try to
wiggle their way out of group stuff.
Let's go together, Ha Na.
I'm so depressed.
Of course she'll come
since all her seniors are coming.
Are you serious?
Damn it!
Yes, of course I'll come...
Wait. How come Professor
Jin isn't in this group chat?
Maybe he forgot to include him?
Then I could call Professor Jin over
and have ourselves a secret date!
Um, Director. I think that you left
Professor Jin out of the group chat.
Should I invite him in?
Let him be!
I didn't include that asshole in the
chat since he hates group activities!
Damn it!
Oh, I see. You're doing him a favor
because you think he'd hate to come.
No, it's not because I thought he'd
hate to come. It's because I hate him.
After eating with him that one time,
it's clear that he's super picky
and just does whatever
the hell he wants.
It pisses me off so, so much
to be anywhere near him.
Yeah, there's no need to tell Premium
Trash! It'll just inconvenience everyone!
Looks like we'll do lots of team-building
by bonding over our hate for him.
Mwahahahaha!
What's with everyone?
Geez! Ugh!
Professor Park, pack
some snacks for us.
Have a light heart
and a heavy pack! Got that?
Ugh, seriously?
Hiking?
Yes. The director wants us all
to go as a team-building activity.
Just refuse and say you
had prior engagements.
And tell them that
it's really important.
I want to do that too, but I'm
not a top lecturer like you are.
And I'm not in a position where
I could just straight-up refuse them.
I can't believe he's taking
your weekend now too.
What a ridiculous director!
He should go hiking by himself if
he wants to go! Team-building, my foot.
Wait. You said that this
was for team-building, right?
But he didn't tell me
anything about it.
Um, well, that is...
He probably didn't
contact you out of respect
since he knows how much
you hate group activities.
No. It's obvious that
he's just leaving me out.
Well, at any rate, I'm really sorry.
All right. Have fun then,
Ms. No Geu Rae.
What the hell!
Man, I even planned my outfit
for tomorrow's date too!
I hate being forced into
lackluster situations such as these!
Joo... Yeon.
It's just a misunderstanding,
Joo Yeon.
If Jin Gong Myung passes
the civil servant exam
I, Park Ha Na, will seriously
consider dating him.
[Delete]
[Delete one audio recording file?]
Um, I thought you wanted to hike.
Why are you dressed like that?
Oh, I lied to my family and said there
was an important meeting I had to go to.
- What?
I mean, it's kimchi-making
day at my house today!
You know how I almost broke my back
making 200 cabbages' worth of kimchi
while listening to my mother-in-law's
never-ending nagging last year, right?
I don't even eat that kimchi anyway
because it's too damn salty.
I really don't want to do it.
So I told a little white lie this time.
But will you be okay hiking
in those clothes, Director?
Director! How about we scrap this idea
and just lie around all day?
That's not a bad idea.
Oh my gosh.
I cannot allow this.
This person... is mine.
- What are you doing now?
- What are you saying?
And why are you wearing
your hat like that?
You're impersonating Park Bo Gum from
"Moonlight Drawn By Clouds," right?
Yep!
Here, look.
I cannot allow this.
Your Highness.
This person is mine.
Well? How was it?
It was the same, right?
Oh, whatever!
Why are you impersonating Park Bo Gum,
of all people, with a face like that?
Ha Na.
That annoyed you too, right?
Say something.
- What?
- Yeah.
I cannot allow it.
Professor Min.
This person is mine.
What are you doing?
I thought you said you didn't do
impersonations on your days off.
I'm going to do this at my lecture
tomorrow, so I thought I'd practice
and see how people react to it.
Whatever. Anyway, you brought
me spare clothes, right?
Hand them over.
I'll go get changed.
- Yes, see you soon.
- Yeah.
Why are you all taking a break already?
We haven't even gone that far yet!
Oh, hello!
Um, what... what brings you here?
What do you mean?
I'm here to hike, of course.
I often hike around here
on weekends.
O-oh! I see, I see!
Yeah, this is a nice trail. Yes.
Yeah, um, we just, um, all happened
to run into each other here.
Yeah, right up there!
What an amazing coincidence, right?
Yes!
Yes. One would even think that you left
just me out and planned all this.
Oh, of course we wouldn't!
How could we come hiking and leave
you, the star of our academy, out?
All right.
Be on your way, then.
I'm sure you don't want
to hike with us anyway.
No, no. Let's hike up together,
since we met up here.
- Huh?
- What? Why?
Why?
What, I can't hike with you all?
Of course you can't...
not come with us.
Of course you can come.
Um, yeah.
Um, okay, then.
Let's go together.
Sure.
Damn that asshole.
Why is he here?
Let's go, sir!
What's going on?
What do you mean?
I came to see my girlfriend.
What?
Ha Na! Hurry!
Oh, okay!
Ugh, damn it!
These pants are too long!
I just want to cut
this part right off!
I will not allow that.
Those are my pants.
What are you doing? Stop it with
that gaze that you can't even pull off!
I cannot allow that.
It's my gaze.
Geez. Ugh!
Why did Premium Trash
insist on coming with us?
Damn it!
I feel so uncomfortable around him
because he rejected me at the club.
No, I shouldn't complain.
You got left behind on a bridge
over the Han River after all.
Um, yes.
Don't worry about me, Ha Na.
Let's forget about Asshole Min Ho
and Jin Jung Seok
and have fun lives
as single women.
Okay?
Wow, look at the fall foliage!
It's so pretty!
Oh wow!
Should I just tell her the truth?
No, she came here to make
herself feel better.
And this will just make
her more depressed.
I'll tell her about me and
Professor Jin when she feels better.
It looks like you're hungry.
Go and eat with Ki Bum.
I have no appetite.
No. There's no use of
eating in this state.
I'm sure that Ki Bum has no appetite
either since he's miserable too.
- Ugh!
- Come on!
What are you doing?
What else, you bastards?
Why are you still lounging around?
Do you know what time it is?
Let's go out.
I'll buy you guys hangover soup.
You looked just like the male protagonist
of a melodrama yesterday
but you totally did a 180 overnight.
Yeah.
Are you crazy?
I heard that your hopes for being
with Master are all gone now!
So what?
I can just find a girl who's much
prettier and much nicer than she is.
So forget about Professor Park, okay?
Let's be real.
She's way too old anyway.
And you forget about
Hwang Joo Yeon too.
You really still want to be with her
when she dumped you?
- What?
What I'm saying is there's
plenty of fish in the sea!
So don't be all depressed
and let's hurry and go out.
Did you even really love
Jung Chae Yeon?
Yeah. To think that I was so worried
about your stupid lighthearted love.
Whatever, man!
Let's go out already!
- No thanks.
This won't do.
If you don't leave this room
by the time I count to 10
I'll call the manager.
You know that there's
a no-guest policy here, right?
10.
Nine.
- Eight.
- Let's hurry and go.
- Seven. Six.
- Come on.
- Five. Four.
- All right, man! Give me a minute!
- Three.
- Okay, already!
We're going!
- All right!
- Two! One! To the manager!
- Get out, please! Get out!
- All right, already!
Oh my gosh!
Why is your bag so heavy?
The director told me
to bring the snacks.
Geez. Does he not have hands?
And I see him using his hands
so, so well, all the time, like this!
Give me your bag.
Oh, it's okay.
What if someone sees?
Everyone else went ahead already.
Nobody will see.
Here, give that to me.
Why aren't you coming, Ha Na?
What are you doing with
Ha Na's bag, Professor Jin?
Oh, um, Jin Yi.
The thing is...
I wanted to see what
brand the bag was from.
The brand?
It looked familiar,
so I just had to look.
But it's just a cheap knockoff,
just as I expected.
Wow, that Premium Trash!
Now he's even looking down
on my bag of all things?
Unbelievable.
Ugh! That trash.
What was that?
Hey.
Here, have this.
Eat with some gusto,
you bastards!
Here.
No, you eat.
Just eat when I'm actually
offering you food, man!
Geez.
- Hey, want to go see a baseball game?
- Why?
It's the bestfor making
you feel be ter!
Man, it's been three years since I've
been to a game because I was stuck here!
And yet you do everything
else that you want to do.
You didn't go to any baseball games?
Hey.
People may call me
a lounging good-for-nothing
but there is one rule that
I always follow.
I can never leave Noryangjin to play.
And I can never go on blind dates
even if I'm interested in the girl.
I do have some morals too, you know.
- Whatever.
- Anyway!
Let's go and cheer up!
Shut it. We don't even have
the money for that.
We may not have money,
but I have my mom's credit card.
Here. Ta-da!
Let's go.
Wow.
Take my hand.
Oh, it's okay.
What if someone sees us again?
Who cares? Didn't you see
my top-quality acting before?
I can explain my way out of any
situation, so hurry and take my hand.
Ha Na!
Let's go together!
Wait up!
Oh, Ms. No Geu Rae!
- What was that?
- Are you all right?
Help me up too, Professor Jin!
- Ow!
- I think so.
- Try moving your leg.
- Ow!
- I'm okay.
Oh yeah. Jin Yi!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry!
What was that, Professor Jin?
How come you helped her up,
but you didn't help me?
Am I not human?
Am I just an animal?
Well, you were definitely acting
the part at the club yesterday.
What did you just say?
I told you yesterday.
Don't act like you know
me outside of work.
I don't want to exchange words with
a low-quality individual like yourself.
Man, this got everywhere!
I'm going to the bathroom for a bit.
Oh, okay.
What's with him?
Geez, Park Ha Na.
You left something behind again!
Ha Na!
Ditch that stupid Professor Hwang
and meet me at the rest stop.
Don't get too close with her.
She's such a low-quality woman.
What is this?
I'm going on the hike now.
I'm sad that I can't see you.
I'm more upset than you are.
Well, anyway, have fun.
Okay!
Wait a second...
are these two dating?
I love you.
I love you more.
Why, these little... ugh!
Oh, Jin Yi!
Oh.
Hey, Park Ha Na.
Are you dating Premium Trash?
Jin Yi.
So he didn't come here by chance.
He came here to see you! Right?
Wow, this is hilarious.
This is so funny!
Then, yesterday, at the club
he came to see you then, too?
And yet I was going on about
how I was going to seduce him!
You two were making
a laughingstock of me, weren't you?
It must have been so funny
for you to watch me, wasn't it?
No, that's not it. I...
No, this is so, so funny.
I thought it'd really be
a while until I smiled again
after breaking up with
that asshole Min Ho.
But thanks to you, I had a real laugh!
Thanks. Really.
Please don't be mad, Jin Yi.
I just couldn't tell you because I didn't
want to make you more depressed.
Yeah, I totally understand
how you must have felt.
Of course.
See how I'm laughing? See?
Thank you for understanding.
Also, I know that this is shameless of me
to ask, but can you keep this a secret?
Of course. It's not like anyone
would believe me anyway!
Premium Trash, who said
he'd only date someone
with supermodel looks and
who graduated from Seoul University
likes someone like you,
of all people!
Who'd believe that? Right?
Oh my! What a riot!
Hey, hurry over to the rest stop
and spend some nice-ass time with him.
I, a low-quality woman
I, who's like an animal
will hold back my tears
and climb the crap out of this hill!
Wow, this is so, so funny.
Unbelievable. Crazy.
- Wow!
- Jin Yi!
Damn it!
You bastards. The game is going
badly because of you downers!
Here.
You have to put these on
your heads so that they'll win!
- Go team!
Whoa!
- Whoa!
- Whoo!
[Calling Jin Gong Myung]
What the hell,
Jin Gong Myung?
Let's study together on the computer.
Log in now.
Jin Gong Myung, are you still asleep?
Jin Gong Myung, how come
you're not responding?
If you do this, I won't study
with you on the computer.
He hasn't even read it yet.
Your call is being redirected...
What is really going on?
He was so determined until yesterday.
Did something happen?
What's up with the triangle kimbap?
I didn't have breakfast
this morning, so I got hungry.
- Do you want to have some?
- No thanks.
My feet are sweating so much.
Take good care of yourself, okay?
Or find a woman who will do that for you.
Why would such a woman go out with me?
I'm a divorced man
who doesn't make much money.
You should meet a woman
who is dying to get married then.
There she is.
What? Professor Hwang?
Why not?
Professor Hwang is dying to get married.
She just happened to
break up with her boyfriend.
This is the perfect time.
You should be forward.
Would Professor Hwang even consider me?
You're not saying you don't want that.
- I guess you like the idea, huh?
- What?
That's not what I'm saying.
She's not my type...
Now is your chance.
- I will support you two.
- What?
When a woman and man go hiking together
they will fall in love without a doubt.
No doubt.
I also fell in love with my wife
while hiking Mt. Seorak.
- Did you really?
- I'm saying you will.
That's why I don't even pee
in the direction of Mt. Seorak.
Because I hate it.
Anyway, it works.
I will support you all the way.
I won't allow it.
It's my private love life.
I won't allow it. It's up to me.
Director Kim. Director Kim!
What was that about?
- What? You want us to bet?
- Yes.
Let's divide into teams
and see who gets to the top first.
Whoever loses will pay
for drinks tonight.
No thanks. That's cheesy.
Come on, it will be fun.
The youngest and oldest,
Professor Park and I, will be one team.
Professors Hwang and Min
are the same team.
- Why are you leaving me out?
- What?
Do you want to bet too?
You won't come to drink
with us anyway. What for?
Well, I will go then.
What? Professor Jin is going
to have drinks with us?
How did that happen?
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
So you will be the judge.
No Geu Rae and I will be a team.
Wow, you're acting really weird today.
- Are you seriously going to bet?
- Yes.
It looks like it's very clear
who is going to win.
I always bet on something
I will definitely win.
- A bet you will definitely win?
- You seem good at hiking, huh?
No matter how good you are at hiking
are you as good as this wild animal?
But you're still an animal
no matter what.
When it comes to hiking
you need a strategy such as knowing
geography and controlling your pace.
Director Kim, let's start, shall we?
Good then.
Whoever reaches the top first
take a photo next to the rock on top
and post it on our chat room.
Then it will be counted as a win.
So let's hike to the top now.
Ready, set, go!
Next team, set, go!
They look better together
than I expected.
I wish them all the best.
No Geu Rae, let me carry your backpack.
No, it's okay.
Give it. We're on the same team,
so no one will suspect anything.
We should win this bet
since we're doing it.
- Hold my hand.
- What? It's okay.
We should win this bet
since we're doing it.
Professor Jin, are you really
coming to drink with us?
Since my girlfriend can't miss it,
I should be there for her.
That's why you're doing this bet.
I wasn't reluctant.
Actually, I was glad to have this bet.
Now I can be with you openly
thanks to it.
Hurry up. Hurry!
We have to beat that team.
Move out of the way. Hurry.
What kind of man are you?
She's a wild animal.
I will make sure he pays a lot
for the drinks tonight.
I will make him spend
all his money and cry.
Professor Hwang, wait up for me.
Hurry up, will you?
We're winning. Let's take a quick break.
I'm so tired now.
No, hurry. Seriously.
You want to push me? You don't have to.
- Climb up now.
- What are you doing?
If you don't hurry, I will stick this in.
- I will give you a wedgie.
- I won't allow it. It's my butt.
It's not a good time to be impersonating.
They've almost caught up with us.
- Hurry up. Hurry.
- Okay, okay.
- Hurry up.
Okay.
Professor Hwang, gosh.
Are you okay?
- I can't.
- You can't, right?
Let's drop out of the race.
Carry me on your back now.
- What?
- Carry me on your back.
I shouldn't be carrying anybody
on my back at the moment.
- Carry me on your back!
- I'm still mourning, you know!
- Hurry up. Hurry.
- Okay, I got it.
Hurry up! Hurry!
- Hurry! Hurry!
- Okay! I got it!
Hurry! Hurry!
Don't do that.
Easy! Easy! I got it!
Where are you guys going?
Hurry! Hurry!
Wow, we won!
I almost forgot.
We should take a photo to prove it.
A photo to prove it.
- I'm beat.
- Gosh, seriously!
One, two, three.
What was that? What kind of man are you?
Now I know why your wife divorced you.
- What did you say?
- Gosh, it sucks!
Gosh, it sucks!
Gosh, what about you?
Now I can see why you were dumped!
You will live alone
for the rest of your life!
It's been three years
since I went to a baseball game.
And we saw a home run.
It was a jackpot.
Agreed. It was my first time
seeing a home run.
I also thought it was amazing.
Guys.
The team hit a home run and won the game.
Why still the long faces, huh?
Snap out of it
and let's go get some cold beer.
It will be my treat tonight.
Can you hold these for a sec?
- What's up, Mom?
- What's up?
You punk.
I just got a text about the charges
for baseball tickets, chicken, and beer.
What is all this?
It was about me relieving stress.
Are you out of your mind?
I let it go when you go out
and drink every day.
Now you're killing time
at a baseball stadium?
It's been three years.
Please have a heart, please...
What? Already?
How could you freeze the credit card
without telling me first?
How am I supposed to get by?
Mom... Mom, Mom. Mom!
I thought you were going overboard today.
Let's go to a convenience store for beer.
I should still have 20,000 won
for my allowance.
How could we have beer at a convenience
store on a day like today?
When there is a will, there is a way.
Follow me.
- Where are you going?
- Wait up.
[38th Alumni Association]
How can we be here pretending
we went to the same school?
What if we get caught?
Why would we get caught?
How can anyone tell
when there are so many people?
- But still... let's leave.
- Gosh, shut it.
You can't speak like a Seoulite in here.
Just shut it and eat.
Guys, let's drink.
Sure.
By the way, you guys don't look familiar.
It's your first time
at the gathering, huh?
Let me pour you one.
But I didn't see you
when I was in school either.
Which class were you in?
- Three.
- Were you? I was in that class too.
But I still don't remember you.
I was in class two, next to class three.
I was confused.
Were you? I was in class two too.
But I don't know who you are.
What's your name?
Oh my, I was in class one,
next to class two.
Were you? I was in class one.
I don't remember you.
What's your name?
Tell us.
What is your name?
Are you sure you guys went to our school?
Say it. Say it!
Who are you?
You punk, where is the president?
Bring your president.
Your president lives in
Namchang-dong, right?
I'd go out for snacks
with your president, you know.
We'd go to a sauna together, huh?
We did everything together, okay?
I'm the president.
And I lived in Gaeshin-dong,
not Namchan-dong.
We're sorry. We didn't eat
more than 10,000 won worth.
What are you still doing here? Run!
You all did a good job today.
Drink this and recharge.
- Cheers.
Cheers.
I feel like I'm getting recharged.
My muscles are pumping up and all.
Pumping up? You wish.
You were so weak.
You were like the walking dead earlier.
What? How can you say that?
Shut it and just drink.
I won't allow it. It's my mouth.
I can say whatever I want
with my own mouth.
- How dare you!
- Stop it.
You two stop.
I'm still not sure if this is
a dream or real, Professor Jin.
I wonder what changed your mind.
You're doing a lot of things
you wouldn't do before.
You came out to lunch with us.
You went hiking with us too.
You joined us for drinking like this.
You always wanted to
promote our friendship.
I'm here to promote our friendship,
as you wish.
Are you sure?
You don't have any other reason?
- Any other reason?
- I have no idea.
Just drink.
Wow, Professor Jin
knows how to drink this.
Now he has a girlfriend
so you will need a lot of energy tonight.
She will be so happy.
Whoever she is.
Who knows? We might know who she is.
It's understandable
Jin Yi is acting that way.
I'd feel betrayed also.
She has every right to be pissed.
Dumpling is made with fillings
inside flour dough.
Gosh, when did I tell
you to search "dumpling"?
How can I make up with Jin Yi?
What should I do?
No Geu Rae, what are you doing out here?
Who were you on the phone with?
Sound like someone close
according to your tone.
We're close, but she's not a human.
What do you mean she's not a human?
I was talking to Siri.
- Siri?
- Yes.
Since I live alone
I don't have anybody to talk
to during tough times.
So that's how it began...
I find it more comforting
than talking to myself.
We should say goodbye for tonight. Bye.
Goodbye.
What is it? Am I weird?
No, I feel sad for you.
Thinking how lonely you must
have felt to end up choosing that.
Now you don't need to do that anymore.
Whether it's something good or bad
you can share it with me and rely on me.
Tell me what you were talking
to her about just now.
It is...
I'm sorry. We decided to
keep it a secret.
But I ended up telling her.
Jin Yi accidentally saw our text.
I had no choice but to tell her.
Well, it's okay.
That's why she's been
onto me all this time.
Please try to understand.
She's not herself after breaking
up with her longtime boyfriend.
She thought she and I
shared the same pain.
But I didn't even tell her
after I started going out with you.
She has every right to feel betrayed.
Again, she's so tacky.
It will be uncomfortable
if you stick around.
- Why don't you leave first?
- No way.
I will stick around, send my drunk
girlfriend home, and then go.
What?
If I don't do that,
you will tell your phone
that your boyfriend has
left you alone and all.
I'd gladly take all the blame from her.
For my girlfriend.
- Let's go back in.
- Sure.
You're doing it again.
Forget about the whole thing and go home.
You argued with your big brother
and ran away from home?
You shouldn't do that.
It will become a habit.
- It's okay.
- What do you mean it's okay?
Plus, continue studying.
It will be a waste if you stop now.
If you take the exam now,
you will do better than me.
Good for you that you
can move on quickly.
How long you suffer
after a breakup is proportional to
how deeply you're in love.
I guess it was easy for him.
You punks are like cubic equations.
Why does it have to be so complicated?
Just snap out of it.
[Jung Chae Yeon]
Hello?
- Hello?
- Hey.
You didn't tell Gong Myung
that I like him, did you?
What am I, a kid?
Why would I tell him that?
Then he's not avoiding me
because I have feelings for him.
I haven't talked to him all day today.
Do you happen to know where he is?
He's here with me.
- What?
- I will put him on. Talk to him.
Take it. It's your master.
Hey, Master.
I'm sorry, but something came up.
I will explain later.
I'm a bit drunk right now.
He even had a drink?
Hey, Kim Ki Bum.
You've really moved on, haven't you?
- What?
- If I were you
I wouldn't have let
him talk to Chae Yeon.
Honestly, I still hate you so much.
For ruining my chance
with Joo Yeon for good.
But you didn't seem to hate Gong Myung.
You took care of him all day
and even let him talk to Chae Yeon.
It seems like you've moved on.
Is it that easy to just
pick up and move on?
- What?
- But when he's suffering already
what's the point of hating him?
What's the big deal about women?
You know how long we've been friends for.
Hey, Kim Ki Bum.
If I lost friends after losing love,
what would I do?
Then I would have
absolutely nothing left.
So please don't hate me so much.
Joo Yeon must have said something
harsh because she got mad.
You two may be able to work things out.
Think about the precious time
when you two were together.
It's different from
unrequited love like mine.
He's acting disgustingly cool.
Thanks so much for the clothes.
Gosh, what do we do?
She's really drunk.
No choice but to take
her home, Professor Min.
What?
Why should I?
What do you mean why?
When she's that pretty,
how can we send her home alone?
Your place is on the way anyway.
Gosh, you were carrying her
on your back in the mountain.
Why are you acting
like you don't care now?
Tell me the truth. You were so happy
that you might die, huh?
I almost died.
What?
A couple hours with her while hiking
was much harder than my entire marriage.
Gosh, it sucks.
Since she's drunk,
I will take her home.
There is no way I will
get entangled with her, ever.
Absolutely not.
It was tough today.
- We should go.
- We should.
What do you mean go home?
We should go for a second round.
- Second round. To a karaoke!
- Just go.
- Director Kim, I'm not going home.
- There is a taxi. Taxi!
- Director Kim.
- Just go home.
- Let's go. Watch your head.
- Director Kim!
Samsung-dong!
- Get in.
- I'm off.
We will go.
- Hey!
- I'm going to a karaoke.
- Get her.
- Director Kim.
Just go!
Watch your head.
Bye now.
- Bye.
- Go ahead.
Mister, go.
Gosh, that piece of bad luck.
I was talking about
Professor Hwang, not you.
Everybody is betraying me.
They are all backstabbing me.
You guys are all the same.
At the end, I'm all alone.
What are you saying?
Can we not talk until we get home?
Sure.
What are you doing? You just got a text.
I wasn't expecting any.
Jin Yi, I'm sorry.
I ended up hurting you unintentionally.
I was debating
if I should tell you the truth.
But you were suffering so much.
I decided it wasn't the right time yet.
When I was suffering
you were there for me.
When you are suffering
I'm sorry that I'm happy alone.
But I hope you don't suffer too long.
You will meet someone very nice.
You really deserve that.
What is it?
What's wrong, Professor Hwang?
I'm so humiliated.
I just realized how pathetic I am.
Because I was unhappy...
I couldn't stand others' happiness.
What are you talking about?
I have such a small mind.
I so deserve to be dumped.
I don't deserve to be loved by anybody.
It's okay.
It was you again, wasn't it?
You talked him into playing
hooky again, didn't you?
- What?
- I don't have to be there to see it.
You're all about playing hooky.
So you talked him into doing it.
If you don't want to study
pack up and leave Noryangjin alone.
Just because you gave up on your life,
don't ruin Gong Myung's life.
Jung Chae Yeon.
Fine. I'm sorry.
You're such an asshole.
How can you say that?
Ki Bum has been friends with
Gong Myung longer than you have.
Ki Bum cares a lot more
about Gong Myung than you.
When he cares so much about him
he talked him into going out to drink?
When he's so determined to study...
Do you even know
why he's so determined to study?
What?
It's because of Professor Park.
He wants to pass the exams
and become her boyfriend.
That's why he was studying so hard.
Jin Gong Myung likes
Professor Park Ha Na.
What?
But it turns out that
she now has a boyfriend.
It was because of Professor Park.
He wants to pass the exams
and become her boyfriend.
That's why he was studying so hard.
Jin Gong Myung likes
Professor Park Ha Na.
What?
But it turns out that
she now has a boyfriend.
That's why he was feeling lost
and not answering his phone all day.
When he was like that all day
Kim Ki Bum was taking care of him.
Get the facts straight.
I'm drinking solo.
When I drink solo
all the emotions that
I suppressed all day
and the feelings
fill me up with the drink.
Where did it go wrong?
Why did we come to this?
We ask questions with no answers.
Soon we have to face
reality and accept it.
But the truth and reality
may not be everything.
If I lose that hope
the love I nourished
until now seems so sad.
So I'm drinking this beer
because I need some courage.
A kind of courage that enables me
to say things I can't if I'm sober.
Gosh, I hate
saying goodbye to you tonight.
Before you go in
can you tell me the text
you sent me earlier?
The text?
You texted that you loved me.
I want to hear it in person.
Jin Yin sent that text, not me.
What?
Gosh, you have no idea
how happy I was after I got it.
What should I do with this tacky woman?
I love you.
- See you tomorrow.
- Go ahead.
Bye.
- What brings you here?
- I wanted to ask that question.
You told me not to mind.
You were going out with Professor Park?
True. Now you know.
When I told you
that I liked Professor Park
you were already seeing her, weren't you?
Why didn't you tell me the truth then?
I didn't want to start
an unnecessary fight.
It was going to go away.
It was going to go away?
True.
Was I supposed to care about
your feelings for your teacher?
My feelings?
How dare you? How dare you judge my love?
What?
"You"?
Don't talk to me that way.
I'm your big brother.
My big brother, my butt.
What kind of brother ridicules
his little brother's feelings?
You do everything your way.
You were always like that
and you're still the same.
You seriously...
Why did I come here?
I came to tell Professor Park
that I won't give up on her.
What?
If she meets a nice guy,
I can let her go.
But that's not you.
I cannot let her go to someone like you.
I cannot give up.
Gosh, that kid, seriously...
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Drink]
Even if I drink solo at home
I can't drink solo at a restaurant.
I'm afraid people will
look at me and get curious.
Excuse me, bring me
another bottle of soju.
Why do you care what others think?
It's not good enough to live
your life for yourself only.
It's good for everybody to give up now.
Teach, are you okay?
Gong Myung, I don't have
to know that, right?
Was it that big a mistake?
Are you human, huh?
If you were going to do this,
why did you date her?
Why did you date her
and hurt her, you selfish punk?
Let go.
What are you two?
Professor Jin is your brother?