(Episode 2)
I like drinking solo.
I talk all day long for my job.
Hence, I thoroughly enjoy not having to talk like this...
and wholeheartedly appreciate...
this moment of solitude.
I have my own rules for enjoying drinking solo.
First.
I must have a quality time in a classy ambiance.
Second.
There must be high-quality drink accompaniments.
Third. I seek to promote a mindful and high-quality drinking culture.
(Your blood alcohol content is 0.065 percent.)
I never drink until my blood alcohol content goes over 0.080 percent.
It's because...
that number represents when I feel happily tipsy.
- Let's toast our almighty chief.
-  Goodness, guys.
- Cheers!
-  Cheers!
I hate feeling obligated to drink...
to win favour of someone.
Drinking has to be...
an enjoyable experience.
He eats all sorts of delicious things alone.
High-quality Trash really gets on my nerves.
Are you the only one who eats crabs?
It's nothing to show off.
I should grab a beer and eat some crabs, too.
Look at you. You look deliciously plump.
Here goes one.
Now, two at the same time.
Three this time.
And many of them!
How many crabs did I just eat?
I didn't even have time to put on makeup.
There's nothing left.
- Did you do your homework?
-  Yes.
Right. Did you read the post on Professor Jin's page...
that claims Professor Jin forged his academic credentials?
I did.
The person who wrote even said to have evidence.
I know.
What is this?
He forged his academic credentials?
Whenever someone writes about it, it gets deleted.
He must be hiding something. Otherwise, he'd explain.
No way.
If that was true, he'd go to jail.
Hello.
Hi.
- Jin Yi.
-  Ha Na, good morning.
Did you hear what they were talking about?
What do you mean?
- That Professor Jin lied?
-  Yes.
I did read that thing.
Forget about it.
That's just one of the false rumours that go around in Noryangjin.
Whenever someone becomes popular, the haters come up with rumours...
to harm his or her reputation.
I guess it's the same everywhere.
Ha Na.
- Why do you look so tired today?
-  Me?
- My goodness.
-  Look at you.
I stayed up all night preparing for my first class. Do I look terrible?
You look horrible.
Look at all those freckles. What will I do with you?
Although it was well predicted,
you're amazing, Professor Jin.
Why is he so amazing?
He never disappoints anyone.
This is unbelievable.
Each of his classes attracted 1,000 students on average.
You're the star.
You're the hope.
- Professor Jin.
-  Please excuse me.
First-class instructor is different, indeed.
How many students do I have?
You did a good job, too.
You have an average of 150 students per class.
150 students?
My goodness!
What about me?
I'm curious.
What are you doing?
Are you trying to imitate Song Joong Ki?
Yes, people say I look just like him.
Salute!
Who says something like that?
Why do you try to do impressions of celebrities?
I should do something different every class...
to keep my students interested.
Just prepare well for your classes instead.
You only have 50 students per class.
You barely managed to break even.
Is that true?
It is true.
I should dispatch you somewhere far away.
Mr Kim. How many students do I have?
Is that true? Do I really have only 10 students?
Yes, it's true. How many times are you going to ask me?
It's a good thing we're not paying you a lot.
You could have lost us money otherwise.
With one less student, your class would have been cancelled.
It barely managed to survive.
I see.
You should take into consideration that it hasn't been advertised well.
Having 10 students is better than nothing.
I agree. She did an okay job...
for being No Geu Rae.
No Geu Rae?
What's that?
It's a nickname I gave her.
I don't know a lot of things because I'm new.
You could teach me how things work.
What?
That's what Jang Geu Rae from "Misaeng" would say.
That's why I call her No Geu Rae.
She's Jang Geu Rae in Noryangjin.
Oh my.
- Oh my.
-  Professor Jin, that's hilarious.
It's so funny.
Are you No Geu Rae, Ha Na?
No Geu Rae?
(Don't give up right away!)
(Your dream will come true.)
(If you don't walk today, you'll have to run tomorrow.)
(Ju Yeon, I'll make sure to pass the exam for you.)
(50 dollars has been transferred from Kim Dong Hee's account.)
(Big sister: 50 dollars)
Dong Hee, I'll pay you back as soon as I pass the exam.
(Memo)
(Big brother: 30 dollars, Grandma: 30 dollars, Gong Myung: 20 dollars)
Until when will I have to receive help from my family?
For my family...
and Ju Yeon, I'll pass the exam by all means.
By all means!
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
I came to wake you up.
You woke up early today.
Of course.
My classes start today. I should study hard from now on.
Look at you.
I like your attitude.
Do you like my attitude?
What are you talking about?
Get out right now!
Look at you.
It's not like you have anything to hide. Don't be so sensitive.
Get out.
Does he have the right to say that?
The myth of Dangun.
It's a story about a bear who turned into a human.
I'm sure you all have heard of it.
I'll tell you what the exam will ask you about.
There was a tribe that worshipped the sky.
- The classroom is full.
-  Another tribe worshipped bears.
There was also a tribe that worshipped tigers.
This is why he's a first-class instructor.
- The tribe...
-  What?
If I work hard, I'll have that many students someday.
Jin Jung Suk, wait and see...
what No Geu Rae is capable of.
Dangun.
It means...
You start working at the academy today, right?
How much discount do you get by doing that?
It's not just a discount. I take classes for free.
Really? That's a good deal.
Hey, Chae Yeon!
Do you remember me? We were in the same class once.
I want to be friends with you.
Can you give me your phone number?
I already said no.
Don't be like that.
Fine. Give me your phone.
- What did you just do?
-  If you're here to study,
focus on your studies.
Wow, that charisma.
No matter how cold she is, she's still popular.
As long as a girl is pretty, nothing seems to matter.
Does she look pretty to you?
Are all guys blind?
I've never thought she's pretty.
What? She's the prettiest girl in Noryangjin.
The prettiest girl?
She's the meanest girl.
Everyone here must be going crazy from studying too much.
How can they think she's pretty?
What's wrong with him? She's super pretty.
Why does he hate her so much?
Hey, make sure you do a good job.
- It's our Professor Pretty's class.
-  Professor Pretty?
Look.
Isn't she hot?
You don't call a girl like her pretty.
This is a pretty girl.
I signed up for this class just to see her in real life.
She's my type.
I love you.
This is not a girl band's concert.
Whatever.
It's none of your business.
Where did this girl go?
Isn't she her aunt?
I thought she'd look like this.
Why does she look so tired and old?
It's nice to meet you.
I'm your Korean teacher, Park Ha Na.
Thank you so much for choosing to take my class...
even though I'm not famous.
I'll do my best not to let you down.
Should we start? Here we go!
Today, we'll study about...
the standard language.
(This is annoying. The picture was filtered.)
The reason is...
Professor.
You should return the microphone.
What?
Oh, I see. Thank you.
Thank you.
Why do you need a microphone?
You only have 10 students.
You could probably whisper and everyone would hear it.
It must feel cosy and friendly. That must be nice,
No Geu Rae.
Yes, sure.
I may look like a No Geu Rae for now,
but you just watch.
I'll make sure my classes are full very soon.
See you later.
Why is she so confident?
She's so clueless.
High-quality Trash.
I used to be a popular instructor at the previous academy.
There wasn't a single student...
that would quit my classes midway.
I want to cancel my course with Professor Park Ha Na.
I want a refund.
What do you mean by a refund?
- What is going on?
-  Do you have a reason?
Of course I do.
Look.
I was very excited...
to take her class after seeing this photograph.
However, her real face isn't like this at all.
Just take the class.
No way.
If it's going to be like this, I'll give up on looks.
I'd rather take Professor Lee Seon Jae's...
Korean class instead.
Hey, kid!
What did you just say?
You're going to give up on looks to take Professor Lee's class?
Professor Lee is as beautiful as a gem.
How dare you talk lowly of her looks?
Yes, I'm Lee Sun Jae. Do you know who you're dealing with here?
I know.
I know that very well.
There's not a soul in Noryangjin that doesn't know you.
You must be upset.
Let's go.
Anyway,
give me a refund.
Hold on a minute.
Can we talk?
Come here.
Hey.
Are you that disappointed with my face?
Enough for you to ask for a refund?
To be honest,
it was filtered too much with Photoshop.
It's not all Photoshop.
I slept in today,
so I didn't get to prepare properly this morning.
I'm just like that with proper makeup.
Anyway, why does an instructor's face matter so much?
What matters is how well they teach.
Ever since I was in high school,
I can focus better if my teacher is pretty.
I also get good marks.
I'll become prettier.
Hey,
can you help me persuade your friend?
Thank you for the food. Goodbye.
Why? Wait for me.
No, I don't have the time. I have to go study.
Professor Park,
can you really become prettier?
Of course. Just trust me.
I'm not sure if that's possible.
We're out of pickles. Let me get some more for you.
Now she's bending over backwards for the students, too.
She's so lowly.
Did he hear everything?
Gosh.
I'm pathetic, right?
I was begging...
a student to take my class.
Why did High-quality Trash have to be there?
He already thinks that I'm dying to flatter everyone.
Now that misconception will look true.
What should I do?
Unfortunately, there is nothing I can do to console you.
As for me,
I get sensitive sometimes when you leave me...
flipped upside down.
What are you doing? Why are you complaining?
I'm already overwhelmed as it is.
Why are there so many annoying things happening?
Do you want to read cartoons?
- I can load the next episode...
-  I'm not in the mood for that.
Forget it. Why do I even bother?
(Gong Myung)
What? You can't come?
Are you going to be like this?
I'm totally serious.
I had a huge fight with Mum then I walked out.
Why do you think?
She keeps nagging at me to take the civil service exam.
Dong Young, come on.
Be a good friend.
Come on, can't you be considerate?
You know my family is saving up to help me study.
I feel so bad. I need to pass the test as soon as possible.
I'm hanging up.
Hey.
Gosh, he's so stern.
I need him to come out.
- That game's more fun with others.
-  Of course.
Well? Should I call him again?
It's no use.
I told you, he's really determined.
I think he'll pass this time.
Brutal.
Ki Bum, did you give up?
What are you talking about?
I was planning to study when you called me out.
You told me to meet you here if I don't have a place to go.
Did I?
Forget it.
I should have ignored you even if you ran away from home.
I was going to study so hard starting today.
How come I can't be as determined as Dong Young?
That's because...
your family is too rich.
Your family's supporting you. It's hard to be spiteful.
Look at Dong Young.
Look at how desperate he is.
You need to be pushed to the edge to be determined.
You're right.
I have to be desperate.
That's it.
That's why I wasn't eager enough to study.
Come with me.
What is it?
Where are you going?
I'm trying to study to become a Grade 9 Public Official.
I don't know which classes to take.
People told me to take Professor Lee's class for Korean.
I see.
What do you think about our pre-set joint classes?
This is a joint class...
organised by Professor Lee Seon Jae.
They have a set schedule like school classes.
All you need to do is take this in order to get ready for your exam.
- The price is...
-  I'm so jealous of them.
- Why?
-  Why do you think?
If you're a part of a joint class with a first-class instructor,
a lot of students sign up automatically,
and you naturally become more well known.
- There's no reason to be jealous.
-  Pardon?
You'll soon become beneficiaries of a first-class instructor.
Beneficiaries?
What do you mean?
Pardon?
The three of us will be in a joint class with Professor Jin?
Yes.
That's why I put you all in the same staff room.
Try to make...
the best joint class while working with Professor Jin.
- Thank you, Sir.
-  We'll do our best.
Didn't around 1000 students...
sign up for Professor Jin's regular classes?
Will as many students sign up for the joint class?
- I assume so.
-  Then...
that means we'll be lecturing in front of 1000 students as well.
Are we getting a raise?
Why are you even asking me?
I'll give you an incentive per student.
Of course the price may differ due to your experience levels.
I'll go get Professor Jin.
Gather around the table.
We'll talk more about this in detail with him.
Yes, Sir.
Salute.
I feel like we won the lottery.
That's what I mean.
How did such an opportunity come to me? I can't believe it.
What is it now?
Why are you shopping for track jackets?
I just got this month's allowance yesterday.
I'm going to use it all up.
If I become penniless,
I'll become desperate like Dong Young.
What?
If Dong Young is poor by nature,
I'll just use all I have...
to acquire poverty.
This looks really cool.
I'll get this.
I'll also get the one beside it.
Are you Paris Hilton of Noryangjin?
How many of these are you getting? Are you crazy?
Don't you know there are so many places you could use money?
You're clueless, aren't you?
Track suits are the pride for students preparing the exam.
It's like your business card if you're working at the office.
Look at him.
Over there.
I saw that jacket at an outlet mall two years ago.
That means he's be preparing for the exam...
for at least three years.
Look. Look at that guy.
You can't find that suit even at an outlet mall.
He must have been preparing...
for at least five years.
- What are you doing?
-  What do you think?
I can tell how long they've been studying just by their clothes.
Look at him. Look.
That's the new fall collection.
That means he just recently moved to Noryangjin.
Look at how clean he looks.
He's so enthusiastic as if he'd pass his exam tomorrow.
I want to...
look like a newbie, just like him.
That looks really cool.
Excuse me, do you have my size in that?
You're really something.
You don't want to be part of the joint class?
What do you mean?
Let's step out for a bit.
- Let's talk outside.
-  There's no need.
I'll make myself clear in front of everyone.
I'm not interested in doing a joint class with these instructors.
Why are you being like this, Professor Jin?
Do you really not know the reason?
Even if you combine all of their classes,
the total number of their students is less than 200 per class.
Why do I have to sacrifice myself to help these instructors?
The employment contract you signed clearly states that you have to...
actively participate in these joint classes.
I specified that I must have a say in selecting whom I'll work with.
Students will choose to take the joint class because of my name.
I'd like to work with competent instructors whom I approve,
not with these mediocre instructors.
Wait, Professor Jin.
Just a moment, okay?
That jerk...
Professor Jin, Professor Jin!
Professor Jin!
What a psycho.
He's really High-quality Trash.
Indeed.
Get off your high horse, you first-class instructor.
Does he think he's entitled to be condescending to us?
That's what I'm saying.
Ha Na, why aren't you saying anything?
Aren't you angry?
What can I say?
I'm a newbie who's just starting out in Noryangjin.
It's natural that I'm not being accepted.
What are you talking about?
In these joint classes,
famous instructors help and support instructors who are not well known.
Don't you know the phrase, "noblesse oblige"?
My blood is boiling. I can't let it slide.
Let's take revenge against High-quality Trash.
Revenge? How?
Let's do something that will completely throw him off.
How about we hide all of the instant coffee in the office pantry?
Goodness! You think that'll throw him off?
He makes 10 million dollars a year. He won't even blink an eye over it.
He can easily afford to open a cafe.
You're right.
If that's the case...
Let's post malicious comments about him online.
Let's write about how horrible his classes are...
and what kind of nasty person he is.
Everyone should know that his nickname is High-quality Trash.
High-quality Trash! Hit enter.
Do you think he'll let it slide?
He'll track down the IP address and get back at us.
Come to think of it, it's very strange.
Why doesn't he do anything...
about the posts on him forging his academic credentials?
Really? There are posts accusing him of it?
Yes. He just deletes them as soon as they get posted.
I mean, we all know how he is. You'd think that he would have...
sued those people for defamation a long time ago.
Exactly.
Is he hiding something?
I know that we can look up all graduates' names...
on the alumni association's website.
Ha Na, didn't you say that your cousin...
graduated from Seoul National University?
He did, right?
Yes. He did, but...
Ask him what his username and password are.
- Hurry up.
-  Sorry?
I don't know how I feel about that.
I feel as though we're doing a background check on him.
What's wrong with doing a little bit of background check?
Ask him. Come on!
(Jin Jung Suk's Page: A new post has been published.)
(Professor Jin Jung Suk forged his academic credentials!)
(He did not graduate from Seoul National University.)
(Are you sure you want to delete this post?)
(Yes)
(Seoul National University Alumni Association)
(Search an alumnus: Jin Jung Suk)
(Your search yielded no results.)
- My gosh!
-  What is this? My goodness.
There's no graduate with that name.
Did you type his name correctly?
- You didn't misspell his name?
-  Are you blind or what?
It only took us this one simple search to find out that he's lying.
He probably didn't think that anyone would go to this extent.
Let's go. We must tell Mr Kim immediately.
- Yes, we should.
-  Hold on a second.
He's been deleting the posts himself, so he must know about it.
How about we let him resolve this issue on his own?
I mean, he might confess to all of us soon.
He might confess? Cut the nonsense.
If that was the case, he wouldn't be that nasty about working with us.
Look at him with his nose in the air.
Besides, this isn't only about getting back at him.
Our students come here to study for their future.
Deceiving people like that is just wrong.
That's true, but...
I get it. You might be uncomfortable with getting involved in this.
You're still new, so you probably want to stay away...
from causing any sort of trouble.
Then...
you should stay out of it.
We'll take care of it.
Pardon? But that's...
I told you, didn't I?
I'm going to help and support you in every way I can.
Just let me handle it.
- Let's go, Professor Min.
-  Okay.
Can I really stay out of it?
I don't even know any more.
I can't afford to worry about that trash's academic credentials.
I need to figure out my life first.
Am I being a coward right now?
Coward. Your search yielded following results.
A wimp. A person who lacks courage.
What? Wimp?
Wimp. Your search yielded the following results.
It refers to when a person exhibits personality traits or behaviours...
that can be described as ineffectual, powerless or timid.
What? Powerless?
I can't really deny it. I am powerless, indeed.
They're doing the right thing for people whose future depends on this.
I got out of it alone because I didn't want to risk my career.
Yes, this is wrong.
Those two have been so nice to me. I can't put it all on them.
That's right.
Mr Kim definitely needs to know this.
Mr Kim, you're here.
I need to talk to you about something.
What? What is it?
You want to be in Professor Jin's joint class?
Goodness. I actually was able to persuade him.
- He'll work with the two of you.
-  Pardon me?
Well, I'm not 100 percent satisfied with you two,
but I do understand that there are no one who can take your place.
Hence, I made a tough decision.
You must do your best, though.
You'll be out if the quality of the class gets compromised.
That's correct.
Mr Kim. This is not what's important right now.
Yes, exactly. This isn't important at all.
Professor Jin. I know that you've been so understanding,
but could you also let Professor Park to join the class?
Gosh, I already told you that I can't do that.
How understanding do I have to be?
She is inexperienced and has a mediocre academic background.
I absolutely cannot work with that No Geu Rae.
Please consider giving her a chance...
Are you going on about my academic background again?
- When did you come in?
-  Is it that important to you?
Is that why you forged yours?
I beg your pardon?
Professor Park!
What are you saying to a Seoul National University graduate?
Oh, I guess you haven't heard.
Professor Jin forged his academic credentials.
What?
(Your search yielded no results.)
How are you going to explain this?
No one with your name graduated from Seoul National University.
Professor Jin, could you please explain this?
- Please say something.
-  Yes.
Say something.
(Please enter a name.)
(Jin)
(Jin Sang)
(Korean History Major, Graduated)
Back in the ancient days, royal meals were called "jinsang".
That's right.
(Identification Card, Jin Sang)
What... What is this, Professor Jin?
It's my real name.
Jin Sang is my birth name.
I started using, Jin Jung Suk, when I first came to Noryangjin.
Seriously?
Are you serious? Are you really...
Is Jin Sang seriously your real name?
Yes.
My ex-boss strongly recommended using a different name.
I didn't think much about it and agreed to it back then.
Anyway, it's my fault.
What's wrong with Jin Sang? Why did your ex-boss want you to change it?
That ex-boss of yours is seriously so ridiculous.
- Are we good now, No Geu Rae?
-  Well...
I'm very sorry, Professor Jin.
Forget it. This confirms my decision.
We'll never be in the same joint class.
You're incompetent, and all you do is dig up people's past.
I absolutely do not want to work with you.
Who told you such groundless rumour anyway?
You two. Is this what you wanted to talk to me about?
Did you two know about this, too?
No, not at all.
I've never heard such rumour.
Same here. This is the first time I'm hearing it.
Look.
If you're broke, go study. Why are you drinking?
Hey.
You ran away from home. I couldn't leave you behind.
I should have a drink with you.
Cut it out. You just want to drink.
You got me.
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I thought I'd focus on studying once I become broke,
but I was wrong.
Forget it. Try calling Dong Young.
He needs to eat, too.
Should I?
I'm having dinner with Gong Myung.
Join us.
Even if you have to study hard, you still need to eat.
Squid sashimi waits for you.
Squid sashimi?
(Ju Yeon, I'll make sure to pass the exam for you.)
I can't. I'm meeting Ju Yeon this weekend.
I have to meet this week's goal before that.
Gosh, he's so determined.
Then again, I can understand him.
He's been together with Ju Yeon for five years.
For two years, he was in the army. Now he's studying for an exam.
She's been taking care of him like a mum.
Wouldn't he want to pass the exam as soon as he can for her?
That's it.
What do you mean?
The reason why I don't want to study even though I'm broke is...
because I don't have a girlfriend.
- What?
-  Think about it.
If I had a girlfriend,
I'd want to pass the exam to make her happy...
just like Dong Young.
Girlfriend.
Excuse me. Do you mind if I sit here?
Are you studying for the civil service exam?
So am I.
Why don't we drink together...
Gosh, I was already stressed out about my studies.
Get lost while I'm still nice.
Okay.
I see two beauties here.
- Why don't we...
-  Get lost.
Okay.
Excuse me. I use that textbook, too. Why don't we...
Come here.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
I'm trying to get a girlfriend.
I need a girlfriend...
to motivate myself.
If you have time to motivate yourself, study instead.
I need motivation.
I said I couldn't go out.
(You have a message from Ju Yeon.)
Dong Young, this is Ju Yeon.
I'm in front of the residence.
Can you come out?
Eat it up. You love samgyetang.
It's yours.
Also, you're busy with your work. You don't have to come here.
I'm really okay.
I came because I could.
Just eat.
Okay.
Slow down. You'll get an upset stomach.
I should eat it up and go back to studying.
Dong Young.
Can't you stay with me a bit longer today?
What?
You don't seem to remember.
It's our fifth anniversary today.
That's right.
I'm sorry. I've been too preoccupied with my studies.
That's why you came.
Yes.
You should stay with me today, okay?
Okay.
Eat up.
What are you talking about?
Do you want to use your real name from now on?
It means exactly what I said.
I don't want rumours about me to go around.
Now that it's out in the open now,
I'd like go by my real name from now on.
Why are you doing this?
The name, Jin Jung Suk, has become a brand.
If you suddenly go by your real name,
it'll confuse the students.
What if you lose students?
I'm ready to go through a bit of a transition period.
Why do I have to go through it together?
Why did you change your mind after starting to work with me?
I'm just wondering.
What's so funny to him?
Professor Jin must be thinking like this.
He's been using a false name.
"Should I apologise?"
"Should I confess?"
You're my everything
Like stars
Stop it!
Jin Jung Suk might turn into Jin Sang overnight.
Don't you realise how serious this is?
You're just happy about joining the joint class.
You're the real trouble.
Do you know that?
What are you going to do now?
I hired you even though you were inexperienced...
in order to put you in Professor Jin's joint class.
How can you do this to me...
when you should bribe me?
What are you going to do now?
I'm sorry.
Professor Jin.
I'm sorry. I apologise.
- Forget it.
-  Professor Jin.
Can we have a little talk somewhere?
Somewhere? Why?
Do you want to treat me to a meal...
just like you did to your students?
- What?
-  You seemed to be good at sales.
Why don't you look into a sales career...
instead of desperately begging me like this?
Ha Na, we're sorry.
We shouldn't have encouraged you to reveal his truth.
You should have let us handle it.
Do you have to say that now?
Ha Na, why don't we go for a drink?
I better go home and prepare for classes.
Are you angry?
Because we pretended we hadn't heard of it?
I'm sorry. I don't know why I said that.
Never mind. I'm really okay.
If you're okay, drink with us.
You should.
We feel so bad about it.
- Let's have just one glass.
-  I'm okay.
- Let's go.
-  Let's go.
It's nice.
Do you remember this song?
When we went to a karaoke together for the first time,
you sang this for me.
Of course, I do.
I was so nervous that day.
We've been together for five years already.
You're right.
Time flies.
I have to go to the restroom.
Stay here.
- Go in.
-  Okay.
Right.
Here.
What is this?
It's a shirt.
You don't have many fall clothes.
I'm sorry I never give you anything back.
Don't worry. Go back to studying.
Okay. Take care.
Okay.
(Isak Residence)
Gosh. Please cheer up.
It doesn't matter even if you don't get into his joint class.
You can do well at your regular classes.
Enough with imitating others.
Jin Jung Suk is such a jerk.
Don't you agree?
Why won't he include you in his joint class?
It's okay.
It's still good news for you two.
Don't mind me and celebrate as much as you want.
Did we come here to celebrate?
No, we came here to cheer you up.
Affirmative.
This is all for you, Professor Park. Eat as much as you want...
and drink as much as you want.
Enough is enough.
This isn't "Descendants of the Sun".
You're more like "Slaves of the Sun".
I'm not doing this for nothing.
I'm trying to entertain Professor Park, that's all.
Thank you, Professor Min.
I feel better thanks to you.
Is that true?
"It was difficult, but I did it once again."
That's so funny.
Excuse me for a moment. I have to go to the restroom.
Gosh.
I'm so happy, but it's hard not to show it in front of her.
- It's so difficult.
-  Gosh.
Why don't we have a toast while she's gone?
Congratulations, Professor Min.
You're going to lecture in front of 1000 students.
Same to you, Professor Hwang. Congratulations.
Bottoms up.
(I'm sorry, Professor Jin. I want to apologise.)
He didn't read it yet.
What should I do?
(I was careless earlier...)
Thank you.
I was careless earlier.
Please let me apologise to you one more time.
She thought I wouldn't be useful to her...
and was accusing me on forging my academic credentials,
but now she's trying to flatter me.
She has no talent, but she tries to sneak her way in.
I hate her type.
(Five years ago)
What's this?
Did you stay here all night again?
What kind of feat are you trying to achieve?
You should go easy on yourself.
Good morning.
Good morning, Sir.
Hold on, Professor.
It's nothing much,
but my parents asked me to give this to you.
They got you a bottle of whisky from their trip abroad.
It's a 50-year-old limited edition.
Why did they bother?
It's not like it's 100 years old.
I'll go order another.
It's okay, I can't drink any more.
Can someone call me a designated driver?
There's no need.
I didn't have any drinks so I could drive you home.
Come with me.
We'll get going.
Watch out.
He's kissing up to the professor.
Congratulations on becoming a professor, Joon Seok.
- You should treat us.
-  Thank you.
- Congratulations.
-  Congratulations.
- I'll treat you guys out.
-  Awesome.
- I thought you'd make it this time.
-  Thank you.
Joon Seok.
Yes?
I read your thesis.
Why did you copy my research material?
I didn't copy it.
- I only referenced it.
-  Why didn't you cite it, then?
I won't let you get away with this.
What are you going to do about it?
What will you do?
If people find out that you ruined me through a rumour,
do you think that will do you any good?
What did you say?
What's good is good.
Since I became a professor thanks to you, I'd help you in return.
I don't need help from an incompetent person like you.
I know I don't deserve it,
but I really hope you'd accept my apology.
I hate her type.
She's the worst.
I thought Professor Jin...
would be like trash per his nickname, but he's gold.
I agree.
Right, right.
What will you do with your incentive, Professor Hwang?
I'm going to get a new car.
I'll get a foreign import.
My lease is up this year.
Do you think I can get myself a new house?
My goodness. I'm so happy.
Gosh. If it wasn't for Professor Park,
we would be up there dancing and singing in celebration.
Well...
Why don't we sing one while she's away?
Shall we?
(I'm sorry, Professor Jin. I want to apologise.)
He's still not reading it.
If they come for me
At the age of 50
Tell them I can't go
Because I'm buying myself a new car
If they come for me
At the age of 60
Tell them I can't go
- Because I'm getting myself a house
-  Because I'm getting myself a house
Professor Hwang. Professor Hwang.
- It's hot.
-  My goodness.
Gosh, it's already 10pm.
- I'll get going.
-  Are you Cinderella?
What are you doing?
Ha Na isn't cheered up yet. How can you leave?
You know how scary my wife is. I have to go.
- See you tomorrow.
-  Bye.
Wow. He's... What a coward.
Ha Na.
Let's drink on our own.
You're upset, right?
How can Professor Min...
just dash off like that and leave you?
My goodness.
Hold on.
Yes, Honey.
You're here to pick me up?
Okay, I'll be right there.
Gosh, why are all men like this?
They never ask and they come to pick you up on a whim.
They're so selfish.
- Should we get up now?
-  What?
Okay.
Dong Young.
Let's not see each other any more.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Dong Young.
Let's not see each other any more.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
I'm the one who should apologise.
I'm sorry for making you apologise to a guy like me.
Dong Young, I'm going to use the restroom quickly.
(Mum: Who knows when he'll pass the exam? You now have a job,)
(so you should find a better guy and get married. )
(Break up with him today, please.)
Dong Young!
This should've happened a long time ago.
I'm sorry that I couldn't let you go sooner.
I'm really sorry.
I'm so sorry...
that I can't be better than this.
I didn't order this, Ma'am.
That girlfriend of yours who used to come here with you all the time...
stopped by today and left a chunk of money with me.
She told me to give you...
the pork stir-fry dish you like every time you come.
Pardon me?
You have such a caring girlfriend.
You have to pass the exam this time to make her happy. Okay?
I drink solo because...
there aren't that many people in my life who can console me...
after a long, hard day and who can really...
understand me.
Hence, I'm not used to sharing my pain,
and I tend to internalise everything.
At times, grabbing a drink alone...
can console me more than anything.
That's why I drink solo.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
My feet hurt.
(The Shortcut to Success, Jin Jung Suk's Korean History!)
(Professor Jin Jung Suk)
Did he get my message or what?
Right.
I wouldn't want to deal with me either if I were him.
I'm the ridiculous one.
I'm definitely the ridiculous one.
Ki Bum.
Just go in and study. Don't do anything stupid.
Look who's talking. Stop being so stupid and go home already.
Don't you think you're too old to run away from home like this?
Give me a dollar. I want to get a bottle of water.
What?
Here, take it.
What's she doing?
It's dangerous to fall asleep there.
Gosh, seriously!
(The Shortcut to Success, Jin Jung Suk's Korean History!)
You jerk.
Oh, right! That part-timer at a sashimi restaurant.
Excuse me.
- Wake up. You should go home.
-  Gosh, yes.
Gosh, that's the last bus! Sir, please wait!
Don't leave yet, Sir! Please open the door.
Thank you. Thank you so much.
What just happened? Wasn't she dozing off here until just now?
She's so fast.
Excuse me! Please throw my shoes over here.
- Oh, okay.
-  Hurry up!
Oh, no!
Just throw them. Hurry up! My goodness!
Isn't she the Korean instructor?
The other one, too. Hurry!
What are they doing right now?
Gosh, my shoe!
Hey, what was that about?
Hey. You remember her, right?
That part-timer who was taking her anger out on that advertisement.
What?
She's not a part-timer.
She teaches Korean at the academy I go to.
What?
(Mum)
Why does she keep calling me?
- Just answer it, you fool.
-  Hey! Goodness.
Yes, Mother.
Why?
Gosh, what did you just say?
Who is it at this hour?
- Mum.
-  I didn't hear a thing,
so I got myself in.
- I didn't know you were home.
-  Right, sorry.
What brings you at this hour?
I have a favour to ask you.
- A favour?
-  It's nothing special.
I want your little brother...
to live with you until he gets a job in the government.
- Sorry?
-  What's this fool doing?
Come in!
- Come in.
-  Mum, please.
I want you to take care of this fool.
(We'd like to thank all of the future government employees...)
(whom we consulted for their help and guidance.)
(Drinking Solo)
Gong Myung will register at the academy you work at.
I told him to go there because you work there.
You'd better not tell anyone that you're my brother.
If people find out that my brother is so hopeless and jobless,
no one would want to take my classes.
Do I seriously have to worry about how I look, too?
I promised to become pretty. Will this be enough?
Chae Yeon, you've been looking tired. This will energise you.
- Take this.
-  I told you that I don't want it.
- Did you say 10,000 dollars?
-  I need it for my rent deposit.
I didn't get paid for three months at the other academy I worked at.
Joining the joint class with Professor Jin...
will solve all of my problems at one blow.
I hate my life.
Go and talk to High-quality Trash.
It's not like I'm immune to shame.
No, this can't be happening.
- What is wrong with me?
-  What's she doing?
I'm embarrassed for her.
I'll do my very best to make sure that every single one of you...
will pass the exam.
Cheer up, Professor Park.
- Cheer up! Cheer up!
-  Cheer up! Cheer up!
- Thank you.
Take Park Ha Na's Korean class!
She'll tell you exactly what's going to be on the exam.
What are you doing right now?
Why do you even care?
Are you out of your mind? Why are you distributing these?
Professor Jin wants to talk to you at the terrace.
I heard you want to speak to me about something.
What is your problem?
You said you wanted to let me know how sorry you really are.
This must be what you actually wanted.
What are you talking about? I don't know anything about this.
No excuses, please. You're...
a lot worse than I expected.