I like drinking solo.
I talk all day long for my job.
Hence, I thoroughly enjoy not having to talk like this...
and wholeheartedly appreciate this moment of solitude.
This academy is huge.
Yes. I work in Noryangjin starting today.
He's our hope. Meet Professor Jin Jung Suk.
Are you Mr Jin Jung Suk?
90 percent of the exam-takers take his classes.
He's the top instructor when it comes to the civil service exam.
Hi, Mum. I'm in Noryangjin.
Why? You told me to take the civil service exam.
I thought Noryangjin would be super depressing, but it's not the case.
You get to live on allowance from your mum,
but you don't have to deal with her nagging. Living here is amazing!
I'll be in charge of your Korean. I'm Park Ha Na.
What do you think of Professor Park's lecture?
She worked in an academy in the outskirts, right?
You can tell her background.
Did you read the post on Professor Jin's page...
that claims Professor Jin forged his academic credentials?
The person who wrote even said to have evidence.
Dong Young, come on.
Come on, can't you be considerate?
You know my family is saving up to help me study.
I feel so bad. I need to pass the test as soon as possible.
Let's break up.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
This should've happened a long time ago.
I'm sorry that I couldn't let you go sooner.
I'm not interested in doing a joint class with these instructors.
He's really High-quality Trash.
Does he think he's entitled to be condescending to us?
She is inexperienced and has a mediocre academic background.
I absolutely cannot work with that No Geu Rae.
Is it that important to you?
Is that why you forged yours?
How are you going to explain this?
No one with your name graduated from Seoul National University.
Professor Jin, could you please explain this?
Jin Sang is my birth name.
I started using, Jin Jung Suk, when I first came to Noryangjin.
What's she doing? It's dangerous to fall asleep there.
Excuse me. Wake up. You should go home.
Gosh, that's the last bus! Sir, please wait!
Don't leave yet, Sir!
Excuse me! Please throw my shoes over here.
- Oh, okay. - Hurry up!
- Isn't she the Korean instructor? - Hurry!
What are they doing right now?
Gosh, my shoe!
I need my shoe!
(Episode 3)
I like drinking solo.
I talk all day long for my job.
Hence, I thoroughly enjoy not having to talk like this...
and wholeheartedly appreciate this moment of solitude.
I have my own rules for enjoying drinking solo.
First. I must have a quality time in a classy ambiance.
Second.
There must be high-quality drink accompaniments.
Third.
I seek to promote a mindful and high-quality drinking culture.
I never drink...
until my blood alcohol content goes over 0.080 percent.
It's because that number represents...
when I feel happily tipsy.
Come on. Drink up.
Look at them. I hate drinking with a bunch of loud people like them.
Drinking solo allows me time to solely focus on myself.
It's such a healing experience.
That's why...
I love drinking by myself.
I lost my shoe...
and looked stupid all day.
What a crazy day.
What's this fool doing?
Come in!
- Come in. - Mum, please.
I want you to take care of this fool.
Why are you doing this all of a sudden?
Do you think anybody can take and pass the civil service exam?
What? Anybody?
Mum.
Do you know how difficult that exam is?
He won't be able to pass it.
You know that studying isn't his strong suit.
That's right. He sounds super annoying,
but he's not wrong.
It's true that I'm not cut out for studying...
Be quiet.
I'm not cut out for looking after you.
I mean, we can't let him stay unemployed forever.
You're the most famous instructor in Noryangjin.
Let him live with you and help him get a job in the government, okay?
I can't.
I cannot force someone with no will power to study.
Plus, I do not want to live with him.
That pathetic loser can't even figure his own life out.
Why do I have to live with him?
Look who's talking! I don't want to live with you, either!
Shut it, you fool.
I told you to obey your brother. Did you not hear me?
I will.
Stop saying no.
Can you please...
think about it again? Please?
You know me, Mum.
I cannot live with anyone.
Living alone is so comfortable.
If you want him to study for the exam, get a small flat for him.
If you don't want to pay for it, I can take care of the rent...
Money isn't the issue here!
I live with him now, yet he's still wasting his life away.
What would he do if we let him live alone?
Who knows what that fool is capable of doing?
You have to live with him,
so that he at least watches his behaviour.
Gong Myung and I really don't get along, Mum.
I know that the two of you are like polar opposites.
I wish Gong Myung was as smart...
and competent as you.
You two are so different even though you're siblings.
That's exactly why I don't want to live with him.
Have I ever forced you into doing anything you don't want to do?
Even when you quit preparing to become a professor...
to teach at academies,
I trusted that you'd make the right decision...
even though I was extremely upset and worried about it.
That's why I didn't say anything to you.
This is the very first time I'm asking you for a favour like this.
You really can't do it for me?
Son, please?
Grant me my wish!
You should eat, too.
I made this cheonggukjang from scratch for you.
It's very delicious.
It's okay. I'll just have a glass of juice.
Why did you make such a smelly dish for breakfast?
Gosh, you're so picky.
I think it smells amazing.
Mum, I'm disappointed in you.
You've never prepared so much food for me.
How many dishes are there?
Be quiet.
If you're unhappy with it, pass the exam and start earning money.
Right. Gong Myung will sign up for your academy today.
I thought it'd be a good idea for him to study where you teach.
What?
Hey.
Don't tell anyone you're my brother.
When they find out I have a brother with no future like you,
no one will want to take my classes.
That makes sense.
They'll wonder why you can't even teach your own brother well.
I hope it won't happen.
Gong Myung, don't let others know he's your brother.
Fine. That's what I want, too.
I don't want others to know that...
a jerk like him is my brother.
- What? - Do you have a problem?
Will you be quiet?
I told you to obey your brother.
It hurts.
Anyway, please take good care of this brat.
I'll visit often.
You don't have to.
Just send us enough money.
Look at you.
I just don't want to bother you.
Of course.
Do I have to even care about how I look now?
Gosh.
I promised I'd become prettier.
Is this enough?
Hello.
Did you read my text?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for revealing that...
your real name is Jin Sang.
So what?
"Now that I've apologised, let me teach the joint class."
Is that what you mean?
That's not it.
I'm okay with not teaching the joint class.
I just wanted to apologise.
All you want is to apologise?
Yes. I have no other purpose.
If that's your only purpose,
I'll accept your apology.
In return, never mention the joint class in front me again.
Do you understand, No Geu Rae?
Yes.
On your message board,
all they talk about is how you look.
That's not true.
- They're so cheeky. - Right?
Hi, Professor Jin.
- Hello. - You came in together.
Have you apologised to him?
Yes.
Really? Is he going to let you teach the joint class?
No. He told me never to mention the joint class again...
in return for him accepting my apology.
What are you talking about?
What are you going to do now?
You should have begged him.
Mr Kim, I'll attract more students to my existing class.
- Please trust me. - How would I trust you?
Why are you so confident?
Did you check the reviews on your class?
It was unbelievable.
Why? Did I get a lot of bad reviews?
Dream on.
See it for yourself.
You have no reviews, which is worse than bad reviews.
This is your reality.
People who leave bad comments are at least interested in you.
If you don't want to go back to an unknown academy,
join the joint class, okay?
You're making me upset so early in the morning.
She's hopeless.
Is this Detective Lee Jae Han? This is Lieutenant Park Hae Young.
Is it Lee Je Hoon in "Signal" today?
You got me.
Detective Lee Jae Han.
At 9am, September 12, 2016.
I arrived at the office on time.
Are you on time, too?
Detective Lee.
You're unbelievable.
Prepare for your class if you have time to practise that.
From this early morning,
you guys are getting on my nerves.
Why is he so on edge today?
I'm just trying. What's wrong with him?
Was my class that bad?
I did my best.
Noryangjin...
I knew it'd be hard,
but this is...
too big of a burden for me.
Do you want burgers?
What are you talking about?
I said, it's a burden.
I'm worried.
Do you want water?
Forget it.
- Are you going to take the exam? - Yes, I am.
What can I do?
Mum will make me work on the orchard otherwise.
Your orchard is quite big.
You could inherit it.
They'll pay me 100 dollars a month.
Do you think I'll inherit it?
I'll just be their slave.
It's a better idea to prepare for the exam.
Are you going to live in the residence?
No, I moved into my brother's house.
Do you mean the one that's very smart unlike you?
- Is he working? - Yes,
- he's doing very well. - Then again,
if he was such a good student, it's only natural.
This is why you should study hard.
You figured that out very fast, didn't you?
Where's Dong Young? Has he already started working?
No, he texted me this morning.
He's sick, so he wants me to fill in for him.
He skipped meals so often to study. It's no wonder.
Are you sure you can do it?
- I've done it a few times. - Jung Chae Yeon.
You look tired these days. Drink this and cheer up.
Forget it. Put it away.
There's another blind guy.
She's famous for being pretty in Noryangjin.
Can you believe that? Doesn't she look plain?
I'd never go out with her...
- even if I could. - Why? She's quite pretty.
What are you talking about?
- Just take it. - I said, no.
If you're here to study, focus on your studies.
What?
- Good morning. - Good morning.
What are you doing there? Will you sit down?
Okay.
- Why... - Cheer up.
Okay?
Thank you. I appreciate it.
All right. Today, we'll learn about "Ode to the Deceased Sister".
(Ode to)
What's wrong with me?
I shouldn't do this.
I'm sorry.
Because I don't have a lot of students...
and there were no reviews about my class,
I was very sad.
But...
to realise there's someone who roots for me,
I feel so sorry and ashamed.
So many emotions go through me.
What is it?
Why do I feel so embarrassed?
If she finds out it was originally for Chae Yeon,
she'll be so embarrassed.
Be quiet.
Until every one of you passes the exam,
I'll give the best lectures I can.
Cheer up, Ms Park!
Cheer up!
- Cheer up! - Cheer up!
- Thank you. - Cheer up!
What's going on here?
After promising she'd become prettier, why does she cry?
It makes her look uglier.
My goodness.
Professor Park.
Do you have any questions?
No, I don't.
I have something to give you.
It's my shoe.
Excuse me! Please throw my shoes over here.
Hurry up!
Hurry!
Was it you that threw me my heels?
Yes.
I'm so glad.
These are pretty new, so I was upset to lose it.
Thank you so much.
You should eat lunch.
I'd love to treat you.
Pardon?
Okay, I won't decline.
I forgot my wallet.
Can you wait for me downstairs?
Sure.
Ha Na.
Ta-da.
Look at this.
What are these?
I ordered promotional tissue for you.
Isn't it nice?
Since you're not in High-quality Trash's joint class,
you should do your best to get more students.
She made it just for you.
Thank you so much, Jin Yi.
It's nothing. I told you,
I'll help you in every way I can.
This is great. I'm going out for lunch,
so I should hand these out on my way back.
Just hire some kids to hand them out.
No, I'll just see my prospective students in person.
- I'll be back. - Have a good one.
Bye.
Gosh. She's so excited.
You should have asked me to chip in.
I've been feeling bad about the joint class.
It doesn't cost much.
Anyway, I want Ha Na to get a lot of students.
Detective Lee Jae Han.
Professor Hwang just performed a good deed.
If this keeps up,
Professor Park's future can be changed.
I want Professor Park to be happy.
What are you doing?
"What are you doing?"
I'm on the walkie-talkie.
You helped me get my shoes back.
I could have taken you to somewhere nicer.
It's okay. I like kalguksu.
- Excuse me. - Use this.
Thank you.
(Park Ha Na's Korean Class)
What is this?
It's tissue for promotional purposes.
- I plan on handing it out after. - I see.
You should talk more comfortably with me.
It's weird to have an instructor talk so formally.
Okay. I will, then.
Like you said, I'm your instructor.
I can't believe the first time we met...
I ended up showing my clumsy self.
I'm so embarrassed.
I wasn't that professional in the classroom, either.
Are you having a hard time?
Not at all.
Even if it's tough, I'm sure it's not as bad compared to you.
My students' lives depend on this exam.
I hope I can be helpful to those people.
All I did was cry.
- I'm ashamed. - Don't be.
You don't have to be in front of me.
I'm not here because I want to become a government employee.
I was forced here by my mum.
Studying is not my thing.
I have a weak will.
Why is that?
I think you'll do great.
- Pardon? - First,
it means you already acknowledge your problem.
If you know your problem, that means it can be fixed.
I think...
you'll do well.
Really?
I'll try not to be so foolish around you guys any more.
I'll do my best, so you should, too.
Okay?
One second.
Yes.
Pardon?
Sure, I'll be right there. Okay.
I'm sorry, something came up. I have to go,
- but finish your food. - I'm sorry?
I'm done, too. Wait for me.
What was that?
Didn't she just say she won't be foolish?
Gosh.
(Residence)
Are you feeling sick?
I got you some porridge.
What's with all the tissue?
I thought you skipped work because you're sick.
Is this what you were up to?
How disgusting.
You did it so many times.
You're so cheap when it comes to everything else.
Why did you waste so much tissue on this?
You have a girlfriend, too. Save it for later.
You'll really get sick from that, you know.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Are you embarrassed?
What is this? Are you crying?
Why are you crying?
We broke up.
Ju Yeon and I.
What?
Are these tissues...
from crying, then?
You didn't get my syllabus?
I swear I sent it.
Well,
I saw it in my inbox.
I think I missed it by accident.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay as long as you have it.
I better go now.
Hi, Mum. What is it?
What is it?
The lease is over already?
How much are you short?
What?
10,000 dollars?
Yes.
I have to pay for the lease.
As you know, I don't have that much money.
I left my previous job without getting three months of pay.
I know.
What should we do?
I lent all of my money to my boyfriend.
His business isn't doing well.
I see.
I'll ask around for you.
Thank you.
What is this?
Professor Park, are you in need of money?
I thought you were from a rich family...
since you didn't bother...
begging Professor Jin.
Was I wrong?
What do you mean?
Then...
get into Professor Jin's joint class somehow.
If you do, I'll get you an advance. Not a problem.
- Pardon? - Right.
You'd get that much money as an incentive in no time.
There's no problem with giving you an advance.
Are you serious?
Yes. Just persuade Professor Jin.
You know,
Korean instructor on the eighth floor is eyeing that spot.
You might lose it if you wait.
Isn't that professor really famous?
I feel like it'd be better for you...
to have that professor in the joint class...
Of course it's better. A whole lot better.
Except for this.
That professor is too expensive.
If I gave everyone the same incentive, I'll go broke.
How can you drink coffee?
Go and talk to High-quality Trash right now.
Cry if you have to. Just get him to let you join.
It's okay.
I promised not to bring up the joint class again.
His real name would have never been revealed...
if it wasn't for me.
I shouldn't be so shameless.
Who cares?
You should flatter him and give him gifts.
You must try everything you can.
She's right. You need money.
I better go.
Gosh.
What are we going to do with her?
Detective Lee Jae Han.
What on earth happened in 1989...
to make Professor Park be born so clueless?
Since we can't change the past, the future...
Enough is enough, Professor Min.
This is no time for that!
What should I do?
If I get into the joint class,
everything will be resolved.
Should I really try to go and persuade him?
I really don't want to do this.
Sometimes there are things you have to do even if you don't want to.
Is that so?
Then do you think I should try everything I can...
like what Jin Yi and Professor Min said?
Professor Jin.
Are you going somewhere?
To the office. I'm meeting my assistants.
I see. Go ahead.
I have to...
bring up the joint class soon.
(Jin Jung Suk Office)
I want you to pay more attention to the comments on my page.
Make sure you answer based on my materials.
Don't make any arbitrary decisions.
- Do you understand? - Yes.
Is the new textbook out for the joint class?
Yes, we're in the final stages of editing.
If you're busy, I can do it.
No, I'll do it myself.
You have a delivery.
Is Professor Jin Jung Suk here?
That's me.
What is this?
Dear respectable Professor Jin.
Please forget about what happened last time...
and allow me to join your joint class.
With most sincere regards, Park Ha Na.
Take Park Ha Na's Korean class!
She'll tell you exactly what's going to be on the exam.
Take Park Ha Na's Korean class.
Gosh, people are so cold.
What are you doing right now?
Why do you even care?
What? Are you out of your mind?
Why are you distributing these?
You said we should pretend to be strangers.
Just continue along.
Take Park Ha Na's Korean class.
Take Park Ha Na's...
Goodness, what is his problem?
He's such a jerk!
Hey, Ki Bum.
What?
Gosh, this fool.
Ease up! Drink slowly.
Hey, I haven't seen that shirt before by the way.
This? Ju Yeon got me this as a breakup gift.
It makes me think about how heartbroken...
she must've been while picking this out for me.
Ju Yeon.
Don't let her go if you're still so hung up on her.
- It's not too late yet. - No, I don't deserve her.
I can't let her go through a rough patch because of me.
Letting her go is the right thing to do.
- Then don't whimper about it. - You have no idea...
how amazing she is.
She's prettier than any of the girls...
- that are here right now. - Then don't let her go.
I told you.
- I must let her go. - Then stop going on about it.
Look around. Ju Yeon is also...
more voluptuous than the girls that are here.
I won't be able to meet a girl like her ever again.
- Ju Yeon... - Then beg her to come back.
- I told you that I must let her go! - Gosh, then just shut your mouth...
and cry your eyes out!
Why are you so chatty? You're so annoying.
Is it true?
- Did Ju Yeon really break it off? - They're done.
Gosh, my Ju Yeon...
Ju Yeon!
If I take everything into consideration, the commission...
Professor Jin.
You're just getting in now?
I've been waiting for you because I want to talk to you about something.
- What is it about? - Well, it's...
It's about the joint class.
Can you please consider letting Professor Park in?
I've been thinking hard about it,
and it looks like joining the joint class you're in...
is the only way we can help her become more known among students.
Where is she right now?
Now? She's probably at the staff room. Why do you ask?
I'm sorry to make you do this,
but please tell her to meet me at the terrace.
Oh, that's no problem. Okay, consider it done.
Where is Professor Park right now?
Professor Park?
Oh, there she is! Professor Park.
Professor Jin wants to talk to you at the terrace now.
- Pardon? He wants to talk to me? - Yes.
I practically begged him to let you join his joint class.
It looks like I finally managed to persuade him.
Why are you just standing there? Hurry up and go talk to him.
Yes, thank you so much.
Hello. I heard you want to speak to me about something.
What is your problem?
I beg your pardon?
- Why do you have these... - How can you make our students...
distribute these, knowing that every second matters to them?
How can you call yourself an instructor?
You don't deserve this job.
That's not what happened. I left these at a restaurant and...
What was this about?
- Pardon me? - You said you wanted to...
let me know how sorry you really are.
This must be what you actually wanted.
You were doing whatever it takes to win me over to join the class.
- What do you mean? I don't know... - That's enough.
I hate people like you who do whatever it takes for their goals.
I must say that you're a lot worse than I expected.
Gosh, what was that about?
These tissues are one thing, but...
what is this?
Who did this?
You sent him a gift certificate and made it look like Ha Na did it?
Yes, I did.
You ordered those tissues to help her promote her classes,
so I was wondering if there's anything I can do for her.
This means that you aren't the one who changed his mind, Mr Kim.
It must've been my gift.
I'm sure Professor Jin...
changed his mind after receiving my gift.
Really? This is the first time you did something to be praised on.
- Good job. - Good work.
Detective Lee.
Mr Kim complimented me for the very first time today.
This world has finally become a pretty good place to live.
Are you in a good place, too?
- Gosh, that was so funny! - Who was that?
Is it because I'm in a good mood right now?
That impersonation was so hilarious.
Stop it. I'm feeling too happy because of you two.
Okay, I'm sorry.
- Oh, there she is. - Hey, Ha Na!
Congratulations, congratulations
Congratulations, congratulations, congratulations
Congratulations, Professor Park!
So you'll be teaching the joint class with us, right?
Take us out for a meal! I'm not sure if you've heard,
but I sent him a gift and made it look like it was from you.
He changed his mind because he was moved by it.
Sorry?
So you're the one who sent this to him?
What happened? Why did he give this to you?
- Did he reject it? - Is that why he wanted to see you?
So he still doesn't want you to be in the joint class?
- That's right. - What?
I practically begged him.
Goodness, Professor Jin is being way too mean about this.
I know that all of you tried your best to help me.
It doesn't look like you need to do anything about it any more.
- Wait, Professor Park. - Ha Na.
Hey, stop drinking.
- Just let me be. - Why are you being so...
Hey, try to get in touch with her.
- It's not too late yet. - Forget it.
I'm sure Ju Yeon thought hard about it before making the decision.
- Being clingy won't solve anything. - Yes, that's right.
I want you guys to hold onto my phone.
- Why? - I'm worried...
that I might end up calling or messaging her.
- That will break her heart. - Hey.
- Just don't do it. - Who knows what I'll do...
when I black out?
Okay. But what is this?
Is this a prop from the TV series, "Reply 1997"?
How old is this phone?
It looks ancient like the one in the TV series.
- You should also hold onto this. - Your wallet? Why?
I'm worried that I might end up grabbing a taxi to go see her...
- if I have cash on me. - Hey, just don't do that.
I told you. Who knows what I'll do...
- after drinking until I drop? - All right. Okay.
Goodness. Is this a wallet or a rag?
You don't even have enough to pay the minimum fare for a taxi.
You're seriously so ridiculous.
- Jin Yi. - Yes?
You said you'd ask around about the money.
Thanks in advance for your help.
Don't worry about it.
I'll get going, then.
Professor Park, are you heading home?
Let's have dinner together. It's on me.
I'll pass. I don't really have any appetite right now.
Get home safely, Ha Na.
Have a good evening, Mr Kim.
All right. You, too.
She seems so down.
How can she not be?
I mean, she can't join the joint class after all.
We should do something.
Shall we go out for drinks with Professor Jin...
to try to persuade him again to let Ha Na in?
Yes! That's such a great idea.
Are you leaving now?
Professor Jin, let's go grab a drink.
I made it clear that I do not drink with co-workers.
Please don't say that. Let's just have one drink together.
I have something important to talk to you about as well.
Professor Jin, please!
Come with us.
You don't want to?
- I apologise. - Have a good evening, everyone.
- Okay. You, too. - But...
See you tomorrow, Professor Jin.
Even my beauty isn't enough to persuade him.
How can he be that cold?
He crushed my pride.
I'm leaving, too.
Where do you think you're going? You made me feel like drinking.
Come on. The three of us should still go out for drinks.
Professor Hwang, what do you feel like?
Hey, are you okay?
I'm not okay.
Everywhere I go, I think about the moments I shared with Ju Yeon.
How can I be okay?
Ju Yeon and I used to come to this café often.
Ju Yeon always...
ordered a caffe mocha with loads of whipped cream on it.
Also,
Ju Yeon liked that Chinese restaurant, too.
She'd always...
pour vinegar over the pickled radish.
We've been to that motel, too.
There, Ju Yeon would...
What did she do there?
Why do you want to know that?
You talked in detail about what happened in other places.
Why can't you tell us what happened in the motel? Shame on you.
- What? - Guys.
Please stop it, you idiots.
Ki Bum.
Check my phone.
Has Ju Yeon sent me anything?
Why would she? That's not going to happen.
- Just check it. - Fine.
This is my phone.
This is my wallet.
I think I left it at the bar.
What? You idiot!
Have you seen any phone or wallet?
It's a very old phone...
and a worn-out wallet...
that no one would want to steal.
- I haven't seen anything. - She hasn't seen anything.
Hey.
Could you have left it in the bathroom?
I'm sure it's in there. I'll go and look.
Go ahead.
My goodness.
Who would steal such a piece of junk?
Right?
Let go of me! Are you crazy?
I'll buy you a new one.
That's not the point.
What if Ju Yeon has called me?
What if she finally took up her courage...
- and thought I ignored her call? - That's just false hope.
Ju Yeon will never call you.
How do you know that?
How? It's obvious.
She must be sick of waiting for you to pass the exam.
- What? - She got a job.
I'm sure she already found another guy.
Her face and body that you liked so much...
are already someone else's.
What?
What's wrong with you?
People are staring at us. Let go of me.
- Let go of me. - It hurts.
- Let go of me. - You let go of me.
- Let go of me. - Let go of me.
- Let go of me. - Are you crazy?
- What did you say? - What's up with you?
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing? Stop it.
- Get off of me. - Let go of me.
Let go of me, will you?
Let go of me right now.
What's the problem with you?
- Let go of me! - Let go of me!
- Let go! - Let go of me!
Let go!
Let go on three.
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Let go! - Let go!
- Hey! - Let go!
People are watching us.
Let go of me!
- Mr Kim, thank you for the dinner. - Thank you.
Where should we go now?
Just pick any place.
We're not in the position to be picky.
I'm so upset about Professor Jin.
So am I.
Why can't he talk it out with us over drinks?
Why does he never drink with us?
Does he not like drinking?
What do you mean I don't like drinking?
I love it.
Only...
when I drink solo.
Oh my. What a coincidence!
I'm so happy to see you!
You said you didn't want to drink with us.
I know.
If you were going to drink alone, why didn't you join us?
You look so lonely.
Drink with us.
What are you doing?
I prefer drinking alone.
It's always better to drink with other people.
Right.
It can be both a welcome party for Professor Jin...
and the joint class team dinner.
Let's drink together.
I'm okay. I'll get going.
Oh my.
Why are you so hasty?
Drink just one glass with us.
Sit down first.
- Sit down. - Sit down.
Just sit down.
Here. Call her.
Find out if she has called you.
If she hasn't, you're dead meat.
Hi, Ju Yeon. It's me.
Have you called me?
What?
You haven't?
I just wanted to check.
You haven't.
I see.
I'm sorry. Bye.
I won't...
call you again.
See? I told you she couldn't have.
You're dead meat.
What?
Hey.
Hey, stop it.
Look on the bright side.
You said you wanted to pass the exam this year.
Now that you don't have a girlfriend, focus on your studies.
What would I pass the exam for?
I wanted to...
marry Ju Yeon and live happily after passing the exam.
There's no Ju Yeon now.
Dong Young, there are other girls.
What's the big deal?
Just get over it.
Right.
I'll buy you a new phone and a new wallet.
Can't you buy me Ju Yeon, too?
I don't think I'll be able to forget her.
You're pathetic.
Stop it.
Stop it now.
I think I'm going to cry.
Gosh.
Ju Yeon.
Stop it.
Professor Jin.
Can't you let Professor Park...
join the joint class?
You should have pity on her.
She's the breadwinner of her family.
Her family went bankrupt when she was in college.
She had to pay for her tuitions and her family's living expenses.
That's right. She said...
she needed 10,000 dollars to pay for her mother's lease.
Oh my.
She must so desperately need to join the joint class.
- She must be so desperate. - So desperate.
Professor Jin, is it really impossible?
Do I work for a charity?
Does my joint class exist to help those unfortunate?
Why not?
Take this and let her join.
I even went to the department store despite my busy schedule.
- Why would you? - Me?
Well...
Professor Park seemed to not have any social skills.
I thought I should help her.
I'm such a nice person, right?
I pretended that it was Professor Park's idea.
Isn't that amazing?
Everyone's asking you. Can't you take her in?
It's already over.
- Where are you going? - Don't leave.
There's so much food left.
I'm going to the bathroom.
I see.
Don't run away.
We have your bag and jacket.
He's unbelievably stubborn.
He seemed angry.
Should we stop?
I'm...
scared of him.
I'm more scared of my in-laws.
After investing some money, they've been nagging me so much.
To make up for the money I had to pay Professor Jin,
we should make the most use of...
cheap instructors like Professor Park.
When Professor Jin comes back,
we'll have to persuade him no matter what.
We have to.
- Here, let's drink. - Cheers.
Cheers.
What's with No Geu Rae?
Why didn't she tell me it wasn't her?
She made me look bad.
Also, what did she do to those people?
Why are they all trying to help her?
She's so annoying.
What is this anyway?
What? Hold on.
Let me see. Isn't this a portable breathalyser?
He's so strange.
Who would he carry this around?
It's working, it's working.
0.150 percent.
Is this enough to get caught?
Detective Lee, I just arrested a drunk driver.
Arrested me? How dare you?
Give that to me.
Let go.
Detective Lee Jae Han. Do they have openings at academies there?
If they do, please take Professor Min over.
We don't need him in 2016!
Don't you dare do it again.
Detective Lee, I think this will be my last message to you.
- However, this message... - Give it back.
- Give it to me. I'll break it. - Sir.
- This is really expensive. - Let go.
- It's expensive. I swear. - Just let go.
- Let go. I'll break it. - Enough with that, just drink.
Stop it.
Hey, you...
What are you doing?
What are you looking at?
I wasn't looking. I wasn't.
- Mr Kim, this is sexual harassment. - Sexual harassment?
Sexual harassment.
What are they doing?
It's definitely not sexual harassment.
They're so low.
It's not sexual harassment.
Gosh.
I'm Professor Park Ha Na from CS Pass Academy.
Come and take my Korean class.
I'm Professor Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Thank you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Thank you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Please come take my class.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. It's nice to meet you.
(Park Ha Na's Korean Class)
I drink solo...
so that I could overcome the harsh daily life.
It's 10pm already.
I better go.
- What? - What? Again?
- No way. You can't go. - I have to go.
- You can't go. - I have to.
- Really. - No, you can't leave.
On days that are so tough, it's hard to drink with others.
Come on.
It's like a spell that helps you console yourself...
and admit to the reality of life.
That's why I'm drinking solo again today.
All right. Let's cheer up.
I'm the rising star in Korean. It's Park Ha Na's Korean Class.
Come and take my class. Here.
Come and take classes for your civil service exam.
It's Park Ha Na's Korean Class.
- Gong Myung. - Professor Park.
- Do you want some help? - No.
You handed them out earlier today for me, didn't you?
I was going to ask you tomorrow in class.
Don't do that again.
Why not?
Did Professor Jin say something?
No. I just feel bad.
You should be studying. Don't waste your time on this.
It's okay. It's not like I study that much.
Don't be like that. You should give your all while you're at it.
I hope you do well and become a government employee.
Go home and study.
Hello, I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy.
It's nice to meet you. Thank you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy.
Hello, I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy.
Please come and take my Korean class.
Thank you.
(Mr Kim)
- Yes. - Where are you, Professor Jin?
I'm on my way home.
What? You're going to leave your jacket and your bag?
- Come and take it. - See you tomorrow.
Then I'll take these with me...
What is she doing?
Everyone, what do you think syllable means?
It's the smallest unit of speech sounds.
You're pretty good.
Look. "Sea".
"Sea".
How many syllables is that?
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm listening to an online lecture.
The consonants can never...
What a great teacher you found.
I'll find you someone better, so take that class instead.
- Don't listen to someone like her. - What?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with her?
She taught at a nameless academy in the outskirts of Seoul.
She has a mediocre academic background, too.
What is there to learn from her?
- Is there a lot to learn from you? - What?
You should speak for yourself. Should you be allowed to lecture?
You look at the world with so much prejudice.
For example, look at how you're treating me.
The jobless students studying for the civil service exam...
must look so pathetic to you.
Before you teach them,
have you ever consoled or sincerely felt sorry for them?
What?
At least she's sincere.
There are only seven kinds.
You have to memorise these ones.
To me, she looks like a hundred times better than you.
Didn't you take her class for the first time today?
How can you tell if she's sincere or not?
Is that why...
you decided to hand out her promotional tissue...
- when she asked you to help? - She didn't ask me for help.
I did it voluntarily.
You didn't say anything to her, did you?
Don't do that.
She already scolded me for it.
What?
What is going on? Same goes with the gift certificate.
Why doesn't she ever speak up for herself?
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Please come take my class.
Here, you should take one, too. Thank you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Nice to meet you.
Try taking a class.
Hello, it's Park Ha Na's Korean Class.
Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy. Nice to meet you.
I'm Park Ha Na of CS Pass Academy.
What is she doing?
Everyone, what do you think syllable means?
It's the smallest unit of speech sounds.
Gosh. You hardly studied.
How can you pass out already?
Hey, are you really asleep?
It's none other than consonants.
Consonants cannot make syllables on their own.
You need vowels.
If you only look at the consonants,
it doesn't work. That's why we need vowels.
Here are the most frequently used ones. Vowels are...
what allows us to be able to pronounce this word as "sea".
You understand it now, right?
Goodness.
Why did these...
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
I should keep them on. I don't want to lose another shoe.
(Professor Jin Jung Suk)
What does he want?
Why is he calling me?
Hello?
Are you confident that you can do a good job in the joint class?
Pardon me?
I'm asking if you're confident that you won't ruin my reputation.
Sorry? Yes, of course!
I'll do my very best!
Doing your best is a given.
You must do a good job.
I'll let you join the class for two months on a trial basis.
Don't forget that this doesn't mean you can relax.
You'll be kicked out if your classes aren't up to my standards.
Thank you so much!
I'll be sure not to disappoint you.
Thank you. I really appreciate it.
Thank you very much. I'm so grateful.
Thank you!
Whatever.
That's such great news!
I can't believe it!
(The Shortcut to Success)
This made my day.
(Drinking Solo)
Professor Jin puts up a cold front,
but he's actually so kind.
Mr Oh had Jang Geu Rae's back in the drama, "Misaeng".
You're like Mr Oh to this No Geu Rae here.
What kind of coffee do you want? Something stylish like you?
Or would you like something as sweet as you, like caffe latte?
Anything would be fine.
Okay! I have a lot of potentials, so I'll be right back with a good one.
Hearing that she has potentials got her all excited.
I think I'm pregnant.
What? Oh, no!
What are you talking about? I'm so happy about it.
What are you doing?
Mr Kim, you must be tired.
You. You over there.
"Go to Mojito and drink a glass of the Maldives."
Have some manners.
I set my eyes on it first.
I grabbed it first.
You little...
You can have this. You know that it's my favourite shirt, right?
- Ki Bum, let me give you a hug. - What is wrong with you, seriously?
Dong Young, don't die.
Please be alive.
Dong Young...
Is that Professor Park?
Professor Park, are you okay?
I saw you bumping into the box earlier and got worried.
I shall introduce a nice guy to you.
What? You're not here alone?
Hello, I'm Jin Gong Myung.
Let's start dating.
- Drink with me. - No, thank you. Ms No Geu Rae.
I heard everything.
So I got in the joint class as a substitute.
What are you doing now?
What? You let me get in because of my potentials?
Why did you lie to my face? Why?
You're seriously so obnoxious.
What did you just say?