This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Drink]
Cheer up, baby, cheer up, baby,
cheer up a little bit more.
- A girl can’t give her heart too easily.
- Is she perhaps the Korean teacher?
Professor Park!
- You're mistaken.
- Oh, come on.
It is you, Professor Park!
You're my favorite student in Noryangjin.
Rather than your favorite student,
can I become your boyfriend?
He must be so angry
because of me.
Oh man!
I thought he put me in the joint class
as a replacement and got so mad.
And I can't even avoid him tomorrow!
Why did she even yell at
me while she was drunk
if she was going to be so
self-conscious about it?
I think it'd be better if
Ms. No Geu Rae stood next to me.
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get over here.
Don't do what others want
you to do all the time.
Be confident and say what you want.
Does he... really like me?
I thought he was crazy.
He is indeed crazy.
Stop playing around. Focus on studying
now that you are in Noryangjin.
You're absolutely right.
Now that I'm in Noryangjin,
I should be studying.
If I'd passed the exam
I would have been so proud
to dance for Grandma at her party today.
What's with No Geu Rae?
Why's she holding her umbrella like that?
She's getting drenched!
Oh, geez.
Well, this is "Powerful Korean,"
so let's start things off powerfully...
let's be strong, and...
- Teach!
- Professor Park fainted in class.
What?
Are you really all right?
It's okay.
Why are you okay
with everything all the time?
You can tell me when you're not okay.
- I'm not okay!
- Whoa!
- I said I'm not fine!
- Professor.
You really should have a boyfriend.
Why not become my girlfriend, huh?
[Episode 7]
I love drinking solo.
Since my job entails talking all day,
having this time when I don't have to...
this solitude...
is the best.
I have a couple of rules for myself
when I drink solo.
First: I have to drink in a place
with a luxurious atmosphere.
Second: I have to snack on
something luxurious while I drink.
Third: I have to drink
with some class.
A time just for myself.
A time of healing.
This is the reason why
I love drinking solo.
Who's the owner of this
delectably divine body?
Who? Oh.
Jin Gong Myung, huh?
Yep, that's me!
What the hell was that?
You're asking as if you don't know?
They're receipts for the toll
gates at Incheon and Yeosu!
You've been taking a hell of
a road trip all over the country, huh?
The miles on my car
went up like crazy
so did you think I really wouldn't notice
just because you filled it with gas?
Fine!
I did drive it a little!
What's wrong with your
one and only little brother
driving a great car
that you don't even use?
What?
If you want to drive a nice car,
earn the money to buy one yourself.
I hate people like you who
freeload off others the most--
Oh?
I'm not the same Jin Gong Myung
you used to boss around.
Don't you see these muscles?
Oh my. To think that I'd dared to stand
up against a strong man such as yourself.
Oh my, oh my.
I'm terribly sorry.
Let me offer you a formal apology.
Don't do that again, all right?
I'm telling you this now
so that we're clear on this
but I have no intention
of letting you live with me for long.
Got that?
If you do anything like this again, your
ass will be on its way to the orchard.
You got that?
Stop right there!
- Stop.
- Would you stop, if you were me?
You act like you're such hot shit just
because you have a house and some cars!
You're so petty!
You better find yourself
the next express bus back home!
Professor!
Oh, why are you here?
I was worried about how you were.
And you didn't pick up my calls either.
Oh, I didn't have time
to check my phone.
I was putting my furniture out to
dry since it's a nice day today.
All of your furniture got wet
when your place flooded, right?
- I'll help you!
- No, no! It's fine!
Go and study.
Hey, I told you already that
I'm a student who doesn't study!
Let me help you out
real quick.
Oh, it's fine!
Oh my!
I told you, it's fine.
Wow, are you a gymnast?
You're good enough to get a gold medal!
I told you
you don't need to help me.
I feel bad that you helped
me move my furniture.
I told you. I don't have anything
else to be doing anyway.
How does it make sense that a student
studying for exams has nothing to do?
You should study!
Teach. Lecturing me
is forbidden today, all right?
I already fought with my
Big Bro this morning.
I got an earful of nagging
just like that from him too.
Ugh, he's so annoying.
Are you not on good terms
with your older brother?
Yes. Totally.
I just can't seem to like him!
He thinks he's all that
and talks down to me all the time!
Doesn't he know that words
hurt more than a knife?
Yeah. Words do hurt
quite a bit.
Whatever. Who else
could I blame but myself?
This is my fault for misjudging you.
It seems that I thought
too highly of you, Ms. No Geu Rae.
Ugh. I'll stop thinking about
that annoying guy and just clean.
Oh, good idea!
My back was starting to hurt too!
Oh my gosh!
Wow, Teach! Looks like you're showing
off your flexibility quite a lot today.
That move was totally
gold medal-worthy too!
Um, Gong Myung...
can you help me up?
Oh, sure.
It's really no joke,
living in a semi-basement.
It floods when it rains, and everything.
It's fine. It's not like
this is the first time.
What a relief.
To tell you the truth,
the real reason why I came
was because I thought
you might be depressed.
Nah. I'm okay now.
I have to shake this off
and work even harder.
And I'll get tons of new
students to take my class
and save some money to move out of
that semi-basement. That's my goal.
My goal is to become
your boyfriend, Teach.
It'd be nice if both of us
achieved our goals soon.
Stop it with that nonsense
and go study already!
I want to, but I just can't
seem to find the willpower.
And it's not like I have
much motivation either.
Sheesh.
Fine, then.
In order to motivate you, I will do
one thing you ask for if you pass.
Really?
Then...
go out with me.
- What?
- You said you'd grant me a wish.
And what I want is to
be your boyfriend.
All right! If I pass,
we'll be dating!
Oh yeah.
I need evidence.
All right, repeat after me.
"I, Park Ha Na, will date Jin Gong Myung
if he passes the civil servant exam."
If Jin Gong Myung passes the civil
servant exam, I, Park Ha Na, will...
will seriously consider dating him.
Hey, come on!
Well, fine.
This much is okay.
Wow. I should hurry and move your
furniture and then go study!
Professor.
You'll become my woman soon.
Come on.
Let's go!
Maybe I shouldn't
have said that.
Oh, whatever. Getting him to
pass is all that matters!
It's not like he'd care about his old
teacher after he passes, anyway.
I love drinking solo.
Drinking solo on an evening
on the weekend feels more leisurely
and comfortable.
I have a couple of rules for myself
when I drink solo--
Oh, look at you,
eating so well!
How is it that you look so pretty
even when you're eating?
You're so pretty!
I hate people who get drunk and
shamelessly get touchy-feely in public!
Hello? This is
Ms. Park Ha Na's phone.
Hello?
I bet that No Geu Rae
is just like that with her boyfriend.
And after she made a mess
of my joint class too!
How dare she be dating
someone in her state?
This is no time for No Geu Rae
to be dating someone!
She should work on
her lesson plans instead!
Figures. Her mind is elsewhere, so how
could she be lesson-planning efficiently?
Your apartment flooded too?
Living in that semi-basement
is the problem.
But still, it's a relief that
your student helped you.
I know, right, Jin Yi?
It was so hard!
Oh no!
- Oof!
- Oh, you're so heavy.
- Just a moment.
- Get your shoe back on!
- Oh my.
- Are you okay?
I'm sorry!
What are you doing?
This is the entrance to the parking lot!
I'm sorry. My shoe fell off.
Why would your shoe fall off here?
It's because your mind is elsewhere
that your shoe fell off!
Hurry up and move!
All right.
What does he mean
your mind is elsewhere?
I'm not sure.
He really is Premium Trash!
He really is an ass.
If he almost hit someone with his car,
he should apologize, not yell at you!
I think it's because
he's mad at me.
He was mad because I passed
out during the first joint class
and ruined the class's image.
He's the type to run you over with
his car if you pass out again!
Are you okay?
I told myself that I'd be strong,
but Professor Jin got so angry at me.
This is so hard on me.
There is a saying for when
you're facing hard times.
They say that suffering is
a necessary ingredient
to bake the bread
called "tomorrow."
Cheer up.
Wow, you're actually consoling me?
Thanks. I think I'll be able to be
strong since you always hear me out.
Wow, look at her
having a fun time.
She's talking to her boyfriend on the
phone as soon as she comes to work?
You'll continue to be by
my side like this, right?
I don't think I'll be
able to live without you.
Um, Professor Jin!
I'm sorry for bothering you with
the issue regarding the joint class.
That won't ever happen again.
Please, trust me.
Well, I don't know.
I can't trust you.
I feel like your mind is
already elsewhere.
So how could I possibly believe you?
What the hell?
Why does he keep saying that?
Hey, Kim Ki Bum.
Lend me some toothpaste.
Whoa. Are you studying
by any chance?
I told you. I'm going to become a
grandson that my grandma can be proud of.
And in order to do that, I have no
choice but to hurry and pass.
I'm really going to study
hard, starting today.
That's good.
Yeah. So leave, so I can study.
I'll just grab a tiny bit of toothpaste
and be on my way.
I can't focus because
my desk is such a mess.
Oh, there we go.
Why is it so messy in here?
Now I really feel like studying!
Why are my nails so long?
It's getting on my nerves.
I'm going to mix my leftovers from
yesterday with some rice and eat it!
What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm cleaning the refrigerator.
I thought you said you made up your
mind to study. Why are you cleaning?
I was going to, see?
But the fact that the refrigerator here
is so dirty bothered me so much
that I couldn't focus!
As if. You're just making up excuses
because you don't want to study.
Is that what it is?
Figures. Cleaning the refrigerator is
so much fun compared to studying.
I want to clean the bathrooms
and even the stairs.
I never knew that cleaning was this fun!
Crazy bastard.
Hey, did you see a can of
spicy tuna in the refrigerator?
Oh, the thing that only
had oil left in the can?
- Yeah.
- I threw it away.
Hey!
Don't you know how good it tastes
if you mix that oil with some rice?
Why did you have to go
and clean when nobody asked you to
and ruin my lunch?
If you're going to be such a nuisance,
just give up on studying
and live the way
you've always lived!
No, I can't! I have to pass and become a
grandson that my grandma can be proud of!
I really am going to study hard!
But I got started with this already,
so let me just finish up.
Crazy bastard.
Damn it, it smudged.
Must you really take those like that?
Did it make you feel
good to do that?
Oh my gosh, you surprised me.
What's the matter?
Did you have to take my tissues?
Did it make you feel good to do that?
Oh my gosh. You're really going to
be like this over some tissues?
Here, take them back!
Why are you dressed
so normally today though?
You're not doing
an impersonation today?
I just did one.
You don't know it?
- Did you really have to...
- take everything like this...
- to make yourself feel better?
If you're going to do an impersonation,
do something that's famous!
I still can't even tell
where this is from.
Why not?
This is super famous!
Geez, how annoying.
What is that noise?
Oh, it's just a telemarketer.
It's my ringtone.
"Chilgapsan."
It's my mom's go-to song
when she goes to karaoke.
It brings back memories.
Young Miss, who's
off to the bean field...
Why is that Young Miss going
to the bean field anyway?
Does she not work?
Well, it's her job to go
and work in the bean field, probably.
At any rate, I don't want to hear it,
so change your ringtone right now.
Got that?
What's with him? What does
he have against bean fields?
I don't know either.
Do you really have to criticize
the woman who's going to the bean field
to make yourself
feel better?
Stop it already!
- Oh, it's her.
- Did you see the video too?
Don't listen to them.
You just have to do well today.
I'll teach an amazing class in
front of those 1,000 students!
Let's go! Let's go!
Let's go!
This is the joint Korean class, right?
Yes.
Is today some special day?
Where is everyone?
All of you were quite shocked because I
passed out during the first class, right?
I'm sorry, everyone.
That won't happen again, so don't worry.
I'll get started now, then.
Does this make any sense?
Professor Park.
You saw, didn't you?
You saw how
your lecture hall is so empty now.
Yes. Actually, I was curious about that.
Is today some special day?
Where were all the students?
You really are naïve, aren't you?
Why else? They didn't want to take
your class, so they didn't come!
I asked some students since
your lecture hall was so empty
and they said that they'd take Korean
under a different instructor
because you're untrustworthy!
What? Oh...
Don't worry too much,
Professor Jin.
I'll do whatever it takes to get
the enrollment numbers back up. Okay?
What are you going to
do about this, huh?
Next time, nobody will take this joint
class even if Professor Jin is in it!
This won't do.
Take over the web broadcast
that Professor Shin Yong Sook
was supposed to do today.
A web broadcast?
You do those here too?
Yes, once a month.
The professors take turns
doing web broadcasts for students.
They promote themselves
and talk to students too.
I don't care what you have to do.
Use that to change the students' minds!
Got that?
I'm going to keep my eyes peeled
and see how many people come in!
Yes, sir.
Don't worry, Professor Jin!
I'll solve this issue no matter what!
This is really your last shot.
Do whatever it takes!
You're way too soft!
Seriously!
When it's too public that
you can't make it private...
and the principle of the market and
performance management come together...
and when things
become predictable...
that's when executive agency is needed.
I'm putting my all into lecturing you.
Did you have to fall asleep like
that to make yourself feel better?
What?
All right, that's the end of this
lecture. See you all next time.
- Thank you!
- Yes!
Thank you!
Geez, he surprised me.
Did you have to yell like that
to make yourself feel better?
Hey. If you were going to sleep, you
should've stayed at the student hostel.
Why did you come all the way
here only to fall asleep?
It's not like I fell asleep
because I wanted to!
I came to study, but just
happened to fall asleep.
Aw man. I studied so hard
that I got tired.
I'll go and study now,
since I got a lot of rest.
See ya.
What are we going to do
about that guy?
He said he'd study hard from now
on, but it doesn't look like he is.
Wait, Ki Bum said that
he's studying hard now too?
Me too.
What? You too?
Weren't you just going to spend a year
here to escape your mom's nagging?
Yeah, but I changed my mind.
I have a reason why I have to pass now.
So, with that in mind... can you give me
your notes from this lecture?
What? What were you doing
if you weren't taking notes?
I was making
a schedule for studying.
Ta-da!
You crazy bastard.
I thought you said that you
made up your mind to study.
But you were drawing this
instead of listening to the lecture?
Hey, if I'm going to do it,
I need to follow a schedule!
I honestly don't want
to study, you know.
Anyway, give me your notes!
Why, you little...
Thanks, buddy!
Oh, hey, Jung Chae Yeon.
I came to Noryangjin to study,
so I'm planning to do just that.
What's with him?
Hey, I heard about what happened.
Oh man, those kids are so cruel.
How could they all drop out like that
just because you fainted once?
It's only natural that they'd do that.
She didn't try her best, so why would
students want to take her class?
What?
What do you mean--
If you're going to teach students who are
putting their lives on the line to study
you have to put your life
at risk to teach them
to be worthy of being their
instructor, Ms. No Geu Rae.
What are you talking about?
I am!
I'm giving this everything that
I've got and doing my best!
You're giving this everything
you've got, eh?
How can you say that
when your mind is elsewhere?
Why do you keep saying that today?
You really don't know? Ms. No Geu Rae
is dating someone right now!
You seriously think you should be
dating someone right now?
What is he saying?
You're dating, Professor Park?
- No!
- Yeah!
She's basically
a chronically single person!
I guess you don't know either
but she was drinking with her boyfriend
on the night she passed out!
I even spoke to her boyfriend
on the phone myself!
What are you talking about?
Seriously!
[Call Yesterday From: Premium Trash]
Oh!
He's not my boyfriend!
He's my student!
I think that the student
I was with picked up my phone.
Oh yeah. You said that your
semi-basement room flooded, right?
You're talking about the student who
came by to help you that day, right?
Professor Jin!
Your assumption was wrong.
What?
Well, who cares if it was a student
instead of a boyfriend?
Do you think it's acceptable to
be drinking with your student?
Get it together!
Got it?
Oh, so that's why he kept on going on
about you being distracted.
It's because he thought
you had a boyfriend, right?
How could he do that to poor Professor
Park, who doesn't have a boyfriend?
Did you have to make her feel pathetic
like that to make yourself feel better?
That terrible man.
What? That wasn't her boyfriend, then?
She's basically chronically single?
Figures. Who'd like
a tacky woman like her?
What's with that No Geu Rae?
She should feel happy that someone
thought she had a boyfriend in her state!
How dare she get mad at me!
It's because she has such a temper that
she doesn't have a boyfriend.
She doesn't even have a boyfriend!
So how dare she get mad at me?
Everyone's taking that bastard's
Korean History class?
Isn't there anyone else's class
besides that asshole's?
[Best Korean History Instructor]
Huh? Kim Hyun Soo
hit a home run?
[Kim Hyun Soo's home run at
the bottom of the ninth outing!]
Wow, my Hyun Soo...
I knew he could do it!
He has such spirit!
I have no time to be happy about
Kim Hyun Soo's home run right now
when my life is at risk here.
[You totally have to buy this!]
[The Boyfriend Look: Guaranteed to make
the girl you're flirting with yours!]
You can make the girl you're flirting
with into your woman?
Oh, looks like he's taking
an online class.
I guess he's really made up
his mind to study hard.
[Panda slides down
a slide and then rolls off]
What are you doing?
Well... this video of the panda sliding
down a slide is really cute, so...
I thought you said that
you were going to study!
Hey, I've been taking an online class
all this time! I'm just taking a break!
[Exclusive!
An X-file on a celebrity!]
"Exclusive! An x-file on a celebrity"?
Well, um...
Move over!
"101 Movies to
watch before you die."
"How to make your hip bones
look super attractive!"
"Alien invasion in the countryside?"
Oh my!
A UFO, eh?
You call this taking a short
break, you crazy bastard?
You sure opened
a ton of tabs, didn't you?
Well, um...
"How to be loved by an older woman"?
What's this nonsense?
Is there an older woman
that you're interested in?
No! I'm just looking!
When I put my mind to studying, I
get curious about the strangest things.
Right now, you don't want to study.
That's why
you're curious about everything.
Just focus on studying, punk.
I'm lost because I was asked to do
a lesson on the Internet suddenly.
I agree.
You're not ready.
How can he ask you on the day?
Gosh, I can't believe Director Kim.
This is what I did before.
You can refer back to it.
Hello, everyone.
That's right. I'm Hwang Jin Yi.
I did yoga stretching then.
Oh my, you were so pretty.
I will tell you how to stretch.
First, we start with the shoulders.
Pull your arms up straight like this.
Repeat after me.
[This is so random, but I love you.]
To the left.
To the right.
To the front.
[I wish I were your chair.]
Wow, so many people viewed it.
Wow, you are so popular.
Why get excited over nothing?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Refer to mine also.
I did a cooking session.
I made a dish.
I invited a student over
to share the meal.
- It's right next to it.
- There it is.
This is my first order for today,
Spaghetti alle vongole.
Repeat after me: Spaghetti alle vongole.
[You're an ugly Lee Sun Geun]
Now, the water is boiling.
To make spaghetti alle vongole...
- Wow.
- Wasn't it good?
Wow, Professor Min
looked like a real chef.
Agreed.
He really looked like a real chef.
So Director Kim said
he wasn't good at being a lecturer.
He told him to quit and become a chef.
Are you happy that you had to
tell her about my painful past?
What's up with you again?
You two had good ideas
and did a good job.
I have no idea what to do,
so I'm really worried.
Director Kim told me to get
as many students to view it as possible
so I can clear my tarnished image.
At a time like this
if a popular instructor like me
appears as a guest
it would be really good.
But Director Kim made
this dinner plan a long time ago.
I can't bail out.
If I don't show, he'll go crazy, right?
Definitely.
Professor Baek's husband
opened a new restaurant.
We're all going there to celebrate it.
There are only a few of us here, so...
Professor Jin!
Later, Ha Na is doing
a lesson on the Internet.
Can you come on it as a guest?
- Why should I?
- Earlier, you said
you were wrong saying
her mind was somewhere else.
Maybe you could
apologize to her this way...
I will pass. Do you think I'm crazy?
What does he mean that he's crazy?
Gosh, how rude.
But if the top star of Noryangjin
Jin Jung Seok shows up once
it will be really good.
I don't know what to say, Professor Park.
I will handle it. Don't worry.
Ha Na, good luck. Look at this one.
Gosh, what am I going to do?
[Gong Myung]
Professor, are you done for the day?
I'm still studying.
Ah, that's right.
Should I ask Gong Myung
what I should do?
He will know better
what kids would want.
No, I shouldn't bother him
when he's finally studying.
I shouldn't bother him.
Now I'm sitting at my desk.
I want to go out to eat,
play, and sleep.
I want to do so many other things.
But I will focus on my goal
and go at it.
Wait for me, Teach.
True. If anybody tries to study
there are a lot of things
they should hold back.
Ah, that's right.
If Jin Gong Myung passes
the civil service exam
I, Park Ha Na,
will seriously consider dating him.
Sung San Byul Gok is...
[Ha Na]
[Will you marry me?]
Gong Myung, did you prepare all this?
Of course, Professor.
Now I'm a civil servant.
I've passed the exam.
[Certificate]
You will marry me, right?
Of course I will.
I've been waiting for this day.
Okay, honey.
Honey.
This is what will happen, right?
Let's cheer up. Good luck.
Gosh, that's irritating.
It's getting on my nerves.
Study hard.
Tell my grandma.
She will make a memorial stone
for her devoted grandson.
Excuse me.
You can also come to us
for the paperwork.
Kim Ki Bum isn't
the only civil servant working here.
But if we can
I'd like to get my paperwork from
a handsome and kind man like him.
Agreed. He's known as a chic
SHINee among civil servants.
- I agree.
- I will wait for him.
- Gosh, don't cut in line.
I was here first.
Excuse me.
Please don't fight.
I, Kim Ki Bum, work for you people.
I don't want you to get hurt.
He's so cool.
I knew it.
[Monthly Civil Servants]
[Best civil servant Kim Ki Bum]
I'd better study hard.
Gosh, I wanted to focus. That sucks.
Get out of my way.
I will let it go
because you're pretty, seriously.
Hello, this is Park Ha Na,
teaching powerful Korean.
The topic for today is...
[Ah, she's the fainting Korean.]
Although there are a lot of
things you like to do
you're holding back
because you're busy studying.
So on your behalf
I'd like to do anything
you want me to do today.
"I will do everything you ask."
Now ask me.
I will do anything you want me to do.
Mr. iMadeafire.
"I want to find a girlfriend"
"but I just can't right now,
due to my studying."
"Think that you're my girlfriend
and act cute with me."
Well, I don't know how to act cute.
I will give it a shot.
Students.
You guys all fainted
because Ha Na is so much fun.
Oh no, don't leave, guys.
I will read the next favor.
This is a good one.
Mr. cook2004.
"I want to have boiled pork and beer."
"I can't have it because it
will hinder my studying tomorrow."
"Show me that
you're eating it on my behalf."
Sure, I will place an order right now.
Ta-da! Boiled pork has finally arrived.
Wow, awesome! It was so fast.
Here, this is boiled park.
Wow, it looks so good, doesn't it?
- It looks delicious.
- Come on. Just dig in.
Just look at that. That.
Students are leaving.
It's so boring.
Is she happy now that
she did such a boring lesson?
Do you think Ha Na is
having a good time? Gosh.
If Professor Jin won't come with us
- why can't he help her?
- Who knows?
- He might be busy today actually.
- No way.
He must be eating
and drinking alone somewhere.
Correct. Again, I'm eating
and drinking solo today.
No, I'm drinking in luxury.
Wait.
No Geu Rae must be
teaching online right now.
I'm not necessarily
interested in it
but I should watch it to be able to
manage my joint class, right?
I will add pepper paste.
Now I will take a bite.
Pardon?
You want five red peppers
and three garlic in here?
- Yes, I got it.
- Gosh, how tacky.
Red peppers...
I will do anything you want!
I will take a bite now.
[Jackpot]
[She's eating it for real.]
[Her mouth is really big.]
Mr. Fire-e.
You want me to sing, huh? Well...
Then I will sing
one of my favorite songs.
Good work today.
[Good work. Let's wrap it up.]
[I will go wash my ears.]
[It's time to leave.]
[Who asked her to sing?!]
- [I did a good job watching this today.]
- [I can't stand it anymore.]
Gosh, the viewers are leaving so fast.
I asked her to promote her image.
She's spending money
to make students hate her.
What do we do?
It's too sad to watch.
Gosh, she's done.
Professor Hwang,
call her to stop the broadcast.
- Turn off that thing too.
- Gosh.
Oh my, who is that?
Professor Hwang,
call her to stop the broadcast.
- Turn off that thing too.
- Gosh.
Oh my, who is that?
Director Kim.
- Isn't that Professor Jin?
- Oh my.
Yes, it is.
What happened?
Hello. I'm today's guest, Jin Jung Seok.
Yes...
Wow, there are so many replies
that I can't read them fast enough.
Ms. Ohora.
"Professor Jin has never
done live broadcasting before."
She asked what changed your mind.
Well, I heard Professor Park was on,
whom I work with for my joint class.
I decided to come on the program today.
Even if it was unfortunate
that she fainted in her class
she's a very talented teacher.
I hope all of you
come to her class next time.
- [Is she really talented?]
- Yes, she is talented.
When did you ever hear me lie?
That would be so tacky.
The topic for today is
that we will do anything you want.
What is it exactly that you want?
Mr. Okaysubari.
"Professor Jin
is famous for not smiling."
"Can you smile?"
Well, sure...
[Cute!]
[I will screenshot this!]
Oh my, what a response.
You have a decent smile,
Jin Jung Seok.
[Wow!]
[Cute!]
Ms. Heartbreaker wants you
to make a heart with your fingers.
Make a heart with fingers?
How do I do that?
We don't do that these days.
This is how.
[The best heart ever.]
[He's the best.]
Now send it away.
Wow, the number of viewers is going up.
201, 202...
Reached 220. Jackpot!
"There is a firework festival
in Yeouido tonight."
"Can you two go there
on our behalf and take photos?"
Well, about this favor...
I can totally do that alone.
Professor Jin is so busy and all...
I will do it if you guys want me to.
But if the number of viewers reaches 500
I will do what you ask then.
No way will it reach 500 viewers.
Good. Please spread the word.
What wouldn't I do to
promote Professor Park?
Mr. Maybe...
"Imagine you two are
in a club and dance away."
Ah, I can't do this one...
I'm good at many things.
But dance is one thing I can't do well.
Me neither.
[Hurry and dance.]
[You said you'd do anything.]
What should we do?
What do you mean?
I will not dance.
Am I drunk?
Am I dreaming now?
I agree.
Why didn't they do it sooner?
[Scream!]
[I feel like dancing!]
[I'm laughing too hard!]
[Am I watching an entertainment show?]
Wow, so many people are watching now.
[Are we studying to pass dance exams?]
[Professor Jin is the best dancer.]
[I'm falling off my chair!]
[You two will go see fireworks.]
[Oh yeah!]
[Come in. This your first time dancing?]
[Dancing queen!]
[Dance okay.]
[Professor Park's hair is pretty.]
[Fantastic couple.]
[Dancing god.]
[Want to edit dance scenes.]
[Continue to dance like that.]
[We only have a few left.]
Students, time is almost up.
I wonder if you had fun watching
us trying our best today.
I tried my best to do anything for you.
Please continue to
watch me do anything for you.
Students,
please support our Professor Park.
Plus, don't miss her class tomorrow.
- If you do, you will be in trouble.
- You will be in trouble.
Students, bye.
Bye.
Wow, the viewers reached 500
and then it ended.
They now have to keep their promise.
I agree. They should keep their promise.
I should go home.
Where do you think you're going?
You can't go.
Don't go.
- Don't leave yet.
- No way.
You know that I will
go home no matter what.
Are you happy that you
have to make it hard for me?
Let go!
- Let go!
- Don't.
I'm off, Director Kim.
How scared is he of his wife
to act that way, huh?
Is she scarier than my wife?
I don't think he's scared of her.
He does that because he just loves her.
What?
That's why he's doing
what she asks him to.
And he's all over her.
Wow, is that why?
His wife must be stunningly beautiful.
- You haven't met his wife yet?
- I haven't.
When I don't even want to see my wife
why would I want
to see someone else's wife?
Is that so?
I do want to see his wife once.
[Appointment time]
Gosh, I almost didn't make it.
- Hello.
Please go right in.
She seems to have been waiting all day.
Sure.
Wait, please help yourself.
Thank you.
He comes by every single day.
He's so devoted.
I agree.
[Patient: Kim Mee Kyung]
You're still up?
Have you been waiting for me?
Crazy punk.
Be quiet.
What are you two doing?
Can't you tell? We're building a wall.
When I was trying to focus
he was bothering me.
Are you kidding me?
You were bothering me more.
Hey, if you were going to build it
why wouldn't you
make it sturdy like mine?
What's with this?
How dare you destroy my fortress?
Hey.
Hey, you can't grab it.
I will grab yours.
- Be quiet.
- Hey.
Come with me now.
- Hey...
- Why did you do that?
- You could just talk to us.
Talking would work with you two, huh?
Ki Bum, you said you'd
make your grandma proud.
But you clean up and sleep during class.
You do other things at the study room.
If your grandma finds out all that
will she be so proud of you, huh?
- My grandma?
- Hey.
Gong Myung, I have no idea
what's going on with you.
You said now you had
a reason to pass the exams.
You've never had a goal all these years.
When you said you had a goal,
I thought you were serious.
- I guess I was wrong.
- No way.
I am serious about my goal.
Then come to your senses, punk.
You think it's easy to pass the exams?
You have to be
really desperate and study hard.
That's the basics.
If someone heard you now
they would think you've already passed.
- What, punk?
- Okay, I got it.
I understand.
- I will study hard.
- Me too.
Good then.
Wow, there is
a firework festival going on, huh?
Let's go study after we watch that.
It will be too noisy
to concentrate anyway.
Agreed. Let's go study after we watch it.
Fine. Go watch it.
Watch, you crazy punks.
- Where are you going?
- Let go of me.
I said, let go. Let me go!
Ah, there is Chae Yeon.
It's the first time I saw her smile.
- She really is pretty.
- I agree.
She really is pretty.
No, I was talking about the fireworks.
What are you looking at?
What's with you?
Now that you are in Noryangjin
you should only study.
I was about to go down anyway.
- Ouch.
- Sorry.
You really did a lot today.
If we weren't asked to take photos here
you could go home to relax.
It's okay.
- I should keep my promise.
- I agree.
By the way, I was shocked to see you.
I couldn't even imagine
that you'd come to help me.
You think I came to help you?
I showed up
to manage my joint class better.
If you lose any more students
it will bring down the quality
of my joint class as well.
I see.
Gosh, traffic is really bad, by the way.
At this rate,
the fireworks will be over soon.
It's not moving at all.
We have no choice.
Why don't we take
a photo over that bridge?
A photo to show we're here.
Here we go.
Students will see it, so please smile.
One, two, three.
It came out well.
I should post it.
If you're done taking photos, let's go.
Pardon? Just a photo and leave?
Since we're here, can we
stay and watch it a little bit?
Gosh, it's annoying.
Let's do that then.
Ah, wow.
It sure is pretty.
It would've been nice
for kids to watch this in person.
I should record this
and post it as a video file.
The kids will feel like they are here.
Gosh, it shook.
Seriously.
Good for that little kid.
From there, he can take good photos.
- Get on my back.
- Pardon?
Get on my back like that little kid.
No, it's okay.
You don't have to do that...
You think I'm doing this for you?
I'm doing this
to manage my joint class better.
Hurry.
Now, before I change my mind.
Gosh, I hope I will pass next year
so I can be with Joo Yeon
and watch it together.
We should watch this
with someone special.
I agree.
I want to watch it with someone I like.
I will go back to studying now.
Wait. Stop.
Come over here.
Professor Park and Jin took a photo
that shows they are here.
They came to watch the fireworks, huh?
What?
Students, are you seeing this?
I hope everyone who's
seeing this will pass the exams.
- Cheer up.
- Excuse me.
If you're done recording,
wrap up and come down.
I'm sorry. I will come down now.
Subtitles by DramaFever
How could I kiss such a woman?
How could I let that happen?
How can I face him tomorrow?
It meant nothing to me
as if a fly ran into a window.
I guess it bothered you a lot.
Don't you think he has feelings for you?
No way.
You two could become
the first couple who teaches civil exams.
You didn't have to come pick me up.
I'm doing this for my joint class.
This is for my joint class, not you.
- Why this wine place?
- I brought you here for my joint class.
- You, top beauty in Noryangjin.
- Why are you picking a fight?
If you're stuck up like that,
you will regret it some day.
I will witness you go down.
Like I hate cockroaches for no reason
I just hate you.
How come she doesn't know how to tell?
Gosh, she has bad eyesight.
- The top beauty in Noryangjin.
- Let's go to the police station.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who hates
me the most in Noryangjin.
- You said you'd put a curse on me.
- No.
It's not me.
It's someone who has a grudge
against you because you rejected him.
- I'm so hot right now.
- This jacket is bothering me.
When we get to Seoul,
you will go drink solo again, right?
Drink with me. I said drink with me.
- Pardon?
- It's for my joint class.
What's with the way you're looking at me?
If you cut your hands
while opening the shrimp
you won't be able to write on the board.
I'm not a leading actress in a TV drama.
He's being really nice to me.
If I don't notice that, I'm a moron.
I think I'm absolutely positive.
Even if it was an accident to you
it's good as long as I meant it.
You like me, don't you?