This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Drink]
[Episode 8]
Why is it so noisy in here?
Lower the volume!
People are going to think that
we're throwing a party here!
You're the one who was
out partying, though.
Wow.
What kind of relationship
do you have with her?
What do you mean?
We're just coworkers.
Oh, just coworkers, huh?
And yet you went on as a guest
on her show and danced
and even went to take a photo
in front of the fireworks with her?
You, the almighty Jin Jung Seok,
who doesn't care about others?
Tell me the truth. What kind of
relationship do you two have?
Hey. You...
You know that Professor Park is
part of my joint class, right?
But she was doing such tacky things today
that I had no choice to go and help her!
For the sake of maintaining
the quality of the joint class.
Really?
Are you telling the truth?
Yes! Geez!
I'm doing this for my sake
and for the sake of my joint class!
But... why do you care what kind
of relationship I have with her?
Huh?
Well, um...
What, I can't be curious
about my Big Bro's life?
Stop being curious about useless things
like that and channel that energy
to try and make something of
yourself in your otherwise dark future.
What is he talking about?
Looks like I got
scared for nothing
that something was actually
going on between them.
I thought us brothers would
become rivals in love or something.
Geez! If he was going to help her,
he should've danced better.
What's with these moves?
If he was going to dance, he should've
busted out cuter moves, like this!
Oh, it would've been great if
I'd been there with her instead!
How could I kiss such a woman?
How could the almighty Jin Jung Seok
lock lips with a woman like that?
Why?
[wiggler: Thank you so much!]
[notomorrow: Thank you!]
[letspass: I feel like studying now!]
[addictedtocoffee: Wow! This is awesome!]
Professor Jin really
helped me out a lot.
How am I supposed to
face him tomorrow?
Damn it, how could I let that happen?
Do you want to search
"how to make beef bone stock?"
What? This is no time to be
making beef bone stock!
What should I do about
my kiss with Professor Jin?
What do I do about this situation?
"Beef shank" is a cut of beef that
is found in the leg of a cow.
Why, I ought to...
If you were a human,
I would've smacked you for that!
Why are you going on and on
about cows?
Man, what do I do?
Are you crazy, Bear?
Get the hell away from me!
This is driving me crazy!
What do I do?
It's fine.
It was nothing,
Jin Jung Seok.
Oh, wait!
Um, Professor Jin.
I hope you don't feel uncomfortable due
to that little mishap from yesterday.
Yesterday?
What do you mean?
Well, yesterday,
the two of us kissed--
Um, I mean,
when our lips met by accident.
Oh... oh yeah! That happened! Oh, yes.
I'd completely forgotten about it.
It was so insignificant, you see.
It was kind of like seeing
a fruit fly running into a window.
A fruit... fly?
Well, I'm not implying that
you're a fruit fly, or anything.
I'm just saying that what
happened was that insignificant.
It seems that
it bothered you a lot, though.
What? Oh, not at all!
I'd forgotten about it as well,
and I just remembered when I saw you.
Yes.
All right.
I've heard that the best public
administration instructor teaches here.
Look, a crowd of students on
their way to take Mr. Min's class!
Oh my, what's this? They're overcome by
admiration as soon as they see him!
"VJs on the Scene," right?
Oh my, oh my,
oh my, oh my!
I'm touched that you
figured it out on the first try!
VJs on the Scene, my ass.
I wish I could call the cops on you.
Go to your seat already!
You're so annoying.
Oh yeah, Professor Park!
Good work on
your web broadcast yesterday.
But what was with Premium Trash?
He even came on the show for you?
Oh yeah! I was going to
ask her about that, but forgot.
That was incredible!
He even came
on the show and danced!
Who would've imagined it?
Maybe Premium Trash likes you?
What? No way!
He said he just helped me
to maintain his joint class's quality.
No. I think
he definitely has feelings for you.
At this rate, our academy might
end up with its first instructor couple!
Right?
If Professor Hwang is right,
I'm overflowing with excitement!
Overflowing with excitement!
I told you, it's nothing like that!
Stop it already, you two!
Seriously!
Professor Jin.
Who are you going to take to the special
lecture you're doing this weekend?
If you raise our brand awareness, we'll
have more people taking online classes.
How about bringing one of these three
as a way of promoting the joint class?
Yes, well... that's what
I was planning to do.
You really are the best.
Let one of these two go this
time instead, Professor Park.
He already helped you so much
with your web broadcast after all.
Of course. I wouldn't even
dream of going this time.
And I'm not worthy of doing
a special lecture either.
Oh, let me make our morning coffee.
Yeah.
Professor Jin!
You know that people have rated
my lectures quite highly, right?
Students just love me so much!
I think I'd do really well at giving
a special lecture with you.
No, I can do it better.
Just look.
They say that a public administration
instructor who's good at impersonations
has appeared in Jeolla-do.
And his name is
Min Jin Woong!
All types of students studying
for the public servant exams
have their eyes brimming with tears since
Professor Min's lectures are so funny!
You don't know the reference?
I'm impersonating "VJs on the Scene."
I do, but why should I care?
Man, how embarrassing.
Professor Min is overflowing with
humiliation because of Professor Jin!
Stop it already
with the overflowing!
Looks like everyone wants
to come with me no matter what.
Well, I'll decide that for myself,
thank you very much!
Speaking of which, why does No Geu Rae
not have any ambition whatsoever?
How is she going to last in Noryangjin
when she's so damn nice?
No. It'd be nice if a nice person did
well for themselves, though.
But it's awkward with her
because we kissed.
Why should I let her come with me?
Wait, no. I should show her that
people get rewarded for being nice.
Hmm, what should I do?
This is a serious error:
not using "had" with a past participle.
Remember that!
All right. That's the end
of today's lecture.
So make sure you put your hearts into
your dreams and head toward tomorrow!
All right?
- Yes.
- Good luck!
- Good work, everyone.
- Thank you!
Wow. She's always been sexy,
but she was super-sexy today!
I couldn't keep my eyes off her!
Ew, my eyes are rotting out!
Noyrangjin's Top Despicable Person!
What?
Why are you picking a fight?
Yeah!
Why are you trying to start something?
She hasn't done anything to you!
Hey, Jung Chae Yeon.
I heard you're really good at studying.
I heard that you were always
the best at every academy you went to.
Speaking of which
could you tutor me?
You crazy bastard!
Are you out of your damn mind?
How could you ask someone
like her to tutor you?
I have no interest in
doing that either!
Why, you ask? Because birds
of a feather flock together.
A friend of Kim Ki Bum
is no friend of mine.
Hey, I hate your guts too, all right?
I'm warning you! One of these days,
someone will knock you down a few pegs!
I can just tell by
seeing how you act!
You're the one who
started it first!
Thanks to you,
she's looking down on me too!
Hey, what do you have against
Jung Chae Yeon anyway?
Why do you hate her so much?
I just hate her, is all!
Like I hate cockroaches for no reason!
I just hate her too!
What's the matter, Jin Yi?
Did something happen?
No, it's nothing.
I'm totally fine.
As if.
She's upset that she's not going
with Professor Jin this weekend.
No, I'm not! Did you read
my mind or something?
Why are you talking about stuff
that you don't even know about?
Why are you getting mad at me?
I'm upset because I can't go either!
Neither of you are going?
Yeah.
You're the one who's going.
Me?
Yeah. Professor Jin said he might as
well go the extra mile to help you
since he helped you
with your web broadcast.
He said it's to maintain
the quality of the joint class.
Wow, you must be so happy,
Professor Park. Seriously.
Why me? I really didn't
have any intention of going.
What? It's good, isn't it?
Do your best, okay?
I hope you do well.
But do you think he keeps on
helping Professor Park
just to maintain the quality
of the joint class?
I think that Premium Trash
really must like you.
At this rate, you two may become a couple
just like Professor Hwang predicted.
- Right, Professor Hwang?
- I don't know.
I don't know, damn it!
If I was that good at predicting things,
I'd be Nostradamus, not Hwang Jin Yi!
Damn, you piss me off!
Ugh, I'm so pissed.
Wait, Jin Yi. I--
What's with her?
She definitely said that before.
I'm overflowing with anger too.
I'll drown myself in soju.
Bye!
- Goodbye.
- All right.
What's with him?
Does he really like me?
Shut up, you crazy girl.
Don't get started with that again.
You thought he did last time
and were totally humiliated for it.
Let's just get packed for
the trip this weekend.
Get it together!
Why are you hitting
my woman's face?
What did you say?
"My woman"?
Why, you little...
Are you just heading home now?
Oh, I'll walk you home
so you won't be bored.
You don't have the luxury of worrying
about me being bored right now.
Go and get some studying done.
Whoa. If you're telling me to go study,
you want me to hurry and pass
and become your boyfriend!
What'd you say?
Oh yeah, Teach. Why didn't you tell me
that you'd be doing the web broadcast?
I only saw it later on
and I was really disappointed!
Why? It was just to encourage you
to get more studying done.
Oh, so what you're saying is you
wanted me to not watch the program
and study hard so I can hurry
and become your boyfriend!
- You're just asking for a scolding!
- Ow!
Oh yeah, Professor.
Don't get too close to this guy.
What?
Something about his face irks me
and he seems like a real asshole.
So... don't get too
close to him, okay?
Geez.
There's nothing to worry about.
He's the best of the best in Noryangjin.
He's on a completely different
plane of existence than I am.
Oh, it's here!
I'll get going then.
Get home safe, Professor!
I'm really going to pass!
Just wait for me!
The hell are you looking at?
You really are an asshole,
just like your name says.
Well, look who it is!
It's Noryangjin's Top Despicable Person!
If you came all the way to Noryangjin
to study, you should be studying.
So why do you have a jump rope?
Don't you know that keeping fit is
the most important thing for studying?
Get out of my way.
Why, you--
Watch your back.
Seriously.
"Don't you know that keeping fit is
the most important thing for studying?"
All right. I've done enough prepping
for the special lecture today.
Oh yeah. What should I wear?
No, this is boring.
The most refined look that
I can pull out of this closet is...
What?
Don't get it wrong, okay?
I'm doing this to look good in front of
the students, not Professor Jin!
[Premium Trash]
Yes, Professor Jin?
What?
Where did you say you were?
You didn't have to
come pick me up.
What if you were late because
you took public transportation?
That would definitely tarnish
the image of my joint class.
I only came to get you to
maintain the quality of my joint class.
I didn't do it for you.
I see.
Wow, what a nice view!
I just wanted you to get a proper look
at the view since you're so into it.
Thank you! You even took
the top down for me!
It wasn't for you.
It was for my joint class.
You'll give a better lecture
if you relax while taking in the view.
It was just to maintain
the quality of my joint class.
I see.
Wow, it's Wine Cave!
So it is around here, huh?
- Wine Cave?
- Yes.
I saw it on TV. There's a wine cellar in
the cave and you can take photos there.
It's really nice.
Don't you want to go
since you're interested in alcohol too?
No. I hate crowded places.
You didn't come with me
to have fun, you know.
Just focus on giving a good lecture!
Don't worry. I really did my best
when planning this lecture.
I want you to see me
giving a good lecture.
Oh, I shouldn't be doing this.
I should review my materials.
What? The special lecture
for today is canceled?
We have a problem with
the electricity at our academy today
so they're doing some
emergency construction.
That's why it's canceled.
Then you should've contacted us sooner!
How could you handle this
situation in such a lackluster way?
My time is money, you know!
I'm Jin Jung Seok!
Yes, I know, sir. That's why I definitely
told the director in Seoul to tell you.
I guess he forgot.
- Director?
- Be right there!
I'm sorry.
Just a moment.
Ugh, seriously?
I'll go and give that director an earful,
so don't worry too much.
I'll make sure we get compensated for
wasting a day here no matter what.
That's not it.
It's just that I put a lot
into planning my lesson.
I just feel a bit disappointed
because of that.
I really did give it my all.
[Have a heart, please! Don't stow
away all the food in your rooms!]
[You all are future public servants!
You need to have a sense of justice!]
- Oh, my back.
- Did you study a lot?
Oh, I don't know.
Oh yeah. Did you see this photo?
Yeah. I saw it on the study forum.
It's spread like wildfire online.
Wow, I can't believe it. Who'd do
this to Noryangjin's Top Beauty?
Right? Seriously.
What's that?
Here, look.
Isn't this insane?
Isn't this Jung Chae Yeon?
So someone put this on Godeung,
but others spread it elsewhere.
Godeung? Oh, you mean that site
where they upload upskirt shots of girls?
But who'd upload this?
Look here, at the title.
"This is my revenge against
Jung Chae Yeon, who rejected me."
"You told me to study if I came
all the way to Noryangjin to do so."
"You came here to study too, but how
about giving Internet stardom a shot?"
It's clear that someone who got
rejected big-time by her did this.
So who is it, exactly?
There's a whole ton of guys
who got dumped by her!
But anyway, I wonder if
Chae Yeon knows about this.
She'll be totally shocked
if she finds out.
Shouldn't we let her know
and report this?
What is it?
What are you talking
about exactly?
- Um, nothing.
- Nothing.
What is it?
- Hey...
- No!
What the hell is this?
Why are we here
at Wine Cave?
It seemed that you were disappointed
because your lecture got canceled
so I brought you here
to cheer you up.
And it seemed like you wanted
to visit this place too.
What?
If you stay disappointed,
you'll be in a bad mood.
And if you do, you'll bring down
the mood of the entire joint class.
So get in a better mood
and lecture well.
Thank you! You're going to
such lengths for me?
Who said that
I'm doing this for you?
I'm doing this
for the sake of my joint class!
I brought you here to maintain
the quality of my joint class!
Well, either way, thank you!
She's that happy over it?
Geez.
She's so tacky.
Whoa!
This is so cool!
But why do they have
a wine cellar in a cave?
It's best to keep wine between
10 to 14 degrees Celsius
and a cave maintains that
temperature 365 days of the year.
Wow, there's nothing that
you don't know, Professor Jin!
Yes. I'm fascinated by
that fact as well.
It's kind of cold in here.
I guess because it's a cave.
Here.
Put it on.
- Um, what?
- I'm quite hot!
Wearing this jacket is bothering me,
so wear this in my stead.
- Is... that okay?
- It's fine if you don't want to.
Wait, no!
Geez. You're so frustrating.
Make sure you button
it up too, okay?
Thank you.
You think I'm doing this for you?
This is all
for the sake of my joint class!
If you catch a cold
and keep sniffling
the quality of your
lecture may go down!
This is all for the sake of maintaining
the quality of my joint class.
Got that?
Okay.
Oh, it's cold.
Let's go.
I wonder if Jung Chae Yeon
reported this to the authorities?
What's she going to do?
I bet she's really shocked.
Hey, Kim Ki Bum!
Give me your phone.
My phone? Why?
It was you, wasn't it?
I knew it was you,
you evil bastard.
What are you talking about?
You're the one who took those photos
and videos of me and put them online!
Are you out of your damn mind?
What are you talking about?
I looked at the metadata to see
what phone took those photos.
Figures. You're stupid, so you
probably didn't even know about this.
But you know, the phone that took these
photos is the same model as yours!
You think that I'm the only one
with a Samsung phone?
You seriously think
I'm the only one with this model?
Hey, hey.
Calm down, Chae Yeon.
You two may be on bad terms, but it's
not so bad that he'd do this to you.
Yeah. The guy who did this has a huge
grudge because you rejected him.
It's definitely not Ki Bum.
That's why it has to be him.
I did reject him once, big-time.
[One Year Ago]
Hey, Noryangjin's Top Beauty!
Wait up.
Take this.
What's with him?
That looked like it hurt.
Does it not hurt?
So he was doing this
instead of taking the exam?
What a disgrace.
If he came all the way to Noryangjin,
he should focus on studying.
Damn it.
Why hasn't she responded?
Hey, did you see
the post on the forum?
What are you talking about?
It's the top post there right now.
Here, look.
Here. "The Love of a Noryangjin Idiot."
"The Love of a Noryangjin Idiot"?
It's so funny.
Look.
"Hi, Jung Chae Yeon. I keep thinking
about you, so I can't study good (sic)."
"You're making such quickly (sic)
progression in your studying, though."
"I wonder if it's okay
for me to like you"
"but I'm actually quite a good
guy once you get to know me."
"I'm not a (sic) old-fashion (sic)
type of guy, either."
"I want to become your boyfriend."
"I'll always make you smile.
I'll be sure to keep this promise."
"A man's world (sic)
is as good as his bond, after all."
"I'll be waiting for your response then.
Don't keep me waiting too long."
"No, this isn't the time for me to
be bossy (sic) people around."
"Just don't reject me, please."
"Naver! (sic)"
Isn't this so funny?
This is the funniest part, though.
"A man's world (sic)
is as good as his bond, after all."
How could anyone make
this kind of mistake?
I mean, what is he even saying here?
Well, come on. That's a mistake
that anyone could've made.
What are you talking about? This idiot
lives somewhere in Noryangjin, though.
- I really want to meet him just once!
- I know, right?
What a freaking idiot!
Hey, Jung Chae Yeon!
You and I need to talk.
What do you want?
Ew, you reek of alcohol!
Did you drink?
Yeah. I did. What, the Idiot of
Noryangjin isn't allowed to drink?
- What?
- How could you upload my letter online?
It's all over the web now!
My feelings of true love are now in
the running for a prize in "Best Humor"!
Hey, I didn't upload that.
I guess someone took what
I threw away and put it online--
You threw it in the trash?
In the trash?
How could you trample all
over my feelings like that?
What's wrong with me?
Why do you hate me so much?
I just do! Just like how people
naturally don't like roaches!
Evil girl.
I'll hate you forever!
I'll curse you forever!
Sure. Whatever.
At any rate, sorry for making you
become Noryangjin's Idiot.
If you're sorry, then keep this a secret.
Keep the fact that I gave you
a love letter, got rejected
and became Noryangjin's Idiot a secret!
Keep all of this a secret!
If you don't...
I'll feel way too humiliated!
All right, already.
If you came all the way to Noryangjin,
stop doing such stupid things
and study so that you'll pass the exam.
Hey.
I didn't make all those grammatical
mistakes because my grammar sucks!
I just made those mistakes
on purpose to make you laugh!
Okay, it's true that I didn't know
the "a man's word" idiom.
Happy?
Then you were Noryangjin's Idiot?
Keep the secret.
I had feelings for you
and wrote you letters.
I was rejected.
I became Noryangjin's Idiot.
Keep all of this a secret!
If you don't...
I'll feel way too humiliated!
Still it's not you?
You're the one who hates
me the most in Noryangjin.
You said you'd hate me
for the rest of your life.
You said you'd put a curse on me.
Only a few days ago, you said
you'd watch me go down.
No. I'm saying it's not me.
Agreed. When you're not positive
you can't just go at him like that.
This was taken right after
we ran into each other.
He was the only one I saw that night.
Will you still deny it?
Why not look into my phone folder?
Take a look to see
if I have your photos or not.
What is it?
Gosh, this punk has narcissistic
photos of himself only.
I agree.
There aren't any of your photos here.
I'm sure he's already deleted them all.
If you were him, would you
have left clear evidence like that?
Let's go to the police station.
If they restore all the deleted photos,
the truth will come out.
I said, it wasn't me.
I didn't do it.
Watch me.
I will find the evidence.
What?
Oh my god!
Director Kim.
Professor Min, there you are.
Have a seat.
I was surprised that you asked
me out here out of the blue.
By the way,
why hiking suddenly?
It's the weekend and all.
I just didn't want to stay home.
As you already know,
my in-laws are living with me.
My in-laws helped me start the academy.
So they've been bossing me around.
It's the weekend and all,
so I just wanted to relax.
They were asking me questions
about the profits and all.
I just had enough.
I see.
We were watching TV on the sofa.
Some funny scene came on
and I started to laugh.
Then they asked if I could laugh
when the academy isn't doing well.
So they started grilling me on and on.
Shouldn't we relax on weekends?
If they grill me about work
even on weekends
what am I supposed to do, huh?
Gosh, it sucks big time.
Oh my, it must have been hard.
No matter how often I talk about this
you will never know how I feel.
I have to work on weekends.
Gosh, I feel suffocated.
Let's hike, shall we?
Wow, I feel alive now that
my in-laws are not grilling me.
We should take a break
on weekends like this.
Why would they talk about work
even on weekends, huh?
- I agree.
- By the way
how come you're not
impersonating anyone today?
"Now that we're hiking,
my sweat is overflowing!"
"Endorphins are overflowing!"
Don't you do anything like that?
I have no lecture today.
I should take a break on weekends too.
I should take it easy on my throat too.
Wow, someone might think
you're such a popular instructor.
You know that only 50 students signed up
to take your class this month, right?
It's not the time
to take it easy on your throat.
What are you doing? Let's go.
Director Kim.
Will you climb up to the top?
I haven't hiked
for a while, so...
I'm already feeling so exhausted.
If I wait here for you,
I would be bothering you less.
- Professor Min, that's your problem.
- What?
You don't ever seem
desperate to achieve anything.
When you don't have
many students signing up
you don't seem to bother
trying to increase the number.
I guess
you're at peace with the situation.
But as your employer,
I'm having a hard time.
Please be desperate, please.
I'm done taking a break.
Let's climb to the top.
That's right.
If you had done so from the beginning,
wouldn't I have been happier?
As I already told you
because of my in-laws who talk
about work even on weekends
I'm so stressed out.
No matter how often I talk about this
you will never know how I feel.
I work even on weekends.
Gosh, I will never know for sure.
Director Kim.
Wow, this tastes so good.
What language is this?
How should I read it?
It looks like Spanish.
I see.
It means "red roses" in Spanish.
Red roses?
That's really amazing.
Professor Jin, have some.
I have to drive.
- You can drink for me instead.
- Okay.
I usually like eating junk food,
chocolate, candy, and anything sweet.
Strangely, I don't like sweet wine.
I'm the same way.
Rather than sweet sparkling
wine or white wine
dry red wine is more for my taste.
Wow, me too!
What's with this tacky gesture?
Wow, this tastes really good.
Should I buy one bottle?
- What's wrong?
- No, it's too expensive.
I will get it
when I celebrate something special.
I will go to the bathroom.
What was that?
Was she shocked by a mere 30,000?
She may faint again if she sees
wine that costs 300,000 then.
So tacky, gosh.
Here.
I don't know
what you will be celebrating.
But drink it when you get to.
Wow, thank you.
You got it for me?
I didn't get it for you.
It's all for my joint class.
If you keep regretting not buying
the wine when you get to Seoul
you will have a hard time
focusing on your lecture.
This is to manage my joint class better.
Professor Jin.
Here.
When we get to Seoul,
you'll go drink solo again, won't you?
Can't you come with me to drink?
I want to take you out for a drink.
- Why should you?
- It's just that
I want to thank you for a lot of things.
It's for our joint class, not for you.
I mean... after you've done a lot for me
you will feel less appreciated
if I don't take you out.
Then it will affect the teamwork
of our joint class.
To manage our joint class better...
After you've done a lot for me
you will feel less appreciated
if I don't take you out.
Then it will affect the teamwork
of our joint class.
To manage our joint class better...
Nothing. Just forget I said anything.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go get a drink.
- What?
- I said let's go get a drink.
You actually have a good point.
What's happening to him?
Gosh, you've hated
Chae Yeon all these years.
I can't believe it all came out.
Hey, how can you say that now?
I've been accused of
recording her secretly.
Gosh, how can I prove my innocence?
What's up with you?
What's with the way you're looking at me?
Well, actually...
I loved reading
"The Love of a Noryangjin Idiot."
I really wanted
to meet that fool.
I can't believe it was you, my friend,
who's been hanging out with me.
What do you call this?
You know, the feeling that I became
close to a celebrity and such.
Crazy punk.
Stop teasing me.
Don't tell me what to do.
You punk, seriously.
You believe I'm innocent, right?
I didn't do it. It really wasn't me.
Sure, if a man says
he didn't do it, he didn't do it.
A man's word is as good as a bond.
You punk, seriously!
I'm sorry. I will not tease you again.
Naver!
Do you want to die? Come here!
You bastard!
Hey, you two. Stop it already.
I have to take an online class.
What are you looking at, creeps?
Gosh, don't worry about it.
Now that I'm in Noryangjin,
I should just study.
I should just pass
the exams as soon as possible.
And leave this place.
Jung Chae Yeon, are you feeling better?
- Did you report the incident?
- Never mind.
It's understandable that you're on edge.
You!
It's you who posted the photos, isn't it?
Who are you?
Hi, Jung Chae Yeon.
If you're free this weekend,
want to have dinner with me?
Wow, it was very good for my soul to
climb the mountain on the weekend.
- Wasn't it?
- Agreed. I liked it.
It's weird. Why can't I see
the chicken neck in here?
What? I already ate it.
What?
Damn it. It was my favorite part.
Ah, was it really?
I wanted you to have
better parts like the chicken legs.
- That's, again, your problem.
- What?
How long have we been working together?
You still don't know that
I like chicken neck?
How can you be
that slow on the uptake?
Figures, since you don't seem
to be bothered by the fact
that your classes have low numbers
and you impersonate celebrities.
Gosh, that's your talent in a way.
What?
How can you say that?
What? What did I say? What?
Damn it. Couldn't you try
to please me at least today?
What did I say?
Because of my in-laws who talk
about work even on weekends
I said I was so stressed out, didn't I?
Well, how are you supposed to know
the feeling that you have
to work on weekends?
I do know what it's like.
Now I really know
exactly what it feels like.
I'm upset that my tears are overflowing.
My sadness is overflowing.
What's that? You said you didn't
impersonate on weekends.
It's my weekend too.
I felt like I was working this weekend.
So my impersonation just came out.
My apologies.
Let me pour you one.
What is it now?
Why did the alarm go off?
It's not even 10:00 p.m. yet.
I should go home earlier on weekends.
- My wife is waiting for me.
- What?
Wait, Professor Min.
Pour me some first! Hey!
Hey, Professor Min!
Do you like your wife that much?
Damn it.
Gosh, I'm so lonely. So lonely.
Cheers.
It's good.
This is an honor.
I get to drink with you,
who always drinks solo.
Honestly, I like drinking solo, like you.
I saw your photos of drinking
alone at home on Instagram.
Did you?
I get tired from giving lectures all day.
I couldn't love it more
that I drink beer alone.
I don't have to talk any more.
I don't have to hear others
talking about unnecessary stuff.
I don't have to worry about others
and can pick the dish I like.
I can enjoy a time just
for myself. A time of healing.
Wow, we sure think alike.
But I'm not
a master of drinking like you.
- I'm a master?
- Yes.
I can drink alone at home just fine.
But I don't think I can
drink alone at a restaurant.
I'm afraid people will stare at me
and wonder why I'm drinking alone.
Why does it matter what others think?
Our lives are too short
to focus on ourselves.
From now on, I will learn a lot from you,
a master of drinking solo.
Drinking solo is good
but isn't
drinking with someone good too?
I like it.
What's with
the tacky way of looking at me?
It was for my joint class.
If your fingers get hurt
while opening the shrimp
you won't be able to write on the board.
I did that
to manage my joint class better.
Our guess was right.
He was a fellow student
who was rejected by you and got mad.
And he committed that crime.
You must have gone through a lot.
But now we've caught the culprit.
I hear there are companies
that delete unwanted photos.
If you hire them,
they will get rid of the photos.
Hey, what's wrong?
You've been tough all this time.
Now everything is over. Why now?
I don't know.
I guess it's overwhelming now.
Honestly, I was really scared.
And I'm still scared.
I have to continue to study.
I have to pass the exam.
What should I do now
when I'm still this scared?
You seemed like such a tough girl.
Now you're more approachable.
Get up.
Stop. Stop crying.
Now go easy on the guys.
As you already know
when studying for exams,
it's a hard life and we're lonely.
Why should you hurt their feelings
when they're already struggling?
If I start dating
and do many other things here
how am I supposed to pass?
Agreed. You're right about that.
But you can still find
a softer way to say no to them.
"Oh, sweetie."
"You should study only
now that you're in Noryangjin."
- Like that?
- What?
I will pass.
Just listen to me, will you?
It's a scary world.
There are a lot of psychopaths.
You need to be careful.
Thank you anyway.
I will never forget what you did for me.
It's okay to forget what I did for you.
Just apologize to Ki Bum.
Let's go.
Really? You've caught the culprit?
Wow, good job, Jin Gong Myung.
Thanks to you, I cleared my name.
You're my best friend, after all.
All right then.
She suspected that I was the one?
I will hate her for the rest of my life.
Bad luck, Jung Chae Yeon.
Hey, Jung Chae Yeon has smoking legs.
Her breasts aren't
as big as I imagined though.
But her face makes up for it.
Honestly, I wish they would never
catch the one who did that.
That way, we can see more photos of her.
I sent all my friends the photos of her.
They all loved them.
You don't have to say.
The guys are all over it
even in my chat room.
You trash!
It's a crime
that someone took those photos.
It's also a crime to send them around.
Delete them all when I ask nicely.
- Who are you?
- Who am I?
I'm a future civil servant, you losers!
You should study only
now that you're in Noryangjin.
[Patient: Kim Mee Kyung]
I'm here.
You don't know who I am?
Mom.
I come by every day to see you.
How can you not recognize me?
Look at me.
I'm your son, Jin Woong.
Ta-da.
And these are your favorite flowers,
chrysanthemums.
These are chrysanthemums.
Aren't they pretty?
Where is my daughter-in-law?
I miss my daughter-in-law.
Mom, don't you remember?
I got a divorce.
No, it's not a good thing to remember.
It's better not to remember that.
Don't you agree?
Mom.
Lie down on your back.
I will massage your legs.
Easy. Easy.
Your legs, please.
I didn't know how much
I'd enjoy drinking with him.
By the way, what's up with him?
Why is he so nice to me?
"It's to manage our joint class better."
He keeps saying that.
Is it okay to be this nice to me?
I hope everyone who's watching
these fireworks will pass the exam.
Make sure you button
it up too, okay?
Here.
I don't know what you will celebrate.
But drink it when you get to.
Seriously?
Like Jin Yi and Professor Min said
does he have feelings for me?
That's right.
I'm not a leading actress in a TV drama.
I'd be a fool not to notice
when he's that nice to me.
I'm positive.
I like drinking solo.
A drink you enjoy
at the end of a tough day
is like a spell that makes us
forget the bad things.
If I drink solo,
it can heal my wound.
It makes me feel
like I have a friend
who will comfort my sorrow without words.
Why bother going home early?
I will have nothing to hear
but my in-laws nagging.
Gosh, none of my family calls
to check up on me until this hour.
Why would they need me anyway?
When you have no one
to lean on in your everyday life
You might be comforted to think
drinking solo feels like
you have a good friend.
That's why I like drinking solo.
But why am I drinking
with that woman today?
Sorry.
I should pull myself together.
I ended up kissing you
by accident last time.
It's okay to make the same mistake again.
Sorry.
I should pull myself together.
I ended up kissing you
by accident last time.
It's okay to make the same mistake again.
What?
Even if it was an accident to you
it's good as long as I meant it.
No Geu Rae.
Look, No Geu Rae.
What was that?
Why did you lift your head that way?
I just had a stiff neck...
I can take your girlfriend
to her place first, right?
She's not my girlfriend.
By the way, how come you
don't have a girlfriend yet?
What do you mean?
When my mind is elsewhere,
how can I focus on my work?
No Geu Rae, you should keep this in mind.
While you're in my joint class
you're not allowed to date anyone.
Come to think of it
you were so upset
when you thought I had a boyfriend.
You said something and got angry.
Can you be honest with me?
You were jealous, weren't you?
What? How jealous?
I was only managing my joint class--
It wasn't to manage your joint class.
You were trying to manage
the woman you liked, no?
- What did you say?
- All day today you were trying
to care for me again.
You like me, don't you?
Such nonsense... no way.
If you are going to say such stuff
why don't you get out here?
See? You're stuttering.
You're saying what you don't really mean.
That's why you're stuttering.
You like me. Isn't that right?
Is that what you really think?
Professor Jin,
why are you doing this? Why?
You're drunk and seem out of your mind.
Get some fresh air
and come to your senses.
Professor Jin. Professor Jin.
Professor Jin.
What just happened?
It's ridiculous.
How dare she gets me wrong like that?
I'd understand if I did
something to lead her on.
What did I ever do to her?
Why is she having such
a ridiculous dream? Oh my gosh.
I'm the top lecturer in the country,
Jin Jung Seok.
I like No Geu Rae?
He told me to drink it
when I have something to celebrate.
I'm drinking this on such a special day.
I'm drinking this
when I was humiliated...
and got dumped.
Crazy, why did I do that?
Where did I get such confidence?
What did I possibly
want to hear from him?
Him saying that he likes me?
Maybe I'm the one who likes him...
Do I like him?
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Let's Drink]
She's gone crazy.
No Geu Rae is really out of her mind.
"You like me, don't you?"
Gosh, the more I think about it,
the more baffled I get.
How can I face him?
Should I tell him that I was drunk
and it came out as a joke?
Should I pretend that I don't remember?
Professor.
- How did you do on your exam?
- Are you curious?
You want me to pass the exam
and become your boyfriend?
Stop kidding around.
Because I let you talk to me that way
you might have forgotten
that I'm your teacher.
Dong Young, you did a good job.
Congratulations,
nine-level civil servant, Kim Dong Young.
What congratulations?
I will go pack up since I have no hope.
Why is his score getting lower and lower?
- Good for you.
- I'm sure you did well on the mock exam.
It's my goal to get out of Noryangjin
no matter what I have to do to pass.
Since we're on that topic
can you teach me how to study?
I will teach you from now on.
Hey, Jin Gong Myung.
Is he dozing off?
I will have to face Professor Jin today.
I'm on my way to hell,
seriously, not to work.
Hey, you're here, Professor Jin.
Do you want to go on a blind date?
I found the woman who can
measure up to your high standards.
What's wrong? Don't want to?
Yes, I'd love to go on that date.
Why would I say no to such a woman?
Why not today?