Subtitles by DramaFever
Episode 3
Let us go.
Why are you acting like this
over some damn urn?
You don't even appreciate her
raising you all this time
and you're lying
and trying to alienate her?
I never should have raised
someone else's child.
Everything will be fine
once you're gone.
I'm... not your real daughter?
You're someone that your mother
had with another man!
All right.
I'll make the special announcement
from the Chairman now.
Ms. Eun Ha Won will be living here at
Sky House with you all, starting today.
What?
She's going to live here?
Really? For real?
Why, though?
Ridiculous.
When you said "everyone" before,
does that include Kang Ji Woon?
Yeah.
Ridiculous.
Why bring back someone
who said he didn't want to live here?
It also doesn't make sense
to force a playboy and his fiancée
into the same house.
There you two go again.
This is something that
the Chairman decided.
Wow, this is ridiculous.
How are we supposed to live with a girl?
It'll be so uncomfortable!
What is Grandpa thinking?
Well, I'm sure he has a plan.
- But he might not.
- He doesn't.
But, there's just one rule.
Dating is forbidden within Sky House.
What do you mean by that?
Isn't she Kang Hyun Min's girlfriend?
So, what do you mean, "no dating"?
It's not like Kang Hyun Min
has only one girlfriend.
Well, duh.
Actually, Hyun Min and Ms. Ha Won--
Yoon Sung!
Wait! Come with me.
What are you doing?
Let's be honest with everyone.
Wait, wait!
I thought you said
we're forbidden to date her.
Think about it carefully.
Wouldn't it be safer if we just let them
believe that she's my fiancée?
Just look at them.
Don't you know that they'd go crazy
for anything in a dress?
Isn't that you?
You don't know it, do you?
Those punks are no joke.
Let's reveal the truth.
Come on, Yoon Sung!
Can you just go along with it?
I promise I can stop all of them
from breaking the rule!
If anything should still happen,
I'll give up all my credit cards. Deal?
You'd better uphold
your end of that promise.
Of course I will!
Hurry, let's go!
Where's Ji Woon?
He left. You know how he is.
At any rate, as long as
Ms. Ha Won is here
dating within Sky House
is strictly forbidden.
Does that mean you have to
break up with her?
I'm an exemption.
You're the most dangerous one of all.
You in particular... be careful.
You heard him, right?
I'm an exception. Ex-cep-tion!
Mom, stay here for just a bit.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry. I'll be just fine here
until Dad isn't mad anymore.
You've now chosen to live
as Kang Ji Woon.
It wasn't a choice.
It was coercion.
But you know, I only came here
because there's something I want to know.
Why are you trying so hard
to get rid of "Han Ji Woon"?
What sort of man was my father
that he abandoned my mother and myself?
And why I was forced
to live as Han Ji Woon!
I need to find all of this out
for myself.
Sure, try and find out for yourself.
However, as long as
you live under this roof
don't you dare
oppose the Chairman's will
Why is there such a big dining room table
when only three people live here?
Who are you?
Oh, um... I was hungry.
If you're a newcomer, you should've
come and said hello first.
Why are you sneaking around
like a stray cat?
Geez, things have really gone downhill
around here ever since Butler Kim left!
I'm sorry.
So, child, what's your name?
How old are you?
My name is Eun Ha Won,
and I'm twenty years old.
Call me Ms. Beolgyo.
Because I'm from Beolgyo, in the south.
Do you know where that is?
Um, yes!
- It's famous for blood cockles.
- Yes.
You'll have a hard time
if the young masters see you here.
Follow me.
Why are you so slow?
Did you eat a turtle or something?
Hurry up!
Um, where are we going?
Shush! I told you, we'll be
in trouble if we're caught!
All right, you can stay here from now on
so don't you dare move,
and just stay here!
Honestly, I like this place better!
Of course you do.
I'll bet you love it!
Why are you here, Miss?
Mister!
Oh, have you two
already been introduced?
This is the youngest one
working with us now--
She's not here to work.
What? What are you talking about?
She's the Chairman's special guest.
Please mind your manners.
What? The Chairman's special guest?
Oh my, forgive me!
Oh, it's okay!
I'm just here as a part-timer.
I'm not a special guest!
Oh my, it seems like
I've made a terrible mistake.
Please forgive me.
You should've said
something sooner, Miss!
Let us go.
It's really okay.
Don't worry too much, okay?
Bye!
Goodbye, Miss!
What the heck?
Weren't you being a bit much?
She's a lot older than me, too!
And yet, you were all like,
"please mind your manners."
That's not very nice!
All the employees in this estate
must serve you with respect.
I'm just a fellow employee!
So people don't need to
give me special treatment--
It's the Chairman's command.
But still, she's much older than I am--
But still, it's not polite!
It's the Chairman's command.
You haven't eaten yet?
Wow!
Thank you for the meal!
Oh.
Would you like some, too?
What is it?
Hey, we're still "engaged," okay?
Stop talking crap.
Hey, you're so fearless as the only girl
living in a house full of guys.
It'll be safer for you
to live here as my fiancée.
How about you just back off?
Are you going to tell everyone
that you put on that act for money?
It doesn't matter. That is what I chose
to do back then, anyway.
Also, didn't you hear what
Mister said before?
Dating is forbidden!
I'm not asking you to date me.
Just pretend like you're my fiancée.
And why do you need me
to do that, exactly?
Is this because I never
paid you for last time?
Want me to pay more?
I told you, I don't need your money!
Then you're doing it for free?
Did you manage to fall for me
in this short amount of time?
Put your hands up.
Okay.
Higher.
Even higher.
Put your hands up.
Okay.
Higher.
Even higher.
I said I'll protect you.
And I... told you not to talk crap.
Hey! Thanks, girlfriend!
How much money did you get this time?
Kang Ji Woon, that jerk!
Kang Seo Woo makes me
feel at ease, though.
But Kang Hyun Min is...
Ugh, that playboy!
From this point on, dating within
Sky House is strictly forbidden.
Keep in mind that dating within
the house can get you kicked out.
It's not like I'm crazy!
Why would I ever date any of them?
Let's continue walking
our own paths, huh?
And not be a nuisance to each other.
What are you doing?
I thought you said
you weren't coming back.
Let's try to see as little
of each other as possible.
That's what I want, too.
Honestly, I'd love it
if you would just ignore me.
But seriously, why did you come back?
Mind your own business.
It hasn't changed a bit.
But seriously, why did you come back?
And I have to find out why
I was forced to live as Han Ji Woon!
Sheesh! Ow!
Ow, my head! My head.
That's right. I slept here last night.
Good morning, National Jackpot Girl!
Did anything happen after yesterday?
I moved into Sky House.
I'll tell you everything later.
Wow! That's insane!
Send me a pic! Send me a pic!
A photo?
One, two, three.
What the heck?
You can totally see into my room!
What the heck!
And what about...
Oh my gosh!
What the heck?
Who is that?
Girlfriend! I'm not exactly
appropriately dressed right now.
I understand that you want to see me,
but let's see each other later!
That's... his room?
My room... what the hell?
They're so close!
You can see straight into my room!
Oh no!
Then, whose room is that over there?
Who is it?
Why are you looking into
someone else's room?
Um, it's not like that...
Then get lost.
This is... my room.
This is Kang Hyun Min's room.
This is Kang Ji Woon's room.
What? I'm surrounded on all sides!
Put the vegetables and other things
like that on top, and the seafood...
Wow. This is crazy.
Why aren't you eating?
I feel kind of bad,
eating before anyone else.
Don't worry and eat.
None of them will come.
Why not?
Because the three of them have
yet to sit down for a meal together.
Not even once?
What do you do with all of this, then?
We have our way of taking care of it.
Wow, what a waste!
So eat to your heart's content.
It's the Chairman.
Aloha!
Hello, Chairman!
So, how was your first night
at Sky House?
Um, I'm not sure yet.
I see. All right, then.
Try eating with all of them together.
What?
Eat with them?
That's your first mission.
Well, I'll be in touch! Aloha!
[Contract]
What is this?
It's a contract that
the Chairman had prepared.
A... contract?
Yes. I'll explain it to you briefly.
You'll be provided with a bonus
every time you successfully complete
one of the Chairman's missions.
A bonus?
Yes.
The reward will be proportional
to the difficulty of the mission.
- What?
- But if you fail the mission
you must leave Sky House.
Oh.
And as I told you yesterday,
dating is strictly forbidden.
All you have to do is refrain
from dating anyone.
All right.
- Oh, about her...
- Huh?
About that girl, Ha Won...
I'm sure she won't last a week
and crawl back here.
Don't you dare let her back in.
Of course not!
But, um... Honey.
Did your past wife
really cheat on you, and...
Don't ever bring that up again!
Oh, okay. Sure.
Yoo Na!
Dad's leaving!
It's fine. Don't wake her up.
This time, I'm working on constructing
an apartment, so it may take a while.
I'll call you later.
All right.
Be careful!
Yes.
Oh, are you calling
because you saw the flyer?
[Looking for Mr. Kang Young Jin,
who lived at Yeongak Apartment, Unit 308]
You used to live at Yeongak
Apartment ten years ago?
Did you know Mr. Kang Young Jin,
who lived in Unit 308?
Yes! He used to be a Taekwondo Master.
Do you know him?
Yes! Yes!
Where are you now?
Haneul Group...
Wait, Haneul Group?
What are you doing?
Who is this?
Is it all right if I take
Ms. Eun Ha Won's belongings?
Please, have some tea.
No, thank you.
Oh... all right.
But, um, how did our Ha Won
get to live at Sky House?
She received an invitation to do so
from Chairman Kang Jong Du.
She was invited... by the chairman?
- But, why?
- You mean, that girl, Eun Ha Won did?
I'll fill you in on the details
at a later time.
I'll be taking my leave now.
Wait, already?
Wait. Yoo Na!
Give him a proper farewell.
He's the General Secretary
for Haneul Group!
Oh. Goodbye!
Oh, yes. Did her father go somewhere?
I feel like I'm doing some really
important work or something!
Shall I get started now, then?
What's so hard about getting them
to eat a meal together?
Yeah!
How is there not a single
family photo in such a huge house?
Hey, Ms. Celebrity!
I picked this up at the hotel.
Oh, really?
I was looking for this
for a really long time!
Wow!
But, did something happen last night?
Why?
You seemed like you were crying...
Oh... I wasn't crying.
It's just because
I got caught in the rain.
Oh! I see.
I thought that something happened
with your family or something!
Why did you think that?
Huh?
Oh, um, just because.
Yeah.
Just because.
Deleting my texts
wasn't on accident, was it?
Of course it was an accident!
Were those texts that bad?
Huh?
Sheesh.
Yeah!
I deleted them because I thought
they would hurt your feelings!
I mean, is that Yoo Na or whoever
really a part of your family?
It's the first time I've seen sisters
who share such a bad relationship!
Our relationship isn't as bad as your
relationship with your cousins, though.
What are you talking about?
I heard that the three of you
have never even eaten together.
What kind of family is that?
I still ate with my family every day
even if only for appearance's sake.
You're such a kind person.
Speaking of which,
how about we all eat together?
What the hell are you looking at?
You saw that, right?
He definitely won't eat with us.
Huh? What is that?
This is Lee Yoon Sung.
Yes, I understand.
Is it a hobby of yours to invade
other people's personal space?
Why do you keep hanging around me?
You shouldn't be in here.
What's so special about this place?
Are you out of your mind?
What?
What made you think
it's okay to live here?
I have my reasons.
Living here won't be as simple
as you may think.
I'm aware.
No, I don't think you are.
I came here to protect something
that's important to me.
What's important to you
is money, isn't it?
I told you, it's not like that!
What, then? Are you going to try
and seduce me or something?
You really must be out of your mind.
What the hell are you doing?
Didn't I tell you never to
lay a hand on me again?
Oh no!
What do I do?
Oh no.
This is the reality of my life, huh?
What's that girl doing over there?
Hey, Ms. Celebrity!
What are you doing over there?
Hey, are you crazy?
Do you enjoy taking cold baths?
And what's with all this garbage?
It's not garbage.
These are my belongings.
This stuff?
Hey, you're going to catch a cold!
Can't you just throw these things away?
Why would I throw my stuff away?
Go back inside, you two.
Sheesh.
How ridiculous.
Hold on!
Hey, you can throw
those kinds of things away!
I can use this sample
for three whole days!
Sheesh.
Get out of there!
Let's go back inside.
It's pretty cold.
It's fine. You two can go inside.
Did you force your way in here
to be treated like this?
How about you take care
of your own things
instead of making other people
worry about you?
Yeah. Don't worry about her.
Because I'll be the one
to worry about her.
Then make sure she's not
in my face all the time.
Or why don't you just get lost?
You heard him, right?
He told me to get lost.
Are you saying that she's
your newest toy or something?
Why, do you want it or something?
Stop it, already.
Don't worry about them.
They're like this every time
they see each other.
Whatever. Leave me alone,
all three of you!
How many times has it been already?
I apologize. I should've been
more careful with your belongings.
Oh, it's okay, Mister.
Thank you for bringing everything here.
Let us go.
The car is waiting.
Go where?
Mister. Are we filming
"Pretty Woman" right now?
It's the Chairman's command.
I told you, I'm okay with
having this one outfit!
Um, then I'll pick out
a few things for you.
- It's the Chairman's--
- "It's the Chairman's command."
That's what you were about
to say just now, right?
I might just go and return
everything you buy, okay?
Then how about you go to
the cafe and rest a bit?
Mister!
Please go there and wait for me.
But...
- Oh my!
- Oh no!
Oh my! What the hell?
You should be more careful!
I'm sorry.
Oh no, my crocodile skin bag!
It got scratched!
I'm sorry.
You think your apology will fix this?
It got scratched because you bumped me!
- Really?
- What do you think you're touching?
This cost me 30 million won, you know!
It's worth 30 million won!
Pay me back for this bag!
Pay me back!
Really, now?
Who the hell are you?
A genuine article has five stitches
on both sides of the logo.
But yours isn't like that.
This material obviously
isn't even S-level quality.
Where did you buy this?
Oh my. How is that any of your business?
Looks like we've run into
each other again.
Oh... yeah.
Did you come to do some shopping?
Um, no. I'm just waiting for someone.
Oh.
I guess we tend to run into each other
at the most inopportune moments.
Thanks so much for earlier.
I was freaking out like crazy!
It was obvious that lady
was being really weird.
But, how did you know
that the bag was a fake?
People who do a lot of needlework
tend to know these things.
Needlework?
I have a lot of interest
in fashion design, you see.
I'm planning to major in
fashion design in college.
Oh, no wonder you're
always dressed so well!
You don't seem like a person
from "that world," either.
"Either"? So, you're not, either?
You didn't know, huh?
I'm not from a super-rich family
like those guys are.
Oh... I thought you'd
definitely be one of them.
Hyun Min and I have lived in the same
neighborhood ever since we were kids.
So we've been close since then.
Oh.
How did you meet Hyun Min?
Um, well, that is...
He came by the convenience store
where I work part-time...
- So, um...
- A convenience store?
Yeah, so...
I'm being too nosy. I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
I did know that Hyun Min dates around
but he's never introduced
anyone as his fiancée.
Oh, really?
I guess you're happy.
Huh?
About what?
Um, to be officially dating Hyun Min.
I mean...
I'm finished shopping, Ms. Ha Won.
Shall we head back now?
Yoon Sung?
Why are you shopping for her?
Did Hyun Min tell him
to do this for you?
- Um...
- No.
Ms. Eun Ha Won is living at Sky House,
so I'm taking care of her.
She's living at Sky House?
Yes.
So the person you were waiting for
was Yoon Sung?
Yeah.
Sorry. I'll get going.
Shall we go?
Um, but, why did you buy
so many things, Mister?
I told you that I'd return everything!
It's the Chairman's command.
Come on, Mister!
I have duties
that I must fulfill, after all.
But still, this is way too much.
I'm sure that you've been having
a hard time due to the Kang Cousins.
I'll be sure to take care of you now,
so that you won't be troubled anymore.
That's also the Chairman's command.
Also...
I'll apologize on behalf
of those three boys.
I'm sorry, Ms. Ha Won.
No, no, Mister!
Then...
I'll just wear this one thing.
It's because it makes me
feel bad to accept all this.
Let's hurry and return
the rest, okay? Let's go!
Come on, let's go!
Eun Ha Won's friend, Kim Ja Young!
It's Hong Ja Young, actually.
Who the hell cares?
What do you want?
You know who I am, right?
I heard that girl, Eun Ha Won,
is living at Sky House?
Oh... um, no!
I don't think so.
"I don't 'think' so?"
It's not even a "No",
but an "I don't think so"?
You know something, don't you?
Spit it out.
Hurry up and spit it out!
I don't know anything.
Really. I don't know.
What the hell are you saying?
I really don't know.
Give me your phone.
Why do you want someone else's phone?
Let me see!
So... it was true.
Wow, I'm so jealous.
You are too, right?
Why the hell would I be jealous?
Happy now?
Hey, give that back.
How do you know
if that's really Sky House?
No. I'm busy!
Hey, let me see!
What... am I holding
in my hand right now?
I don't know.
Three-day-old toilet paper?
Mommy! Ew!
Oh my gosh! Mommy!
Oh, I guess it's Eun Ha Won's.
How cute.
[Payment of 3,995,000 won
to Haneul Crematorium]
She only has 800 won left?
Oh.
Don't worry too much about me.
The part-time jobs I took on before
and the work I'm doing now
are all just jobs for me to earn money.
I don't have any reason
to feel hurt by them.
I've experienced far worse.
You're not just a part-timer.
You're our precious guest.
Even so, I'm going to do all the work
that the Chairman asks me to do
before I leave Sky House.
My life is on the line, after all.
I can do it!
Ms. Eun Ha Won is living at Sky House now
so I'm taking care of her.
I really don't get it.
Did something happen?
Can I ask you something?
I heard that Hyun Min's fiancée
is living at Sky House now?
Yeah.
So it is true.
It just ended up this way, somehow.
This is so frustrating.
I can't take this anymore.
I don't think you'd tell me,
so I'll have to go ask Hyun Min myself.
Right now?
Hey, Ms. Celebrity!
Hey!
Did you go out with Yoon Sung?
Yeah. My clothes all got wet,
so he bought me some new ones.
Oh yeah.
This is yours, right?
Oh... where did you find this?
It was on the floor.
Oh, really?
Thanks for finding this for me.
But, um, did you...
Sorry. I looked inside.
Oh, you did?
I mean, just in case it wasn't yours,
I was trying to find who it belonged to.
Who else in this house would
have a bank book like this?
You seem more like yourself now.
But it seems that I keep learning
all your secrets, bit by bit.
Oh.
Hey, come on!
It's only natural that
a high schooler has no money.
What about you guys, then?
Um, us?
Well, we're...
It's fine.
You guys have your own world,
and I have mine.
It's just that our worlds are
overlapping for a short while.
Hearing you say that saddens me.
No, no. My world is right here.
And I just realized once more
that I can't forget that.
I wasn't talking about that part.
You said that our worlds are
only overlapping for a short while.
Yeah, just for a short while.
Are you going to briefly
stay with Hyun Min
and then break off
your engagement?
Oh. Well, um, that's...
Or are you a bigger Casanova
than Kang Hyun Min himself?
Kang Seo Woo,
don't try to pry too much.
You'll end up getting hurt!
Who left this here?
Oh, was it Mister?
[Asshole Kang Hyun Min]
- Are you ignoring me?
- Yep yep.
Come here for a sec.
I have something to give you.
- Where?
- My room.
Nope nope.
I said I have something to give you!
No thanks!
You'll be surprised and touched
if you see it! Seriously!
Wow, did I just get ignored?
What?
Stay right there.
What the hell?
Oh, that's my uniform!
Hey, why do you have that?
Hurry up and give it back!
Come and get it.
What the hell?
Hurry up and give it to me!
Hmm, can I cut one of the arms off?
The spring/summer season
is approaching.
Hey. No! No!
I have to wear that to my graduation!
No, no, please!
Give it back!
Hey, slow down. You're making a lot
of sudden movements right now.
Okay, fine.
Come on, hurry up!
Hurry and give it back!
Are you holding my uniform hostage?
Yeah.
- No, you can't!
- Hey!
You're the first girl who has
ever entered my room.
Sorry. Can you forget
about that, please?
Hey, I even got this
dry-cleaned for you!
Give it back.
Want to have some ramen
before you go?
We can put some caviar in it.
You know, there are only
two types of customers
that come to convenience
stores after 4 a.m.
People who are going to work early,
and good-for-nothings still partying.
And the worst of the lot
always come on strong, like you.
Are you comparing your one-and-only-honey
to those types of guys?
That's not very nice.
Do you know what I do
when that happens to me?
What do you do?
Assholery for assholery.
Informal speech for informal speech.
Violence for violence.
Oh, are you going to
come on to me, then?
Yeah.
Was I a bit too forward with you?
You sure are unpredictable,
Eun Ha Won.
Here.
Geez, not again--
You're becoming more and more...
amusing.
Subtitles by DramaFever