[Cinderella and Four Knights]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ow, my head.
Wow, that was one strange dream.
Oof!
Oh my gosh, I must be crazy!
Wait, why am I happy?
Stop it! I'm not happy!
I must be crazy!
Oh man, I really must be crazy!
Come on, Eun Ha Won!
Get it together, girl!
What's going on?
Hey, Eun Ha Won!
Are you okay?
Ha Won!
It seems like a minor concussion.
Will she regain consciousness soon?
Yes. She's merely asleep right now.
Then, is it okay for us to transfer
the patient to a facility in Seoul?
Yes. If there's a hospital that she
regularly goes to, you can do that.
I'm sure she'll be getting up soon.
All right. I'll go and take care of
her discharge paperwork, then.
All right.
Yeah. I'll take Ms. Ha Won to Seoul
so I think it'd be best for you guys
to find your own way home.
All right. Do that, then.
You don't need to worry.
He says that she's fine.
Yoon Sung said he'll take her to Seoul.
What about us, then?
We don't need to go see her?
Right. He said that it was
only a minor concussion
and he wants us to go home and wait.
Just how did she manage to fall over
in the bathroom, and get a concussion?
She really is...
She really is a weird girl.
Let's pack our things
and hurry back home.
Yeah. It's not like we'd do anything by
ourselves without her around, anyway.
Aren't you going to go
and pack your things?
What?
It won't take me too long to pack.
I'll pack my things too,
and come out, then.
Wait for me.
Um, excuse me.
Oh, you're awake?
What day is it today?
It's the 15th.
Huh?
What the...
not even a single day has gone by?
Excuse me?
I mean, usually when people
pass out and stuff
and then wake up,
a week or so has gone by.
Isn't that how it usually is?
Thankfully, that's not the
case with you, so don't worry.
Hey, are you okay?
Oh, um... yeah, I think so.
I was super worried about you because
you were passed out in the bathroom!
- Aw, you were?
- Yeah!
Oh yeah! Where's everyone else?
Mr. Yoon Sung only brought you here.
He was in a huge rush.
Oh. But, um, Ja Young.
When people usually pass out, don't
people get temporary amnesia
or something like that, and not remember
anything that happened the night before?
What's with you?
Oh, never mind.
It's nothing.
- Are you really okay?
- Yeah. I'm fine.
I was quite worried about you.
I'm quite relieved.
Oh. I'm sorry, Mister.
Because of me, you...
Oh, let's hurry back!
I'm sure the rest of them are waiting.
No. You must go to Seoul
and get a cast put on your leg.
I've made an appointment for you at a
hospital that is owned by Haneul Group.
All they did here
was emergency first aid.
A cast?
They said that you
sprained your ankle, too.
Oh man, are you serious?
Please get on.
I'll escort you to the car.
Huh? She left all her clothes here.
How tacky.
Why does she always focus on
such unimportant things?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
Let's go.
What about everyone else?
They've taken another car,
and are on their way back to Seoul.
Oh. Did I cut this trip short
for everyone?
It's quite all right, Ms. Ha Won.
None of them would've come
if it hadn't been for you, anyway.
What is it?
You seemed to have quite
a low tolerance for alcohol!
You didn't even seem like you had a lot,
but you passed out before we knew it!
I saw a side of you that
I've never seen, Mister!
Please... um... erase that memory
from your mind, ma'am.
Oh, your face is all red, Mister!
I... suppose that you didn't
get drunk, then, Ms. Ha Won?
Well, I--
No. I was super drunk last night, too.
And because of that, I don't remember
a single thing that happened last night.
Did something happen last night?
Um, no.
Nothing happened.
But you just said that you
don't remember anything.
Well, that is...
Yes, um, I don't remember anything.
But nothing really happened.
You've stretched the tendon
in your ankle.
It's not a serious injury
so you'll be fine if you're careful
with it for the next couple of days.
Yes, thank you.
Have you used crutches before?
It's hard to get used to them at first,
but they'll be quite useful when you do.
- Can she go now?
- Yes.
Please schedule your next appointment.
And be extra careful
for the next couple of days!
Yes, I will.
Mister!
Let's go.
[Organ Transplantation Center]
Organ Transplantation?
It really won't be easy
to find an organ donor.
Oh... I see.
It'd be best for him to tell their
family about their condition outright
and find a donor among
his family members--
He's staunchly against that idea.
We have no other options
to offer you, at present.
All I can tell you to do now is wait.
All right. If you do find a donor,
please contact me.
I will.
- Um, Mister.
- Yes?
Oh, it's nothing.
Let's hurry and go.
We need to talk.
About what?
About last night...
Oh, that?
Let's just pretend that it didn't happen.
What?
It's simple. Let's just pretend
that none of that happened.
Okay?
What is it?
Did something happen?
Um, no.
Eun Ha Won!
Are you okay? You even
have to use crutches now?
Oh, it's only for a couple of days.
Whoa!
I'm fine!
What a shame.
That must be so uncomfortable.
It doesn't hurt, or anything?
They said that I just stretched
my tendon out a bit. I'm fine.
You should've been careful.
I'll be your human crutch.
Even though she's not your fiancee?
- Ms. Celebrity! I'll help you.
- No!
Um, it's because I'm not quite
used to them yet. I'll be fine soon.
I'll help you, Ms. Ha Won.
Then, can you hold these for me, Mister?
Why is she hopping off like that,
as if she's running away from us?
What's with her now?
Let's go.
I'll take you home.
Good work. Ms. Ha Won
is fine now, I presume?
Yes. I've brought her back to Sky House.
I was planning to get some rest here,
and keep it a secret from the kids.
But instead, I almost got caught.
How long are you planning
to hide your condition, Chairman?
I don't know.
Until I die, perhaps?
Honey! How could you say
something like that?
Is it all right for him
to be discharged?
His hepatic cirrhosis
is getting worse by the day.
It won't be long before
his liver fails completely.
The only option left to us now is...
It's fine. Whatever.
- I'll quit drinking, and--
- You must receive a transplant.
I thought you said you added my name on
the list of people looking for donors.
Yes. That is true, but a fitting
donor for you has yet to...
Well, I'm sure we'll find one
soon enough.
Isn't that right?
Chairman!
What good will it do anyone to go
around telling everyone that I'm sick?
Let's go.
Yes.
I'll take that, ma'am.
Thank you.
No. This is merely a part of my duty.
It would've been quite nice
if I had a son like you.
You're too kind.
Did something happen
between you and Ha Won yesterday?
Huh?
Um, why?
You two seemed a bit off,
back at Sky House.
No, I don't know about that.
It kind of seemed as if
Ha Won was avoiding you.
She probably feels embarrassed about
the fact that she tripped and fell over.
Figures. We all drank way too much.
My head still hurts a bit.
Yeah.
Wow, I feel like I have a really
bad headache coming on.
You were quite cute when
you were drunk, Kang Ji Woon.
Stop messing around, punk!
No, really. It's been a while
since I saw you smiling like that.
Really?
Are you the daughter of the people
who live here, by any chance?
Yes.
Is your father home?
No, he went on a business trip.
Oh.
Who are you?
Oh, it's nothing.
We'll come back another time.
What's with those guys?
I don't know. Maybe they're
people that my dad knows?
Will you be all right?
Yeah. I want to head in,
wash up, and get some rest.
All right.
Thanks for dropping me off.
Yes, go ahead.
Really?
I'll head over there right now.
Did something happen
between you and Ha Won?
It seemed like she was avoiding you.
I knew this would happen.
Don't you want my help?
I was about to change
into something else.
Yeah.
Get out!
Nah.
Hey!
Wow! Is this really all for Eun Ha Won?
Yeah. She's injured,
so she needs to eat up.
Isn't that right?
Oh, of course!
I'll bring this to her.
- Please be careful.
- All right.
How could this be?
No way. This can't be.
Hey, what about my clothes?
Why don't you have anything with you?
Your wardrobe is a crime against fashion.
There's nothing in there
that's actually worth wearing!
That's not true. I'm sure that there are
tons of things worth wearing in there.
- Just wait.
- Where are you going?
To buy some clothes that
are actually half-decent!
- Oh my--
- Hey!
- You surprised me!
You almost knocked everything over!
- And why are you here?
- Oh, for Eun Ha Won.
Food is the most important
thing to her, as you know.
And what about you?
Oh, I just had a couple of things
I had to take care of.
Get out of my way, already!
Hey, be careful!
Why, you little!
Damn it.
All right. Ta-da!
Your breakfast!
Wow, Kang Seo Woo!
I'm totally touched!
I'm not the one who made all this.
I know. It was probably
Ms. Beolgyo who made this.
She's quite a generous person!
No, it's not that she's
a generous person.
It's just that you have
a crazy-huge appetite.
- That's weird.
- What?
Why are you eating so little?
I don't really have much of an appetite.
What?
Wait a second.
I'm fine.
How could this be?
Eun Ha Won has no appetite?
Did you hurt another part of
your body besides just your leg?
Oh! Did you get
a bump on your head?
Maybe your concussion
affected your brain somehow?
I'm telling you, I'm fine!
- Really?
- Yeah!
It tastes good.
Looks like I'll have to eat a ton,
seeing as how you're freaking out
You're even taking care of me
like this because I'm sick! Thanks.
I have to go on a music show tomorrow,
though, so I won't be home all day.
It's fine. I'll be okay on my own.
- Really?
- Of course!
Eun Ha Won.
Yeah?
Did you even wash your face today?
- Nope.
- Hey!
See? You're not fine at all!
Here. Clean your face
with this, if anything.
What? Do you need me to get you
water in a basin, too, or something?
Wow, you're totally a genius!
- Give me your phone.
- Why?
Sheesh.
Hey, why are you taking
someone else's phone--
Change the pattern for the
lock on your phone! Sheesh.
What are you doing?
Oh, I'll download some
fun games for you to play.
You'll probably get bored
being cooped up in here.
Wow, really?
There's a ton of games that
I play when I'm in my dressing room.
These are the best things
to play to kill some time.
Thanks, friend!
At his current place on the waitlist...
he'll have to wait two to
three years, at the very least.
However, if a relative
is willing to be a live donor
he can get pushed up the waitlist.
The Chairman told me to keep this
a secret from his family, at all costs.
Yes, of course.
I know that.
The person in need of the
donation is being stubborn
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
but there aren't enough donors.
Those who care about him
must be quite worried.
But, he refuses to let his condition
be known to his family members?
Yes. That's how things stand now.
If the donor is his relative,
he can be operated on first
regardless of his place on the waitlist.
Excuse me?
There are currently over 200 brain-dead
patients who are potential donors.
However, there are thousands more
on the transplant waitlist.
However, if the recipient
is related to the donor
then that patient gets moved up
to the top of the list.
This also applies to people
who are only relatives on paper.
But of course, fabricating such
documents will cost you a bit.
It's not something that
I can do myself, you see.
Isn't saving a person's life
the most important thing right now?
[Manager]
I told you that I'm
taking the day off today!
Hey, where are you right now?
Man, staying in my room this whole time
sure makes me feel cramped!
Just where did this guy go, though?
Why are you peeking
into someone else's room?
I'm... I'm not peeking!
Hey.
What?
Um... about what happened last night...
It was the first time, for me.
Huh?
It was the first time
that I got drunk...
and blacked out.
O-oh.
- What about you?
- Me?
Well, I... I...
Well, you know, I even got a concussion!
So I forgot pretty much everything!
Sure.
Control your alcohol intake from now on!
Oh, come on!
I'm sorry for making you spend
so much time at the hospital
when such a life doesn't
suit a lady like yourself.
If there's anything you want
to buy, just say the word.
Do you think that I stayed with you
just so I could get to shop?
Buy some things for yourself, instead!
I don't need anything.
Do you want to make me buy you
all the clothes that this store sells?
That's what I'll be forced to do
if you don't pick something out yourself!
Oh, darling!
You're so silly!
Right? Can't stop, won't stop.
Wow, that's pretty.
Let's take a look at that.
Are you looking for a gift for someone?
Yes. I want to get them a valuable gift.
Refined gentlemen like
styles like these ones here.
No, these are too boring!
How old is the person
you want to give this to?
He's young enough that he could
wear something more flashy.
Oh, I see. Then...
How about this, ma'am?
I like it.
Of course.
I'm quite young.
At heart.
Look at her, buying a present for me when
I told her to get herself something.
What is it?
See for yourself.
What is all this?
I got a call from the paparazzi.
They're going to release these photos,
saying you got yourself a girlfriend.
What kind of nonsense is this?
That's not true!
Right? It's not true, right?
You two don't have
anything going on, right?
Well, we can't do anything about
the fact that these photos exist.
So if they do release these, let's just
deny that you have a girlfriend. Okay?
They said they're planning
to release these early tomorrow.
No. These definitely can't get out!
I'm sure we'll be getting tons of calls.
Things will be hard for a while.
But I'm sure this won't
hurt you in any way.
I mean, it's not like there was a photo
of you kissing her, or anything.
All you have to do is say,
"we're not dating!"
I told you, no!
Haven't you given any consideration to
how Eun Ha Won will be affected?
Last time, she suffered because of
that issue between her and Hyun Min!
How do you think she'd feel if she had
to go through something like this again?
Hey, why are you acting like this,
all of a sudden?
- Find another way.
- Another... way?
Hey, these guys are totally relentless!
You know that, don't you?
You know that they go crazy
when something juicy pops up!
Really? Then give them something
even crazier to report on.
And where in the world would we get that?
You don't mean "that," do you?
Yeah. I have something that's
even juicier than those photos.
Don't let your imagination run wild.
It's nothing like that, okay?
My heart totally
skipped a beat just now.
When did my Seo Woo grow up so much?
Come on, snap back to reality!
What the heck? He can't even
remember what happened?
Did he really only do that
because he was under the influence?
That's not fair!
Or, maybe I'm wrong.
Is it actually better that
he forgot about everything?
But still, this isn't right!
Damn him.
Should I go yell at him?
Oh, but even if I do, he won't
be able to remember anything!
Oh, forget it!
What are you doing?
Hey, what are you doing?
Ta-da!
Hey, why did you buy so much?
You feel totally thankful, right?
I even cut them for you, like this
so that you'll be able to wear
everything comfortably! See?
Hey! Why did you cut up
new clothes like that?
It's fine! They said that
they'd re-stitch them for me!
What does it matter if you cut it there?
I'm sure that my thighs
won't even fit into those!
Don't worry. I knew
you'd say that, and...
You see this? I even bought you a dress.
At any rate, I'll fill up your closet
for you, so wear these clothes.
Got it?
Geez, you...
What? Want me to put
these clothes on you, too?
- Sure, if you want--
- Wait!
That's enough.
- Thanks.
- Okay.
- Thanks!
- Sure!
Chairman.
What is it? Are you worried
that I'm worried about "that?"
Excuse me?
It's written all over your face.
Shall I... give them a call?
No, the opposite of that.
I don't even know how many
years this body has left
so I don't want to act like a coward
and cut the line, just to save my skin.
- But this might be the last option--
- I know how you must feel.
But there are some lines
that you just can't cut, in life.
There are things that no
amount of money can buy
and there are things that
one must never buy, too.
What, do you pity me that much?
No, sir.
I was just thinking to myself
about what a great man I serve.
You've worked quite hard.
You must be, to notice something
as insignificant as that.
About what happened last night...
Oh, that? Let's just pretend
that it never happened.
What?
It's simple. Let's just pretend
that none of that happened.
Okay?
What's wrong with me?
Oh, geez!
He's supposed to be a man, but he
blacked out from just a couple drinks?
How could you not remember what you did?
Geez!
Oh no!
Wait a minute.
Why should I have to hide?
What is all this?
Hey, Ms. Celebrity!
Eun Ha Won!
Can you open the door for me?
Hey, what are you doing here?
- Shush!
- What?
Can you help me up? Quick!
What are you doing here?
Did you get hurt badly?
- Quick! Get in!
- What? Why?
- Hurry up!
- Why?
- Geez.
- The door! Close the door!
What, the door?
You want it closed?
Geez. Why did you go out,
when your foot is still hurt?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Sheesh. Wait just a sec.
Hey, why am I your girlfriend?
Our engagement wasn't even real!
You're just my employer.
Why are you being
so nice to her, Seo Woo?
Oh, geez.
Give me your hand.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What were you doing outside?
Oh... I was just getting some fresh air.
- Oh, thanks.
- Geez.
What the hell is he doing?
Here, keep this wrapped
around your hands.
But, where did you go,
dressed like that?
- What's wrong with this outfit?
- What is this?
It's this new thing called
"curtain style!"
What even is that?
[Banana milk]
Wow, what kind of stain is this?
It just won't come out!
Um, about that shirt...
please just give it to me.
Oh, Young Master! It hasn't been
properly washed yet, though.
I'll be sure
to wash it properly this time.
No, I'll just take this.
No, no. Washing your clothes
is one of my duties.
You can just give this back to me.
Why are you acting like this
all of a sudden, Young Master?
This is a part of my duties!
- I told you, it's really fine!
- Oh my!
Oh my! Are you all right, Young Master?
Are you hurt?
A man's hips are the most
important part of a man's body!
- Ow!
- Oh no!
I'm fine.
Um, Young Master. It's nice to see
you around more often these days.
And you seem to be smiling
a lot more these days, too.
- I do?
- Yes.
Oh, really?
Here, have this.
Is he giving this to me
so that I get younger?
What the heck...
Why did I take this, though?
It's not like I want evidence
of what happened, or anything.
Are you sleeping?
Come out to the balcony for a second.
[To: Eun Ha Won]
- Ta-da!
- Wow! What is all this?
- A midnight snack?
- Hurry and sit.
Wow, I really wanted to
eat this kind of stuff!
You're the best!
Wow, seasoned fried chicken?
It looks so delicious!
Hey, how did you know that
this stuff is the good stuff?
Wow, this looks delicious!
You're totally touched, right?
See, this is why chicks
are crazy for me.
What, did another girl confess
her feelings to you lately?
As if you need to reaffirm that fact!
You're not that popular lately, though.
Hey, what are you talking about?
Does anyone really like you
for who you are?
Like Hye Ji does?
Well, duh.
Hey! You're being really mean, you know.
- What now?
- You know Hye Ji really likes you.
I think that Hye Ji
is really quite brave.
She's honest about her feelings,
and tries her best to be loved.
Do you know how hard that is to do?
She's like a tree.
She's planted her roots to one spot
and won't be shaken,
no matter what comes her way.
What about me, then?
You're...
like the wind, that just keeps blowing,
completely unaware of her efforts.
In other words, you're a real player!
Geez.
I wonder if I could ever bring
myself to do what she's doing.
Do you think you could,
if you were in her shoes?
I never had a chance to date because
I was too busy with part-time jobs
so I really know nothing
about how that must feel
but even I could tell whether or
not her feelings for you are real.
Hye Ji really has
earnest feelings for you.
Stop eating.
It doesn't suit you.
But I feel like you're that
way sometimes, too.
What do you mean?
I'm talking about the way
you look at Hye Ji!
You're so rude to her
when you talk to her
but sometimes,
you look at her quite tenderly.
I'm not that complicated, you know.
But keep this in mind.
There's no tree that will wait
around for you forever.
Don't regret this later.
Eat up.
Hey!
I'm visiting someone who's sick, so
please don't make it too over-the-top.
Yes, I understand.
Here.
Happy?
[Kang Seo Woo Flees While Wearing
Jungsan Girls' High Uniform!]
I must be a genius, Manager.
Whatever. Let's not talk
about this anymore.
Come on, check out these comments!
"Kang Seo Woo looks cool,
no matter what he does!"
"He's so adorable!"
"Shield your eyes, my body!"
See? Everyone's going crazy over these.
Wait, really?
See? I told you!
I'm successful no matter what I do.
My Seo Woo... you're all
grown up now, aren't you?
You're all grown up!
Maybe I should've just said
that we're dating.
You're outside?
Huh? What brings you here?
I came by because I was
wondering how you were doing.
Oh... thanks!
I'm not that badly hurt, though.
I felt like you'd pretty much
have access to anything here
so I brought you a bouquet of flowers.
Wow! Thanks!
Wow, they're so pretty!
Oh, do you want to come in for a second?
Sure.
Thanks.
It's this way.
So this is your room?
Oh, it's not my room, per se.
It's really nice. Looks like the
Chairman put a lot of work into it!
Well, you know.
Thank you, Ms. Beolgyo!
I should've gotten this myself!
What are you saying, with that leg?
Don't such say such things.
I'll come and clean this up
after you're finished.
Yes, ma'am. Thank you.
- Then, have a pleasant time conversing.
- We will!
Eat up, Hye Ji!
Oh, okay.
Looks like everyone here likes you.
Me?
Well, you know.
Sometimes, I'm a bit jealous of you.
You get along so well
with all of the Kang Cousins.
Oh, it only seems like that
on the surface!
Everyone here actually fights a lot!
Sorry.
My head itches because I couldn't
wash my hair for a couple of days.
Want me to help you?
Oh, it's okay! I hurt my ankle
and not my wrist, after all.
Okay, then. Go ahead.
Sorry. I'll be back soon.
Are you sleeping?
What are you doing?
Get out.
We need to talk.
I have nothing to say to you.
I can't pretend that nothing
happened between us.
Don't be like this.
What am I to you?
A friend?
Or... the younger sister of my brother,
your friend that died?
We don't have any kind of relationship.
And does this also mean nothing to you?
If you keep acting this way...
I really won't ever see you again.
You're not leaving?
I'll... leave, then.
Who's there?
Can you help me?
Oh man!
Hey. What are you doing down there?
What happened?
Well, uh...
I was trying to wash my hair, and...
Sorry, but can you call
Ms. Beolgyo for me?
She... went out before.
Oh... really?
Then... I'm really sorry, but...
But can you help me up?
Sorry.
Geez.
Wait just a sec.
Geez, way to go.
Stay still.
Okay.
Thanks!
Um, thanks.
- Hey. You...
- What?
Are you planning to leave the bathroom
with your hair looking like that?
Oh.
Wow... no other guy but me
would do this for you!
Thanks.
Hey! You're getting water in my eyes!
Ugh!
All right, already!
Ah, my ear! Oh no!
There's water in my ear!
Geez, stop protesting so much!
Hey, what are you doing?
You have to dry it like this for it
to dry well. Just stay still, okay?
I knew you'd do this!
No! I'll do it! It's fine!
Oh, no, ma'am! You've hurt
your leg! Please, sit still.
I told you, it's fine!
I'll do it! I'll...
I told you, I'll do it myself!
Sheesh.
Geez, you even complain
when I try to help you.
The dryer's in the bathroom.
Oh... thanks!
Wait a sec.
If you keep acting like this...
I won't see you ever again.
Hye Ji!
What's wrong, Hye Ji?
I told you not to make
Hye Ji cry, didn't I?
Who do you think you are?
What gives you that right?
Ji Woon has the right to say that.
I...
don't want to cry
because of Hyun Min anymore.
I...
want to take a break from you.
Will you...
accept me?
Subtitles by DramaFever