BK
Why are you doing this to me?
(Episode 10)
Why are you doing this?
Do you really want to die?
Why do you spread rumors about me?
What do you know about me?
Excuse me.
I told you that I'm not David Lee.
So why do you keep telling people about it?
Do you really want me to teach you a lesson?
What did you just say?
You're going to...
teach me a lesson?
Are you going to kill me?
Do you think you can kill Han Jeong Eun?
Do you?
Look at that.
What are you going to do?
Let go!
What did I do wrong to make you do this to me?
Did I steal your money or hurt you?
I didn't even bother you!
Why are you trying to kill me?
It's not like I know your secret.
What's wrong with once being David Lee of Golden Street?
Businesses always go down. It's nothing to be ashamed of.
- Hey! - What?
After your business totally went down,
you came back to Korea and became a construction manager.
You're going to be humiliated if I tell people about that, right?
You won over my grandmother and aunt,
so your pride will be hurt when they find out about it.
Even if a rich man falls, three generations thrive.
Even if a man fails, he can't give up his pride.
So things have been difficult for you in many ways,
and I kept going around giving people hints about your situation.
So you're very annoyed. Isn't that it?
But is that enough reason to kill a person?
And threaten me to kill me?
All right.
I won't talk about you any more.
I will keep your secrets.
But instead,
fix your personalty.
Stop being so angry.
You're not David Lee any more. Aren't I right?
Can I go now?
I'm leaving.
In the old days
David lived
That bad-tempered man
Ended up losing everything
But his pride was still intact
So he lashed out at his neighbor
(Kanghan Hospital)
Aunt.
When did he become like this?
I don't know. He always said he was tired.
He fainted on the way back from the community service.
I feel so bad for him.
Ji Hoon will be okay, Aunt.
The nurse said he will be fine after he gets the fluid.
Aren't you going home?
What?
Ji Hoon can't rest well if you are here.
Go home now
- Thank you taking him here. - It's okay.
I'm okay, Aunt.
Chang Soo.
These are the pictures of babies born here.
This baby wearing the crown...
is the millennium baby.
This is the first baby born in this hospital.
Come here.
Who do you think they are?
They are you and Ji Hoon.
Really?
On the day of 2002 World Cup, June 22, 2002,
when Korea fought against Spain and made it to the semifinal,
you guys were born.
You two were World Cup babies.
That's why we put up a picture of you here.
That's so cool.
That must be me.
No, that's Ji Hoon.
You're the one on the right.
I see.
I was smaller than Ji Hoon.
Yes, you were. What did you eat to grow so big?
He went to do the community service.
Why isn't he back yet?
Well, what's the point...
of waiting for the kid who wants to live with his aunt?
I don't know.
I don't know what children are to me.
If you like your aunt, you can go live with her, too.
I love you, Mommy.
I'm going to live with you.
Okay. Okay.
Okay, Darling.
I'm sorry. Mommy's sorry.
Mommy loves you a lot, Ah In.
Don't cry. Mommy's sorry.
Why did you make her cry?
Father.
Grandpa.
My pumpkin.
What brings you here, Father?
Why? Can't I come here?
That's not what I meant.
- Do you want some tea? - It's okay.
I had it upstairs.
Have a seat.
Ah In,
great-grandma came downstairs.
She will love it if you sing for her.
- She will give you some candy, too. - Okay.
Mommy, can I go play with great-grandma?
Of course you can. Don't run.
Go, sweetie.
It's tough, isn't it?
No, it's not, Father.
Many people live without a house.
We get to stay with you here. What's so tough about it?
Hye Joo,
you don't have to do that in front of me.
Here.
What's this, Father?
Keep it.
No, no, Father.
Keep it down.
Listen to your father-in-law for once.
I'm sorry.
Your mother-in-law is making you miserable...
by asking to pay rent, isn't she?
I paid her this morning.
Seong Hoon managed to get money somewhere.
He doesn't even have a job. Where did he get the money?
I don't know.
It's good.
Just keep it...
and use it to pay the next month's rent.
Get some snacks for the kids.
Also, fill your grandmother's fridge with some food.
Old people need to eat well.
Why do you keep crying?
Father,
I am so sorry.
I am truly ashamed.
I am sorry, Father.
Don't feel too bad.
At times of hardship,
family has to help each other.
You are going to help me when I'm struggling, right?
Goodness.
It's okay.
Stop now.
I am sorry, Father.
The facility is nice, and the location is good, too.
When you renovate the interior,
it will be perfect for a cafe.
By the way, how much is the monthly rent?
There's a market price,
but I still need to ask the owner of the building.
Who owns this building?
You ran into him before in front of our office.
He's the old man with gray hair.
The one who looks like Richard Gere.
Richard Gere?
If you talk to him well, he might give you a discount.
Wait. I'll give him a call.
(Rental inquiries)
Is he really coming here?
He won't be coming himself.
His agent will come.
He's here.
- Hello. - Yes.
I am sorry for making you come on the weekend.
It's okay.
Why don't you greet each other?
She's trying to rent the place,
and he's the building owner's agent.
Never mind.
What's wrong with him? Excuse me. Wait!
I don't want it either!
You go do your thing.
I'll help you, Granny.
I said, go do your thing.
If you do what I do, you will be like me.
Keep writing. Come on.
Okay.
(Scene 48, Montage)
Dong Hui. Grandma.
Why did you come here at this late hour?
Hello.
Hey.
I can come anytime since we live in the same building.
You live with your in-laws.
Nobody would like it if you keep coming here.
My mother and father-in-law are not petty like that.
Grandma,
I brought some beef.
Why would you bring that expensive meat?
You have to eat well at your age.
Dong Hui, cook some for her, okay?
Okay.
And I also bought the yellow corbina you like. You can eat it sometimes.
Where did you get the money?
You must have spent so much buying yellow corbina and beef.
Are you out of your mind?
Even if we're struggling, we have to eat well.
So you should eat well, too. Don't eat only vegetables.
- What's this by the way? - You don't need to know.
She got the job...
from the grocery store in front.
- Grandma! - Don't say anything.
You keep wasting money.
I have to earn money to compensate the spending.
Open it.
- What is this? - I heard you got a job.
Ta-da.
This is...
how you use this.
This is essence.
Then you use...
this cream. Use them in that order.
These are our company's new products.
Congratulations on getting a job.
Thank you, Hye Joo. I will use it well.
Gosh, you.
By the way,
I heard you pulled an all-nighter and didn't even come home.
Do you want me to get upset?
Which company do you work for?
Hey. What's wrong?
Be quiet.
What?
You work with my brother-in-law?
Yes.
Is that true?
This is crazy. Cheol Min's such an idiot!
Calm down.
How will I face Seong Joon now?
Don't worry, Hye Joo. I'll take care of it.
It's not something you can take care of.
But still.
Anyway, never tell Grandma. Okay?
Of course.
What are you doing outside?
Go in.
Go inside. I'm leaving.
Okay. Good night.
Bye.
Ah In, isn't it good?
This is crazy.
Hey, what's that?
What?
Where have you been all day?
And what's this?
I told you that I was going to do the community service.
And Ji Hoon's uncle bought us this.
What?
- Dr. Kang, you mean? - Yes.
Ji Hoon fainted on the way back from the community service.
What? Ji Hoon fainted?
- Yes. - Why?
I don't know much. I think he was just tired.
That wench Hee Sook...
finally made her child get sick.
How's Ji Hoon?
- He's getting an IV fluid. - Is it?
Poor Ji Hoon.
Anyway, is Dr. Kang well?
Yes. He's well. By the way,
did he deliver me?
- How did you know? - I saw my baby picture.
The one with Ji Hoon.
That's right.
Treat your mom well, okay?
I almost died while giving birth to you.
You know nothing about it.
How can you say you want to live with your Aunt?
I can't believe I celebrated after giving birth to you.
Stop hitting your precious son.
Who told you that you are precious?
Dr. Kang told me so.
He told me that every life is precious and beautiful.
Did he say that?
If you keep treating me like this, I'll go and live with Aunt.
Is that so? Do you think she will accept you?
Hee Sook will only accept you when you are top of your class.
What will you do?
You still don't know anything about her.
Why are you sleeping here when you have a home?
I want to sleep here for the night.
How can you sleep here? You just moved into your mother's house.
Please go home.
I think she's experiencing menopause. She looked depressed.
Grandmother, she already experienced it.
It's because she has a mean personality.
Moreover, my mom and I don't get along at all.
I'll just sleep here.
I raised you for nothing.
I don't know why I raised you all these years.
Why are you hitting me? My gosh?
Did you just say "My gosh"?
No, I didn't.
You don't think I heard you?
How dare you talk to me like this? To your own grandmother?
You're hurting me.
That's why I'm hitting you. I'm not hitting you for your happiness.
Hey, you.
You'd better come here.
Go to your mother's house.
My mother doesn't like me.
Just go to your mother's house.
- Stop hitting me. - There's a saying.
"If you can't defeat your enemy, be its friend."
I think you should follow the saying.
Everyone, please save me.
Go to your mother's house.
Moong Chi.
Moong Chi, what's the matter? Are you scared?
Are you cold? Should I give you a hug?
I didn't get to wrap it nicely. I'm just lending it to you.
Please use it well.
- How much is it? - That will be 270 dollars.
Here you go.
- Goodbye. - Thank you.
What is all this?
Do you have to ask? They're napa cabbages.
Are you going to make kimchi?
It's so sudden.
When will I do if not today? I should do when everyone's home.
Don't just stand there and move them.
Okay.
- Did napa cabbages arrive? - Yes, they did.
Today's going to be a long day.
Why did you buy so many of them?
Some of them will go to our children.
Really?
Are you going to make kimchi for our children?
Why are you surprised? Why?
Are you happy that I'm making kimchi for them?
Of course, I am.
They're busy. They don't have time for this.
Since we don't work,
we should make for them. Then their lives will be easier.
Goodness, this is the best idea you had.
I told everyone to come up, today.
But still, it would be great if you make kimchi for them...
when you do yours.
Stop talking and move them to the kitchen.
Yes, Mom.
Don't worry. Children get sick.
I know that.
It's an important time for him. I don't want him in the hospital.
Then ask your brother to give him a good IV infusion.
I don't know. He's been acting weird, too.
What do you mean?
Forget it. Get ready and go.
How about you?
I have to make kimchi today.
I'm so distracted since Ji Hoon's sick.
Why does she want to make kimchi? She should just buy it.
Anyway, it's so hard to get along with your parents.
But take a good care of them.
What did you say? Are you mocking me?
"Father, I'll take a good care of you."
- What did you say? - Okay, I'm going.
Goodness.
Seong Hoon, are you going somewhere?
Did you get a job?
Move.
Seong Hoon.
What happened? Seong Hoon.
Mom, you look scary.
Scary? I don't look scary.
I need to make kimchi today.
Ah In, you're on your own today.
- Did you get that? - Yes.
Why aren't you coming up?
Why did Hee Sook have to teach...
Mother how to use the messenger?
Yes, Mother. I'll be there now.
We're making Kimchi today. What a happy day.
I can't wait to make kimchi with you.
I'll try my best to learn from you.
This is driving me crazy.
She was born to flatter her superior.
My gosh.
Okay.
Goodness.
What?
Hey Joo, what...
are you wearing? Are you going to swim?
Do you plan to dig up cockles?
Or are you an Afghanistan soldier?
My goodness.
If you put the rubber bucket away and have a gun, that'll be perfect.
Should I put my hands in the air?
You'd better stop talking.
You're pretentious.
Then what about you? Are you Heidi from the Alps?
Chilli pepper powder will get all over you.
How can you wear a white apron and a white hat?
Gosh, you are never sincere.
- My goodness. - Move.
Hye Joo, can you please get rid of the scarf on your head?
It's scaring me.
Hye Joo. Gosh, that's so frightening.
Seong Hoon, get in. I'll give you a ride.
Where did you get a job?
Why do you have to work on Sundays?
I'm filming a show, but why do you work on Sundays?
- Hey. - You scared me.
You'd better go when you have a chance.
You, jerk.
What was that for?
How can you be angry when I was trying to help you?
Forget it.
- Really? - Seriously?
- Yes. - How did that happened?
I think he studied too hard.
Gosh, is he okay?
Yes, he's getting better.
Shouldn't you be there for him? He's sick.
I should,
but I want to help out before I go.
What should I do first, Mother?
Right.
I'm so tired.
Grandmother, Father, and Mother, please look at the camera.
- What are you doing? - I want to post this photo online.
Look at the camera. Her arm must be hurting.
Here it goes. In 1, 2, and 3.
- I took the photo. - How does it look?
Hold on, Mother.
This is a nice photo, Hee Sook.
Mother, where should I put these?
Bring them here.
Okay.
Put them gently. You're going to ruin them.
I'm sorry.
I uploaded the picture online,
and my friends said you look really young.
- They asked if you're my sister. - Really?
Do you seriously believe it?
Please tell them to stop it.
If she's your sister, is she your mother-in-law?
Gosh, you're right.
Why are you dressed like that?
Although we're working today, it's too untidy.
I thought it'd be of better help in this.
What are you doing now?
Slice the radishes now.
Hold on, Father.
My friends left too many comments,
so I'll just reply them quickly.
I'm done.
Mother, I sliced the carrots.
- Put in to the bowl, then. - I will.
I'm finished, Father.
Actually,
I'm so worried about Ji Hoon,
so I think I should go see him.
I see. Then, you'd better go.
Right. You may leave. I'm sorry for that poor smart boy.
You can leave.
Don't worry about us and just leave.
Then,
Grandmother, Mother, and Father,
I'll get going.
- I'm really sorry. - Don't be. Hurry yourself.
- I will, Grandmother. - See you.
Hye Joo, good luck.
Gosh.
What are you doing with napa cabbages?
Focus.
Okay. I'm sorry.
I succeeded in escaping.
Let me see. Let's call him.
Hello, Sir.
I'm Ji Hoon's mom who visited you the other day.
Can I visit you to register for your class today?
Sorry?
He has to take an exam?
Really?
Right. I forgot to invite Hye Joo's grandmother.
Wait a minute.
Thank you. Please hold on.
Thank you.
Please let me know if there's anything I do.
- Okay, I'll call you later. - Thank you.
- Hello. - Where are you?
I'm just around the house. What is it?
We're making kimchi today.
Really?
Wait for me. I'll be right there.
We'll be waiting for you.
(Scene 54, Afternoon)
Is she writing a script?
- I need more salted seafood. - Okay. Here you go.
You're such a great cook.
Thanks to Hye Joo's grandmother, we'll be able to eat...
premium kimchi throughout next year.
You're right, Mother.
Thank you, Ms. Oh.
- Bring me more chopped onion. - Okay.
- Are you making kimchi? - Where have you been?
I walked Moong Chi.
I'll help you, too. What should I do?
We don't need your help. Just stay in your room.
Hye Joo went to take something. Go to the kitchen.
Okay.
Hye Joo.
Gosh, Seong Joon.
Is there anything I can help?
It's okay.
- Let me do it. - It's all right, Seong Joon.
- Please let me do it. - By the way,
thank you so much.
- For what? - Dong Hui told me everything.
I see.
Please give it to me.
Okay.
Don't worry, Hye Joo.
Seong Joon,
I'm really sorry.
Please...
take good care of Dong Hui.
She grew up without her parents,
so she's gone through a lot.
Please don't worry. I'll make sure to take care of her.
What are you doing in there? I told you I need onion.
Okay! I'm on my way.
We'll be right there.
- I can do it. - Okay.
Here.
What were you doing? You took too long.
It'll take all day long because of you.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Grandmother.
You're so skillful.
Hye Joo, go tell Dong Hui to bring some plum extract.
- And tell her to come help us. - Okay.
I'll do it for you.
What are you doing inside all day long on Sunday?
Well, I was working.
What work were you doing?
I was writing.
Do you like your lab top?
I do!
I was just going to call you to say thank you.
We're living in the same house.
Anyway, let's go downstairs.
They're making kimchi today.
Your grandmother wants you to bring plum extract now.
Okay. Please wait a minute.
Everyone is working. You'd better go help them now.
Hurry.
Wait.
Keep it up.
- Okay. - Okay.
Wait,
do I look especially great today?
Why is everyone staring at me?
Well,
it kind of feels good, though.
Goodness.
He must have gone out of mind.
- He spilled coffee, didn't he? - Wait.
What's the matter with you all?
Did something happen today?
- Here's the online star. - Sorry?
What do you mean I'm an online star?
I told you to be careful.
Be careful of what?
I guess you haven't seen it yet.
Look.
Someone filmed this scene.
- It's really hot. - Gosh, look what happened.
Gosh.
Wait... This... This isn't what you think.
This is not it.
All of you were right here when this happened!
Who edited this out of context? It's so evil.
Come forward right now.
Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang, did you see this?
Move. Don't come near me.
What? My gosh.
What shall we do?
How could she live like this?
Why doesn't she just go ahead and camp out in the living room?
It's better if she was wandering in the mountain and the sea.
Why did she have to move back and upset me?
I don't know what to do with her.
Mom, what are you doing?
Where have you been?
Where did you sleep last night?
I slept at grandmother's house.
Are you out of your mind?
How could you stay out overnight when you just got back?
What do you mean? I slept at grandmother's house.
That's still staying out overnight.
Why would you sleep at grandmother's house when you have a home?
It's not my first time sleeping at grandmother's house.
What did you say?
Forget it. Let's stop here.
And leave it. I'll clean it up.
What a rude wench.
Why are you hitting me?
How dare you raise your voice to your mother?
Are you sure you're my daughter?
Then are you sure you're my mother?
What? Say that again!
What's wrong with sleeping at grandmother's house?
I've been living at grandmother's house my entire life.
I attended school from her house from elementary school to college.
This isn't new. What's wrong with you?
How many nights did I spend here?
Even when I spent nights here, all you did was playing that piano.
Have you ever spent a night with me?
How could you say such things?
Have you ever read me a book?
Have you ever woken me up for school?
What about a field trip? Have you ever packed me lunch?
Grandmother or Aunt did all these for me.
Hey. It was hard for me to give birth to you.
Do you think you're the only one who had a hard time?
Why?
Because you weren't married when you had me?
Han Jeong Eun.
Yes. My name is Han Jeong Eun.
I'm listed on Aunt and Uncle's family registry.
So why is it so bad about sleeping at Grandma's place?
How dare you speak to me like this?
Don't worry.
I'll make money.
And I'll leave Korea again.
How could she...
It's over there.
How can it be?
This is a mere misunderstanding.
It's a conspiracy and defamation. Someone's plotting against me.
This is all Ms. Jang's fault.
My goodness.
What happened? What is this?
What?
What are you going to do?
Do you know how much this car is?
I bought it with 36-month installment plan.
I still have 28 months to go. It's a new car.
He's making a fuss.
Wait, I thought I was supposed to pile up the bricks there.
You shouldn't pile up the bricks here.
Why would you pile up the bricks here?
What am I going to do?
I apologize.
Is that all?
How are you going to fix this?
We'll compensate for the damage.
I don't care about the compensation.
How are you going to fix my car?
Goodness.
Are you feeling better?
A little.
That's why you shouldn't study too hard.
You know I can't.
Right.
But,
let's try our best, okay?
Have your meal.
Look at you.
I didn't know you were eating.
Hello.
Did you sleep well?
Yes?
Maybe it's the sleep. You look much better.
Right, Min Seok?
I'm glad it's nothing serious.
Thanks to Min Seok,
you'll get better.
I brought you a gift.
I understand it must have been hard for you to study.
I bought you something you like.
What is it?
It's the headphone...
you wanted to have.
You don't like when I listen to music.
You shouldn't listen to music for long.
You can listen to it once in a while,
but not too long. You know what I mean, right?
But Ji Hoon, do you need to stay in the hospital?
What?
What do you mean? Where will he be if not here?
Min Seok, I want to him discharged today.
No way. He can't be discharged.
If he can sit up and eat,
- he is recovered. - Hee Sook.
Ji Hoon, there's an important exam, tomorrow.
Remember the boarding academy that I talked out before?
The one you were supposed to go during the winter break.
It became a competitive academy to get in. You have to take a test.
But do you know why it became competitive?
The students who studied there...
all went to either Seoul National University or KAIST.
- That's why you should... - Come outside.
- Come outside. - What are you doing?
Min Seok.
Come here.
What are you doing?
Are you out of your mind?
How can you think of taking him home when he hasn't fully recovered?
He has recovered.
Do you think he's recovered?
He hasn't? Look at him. He's sitting up and eating.
Min Seok.
It's an important time for Ji Hoon.
He doesn't have time to be in the hospital.
If he doesn't get into that academy, he won't get into the gifted school.
What's the point when your son isn't well?
You can still raise him well without sending him to that school.
Min Seok.
You're talking like this because he isn't your son.
How about you, Min Seok?
You sent your three daughters to a boarding school in the States.
You send them millions of dollars for their education.
How could you talk to me like this?
You don't even live with your wife for your children's education.
There's a reason to it.
I have my reasons, too.
Did you forget?
How our father treated us differently?
I'm not going to raise my son like he raised me.
It's a very important exam.
He can just go for a day tomorrow.
No, he can't. You can't take him there.
No, I will. He's my son.
Don't get involved.
Hee Sook.
Fine.
If this is what you want, you can stay here tonight.
But I'll bring you textbooks and study materials.
You'll prepare for the exam here,
and I'll drive you to the academy for the exam tomorrow.
Rest. I'll be back soon.
Hooray!
Hello.
Hi, Chang Soo.
Are you here to see Ji Hoon?
Yes. I won these two dolls.
I want to give them to Ji Hoon.
I see.
Gosh, it looks just like you.
I think so, too.
Why is it so hard?
His parents give him food, shelter, and they pay for his school.
The least he can do is listen to his parents.
The nurses here listen to what you say, right?
Why would they do that?
It's because you pay their salaries.
His parents do all that stuff for him.
Then he should listen to them.
If he doesn't want to, he should go out and live by himself.
- You rascal. - He receives his Mom's help.
It's ridiculous that...
he doesn't listen to such a good mom.
You do well at school, don't you?
Please don't ask me that.
Anyway, I hope...
you'd help Ji Hoon.
I won't be a good help to him.
It's not like I can switch our moms.
Poor Ji Hoon.
If it was as simple as class duty, I'd switch them for him.
Dr. Kang.
Ji Hoon disappeared.
What?
Ji Hoon!
What should we do, Dr. Kang?
Let's check that side.
- Ji Hoon. - Ji Hoon.
Ji Hoon. What should I do?
- He's not there? - He's not.
- What should we do? - Please come down.
Please don't do that.
Ji Hoon!
Ji Hoon. Why are you doing this?
What do you think you're doing? Come down at once.
Ji Hoon!
Uncle.
I don't want to live any more.
Come down first. We'll talk after you come down.
You shouldn't do this.
Ji Hoon. Please calm down, and get down here. Ji Hoon.
I'm sorry.
You understood me,
but I don't think I can hold out any longer.
Ji Hoon.
Mom wants me to go to a boarding school.
Do you know what people do there?
They study all day every day.
I will...
convince your mom, okay?
- So please come down here. - That's not going to work.
She will kill me.
She will send me to a boarding school and kill me eventually.
Rather than dying while being forced to study,
I'll just kill myself instead.
- Watch out! - Don't come near me.
I will kill myself! I'll do it!
Let go of me! I will kill myself.
- Ji Hoon. It's okay. - I want to die! I'm going to die!
- Calm down. - Let me go.
Ji Hoon!
- No. - Get off of me!
Calm down, Ji Hoon!
- Let me go. - Ji Hoon!
- Ji Hoon. - Please calm down, Ji Hoon!
How could you forget to buy the pork?
You should buy the pork first before you buy napa cabbage.
Why bother make kimchi for winter? We don't even have pork.
Why would I make kimchi without pork?
I'm sorry, Mother. I forgot to buy it. I'm so sorry.
There're things you must not forget.
You know the things I like.
How could you forget to buy it?
I guess I've been too lenient.
Not at all, Mother. That's not true.
I'm sorry, Mother. Please forgive me.
Freshly made kimchi with...
softly boiled pork,
a little oyster,
and a bit of pickled shrimp wrapped together.
You know how much I love to eat it.
Imagining it makes me want to eat it even more.
I'm so sorry.
I guess I did get old. Please forgive me.
I can never let this slide, Jeong Ae!
- Starting from today... - Mother, please.
My goodness. Stop it already.
You can just have pork tomorrow.
What did you say?
She worked hard all day to make kimchi.
Why are you tormenting her?
Grandma.
I can't take this.
Are you lecturing me right now?
Yes. I am lecturing you.
You're an elder. Why are you being...
so petty over food?
What did you just say?
What are you doing? I said come in.
I am coming in.
Ms. Oh.
How could you do that to me in front of the kids?
Your daughter-in-law was on her knees in front of me.
You should consider her, too.
She's in her 60s, and she got scolded in front of me.
That's not right.
That's for me to decide. I decide that!
I can scold my daughter-in-law in my own house.
No matter how upset you are,
please consider the circumstances and behave appropriately.
When have I ever behaved inappropriately?
Gosh.
You're so childish.
What did you say?
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
All right.
(Butcher's shop)
Aren't you tired?
I've made kimchi before. My grandma used to run a grocery store.
I see.
Have you written the script?
Just a little. I thought I should write as much as I can on weekends.
Thank you so much for the laptop.
It's no problem.
Thank you anyway.
Don't go to the library any more.
Don't stay late in the office, either.
Did you know?
Of course. Now I know everything you do.
That's right. I didn't tell you about the rental fee.
- Are you going to make me pay? - Of course.
Nothing is free in this world.
Show me.
- Show you what? - Your script.
- What? - That laptop is very expensive.
So...
please let me be the first one to read your script.
Okay?
I'll think about it.
Hi, Mi Joo.
What's up?
What are you doing, Seong Joon?
Well, I came outside.
It's weekend. Why didn't you call me?
You said you'd be playing golf with the directors.
I just came home.
Mr. Park is a golf maniac. I'm so tired.
You must be. Did your golf skills get any better?
I can play singles now.
Gosh. That's amazing.
What did you do today?
- We made kimchi today. - You made it?
My mom did. I just helped her.
Mi Joo. I'll call you back.
Dong Hui! Wait for me.
Seong Joon.
What was that?
Dong Hui.
What are you looking at?
Dear Lord, our family made kimchi for winter today.
We do it around this time every year.
But it ended in a very bad way.
It's not that I wanted to eat the pork.
I was just disappointed in Jeong Ae.
I was so disappointed that she didn't remember such a small thing.
- Please hear my prayers. - But Ms. Oh treated me like...
- a greedy old lady. - Please protect my children.
Dear Lord, please do something about...
her victim mentality, inferiority complex,
and her huge ego.
To be honest with you, I can't take it any more.
Please answer to my prayers.
Please help my grandson return home safely.
Please help Dong Hui to become a scriptwriter,
so that she can achieve her dream.
Please answer to my prayers.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Massage my arm, please.
- Gosh. - I'm so exhausted.
We decided to cook the pork tomorrow.
I'll eat it tomorrow...
and forgive Jeong Ae. What else can I do?
I can be mean sometimes because I'm getting old.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
Still, I am...
so grateful that I'm healthy enough...
to make kimchi with my family.
Ji Hoon is very sick.
Please have mercy on him, and help him get better.
This is an amazing car. Are you really going to give me...
I mean...
rent it to me?
Please feel free to use it until your car gets fixed.
But...
this is such a luxurious car.
You're on TV shows. You should drive a car like this.
How did you know that I'm on TV shows?
I often watch your show, "Today's Current Event".
I'm also a fan of yours.
My goodness. What a pleasure!
I didn't know my fan was living right across from me.
It's so good to meet you.
- Gosh. I'm honored. - Honored?
I'm flattered.
Please get in.
We'll take two A course meals, and a bottle of 1997 Sangiovese.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
I am...
the one you saw in New York.
Excuse me?
I am David Lee.
What?
- What? What did you say? - What did you say?
- Our sons were switched? - Our sons were switched?
Min Seok. What...
What are you talking about?
Our boys were switched?
I'm sorry, Hee Sook.
Ji Hoon isn't...
your son.
He's not your son.
Min Seok!
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
My business failed completely.
We traveled thousands of miles and met again here in Bangbae-dong.
It's a miracle.
That was great to watch.
Are you shooting a movie?
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
Chang Soo is here.
How can you be my son? You're not my son. Get out!
You didn't do anything to me, did you?
This is the rental fee for the laptop.
You said you want to see my script when it's done.
You did great. Good night.