BioskopKeren
Goodness.
What's wrong, baby?
Is something wrong? Are you feeling bad?
What's wrong?
It's because of Mona Lisa, isn't it?
My darling.
You like Mona Lisa, don't you?
You are...
so special, my baby.
(Sweetie. Do you like Mona Lisa, baby?)
(Do you like Mona Lisa, baby?)
I'm sorry. Sorry.
That's what I'm saying, you moron!
I said the logo's color is darker by one tone and it's not clear.
You should fix it immediately.
I told you ages ago. So why is it still not fixed?
If you keep working like this,
we will remove you from our subcontractor list.
What?
What did you say?
Hey! Do you want to die?
You stupid idiots.
Come if you can.
But make sure to come before I go home.
I will kill you if you are late!
They never listen, do they?
This is Seo Hye Joo speaking.
Ms. Seo, why don't you come to deliver the baby?
It's one week past your due date. Do you know that?
Has it passed already?
I am sorry,
but I am really busy right now. Can I go next week?
Yes. Yes. I have an important meeting after work.
I will go right after the meeting.
Yes. I am sorry.
I will go right now, then.
Okay.
Gosh.
Hello, ma'am.
My due date is next Tuesday.
But I've been feeling contractions every 20 minutes for 30 seconds.
The back pain indicates that it will get more active soon.
Therefore, it's estimated that I will give birth...
within 4 to maximum 12 hours from now on.
I see.
I called my husband on the way.
He must be coming here from the conference.
Yes, Ms. Kim.
I came to give birth right now.
Why does it suddenly hurt?
Yes. We have to send the experiment results of...
new product by tomorrow. Don't make any mistake.
Also, call that idiotic...
contractor,
and tell him that I will kill him after I give birth...
if he doesn't fix the logo within today. Okay?
Okay.
I will try my best to be as quick as possible.
So work hard while I'm away. Bye.
Mr. Kang is coming today, right?
He said he's going to give me a lot of discounts.
Oh, my gosh.
(Kanghan Hospital)
So? So what now?
It seems like...
Ji Hoon is not your son.
The chance of him not being your son...
is 99 percent.
Min Seok!
What?
Why are you doing this, Min Seok? Why are you doing this to me?
Is this because I asked you to release Ji Hoon sooner?
- That's not it. - Then?
What do you mean the children are switched?
Honey, what is he saying right now?
Calm down.
- Calm down. - Okay.
Calm down, Hee Sook.
Let's listen Dr. Kang first.
This is crazy.
Honey, have a seat first. Sit.
So what on earth happened?
Yes.
What on earth happened, Min Seok?
Just 20 days ago,
I did the medical checkup...
for the students of Woosoo Middle School students.
Ji Hoon and Chang Soo came.
So they got checked, too.
So? What happened next?
Be quiet!
- Doctor. - Yes.
This is the result of Woosoo Middle School students' medical checkup.
- Thank you. - No problem.
I was...
worried about Ji Hoon's health.
So I was checking his result.
It turned out Ji Hoon's blood type was O.
What?
Ji Hoon's blood type is O? Not B?
Min Seok!
I know Hee Sook's blood type.
As you know, a child with blood type O...
cannot be born from a parent with blood type AB.
Then? What happened?
Here's the result for Han Chang Soo.
However, Chang Soo's...
blood type turns out to be B.
What?
What? I mean...
my blood type is O...
and his blood type is A.
How can my Chang Soo's blood type be B?
That's nonsense.
It looks like...
the two kids were switched.
What?
I am sorry,
but we should...
do the DNA test for the two kids.
What nonsense are you saying?
Honey. Honey.
What is he saying, honey?
Honey.
What are you doing, rookie?
- I'm coming. - Hurry up.
I'm working so hard, too. Can you hurry up?
- Okay. - Dong Hui.
Bring me some props, too.
Coming.
The mise-en-scene is Oscar worthy.
- Yes, Ms. Hong. - Where are you, Producer Kim?
Where would I be? I'm at the new store.
Ms. Kim Mi Gyeong is coming in today. Why are you there?
What do I do, then? The Marketing Team asked for assistance.
Even if I don't like it,
I need to do this to get our projects funded.
- Goodness. - Are you okay?
It's a lovely picture.
Get up, you two. Are you shooting a film?
Goodness. You need to work now, rookie.
Why are you so heavy?
- Goodness. - Goodness.
Is everything getting ready for opening?
Everything was ready,
but you two just ruined the entire display.
We're done preparing the props.
The display will be done with the new line products.
Good job.
The opening of this store will be very important.
Please make sure to run everything smoothly until the end.
The company hasn't done anything for us.
I will treat you a pork barbecue and soju.
- Really? - Really?
Yes!
- Pork barbecue. - We'll go back to work now.
Let's go.
We should do art again.
Let's drink until tomorrow.
Congratulations.
Yes, Director Bang. Why didn't you come?
Seong Joon, the chairman is here.
Come to the office right away.
Okay. I'm coming now.
Dong Hui, can you take this?
Directer Han!
Why did he leave? He said he would treat us.
Goodness, something must have gone wrong again.
Idiots. They have been doing whatever they want while I was away.
I am going to fire them all.
- What now? - It's nothing.
Did you tell Han Seong Joon to come to the office or not?
He will come right away.
Okay. Bring the documents.
Here they are.
What did you say?
Didn't you hear me?
I said I'm David Lee.
Why are you so surprised?
You suddenly confessed it.
And I feel a little flustered.
You left me no other option.
Perhaps you were a Nazi councilor...
who used to interrogate the French Resistance in your past life.
What?
You were the cool French Resistance,
and I was the shameless man who tortured people?
You are right.
I completely failed.
Completely.
Why?
That's how it's like working in Wall Street.
You can become rich with astronomical wealth in an instant,
and you can also become a beggar in an instant, too.
You know.
Why did you lie, then?
You even treated me like a lunatic. Why did you deny it all along?
I was ashamed.
Like you said, I was ashamed that I completely failed.
I was once the best investor in Wall Street.
After losing everything I had, I am sponging off my uncle.
And I am working as a construction manager here.
Would it be easy to admit that if you were me?
Right. You make sense.
By the way,
how did you get completely bankrupted?
There's a saying that wealth continues for three generations.
So I expected the situation to end smoothly,
and bet 10 billion euros on Greek bonds and bank notes.
But it turned out to be something very reckless.
Goodness. You must have...
made a careful investment choice.
I know.
I am sorry. I didn't know.
I was so happy to see you.
It's not easy to meet someone you meet in New York in Seoul again.
I know.
Right.
You said you're preparing to open a cafe, right?
Yes.
Is it going well?
Tell me about it.
Even if I want to do it, I can't afford the expensive rent.
I envy you. You lost everything, but you have a rich uncle.
Do you want me to ask my uncle to help you?
What?
Ask him what?
I will ask him to rent it out to you at a cheaper price.
Really?
Like you said, we're special friends, you know?
Thank you so much. Thanks a lot.
I will...
never forget your kindness.
Let's make a toast to celebrate this moment.
Cheers.
Look who's here.
My son-in-law is here.
Hello, sir. Have you been well?
Yes, I am always well.
Did you have a good time...
with my Mi Joo while I was away?
- Dad. - What, girl?
There's rumor everywhere that you're so desperate for him.
My pride is hurt.
Seong Joon, you should go desperate for her.
Don't you think you're too mean?
Do you want the chairman's daughter to follow you around?
You are too stiff. That's your problem.
Dad.
I am sorry.
Watch him speak. He says he's sorry.
Girl, what do you like about him anyway?
Goodness.
Dad, what are you doing right now?
Be quiet. How dare you yell at your father?
Take a seat, Seong Joon.
Let's talk about business.
Okay.
What are you doing, Granny?
Just keep writing. Don't care about me.
Eat this boiled pork...
for dinner.
Will you not eat with me?
What is this "No Caller ID"?
Hello?
You called me, so you should talk.
Why do you always call me and not talk?
And why do you keep hiding your identity?
Why would you not reveal your caller ID?
You evil and nasty man.
Reveal your identity right away.
Goodness, Granny.
She's so nasty.
I love everything about her,
except for her hot temperament.
How can you ignore my desperate craving for pork...
in such a rough way?
And how can she not call me?
I can't talk to her first.
I am so bored.
Who is it?
- What brings you here? - Move.
Did she find out that I called her?
Wait.
It's so delicious.
- Is it that delicious? - Of course it is delicious.
How do you cook boiled pork so well, Elizabeth?
Thanks to Elizabeth, Grace Kelly is happy.
I will eat one more. I could have brought it down sooner,
I could have brought it down sooner, but a crazy person called me,
and said nothing.
I'll teach that person a lesson if I find out who it is.
My gosh, what a crazy man.
How do you know it's a man?
It must be a man. I'm sure of it.
My goodness, this is so delicious.
Elizabeth.
Why don't you spend the night here?
Why do you want me to spend the night here?
Elizabeth.
Stop nagging.
My gosh.
What is all this?
Leave them right there.
What is it?
Just leave it.
It's the bill for the kimchi.
Are you planning to make them pay for it?
Of course, I will.
Do you know how much nappa cabbages and red pepper powder cost?
Don't forget about the salted shrimps and the seasoning.
Do you know how much it is...
if you add all of them up?
How can we pay for everything? We need to split the bill.
How can you do this as a mother? You're so cruel.
Is this how you're going to treat them?
My hands are tied. We need to live, too.
I told them to take the kimchi.
Where are they? I haven't seen them all day.
Honey, what are you doing?
Give me that.
You know how hard it was for me to calculate all that?
Give it back. Come on.
What are you doing? My gosh. Honey?
Spit it out. Come on.
You're not going to spit it out?
You...
Spit it out. Spit it out now.
My goodness. I can't believe this.
Honey, I think I'm going to die.
I'm going to die.
We're home. Hang in there.
Be careful. Are you okay, honey?
Should you stay in the hospital?
No.
It's because I had to take...
that ridiculous DNA test based on a ridiculous reason.
I'm going to disown Min Seok.
- Be careful. - Aunt.
What do you want?
Why are you up here?
I'm sorry.
I wanted to cook jjajang ramyeon with Ah In, but I didn't have a pot.
My mother didn't do the dishes.
You'd better go downstairs.
I told you not to come upstairs.
Hey.
How dare you to yell at my son?
Then,
take your son...
and go downstairs immediately.
Chang Soo.
Let's go. Let's go with me.
Never...
come upstairs ever again. Did you get that?
Honey.
Mother, what's wrong? Are you sick?
Mom.
She's okay. It's nothing.
Honey, why don't you lie down?
I told you. If they never...
moved in here,
this wouldn't have happened.
What did she...
Hey.
Do you think it happened because we moved in together?
Besides,
you followed us when we moved in here.
We didn't follow you.
You tried to get here before us so you can unload your stuff.
Stop it. The children are listening.
Move aside.
And...
Because we were getting married,
you decided to get married.
We got married on the same day because of you, two.
Hey, listen.
We got married in a traditional Korean village of Andong.
But you two...
got married in a high-class hotel.
Because of the fuss you made,
our parents had to be split.
At the end, they got on the bus late.
Because of you, my wedding started late in the evening.
I saw the Moon in the sky. Did you know that?
That was the only day which was available for us.
What was I supposed to do?
That, witch.
- What? - Honey.
That's enough.
Let me go.
Stop it. Chang Soo, go upstairs and stop your Aunt.
Yes.
Why did you come up? Go downstairs.
Honey.
Okay.
Then, why would you give birth...
at my brother's hospital?
There are thousands of hospitals.
Why did you have to choose...
my brother's hospital to give birth?
Hey!
It's not like I wanted to give birth at that hospital.
You introduced me to that hospital.
You wanted to show off that...
your brother was the director of the hospital.
Hey, you told me that he gave...
a big discount for family members.
Do you think I went there because I wanted to?
Honey, that's enough.
Chang Soo, I told you to stop your Aunt. Why are you here?
Okay.
I told you not to come up. Go downstairs.
I'm going to lose it.
Look at Hee Sook being so unreasonable.
Mother, stop it.
Why do you always fight with Aunt?
If you keep arguing with Aunt,
I'm going to go upstairs and live with Aunt.
- Hey! - Chang Soo.
What did you say?
What did you just say?
I raised you for 15 years...
the best I can.
What? You're going to live with Aunt?
Honey.
Did you hear what he said?
How dare you say that to your mother?
Why does she argue with pretty Aunt?
Pretty? How is she pretty?
Your mother is much prettier.
We raised you for nothing. Han Chang Soo.
How could you betray us?
When did I betray you, Father?
Come here, Chang Soo.
Come here. Come to your mother.
Mom.
I don't think you should hug me. I'm all grown up.
Please, refrain from touching me.
My son, Chang Soo.
Mom, what are you doing?
My son.
Honey.
Ji Hoon.
Honey, calm down.
Honey, I can't do this. I have to go back to the hospital.
- I have to go see Ji Hoon. - Honey.
Please, calm down. Stop acting like this.
Honey, get some sleep.
You should get some sleep.
Please, sleep.
- Get some sleep. - Ji Hoon.
What do you want, punk?
Punk?
Don't you think I'm not devastated?
I'm so devastated that I'm going to lose my mind or die.
How can Chang Soo be my son? Does it make sense?
You see it, too. Don't you?
How can I and Chang Soo...
How can this be...
How? What?
This doesn't make sense at all. As you know...
What's wrong with Chang Soo? My wife and I wouldn't...
trade Chang Soo even if we get a hundred of you.
Seong Hoon.
It's not an issue between Chang Soo and me.
How can you compare me to him?
Anyway,
We need to wait until the DNA result is out.
I am sure...
Chang Soo is my son.
Goodness. Then,
I am sure...
smart Ji Hoon is my son, too.
Move aside, you punk.
Come on.
Do you know how hard I raised Ji Hoon?
I'd never give Ji Hoon to you.
Not a chance. I'll never give you my son, okay?
- Here you go. Enjoy. - Thank you.
How many bottles are you drinking?
Look at the empty bottles.
Can you see them?
Today's is a very special and lucky day.
From New York to Seoul.
We have flied thousands of miles and met here in Bangbae-dong again.
It's such an amazing miracle, isn't it?
Come on. Let's make another toast.
You're a heavy drinker.
I was a good student, too.
That's hard to believe.
You're really bad at recognizing good people.
You're also very slow-witted, too.
Tell me about you, then.
Who are your parents?
As you know, my uncle is my parent.
Do you have siblings?
I have a younger brother.
Do you have a girlfriend, then?
I don't.
I knew you wouldn't.
What kind of girls do you like?
I like elegant and calm person.
That's exact opposite of me.
It's good, isn't it?
You may not believe it, but I have boyfriends...
in 150 countries I traveled except Korea.
I don't believe it.
And I'm not jealous either.
But...
I didn't have one in New York.
What do you mean?
Please fill my last glass. That's all for today.
Help me. Please help me.
I need money to feed my baby. Please help me.
- Sorry. Excuse me. - Please. Please.
Here are your sandwich and coffee.
- Thank you so much. - No problem.
- Enjoy your meal. - Thank you.
Please, Sir.
I need money to feed my baby. My baby is hungry. Please.
Please.
My baby is hungry. Please, Sir.
It's freezing today.
Don't let your baby catch a cold.
Thank you, Sir. Thank you very much.
Bless you, Sir. Happy holiday. Thank you.
Thank you, Sir. Thank you.
I've gone through the report on closing accounts you wrote.
So we made a great deal of profit...
- through the existing marketing. - Thank you.
Anyway,
do you really have to produce dramas?
Dad!
I need you to stay silent.
Director Han, I'm a businessman.
I'm a very cool-headed businessman.
I never invest in business that's unprofitable.
I appointed Mi Joo to the director of Outdoor Department.
Then, one day,
she created Contents Team and has been hit it off with you...
for few years.
Why are you talking about it out of the blue?
I said be quiet.
I'm here to suggest you to stop such expensive dates...
with my daughter.
I'm sure we'll make profits this time.
I promise you. Contents Team will make profits this time.
When and how?
I, Bang Gwang Jin,
gave you three years of time, and it's a very long time for me.
I believe that any business...
with no profit in three years must be abolished.
There's more. There's 200 million dollars of deficit all of a sudden.
How will you explain it to me?
Is that true that you were scammed...
by a coordinator in Shanghai?
Fine.
That's enough.
Give up the business. Director Han,
work at the Management Support Team.
Dad.
Why? Did I offend you?
No, Sir.
And what are you...
going to do with Mi Joo?
Will you just sit back and watch the rumors widespread like now?
(Scene, Prison)
(Print)
("Theoretical Love", Episode 1)
(Mini-series, Oh Dong Hui)
Moong Chi, it's snowing.
It's the first snow of the season.
Your brother is late today, right?
Please don't mind what my dad said.
Seong Joon.
Let's go.
I'll make sure to maintain the Contents Team in any means,
so don't be frustrated.
I'm not frustrated.
I'm disappointed at my own competence.
Seong Joon.
Moong Chi.
Here's my good girl.
I'm late, aren't I?
I'm sorry.
I should have come earlier and played with you.
You didn't have dinner, right? Let's have dinner.
I fed her already.
- You're still up. - Yes.
You came home late.
I did.
- Did you have drink? - I had a little.
Did something bad happen? You don't look good.
I'm fine.
Nothing happened.
I see.
Please take this.
("Theoretical Love" by Oh Dong Hui)
This is the rental fee for the laptop.
You said you want to see my script when it's done.
("Theoretical Love" by Oh Dong Hui)
Well...
you really finished it.
I'm not finished yet.
It's a proposal for a 16-episode drama,
and scripts for first two episodes.
I see. You stayed in your room to finish these.
I'm proud of you.
Read them downstairs.
Okay.
I'll finish reading them tonight and give you some feedback tomorrow.
It's late. Go get some sleep.
It's snowing.
Good night.
Good job on finishing it. I'll read them thoroughly.
Okay.
She's a handful.
Excuse me.
Hey, wake up.
Honey, don't worry too much.
I'm sure the result will say...
Ji Hoon is our son.
Can't you see?
I graduated from a law school.
Our smart son, Ji Hoon takes after me.
Also,
he has long legs just like me.
Just like me,
he has resilient buttocks.
He has resilient buttocks and his buttocks are not sagging.
He resembles me.
Because he takes after you,
he is so clean.
After he takes a shower,
he cleans the whole bathroom with a towel.
Just like you who haven't weighed more than 45kg,
he's slim unlike Chang Soo.
Wait...
Mom. Mom.
What's the matter with you?
Stay quiet, mom.
I told you to pay me for the kimchi.
Why are you looking through the old photos?
What's going on?
What is it?
What are you looking at?
Mom...
Was I fat when I was in middle school?
Why do you ask?
Are you seriously asking us that?
You always said that we favored Seong Hoon.
You thought we gave good food to your brother and you got so greedy.
You were as fat as Chang Soo.
What's wrong with you?
It's nothing, Mom.
What's going on?
It's nothing, Dad.
What is it, Uncle?
I mean...
It's nothing.
Where did you get that bow tie?
Why do you have it on?
We have a musical at school before our winter break.
I need to sing and dance.
I came upstairs to ask what Grandmother thinks.
- Is that so? - Yes.
- You... - Yes?
Come here.
What are you doing?
Don't move.
This brings me back some old memories.
Should I put it in a frame?
Hold on.
What is it?
Ji Hoon, I'll get going.
Please get better soon, okay?
I'll visit you again. Get better.
What a nice child.
Come inside, Mom.
Why would you bring it? It's heavy.
Because you won't come. So I brought it even though I'm old.
- So what? - Wasn't the road slippery?
The snow melted.
Hey,
don't fight with your daughter. Invest in her.
How can I invest in her more?
It's enough that I fed, clothed, and educated her.
I don't mean it financially.
Show more affections to your daughter.
Moms and daughters give and take as well.
You need to give her more love now...
so that you won't be lonely later.
I won't be lonely.
I'm certain you will be.
There's something you don't know.
A pigeon and a crow come to my balcony...
in the morning.
So do you talk to them?
They're better than my daughter sometimes.
What's going to happen when you are sick and old?
I won't be sick.
No, you will be.
Don't be so sure.
My insurance covers caregivers, too.
What if you pass away...
when the caregiver is gone?
Don't worry about that, too.
When I turn 77 years old,
I'll head to Switzerland.
I'm going to apply for euthanasia.
I've already prepared the fee, too.
Hey.
How dare you say those words to your mother?
Why would you go all the way to Switzerland wasting all that money?
Why don't you die here? What a horrible daughter.
You're hurting me, Mom.
I'm hitting you to hurt you. I'm not trying to tickle you.
- My gosh. - Jeong Eun.
- Goodness. - Come out, Jeong Eun.
Listen to what your mother's saying.
Learn from her and act just like her in front of her.
That's how she will know how I feel.
Mother, Jeong Eun is not here.
- Why isn't she here? - Didn't she sleep at your house?
- She's not at your house? - What?
- Where did she... - Where did she...
- sleep last night? - sleep last night?
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
I have two children. Please.
Please forgive me this one time.
How can you do such a thing when you have children?
- We must send him to jail. - That's right.
You need to experience what you did.
- We should teach him a lesson! - Yes!
Shame on you.
- How could you do that? - That's right.
- You're waste of space. - You should be ashamed of yourself.
- How can you do this? - You jerk.
- Shame on you! - What a jerk.
What is this?
Where am I?
My gosh.
How can you kick me out just because the landlord has changed?
Hey. Do you know how much premium I paid for this store?
Who should I ask for the premium?
If I can't get it back, my family will have to live on the street.
This is so upsetting.
All right.
It's 10 dollars.
I drank too much last night.
Did you live here before by any chance?
No. That can't be right.
Have a good day.
(Mina Supermarket)
You should get started.
Oh, my.
No!
You jerk! What are you doing?
Stop it!
Stop!
I said stop!
(Kanghan Hospital)
- What? - What?
What did you say? That's...
What did you just say to us?
Dr. Kang. Please tell us again.
What happened?
According to the DNA test,
it's confirmed that Han Chang Soo isn't...
the biological son of Seo Hye Joo and Han Seong Hoon.
- Excuse me? - And...
it's also confirmed that Han Ji Hoon isn't...
the biological son of Kang Hee Sook and Han Seong Sik, either.
That's... I can't believe this is happening.
What... What are you saying?
Please forgive me.
I'm so sorry.
I should have delivered the right baby.
- What? - I delivered two babies at once.
Please forgive me.
So?
What are you trying to say?
- Dr. Kang! - I sincerely apologize.
According to the DNA test,
it shows that...
your sons have been switched.
The possibility of Ji Hoon being your son...
is 99 percent.
Also, Seong Hoon...
and Hee Sook.
The possibility of Chang Soo being your son...
is 99 percent.
I'm so sorry.
What kind of nonsense is this?
How can... This is absurd!
It's total nonsense!
Are you sure that the DNA test is accurate?
Unfortunately, yes.
I'm truly sorry.
Goodness... Min Seok!
Please forgive us.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Seong Hoon.
What are they saying?
What are they...
Hye Joo.
Don't be ridiculous.
Do you think I will believe you?
Do you think I will believe this?
Not a chance. I will...
run the DNA test again.
Hee Sook... Hee Sook!
Hee Sook!
Honey. Wake up.
Hye Joo!
Hee Sook.
Where is he?
Hee Sook. Hee Sook!
Hee Sook!
- Aunt. - You...
- You... You brat. - Wait.
Why aren't they taking it when we told them to?
Are they trying to get out of paying me for the kimchi?
Gosh. How can you think that?
Are the kids home? The light is on.
Why are you doing this to me, Aunt?
Why are you doing this?
It sounds like Chang Soo is crying.
- Hee Sook. - I said come here.
- Aunt... - Run, Chang Soo.
- Come here. - Hee Sook.
Wait, Hee Sook.
Aunt. Why are you doing this to me?
- You're scaring me. - Hee Sook.
Stop it already.
- Stay out of the way. - Why are you... Gosh.
I said come here. Why won't you listen to me?
- Why won't you? Give me your hair. - Hee Sook. Wait.
Give me your hair. Get off of me.
Give me your hair. Give it to me!
- Get off of me! - Hee Sook!
What are you doing?
What? What did you just say?
Your sons have been switched?
Yes.
Oh, dear.
- Mother. - Hee Sook.
Don't worry. It's not true.
It's not true.
She is...
What's wrong with her? Oh, my. Hyung Seop.
I know I'm right.
- I'm sure it's true. - It's only a rumor.
Anyway, they don't seem happy.
- I told you I'm sure of it. - Do you know anything?
It does look strange.
We have to hire a star writer,
and air the show no matter what.
And we must make a hit. That's the only option we have.
I guess so.
That's the only way to protect those people.
Wait around for a while. I have a meeting with the directors.
Let's have a glass of wine afterwards.
I'm having dinner with our team.
- Go, Marketing Team! - Go, Contents Team!
- Cheers! - Cheers! It's good to be here.
Director Han. Let me pour you a drink.
Okay.
You're so wild, Director Han.
My dear Director Han,
let me pour you a drink this time.
You're going to knock it back again, right?
- Slam it! Bottoms up! - Bottoms up!
He drinks a lot because he's still young.
Are you going to pour me a glass?
Gosh, thank you.
What are you doing, rookie? Drink that, and let me pour you another.
Okay.
Don't try to get out of drinking. You should knock it back,
and flip the glass above your head.
Okay.
Good.
Anyway, hang in there, everyone. We can do it!
Let's all say, "We can do it."
- We can do it! - We can do it!
- Drink up! - Yes!
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
Why did I ask her to sleep here? I can't believe this.
I guess I won't be able to sleep anymore.
It looks like loneliness and snoring are big problems for old people.
We'll get going now, Sir.
Ms. Hong and Ms. Na, you can go home yourselves, right?
Don't mind us and take care of Mr. Park.
He's totally drunk.
I love you, everyone.
You should love your wife instead.
Go on.
Our handsome Director Han, we'll go and have a couple of more drinks.
I'll see you. Please don't drink too much
We always drink too much.
Are you okay? You drank quite a lot.
I'm okay.
We should go, too.
Seong Joon.
Where did you say you live, Dong Hui?
Me?
I live in Cheonho-dong.
Where in Cheonho-dong? I'll drop you off.
No, I'm fine.
Let me get off here. I can go home by myself.
It's fine.
We're going to a hotel near there to drink wine.
I can drop you off on the way.
Seong Joon. It seems like you drank a lot.
Are you feeling okay?
After dropping off Dong Hui, let's just have some...
hangover food instead of wine.
I'm fine. Focus on your driving.
I should have called chauffeur service.
No. I don't like to be disturbed by others when I'm with you.
You're still wearing that watch.
We bought one for each when we were on...
a business trip to Switzerland together.
You still wear that.
I hope you're not offended by what my dad said.
He's being hard on you because he thinks you'll be...
his successor.
We shouldn't talk about that now.
Oh, my. Can you pretend you didn't hear that, Dong Hui?
We haven't made it official at the company.
Okay.
Seong Joon, I spilled coffee. There should be some tissues there.
I'm so clumsy.
I should be more composed when I get married.
Don't you think?
Is this your house, Dong Hui?
Yes.
I didn't know there were still houses like this in Seoul.
Well... I'll get going, then.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Dong Hui.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Stop it already!
Many people still live in places like that.
Dong Hui. Why aren't you answering my calls?
I worked so hard to raise my son.
I worked hard to raise my son, too.
I'm not your boyfriend or husband.
My mom and my family don't like me very much.
Am I really...
Aunt's son?
Thank you for everything.
Why do you worry about me?
I'm sorry about that, but I meant it.