BioskopKeren
(Episode 12)
Is this where you live, Dong Hui?
Yes.
I never knew there was such a shabby town in Seoul.
It's creepy.
Mi Joo.
Well... I'll get going, then.
Thank you.
See you, Dong Hui.
Why do you look so anxious?
I'm fine.
You're strange today.
By the way, I can't believe that Dong Hui lives in such town.
I can't never live there even if I get paid.
It was shocking to find out such a backward region in this city.
Why don't they redevelop the town?
They should bulldoze out and rebuild a new town to make Seoul clean,
right?
It was so spooky.
I thought it was a shooting place.
Let's shoot our dramas in that neighborhood.
I guess we have found a good location today.
Please stop.
Why?
What's the matter with you?
Please stop it already!
What's wrong? What makes you burst out?
It's your attitude.
What's wrong with my attitude?
How could you say that in front of her?
I just said the town she lives in is creepy,
not herself.
You may not know, but not only in Seoul,
but also in Korea, many people still live in places like that.
(Ms. Oh Dong Hui)
(Mr. Seo Cheol Min)
What's gotten into you all of a sudden?
Did I do anything wrong?
We all live in a different circumstance.
Why do you never bother to care about others' feelings?
That's ridiculous, Seong Joon.
So you want me to care about her feelings?
Are you taking on Dong Hui's side in front of me?
Did you just say I should care about how she'd feel?
I didn't mean to offend her. The building was too old,
so I just said what I felt.
Am I wrong?
Whether you're right or wrong, that doesn't matter at all.
You should think how others would feel before you speak.
That's their one and only home.
Do you know how terrible it sounded...
when you said it should be bulldozed out?
So what?
Are you saying I should apologize to Dong Hui...
for despising her place?
Mi Joo!
Fine, I am sorry. That was too much.
I know you hate when I'm being rude,
but I've become sensitive because of my dad.
Seong Joon!
Dong Hui, please answer the phone.
(Director Han)
Dong Hui. Dong Hui.
Dong Hui.
Please go to Bangbae-dong.
The number you have dialed is not in service.
(Director Han)
(10 missed calls)
The number you have dialed is not in service.
(9.70 dollars)
I am sorry, but I will get off here. I am sorry.
Wait, can you stop the car?
(Director Han)
(11 missed calls)
Why aren't you picking up my calls?
Why won't you pick up my calls?
Do I have to take your calls?
I was worried. You made me worried.
Why don't you listen to me? Why won't you pick up the phone?
It's funny.
Isn't it?
Why would you be worried about me?
You could have just said that you live in Bangbae-dong.
Our house is not the only house in Bangbae-dong, is it?
But we couldn't get off together.
We can't say that we live in the same town.
I already know...
that I put you in a difficult situation at work.
So how could I?
What are you doing?
You must be crazy.
Do you think you are the only one who drank?
I drank, too.
Do you think you're the only one who's drunk? I'm drunk, too.
But still...
What am I suppose to do?
Dong Hui. Dong Hui.
- Let go of me! - Let go!
Let go!
You can't do this.
You can't do this to us.
I gave my everything to this store.
I came here day and night for the past 30 years.
I spent all my youth working here.
You sold this building, didn't you?
Where's the building owner?
Let me meet the owner. You know who it is.
Let go of me.
You should've left when I offered to pay. Why are you doing this now?
This is wrong. You can't do this to me.
I've been a good person all my life.
- Oh, dear. - What's happening to our town?
It's so unsettling.
I heard that someone is buying up the buildings here.
What's going on?
Hey, you must know everything. Who will be the next?
You should share such information with neighbors.
Stop right there.
It's your uncle who bought my building, right?
Where is he? Tell me where he is now!
What are you doing? Please calm down.
I need to see him right now. I can't move out like this.
I can't reach him right now.
I don't get to meet him these days.
My goodness.
So your uncle is the owner of this building?
Didn't you just hear him?
Ma'am, you can't do this here.
Bring him here!
Tell him to come here right now.
Mr. Lee, are you all right?
Are you out of mind? Come here.
- I said stop it. - Get off. Let go of me.
Do you want to see me die here?
Go find him right now.
Bring your uncle here now.
This is so unfair.
I can't live like this.
We didn't steal anything. It wasn't us!
How dare you lie to me?
What's that snack your brother is holding, then?
Stop crying!
Don't hit my brother.
My brother didn't steal it.
A passer-by gave this to him!
Who on earth would give snacks to kids like you?
I can't let it slide. You're just like your father.
I'll teach you some lessons today.
Come here.
Go find him right now.
Bring your uncle here now.
This is nonsense. I'm going to die.
What are you doing here?
Did you think I wouldn't be able to find you?
Can you see me?
I'm looking at you right now.
I guess you have shame at least.
You ran away...
and even hid when you saw me.
I am sorry. I drank too much that day.
I knew what kind of person you were,
so it's not surprising at all.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's wrong with me, either.
I'm really doing my best...
to be girlish and modest.
What did you just say?
But...
it seems impossible.
I've tried in my entire life,
but I always end up like that.
I'm really bad at romance.
The beginning may be romantic,
but it turns out to be comedy or horror.
Speaking of it,
on that night...
What about that night?
Did you do anything...
to me by any chance?
What?
I'm so sorry. I did it again.
I always try not to speak what's on my mind,
but I speak it out in spite of myself.
You're bleeding!
You should work in the office.
You got hurt because you're working at a construction site.
- I can do it myself. - Stay still.
If you don't treat it now, it'll leave a big scar.
So why did you...
make such reckless investment?
I can't believe you bankrupted that big company.
Look how you ended up now.
Right, I promised you not to mention your company.
I'm sorry.
Gosh, it must hurt a lot.
Did you have lunch?
Sorry?
All I have is ramyeon.
My goodness. This isn't a place where a person lives.
Look, there's nothing in your fridge.
I'd better bring my aunt's kimchi here.
Stop. Let me do it.
I'm good at making ramyeon.
Hyun Woo!
It's ready. Come eat some.
What?
You want 50 percent of the profit of my cafe?
I asked neither for the deposit nor the rent.
This is not a bad deal.
I have to stand there and work all day long to make money,
and you'll take 50 percent for doing nothing? It's too much.
Please don't blame me.
That's all I can do for you.
Your uncle is such a cold-hearted person.
So will you sign the contract or not?
This is not fair.
I need to meet with your uncle.
What will you do, then?
I'll persuade him.
You said you're not good at it.
What if you end up in a ridiculous or a horrible situation?
Darn it.
Please, come on. You said it'll be all right.
- Please let me meet him. - What's wrong with you?
Tell me what you're going to do.
- Come on. Let me see him. - Hey.
You're so mean.
What do you mean your kids are switched?
What on earth are you talking about?
Why are you crying?
Stop and explain it to me.
Someone has to explain what happened to me.
Are you in, Ms. Hwang?
Ji Hoon and Chang Soo are switched?
Are you joking me now?
Wait,
what did you just say?
How on earth could this happen?
This is total nonsense.
They were switched at the hospital?
It's my fault. I lived too long.
If I hadn't, I wouldn't have to see this ridiculous situation.
Hyung Seop and Jeong Ae, why are you so silent?
Say something.
You should say something...
as their grandparents.
We're also about to go out of mind.
This is way too ridiculous.
I can't believe such nonsense actually happened.
How can this absurd thing I saw on television...
happen to our family?
You can't call yourselves parents.
You've raised them for 15 years.
How could you not notice that your kids are switched?
It's not their fault.
They must have been shocked the most.
Hye Joo...
How is Hye Joo doing now?
She has almost lost her mind.
She didn't even to go work today.
Tell Hee Sook to come here.
Grandma,
She's also in shock,
and failed to pull herself together.
That's understandable.
We must take care of their moms...
more than the kids.
What if they fall seriously ill?
I devoted my life to raise him.
Do you think you're the only one who devoted your life to your son?
I also dedicated my whole life for Chang Soo!
Do you want to go to Jongno?
Do you want to go to Youngdeungpo?
Or should we head to Cheongnyangni?
Honey.
You just got home. Aren't you tired? Please go to sleep.
Chang Soo isn't sleepy yet.
Do you want to go to Jongno?
Do you want to go to Youngdeungpo?
Is that a new song?
Yes, Chang Soo likes this song.
Why does he like trot songs?
He's so clever that he already knows what life is really about.
You're such a lovely boy. Dear my Chang Soo.
I'm sure he'll be a good student as he's awake until late at night.
Good boy.
Let's study every night with me.
Okay?
Do you want to go to Jongno?
What are you doing? Aren't you going to sleep?
What are you doing, honey?
My Leonardo isn't sleeping.
What? Leonardo?
You...
Get out.
Okay. I'll sleep. Hold on.
I'll be quiet.
Ji Hoon, I finished your science homework.
So don't worry about anything. Just study hard and come home.
You should've told me about school supplies before, so I can get them.
Where would I get 30 yogurt bottles out of the blue?
Anyway, I'll send you the empty bottles...
to your school by a delivery service. Okay?
Okay.
This is so cute.
This is his teacher's.
This is Ji Hoon's.
Gosh, I'm so busy.
Come on.
My goodness.
- Move it, Hye Joo. - Hey.
Hye Joo, get your kite away from mine.
I need to fly this before Ji Hoon gets here.
I have to take a picture.
Ji Hoon has to take a picture, too. It's his winter vacation homework.
- Come on. You're bothering me. - Go somewhere else, Hye Joo.
- Take yours away. - My goodness.
Hey. Hee Sook.
It's winter vacation at last.
Poor Ji Hoon. How can he be in the hospital on the day of our break?
I'm on my winter break.
Mother, this is Ji Hoon's uncle.
My gosh. Welcome.
Mr. Kang, what is going on?
I'm sorry.
I don't know...
what to say.
This is...
Chang Soo's great-grandmother.
My goodness.
Hello.
I sincerely...
apologize.
You can apologize later.
Dr. Kang, you need to explain...
what happened.
Let him sit down, first.
- Why don't you take a seat. - Okay.
I am going to...
sue you.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what else to tell you.
How could you...
ruin my family like this?
I'm about to lose my son...
who I raised and cherished for 15 years.
Do you think I'm going to let it go?
I will do everything in my power...
to put you in jail.
I sincerely apologize.
I don't have...
anything to say to you,
except that I am sorry.
I don't know how I caused you...
this horrendous accident in your family.
Mr. Han and Ms. Moon,
I am so sorry.
You should have done your job right.
How could you switch your own cousin...
with someone else?
Honey.
I apologize.
Mr. Han...
and Seong Sik,
I am incredibly sorry.
This is...
all my fault.
Mr. Kang.
- Please, don't. Please, get up. - No.
I deserved to be be punished.
Please, just kill me.
Please get up. Just because you're kneeling down,
we can't fix what's already been done.
What are we going to do?
What are you doing? Let him get up.
Please, stand up.
No.
So what?
If you really want,
I know a trustworthy laboratory.
- I can't trust my brother. - Exactly.
I'll send the samples again without informing Dr. Kang.
So please. Don't sue me.
Please don't sue me.
You'd better do it right this time.
Mr. Han, let me pour you a drink.
I am sincerely sorry.
It's not like you did it on purpose.
I'm just sad...
when I think about the children.
It's been a while.
I'm sorry to meet again in a predicament.
How's your hospital?
It's okay.
How are your daughters?
They're good.
Now I remember.
You told me that your youngest daughter is...
the same age as Chang Soo and Ji Hoon.
Yes, that's right.
Right now, she's in the States...
with her sisters and mother.
Goodness, all of your family live abroad.
That's right.
Actually,
my youngest daughter...
has a problem.
What kind of problem?
She's in a wheel-chair.
Her spine was seriously injured.
Really?
- Yes. - How did that happen?
My wife...
was just like my sister,
Hee Sook.
I won't say it again. Disband Contents and Marketing Department.
Dad.
You can't operate a business with a foolish dream.
A business man should make profits.
Until when are you going to waste your time and money?
Please allow a little more time.
Three years are enough.
- Disband the department. - Dad.
Seong Joon.
Writer Jo is coming back to Korea today. I must meet her.
Do you think you can? She already refused to meet with us.
I need to convince her.
If we get her, we might have a shot.
I heard that she is very stubborn.
I don't think she would reconsider.
I still have to try.
I can't just sit here and do nothing.
Okay. Give me a call when you meet.
I'll try to persuade my dad again.
Good luck.
If we don't get to air the show and have a hit drama, we are done.
Goodness, Contents Team is in trouble.
What are they going to do?
What is going on? Is there a problem?
Contents Team...
will be disbanded.
- Excuse me? - That's why...
Director Han is all over the place.
He's trying his best to save the team.
It won't look good on his resume as well.
He was leading the team for three years.
He will be criticized for its failure.
Poor Director Han.
If you take the half of the profit as the rental fee,
I have to pay the tax and other ingredients with the rest.
Then, there won't be any profit left from me.
I might even lose money.
So, I wrote...
the contract again.
You will take 10 percent as the rental fee.
How could you only give him 10 percent?
Stay out of it, please.
But you will get the money daily.
I will give you 10 percent of my profit everyday.
And for you and your nephew,
I will provide free cucumber sandwich and coffee.
You can even come everyday.
I will come right away...
whenever you or your nephew need me.
I will clean and do the laundry.
I will do everything like a house maid.
You can call me whenever.
All I have is my body.
How can you say such things as a lady?
Well,
do you think my offers are not good enough?
You are one brave lady just like Hyun Woo said.
Okay.
I will sign your contract.
Really?
President.
Thank you. I sincerely thank you.
I will make sure to pay the rent daily.
Thank you so much.
That's not where finishing materials go.
- You should go and help him. - Okay.
Thank you. I won't forget this.
What are you doing?
I'm just thanking you.
Why is Jeong Eun doing here?
What's the matter with you?
I just want to say thank you.
Did you have to hug me in front of everyone to thank me?
Did I do that?
Sorry.
I am not your boyfriend or your husband.
You're the nephew of my landlord.
Right. So why would you hug me?
Why are you smiling?
What is your plan today?
- Why? - If you have time,
could you go shopping with me?
Shopping?
I need to buy a lot of things to open the cafe.
Forget it. I'm busy.
If you don't come with me, I will tell everyone.
Tell everyone what?
Long time ago
- David Lee - Okay, fine.
You should have said yes at the first place.
How cute.
They are so nice.
They're so pretty.
I really wanted to have that.
Shouldn't you stay focused?
There are so many pretty things here.
I can see that, too.
Everything is pretty except you here.
How could you compare me to an object?
We're friends.
Who said that we are?
We had a meal and drank together.
Also, we are shopping together. That's what friends do.
Goodness. That is really cute.
Why are you buying so many cups?
You told me that it was a franchise.
Why can't I?
I really wanted to have those.
That's enough. We are done here.
Wait for me.
You don't need these.
You need to buy these.
They come in handy.
I don't know how to use the drill.
Who would hang them for me?
How should I know?
Maybe you can help me.
You're dreaming.
Wait for me.
Where have you been?
What's wrong?
How come you are always away?
Grandma, I am busy.
- How can you be busy? - I'm starting a business.
You should just get married.
Stop wandering off. How could you run a business?
Grandma.
What happened? What's gotten into you?
You are asking me that now?
Do you have a slightest idea what's happening in our family?
What's going on?
Grandmother.
I can't accept this.
How could something like this happen?
I'm sorry, Hye Joo.
What's going to happen to Chang Soo?
Grandmother.
I am...
never going to...
let go of my Chang Soo.
I will do whatever it takes...
to raise Chang Soo.
Of course, you will. I don't want to let go of Chang Soo, too.
What are we going to do?
Grandmother.
Hye Joo.
Poor Chang Soo.
Moong Chi, what is wrong?
I told you that you can't bark at night.
I'm so sad right now. I can't play with you now.
Moong Chi, I'm going to tell on you.
I was worried. You made me worried.
Did Moong Chi bark a lot?
Yes, a little.
Moong Chi, why did you bark?
I told you that you can't bark at night.
Do you want some treats?
Here you go.
You're home early.
Yes, I am.
Well,
I'm sorry...
about that night.
I'm sorry.
But...
I meant it.
Good night.
(DNA Test Result)
(The possibility of Han Chang Soo being your son is 99.9 percent.)
How... How can this be?
Hee Sook. Do you have the result?
What happened? Did the result come out?
"The possibility of..."
"Han Chang Soo being the biological son of..."
"Han Seong Sik and Kang Hee Sook is 99.9 percent."
"The possibility of..."
"Han Ji Hoon being..."
"the biological son of..."
"Han Seong Hoon and Seo Hye Joo is 99.9 percent."
What... What is this?
Seong Hoon. This is...
I can't accept this result.
- I'll find another institution. - Hee Sook.
Hee Sook.
Let go of me. I'll find another institution.
No, Hee Sook. Hee Sook!
- Let go of me! - Hee Sook!
Hee Sook. Hee Sook...
Hee Sook! Hee Sook!
Wake up!
Why would you think it's so complicated?
Just switch them back.
It's not like we're sending the kids to another family.
They're in the same family. It only makes Ji Hoon the eldest grandson.
I don't understand why you're taking it so seriously.
Be quiet, Ae Ri.
And to put it bluntly,
there are even total strangers...
who find out their kids have been switched.
Ji Hoon and Chang Soo are cousins, and they live together.
It's not that bad.
You should consider how their parents feel.
They've raised the kids for 15 years thinking they're their own sons.
Even if you say it's not that bad because they're cousins,
it won't comfort them.
Let me tell you a thing, Mom.
It doesn't make such a big difference whether the child...
is your own or not as time goes by.
Whether it's the child you raised and cherished,
or a stranger's child that you've never met, they're all the same.
My gosh. Sometimes,
a total stranger is better in some way.
So, let's not cling onto our children too much. Okay?
- Ae Ri. - That's...
Aunt.
What? Am I wrong?
- Get her out of here. - Let's go, Aunt.
What's the matter?
- Let's go. - Fine. I'll go,
- but you know I'm right. - Get her out.
- Think about it. - Get her out, lock the door,
- and sprinkle some salt. - Sprinkle a lot of it.
My gosh. What's wrong with her?
Goodness.
Ms. Oh.
I think it's time for us to make a decision.
But I don't know...
how we should handle this situation.
Tell me about it.
I don't know what to do, either.
I think...
this is all because their parents lack virtue.
Their parents lack virtue?
Their parents shouldn't have looked out for their children only.
They should have done...
many good deeds for the world, too.
Are you saying this happened...
because my children are sinful?
I'm just...
looking at the bigger picture.
I don't care if it's bigger or small.
You shouldn't say this in front of the kids.
Forget it. Let's stop.
Anyway, what are you going to do now?
Stop crying.
Seong Hoon.
I can't let him go.
I can never let him go.
You know that.
I know. I do. I'm his father, too.
I know...
Chang Soo isn't so smart,
but he is a perfect son.
He's nice, kind-hearted,
and cares his sister well.
He's good at playing games,
and he is...
such a fun person to play with.
He also sleeps 10 hours a day.
No one can sleep well and healthy like Chang Soo.
Also...
he eats...
everything so well.
All right. Let's just raise both Ji Hoon and Chang Soo.
No matter what I do, I'll make more money.
Let's just raise them both.
- Honey. - I know.
It's okay.
Aunt is in the hospital,
and Mom keeps crying.
I'm sure there is something going on in our house.
I'm the only one who doesn't know it.
What can it be?
What's going on in our house?
Grandma, it's me.
- What is it? - I was wondering how Hye Joo was.
- She must be crying a lot. - That's not all.
I'm worried that it might ruin her health.
What should we do? I feel terrible, too.
What can we do?
They should just follow their fate.
- Grandma. - You should focus on your work.
Keep your head on straight.
- I'm hanging up now. - Okay.
My gosh.
Producer Kim.
- Did you revise the budget? - I did.
I posted it online. Print it out right away.
- Dong Hui. Please print it out. - Okay.
Seong Joon!
Dong Hui.
Director Bang. Are you ready?
Yes. I got the contract ready for the investors.
We only have to make a contract with the writer now, right?
We can meet with Writer Jo within this week.
But we still need a backup plan,
so I set up meetings with Writer Kim Mi Kyung and Writer Lee Jung Min.
- I'll contact them just in case. - Let me come with you.
I know Writer Lee Jung Min.
I can convince her when it comes to the pinch.
Producer Kim. Please send an email to Writer Jo with a contract.
Okay. I will.
- Where is the budget bill? - Dong Hui.
Come on, Seong Joon.
Good luck, Director Han.
Things are going crazy in Contents Team.
How terrible.
We'll be fine.
Hang in there.
You said you'd do it, so please do it.
You're now...
treating me like your subordinate.
You said you'd do it.
When did I say that?
You said you'd do it. Think carefully.
You're renting this place for free, and I'm working for you for free.
Don't you think it's too much?
I'll make you delicious coffee in return.
You aren't going to sleep here, are you?
What's wrong with that?
You have a house to sleep in.
Do you like sleeping in the open?
Things are crazy at my grandma's house,
and I'm not on good terms with my mom.
That's why I set out on a trip,
and I met you in New York.
But even after I came back, nothing is different between me and my mom.
I guess your mother...
let you do this kind of things.
She neglected me even when I was just born.
So, if I make money from this cafe,
I'll go abroad again.
When I do,
I won't come back.
My mom...
and my family don't like me that much.
That's none of my business.
Hee Sook, we're home.
Just hang in there a little longer. Gosh, be careful.
Be careful, okay?
Hold on, Hee Sook.
Here you go.
My gosh.
Hee Sook.
Gosh, Hee Sook.
Please...
Please try to get your strength back.
Please get your strength back.
You should take care of your health, so you won't be sick again.
Okay, Uncle. Thank you for everything.
Goodbye.
All right, Ji Hoon. Get home safely.
Okay.
Really?
Yes.
Dad.
Mom.
No. You are...
my son.
Yes...
You're my son.
Hye Joo.
We are...
so sorry, Chang Soo.
No. I can't...
let him go. I can't let him go.
I can never do that.
I'll raise him.
I'll raise him. I'll raise him.
Am I really...
Aunt's son?
I'll raise him.
Mom...
We're all very sorry to you.
But sometimes, even grown-ups...
make mistakes.
Still,
this isn't something we can mess up with.
We are truly sorry.
That's why...
we want to hear your thoughts.
Chang Soo. Go ahead.
I'm grateful that my mom has raised me so far,
and I think she regrets that she hasn't been feeding me well.
I'll just...
continue to live with my parents.
Gosh, Seong Hoon.
My dear Chang Soo.
That's right, my baby.
Don't touch me, though.
You little...
Let's hear what Ji Hoon thinks.
I want...
to live in the basement.
Ji Hoon. What are you saying, you brat?
I'm grateful that my parents have raised me so far,
but now I've found my true parents.
I want to live with my true parents.
I'll move to downstairs right away.
Ji Hoon.
- Ji Hoon... - You brat!
What are you talking about?
Ji Hoon!
What happened?
You woke up.
I guess you were very tired.
You didn't sleep for two days. You must have been tired.
What about the company?
Go home and get some rest.
Don't go back to the company.
You stayed up all night at Writer Jo's workroom.
It's a relief that we convinced her.
We don't know that...
until she signs the contract.
I still think she is half convinced.
I heard Writer Jo talks a lot when it's close to signing the contract.
She doesn't even say a word if she doesn't want to do it,
but she talked to you a lot.
Of course. There aren't any women who won't talk to you.
Don't be silly.
Go on and sleep. I'll wake you up when we get to your house.
Moong Chi. Things are crazy at home.
We should stay outside.
Seong Joon. Get some rest.
Dong Hui.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I want to live with my true parents.
How can he be so cold-hearted?
Thank you for everything you've done for me.
Does his uncle have a grudge against people in Bangbae-dong?
Give me back my son, you jerk!
Do you expect me to believe that?
What do you want me to do?
I never told you we were in a relationship.
What does it have to do with me?
Is there someone you like, Dong Hui?
No.
Are you running away because you're scared?