BioskopKeren
Moong Chi. Things are crazy at home.
We should stay outside.
Seong Joon, have some rest.
Dong Hui.
What are you doing here?
Seong Joon.
Isn't it your dog?
What's going on between you two?
Well,
I can explain this.
Dong Hui, that's not necessary.
I'll explain instead.
I'll never make it to 100 years old.
I'm sure that I'll be watching down from above in the near future.
I'm about to lose my mind because of them.
Seong Joon, what are you doing here?
- Grandma. - Why didn't you come home?
What about you, Dong Hui?
Is Ms. Oh doing well?
Yes, she has calm down now.
I'm happy to hear that.
Who is this beautiful lady here?
Hello, Grandmother. I am Bang Mi Joo.
Ms. Bang Mi Joo?
Gosh, is she your girlfriend by any chance?
Well, Grandma...
I should have visited you earlier. It's nice to meet you.
My goodness. Are you really his girlfriend?
I'm very happy to meet you.
I never knew my grandson would...
bring his girlfriend home today.
I'm sorry. We can't let you in as we have some problem at home.
It's okay, Grandmother. I'll visit you soon again.
You came all the way here. I hope we can have a talk.
Well,
I'll get going, then.
See you, Dong Hui.
It's good that you're here, Seong Joon.
Please give me a ride to the church.
I will take you there, Grandmother.
Thank goodness.
I wished I could have some time with you.
I guess we can introduce ourselves in here.
What was your name again?
I am Bang Mi Joo.
That's such a lovely name.
What do your parents do?
- Grandma... - Stay quiet.
I don't know how you'd feel about it...
Her father is the president of the company I work for.
And Director Bang is my colleague.
I see.
My father really likes Seong Joon,
so he has a lot of work at the company.
He stayed up all night long for two days,
so I gave him a ride home.
Really? It's very nice to meet you.
Please visit us as soon as possible.
I will. Thank you, Grandmother.
My lord,
my entire family is in a huge shock.
My grandsons are switched.
I really don't know what to do.
My lord,
please help my grandsons...
- not to get a shock by this. - Why didn't you tell me earlier?
I had no clue so I misunderstood you.
Misunderstood me for what?
By the way, if the company finds this out,
you'll get in trouble.
Did you make sure that Dong Hui doesn't say anything about this?
Dong Hui understands me better than anyone else, so...
Is that why she said she lives in Cheonho-dong?
Was that because she cared about you?
Mi Joo.
As long as I know everything, it doesn't matter anymore.
I'll manage Dong Hui from now on,
so that she doesn't get in your way.
What do you mean by that?
Why?
Are you angry at me like the other day...
because I looked down on her?
You know my father is watching you.
If you miss this chance,
the three years of your hardworking...
will come to nothing.
Don't blame my rude attitude.
Please face the harsh reality.
It wasn't pointless after all...
as I could meet your grandmother.
You look lean.
Forget everything and get a good rest.
Hello, Ms. Oh.
Why are you here?
Well...
I came to see Moong Chi.
Dong Hui walked Moong Chi...
and came home a while ago.
I see.
- See you, then. - Thank you.
Dong Hui, it's me.
Can we talk for a while?
Dong Hui, please spare a moment.
We're all very sorry to you.
But sometimes, even grown-ups...
make mistakes.
That's why...
we want to hear your thoughts.
Tell us what you think first.
We think...
we have lived very differently so far.
You two also have grown up...
in very different environments.
So we think...
it'd be the best to just keep living as we've lived up until now.
However, we'll visit Chang Soo from time to time,
and my brother and Hye Joo will come here to visit Ji Hoon.
Moreover, isn't it perfect since we all live in the same house?
We can see and take care of you guys anytime.
That's right. Chang Soo, you can come here...
and have a meal anytime you want.
Chang Soo. Go ahead.
What do you think?
- First, - Okay.
I am upset.
- Okay. That's understandable. - We can understand that.
- That's right. - You can be upset.
- Of course. - Okay.
You tell me I am disorganized and distracted.
You nagged me that I'm dirty.
How can you, adults be so distracted that...
you don't even know your child is switched?
- That's right. We are sorry. - We're sorry.
We are sincerely sorry.
But I'm grateful that my mom has raised me so far,
and I think she regrets that she hasn't been feeding me well.
I'll just...
continue to live with my parents.
Honey.
Okay, Chang Soo. That's right, my baby.
Don't touch me, though.
You little...
Now we should listen to Ji Hoon's thought.
I want...
to live in the basement.
Ji Hoon. What are you saying, you brat?
- Han Ji Hoon. - I'm grateful that you raised me,
but now I've found my true parents.
I want to live with my true parents.
I'll move to downstairs right away.
- Ji Hoon... - You brat!
What are you talking about?
Ji Hoon. Honey.
- Let go of me. - Honey.
Honey, calm down. Compose yourself.
How can he do this to me? How?
What are we going to do?
Not a day goes by without someone causing trouble.
Father and Mother,
thank you for raising me. Take care.
Hey, Ji Hoon. How could you do this to your mother?
Honey, I can't let him go. I can't.
Honey, Honey.
Honey. Get up.
Honey. Ji Hoon.
Ji Hoon said he wanted to go downstairs?
Yes, that's what he wants.
How can he be so cold-hearted?
He's not even thinking about his parents who raised him.
He said he will just move to the basement?
He already moved. He even packed his own bag.
My goodness. Is that true?
What an ungrateful and apathetic child.
We were happy he was top of his class, but they raised him wrong.
How about Chang Soo?
He wanted to live with his parents,
but he is flustered seeing what Ji Hoon did.
That's how a child ought to be.
I mean Hee Sook...
nagged Ji Hoon a lot.
But still, that isn't an excuse. I might have expected this...
from Chang Soon, but not from Ji Hoon.
Ms. Oh, what do you think we should do about this?
What can we do?
He wants to go to his biological parents.
What?
We as adults...
and parents can't tell them what to do.
Children are the ones who are suffering the most.
We should let them do whatever they desire.
But Chang Soo doesn't want to leave his parents.
You should let Chang Soo go.
- Excuse me? - Excuse me?
How can we stop Ji Hoon if he wants to live with his biological parents?
We should let the child leave if he wants to leave.
Also, Chang Soo is stronger than Ji Hoon.
I'm sure he will adapt just fine.
I do agree on that, Ms. Oh.
When they live with their biological parents,
they will appreciate the parents who raised them.
As they adapt to their new environment,
they may mature if they are not now.
A cold-hearted child may turn into...
a warm-hearted child. Who knows?
After listening to you, you're right.
I keep thinking I lived too long.
Mother, what should we do?
What choice do we have? If they want to switch, then let them switch.
Chang Soo. My goodness.
- Chang Soo. - Mom.
I can't live like this.
- Chang Soo. - My goodness.
- I can't let him go. I can't. - Honey.
- I can't let him go. - Come here, Ah In.
- Chang Soo. - Father.
Please take care.
Thank you for raising me all these years.
My gosh.
This can't be happening.
This can't be true.
Let's go in.
Honey.
Our Chang Soo...
Chang Soo is here.
Hello,
Mother.
This isn't happening.
This can't be right.
Get out.
- Honey. - How can you be my son?
- Honey. - You are not my son.
- Get out. - Honey.
Why are you coming to my house so often?
Our house is in a chaos.
- I am so upset. - My goodness.
Everyone already knows that your children moved back in.
What? What did you say? This is getting too much.
- Drink up and leave. - My gosh.
Why aren't you drinking your coffee?
What's on your mind?
I shouldn't be drinking coffee now.
Why? Did something happen?
Few days ago, Mina Supermarket was bought out.
That's right. What happened to Mina Supermarket?
How can she get kicked out overnight?
The landlord kicked her out mercilessly.
He even mobilized thugs.
How can he bring in thugs?
It's not just Mina Supermarket.
You know Seo In Sook from Zumba class?
Her cold noodle restaurant was also bought out.
She didn't get her premium back when she was kicked out.
Don't you think it's strange?
One day, someone acquired all the buildings in Bangbae-dong.
And they are all knocked down.
The tenants are being kicked out without getting their premium back.
That's what real estate dealers do to make money.
But then...
the problem is that one person is buying up all the property.
- Who is that? - He is an uncle of your neighbor.
By any chance, have you seen him?
No. I've only seen that man, not his uncle.
Why? He is kind and amiable.
Does his uncle have something against Bangbae-dong?
Ever since he moved into the neighborhood, it's been chaotic.
This isn't the first time.
Don't you remember the accident 23 years ago?
- My children could have died. - Hey.
What would you bring that up?
I didn't bring it up first. Dr. Yoon brought it up first.
That's right. It's not a good subject to talk about.
My daughter Jeong Hwa was hurt, too. That was crazy.
Do you know how scared we were?
But our children lived luckily.
- Only the driver was dead. - Hey.
- Good bye. - Get on the bus carefully.
- Good bye. - Okay, good bye.
Okay.
Mind the steps.
Everyone, put on your seat belt.
- We will. - Okay.
- Please drive carefully. - I will.
- I'll be back. - Okay.
(Geumbit Academy)
The weather is strange today.
- You promised. - Did you really do it?
- I don't like it. - What about this?
This is so hilarious.
What's wrong?
Get out!
(Geumbit Academy)
- Hey! Kids! - There are kids inside.
Open the door!
Let's rescue the kids first.
Call 911 now.
Gosh, stop it.
I don't want to know details of the tragedy.
She's right. Stop it. That's a sad incident.
Fine. I won't talk any more.
By the way,
I heard that the driver...
- Hey! - Hey!
You know the driver committed suicide...
after the accident.
I said stop it.
Listen to me.
I heard that he had...
two sons back then.
Where would his sons be now?
Did he have children?
He did. He had two sons.
He's my father.
He met undeserved death...
in this town 23 years ago.
That's when I lost my brother.
I'll take my father's revenge...
and find my brother.
I'll do by any means.
What happened to Dad?
No. You shouldn't look at it.
Don't look at it, Sang Woo.
Sir.
What is it?
We've signed the contract to merge the company.
We agreed to write off its 120 million dollars...
and to hire all its employees.
Then, the Korean branch of Golden Street...
will take over the company.
How is the property purchase in Bangbae-dong going on?
We should renew the rental contract...
with Principal Kim Geum Ja of Geumbit Academy next week.
Would you do it yourself, Sir?
Of course, I will. I'm your proxy.
People's face reflects their life.
She's the one who humiliated so many people.
I'd like to see how her face has changed.
Right, I also pushed ahead with the contract...
with Han Jeong Eun and had her sign it.
Thank you.
It might become tiresome, but it'd be better to have...
such a loosen canon near me.
By the way,
she is a pretty cute lady.
What do you mean she's cute?
I apologize.
I'll head to the site.
Okay.
Watch out!
Someone already fell off a few days ago.
Okay.
I said be careful.
Be careful.
I will.
I am sorry.
Hello.
You're here today.
Why are you here?
I brought you coffee and sandwiches.
Hello, please have some coffee and sandwiches.
Thank you.
Come out, everyone!
- Okay! - Let's drink coffee.
What's going on?
Please take this.
Where are you taking me to?
Why does she show up here every day?
Seriously.
Why are you doing this to me? It really hurts.
Why do you keep coming to my working place?
What did you say?
How can you say such mean things to me?
Have you already forgotten what happened between us?
What do you mean by that?
I think we have a pretty special relationship.
And you even let me rent this cafe...
at a really low rent.
So,
I rented this place for almost free,
went shopping with you...
and even installed that for you.
Don't you think you should stop showing up in front of me, then?
What's wrong with you today?
It's like you've returned to the cold-hearted David Lee.
You'd been so sweet to me until yesterday.
When have I been sweet to you?
Forget it.
I knew you'd never change. I shouldn't have trusted you.
It's not I went there because I wanted.
Wait here.
Look at this.
This is the contract.
According to this,
I should provide you cucumber sandwiches and coffee every day.
In return, I just need to pay you 10 percent of the profit...
for rent, which is almost impossible in Bangbae-dong.
So I must visit you every day although I really don't want to.
Who made this contract?
What do you think? Of course, it's your uncle and me.
I'll tell my uncle to revise the contract.
- Sorry? - So please,
stay inside your cafe, okay?
Hey! Stop there!
What's wrong? He's so fickle.
He must have some issues.
As you've seen, Director Han and I are in-laws.
But the reason Director Han signed...
a contract with my brother isn't because we're in-laws.
I know that better than anyone.
Director Han isn't a man who would do such a thing.
I didn't know about it until a while ago.
I didn't know that the company...
my brother conned was Director Han's company.
And my brother doesn't know about it yet.
Do you think I can believe it?
Do you think it makes sense that in-laws failed...
to recognize each other?
You may not believe it,
but we haven't seen each other since my sister's wedding.
And I was only 10 at that time.
I'm doing my best not to cause him...
further trouble.
I am really sorry.
If you really don't want to cause him any trouble and are sorry,
how can you keep working...
at the same company with him while living in the same house?
He'll get in trouble if the company finds this out.
Do you know about this?
They'll think he's a shameless jerk...
who contracted with his relative,
got stabbed in his back, and hired his another relative.
If you really cared about Director Han,
you shouldn't have worked here in the first place.
Did you think you'd be able to fool everyone...
if you just say you live in Cheonho-dong?
Then,
please tell me what I should do.
Why don't you think of it yourself?
Do I even have to tell you that?
- What time are you meeting her? - At 5pm in the writing room.
We're going to have dinner afterwards.
- Do you have the contract ready? - Of course, I do.
Director Han, it's almost rush hour soon. We need to hurry.
Okay.
I don't have the storyboard for the commercial. I asked ages ago.
Ms. Hong, is this how you are going to work?
This is why the Contents Team might be disbanded.
Because you recruited Writer Jo, do you think you'll survive?
That's Marketing Team's job to do.
I believe you were supposed to finish it.
The proposal for the commercial was Dong Hui's idea.
Is that so? Was it Dong Hui's idea?
Who knew you could do such thing?
Then why don't you make the storyboard, too?
- Me? - Yes, you.
Since it was your idea, come up with a storyline like a drama.
Okay, I will.
Do your work hard.
You are getting paid for your work.
("They lie down side by side.")
I'm sorry. Please drive.
Cheol Min.
- Who are you? - Stay out of it.
It's dangerous. You need to run.
Why didn't you pick up my calls?
Why aren't you answering my calls?
I was worried about you. You made me worry.
("Look into each other's eyes.")
If you really cared about Director Han,
you shouldn't have worked here in the first place.
He'll get in trouble if the company finds this out.
Do you know about this?
You are home.
Ms. Hong told me that you stayed late at the office by yourself.
I just got home.
Did you?
Are you okay?
What do you mean?
About everything.
The time Director Bang came to my house...
How does that concern me?
That can happen.
You two work together and are dating each other.
I never said we were dating.
Why would you assume that?
I'm sorry if I did.
But nothing changes.
I'm okay. Don't worry about me.
Good bye.
Ji Hoon.
As your aunt,
I mean as your mother...
This is a bit too much.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I can understand.
Hey.
Just because you are smart,
don't understand things too quickly.
I'm sorry.
Come here.
Let me hug you for once.
What? Hug me?
Yes. Don't you know how to hug?
- Let's hug. - I mean...
I know that.
Why? Didn't Hee Sook ever hug you?
Maybe when I was little.
I don't remember much, though.
But when I grew up, she didn't.
What?
How can she do that to my son?
I'm sorry. To be Aunt's...
I mean...
As your son,
I know I am not good enough.
I'm sure you gave me birth the best you can.
I'm sorry to have turned out to be...
an inadequate student.
Even though you might hate me,
please raise me until I turn 20 years old.
Then, I will voluntarily...
leave the house.
Please raise me until I turn 20 years old.
Honey, what are you doing to Chang Soo?
Chang Soo, get up.
I think she is angry because of me.
Come on, Chang Soo.
But that doesn't mean you should kneel down.
Get up now. Get up.
Are you okay, Chang Soo?
I'm okay. I've done this a lot at school.
Be quiet.
What are you going to do?
What else can you do instead of accepting him?
Do you think you're the only one who's having a hard time?
But still, honey...
This is the reality.
I know it will be difficult,
but we should accept him little by little.
Chang Soo.
- Yes. - Aunt...
I mean...
Don't be disheartened by your mother.
- Okay. - As your uncle...
My goodness. I'm going crazy.
Let's just...
- eat ramyeon. - Okay.
I'll cook it right away,
Father.
"Father"?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I wondered...
why ramyeon you cook for me...
suits my taste.
Does it? I bet it does suit your taste.
- Hey, Mr. Han. - Yes.
Clean up the trash on the third floor.
Okay, I will.
How long are you going to stay on the second floor?
I will move on right away.
I'm sorry.
Why aren't you taking a shower?
You climbed a mountain. You should get washed up and sleep.
What are you doing?
Jeong Ae.
What is it?
We get pensions, right?
What about it?
How much do we get per month?
Do you even have to ask? It's chicken feed.
Why?
What if...
we cancel it...
and open up a shop for Seong Hoon with that money?
What?
Don't yell at me right away.
What on earth are you talking about?
Ji Hoon is now living with his family.
He'll have to spend more money to educate him.
He has children to support, but he doesn't have a job.
He does have a job. He goes out to work every morning.
I'm saying this because I don't think it's a decent job.
Still, we can't cancel our pensions to open up a shop for him.
We can ask him to give us the profit he makes.
- It's something you're good at. - I know you wouldn't do that.
The only things we're counting on are...
our pensions and the apartment downstairs.
Our children already took away the apartment downstairs.
Are you saying we have to give up our pensions for them, too?
I'm not saying we have to give it up.
I'm just saying we should invest it.
That's enough. I know what you're thinking.
Don't be ridiculous. My goodness.
You're a evil woman like a witch.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
Let's get divorced instead.
- What? - Let's get a divorce,
sell this house, and split the money.
I'll open up a shop for Seong Hoon with that money.
I can't believe this.
My goodness. What did you just say?
Oh, dear. I just...
I don't believe this.
You can turn the light on.
It's okay.
I heard your company makes TV dramas.
Yes.
Then you should try harder.
Only then you'll achieve your dream and become a scriptwriter.
I'm doing my best.
Did you see Chang Soo?
Yes. I went out and ate tteokbokki with him.
What about Ji Hoon?
Hye Joo brought him here to introduce him to me earlier today.
When you're home,
let's invite him here and have a meal together.
Okay.
Anyway,
I feel bad that...
his great grandmother lives in a place like this.
Grandma.
Dong Hui. Let's move out of here as soon as possible.
Okay. I think we should do that, too.
What brings you here at this hour?
Darn it.
Hyung Seop. What's wrong?
Mom.
I'm going to divorce Jeong Ae.
What?
- What did you say he said? - He said..
we should get our pensions in advance,
and open up a shop for Seong Hoon with that money.
Why is he talking about opening up a shop all of a sudden?
He said Seong Hoon will have to spend more money...
to educate Ji Hoon now. When I said no,
he said he will divorce me.
What?
He will divorce me, sell this place, split the money,
and open up a shop for Seong Hoon.
Mother. Can you believe that?
He called me a witch...
because I'm mean to my children.
How can we survive if I'm not?
All we've got left is our pensions. How can I let him cancel it?
But he's being so stubborn and unreasonable.
He's just crazy about his children, Mother.
Gosh, this is driving me crazy.
We solve one problem, and another problem comes up.
It's all because we're all living in the same building.
That's what I'm saying.
You brat.
Of course. I knew you'd be okay.
You're a strong and optimistic boy.
Chang Soo.
I'm still sorry to you.
Mom. I'm here.
Where are you?
Is she in her room?
Oh, my.
You're here.
What's wrong?
Mom. What on earth are you doing?
What am I doing?
How can you bring a man into your house at your age?
- I don't do that myself. - My gosh. You silly thing.
Go inside and take a look. He's someone you know.
Someone I know?
Hyung Seop.
I was startled to see my grandchildren...
move back in after all those years.
Goodness. My own child has come back home again.
Who would have imagined he would become a kangaroo and return?
Hyung Seop.
You should go back to your house.
No.
I'm divorcing Jeong Ae.
If you divorce her, whom are you going to live with?
Me? I don't want that.
Gosh. You're so mean, Mom.
My gosh. Do you expect me to feed my son at this age?
I'll feed myself.
No. I don't want to see you,
and I don't want people to misunderstand. Go back downstairs.
Why would people misunderstand?
Ae Ri saw you sleeping,
and thought I brought a man into my house.
How silly.
I guess you're not Mom's type.
Stop talking nonsense.
So please go back to your house.
This is absurd. You're not newlyweds.
Forget it. I'm fully determined this time.
I'm not going to live with that woman anymore.
Go back downstairs! I was sleeping last night,
and I got startled because I saw you and I thought you were a goblin.
Ae Ri. Take that...
ginseng preserve.
Give it to Jeong Ae,
and curry favor with her. Say it'll boost her immune system.
If he divorces her, it will give us so much trouble.
I know.
Hyung Seop.
You should eat some of it as well, okay?
It will melt away the old grudge between you two.
Everything will be melted down...
like the snow.
- Look. - That's right.
Hyung Seop!
Mother, what are you talking about?
Don't you get it?
I have never heard of this.
What I'm saying is if you asked your father-in-law...
to help you financially to open you a shop.
No, Mother, no.
Why would your father-in-law say that suddenly, then?
I have no idea.
Aren't you pretending not to know everything even though you do?
- Mother! - Do you think I don't know...
that you get allowance from your father-in-law every now and then?
Mother,
that's something he gave me once.
The number of times is not what matters. Would you want to get...
allowance from your old parents-in-law, not give?
Sure, you can get allowance.
However, it's too much to ask him to help you...
to open the shop with our pension.
We already let you live downstairs.
Must we open the coffee shop for you with our pension?
Mother, that's not true. I really didn't do that.
Whether you've done it or not, that's what you do.
That's why you lived for 15 years without knowing your child's switch.
What are you talking about, Mother?
You don't take care of housework and keep going outside.
That's why your house and your child's like that.
You got depressed soon as your husband lost his job.
Is there anything you do right?
Mother,
you can't talk about Ji Hoon and Chang Soo like that.
Did I make anything up? Look at Hee Sook.
She raised her son to be the first student at school,
but you have raised your son as the last one.
If you switch the two of them now, she will find it preposterous.
Mother.
At least I raised Chang Soo with love.
I never wanted to switch him with Ji Hoon.
Then tell Hee Sook to raise Ji Hoon.
Don't make him become the last student at school.
- Mother! - Anyway,
we can't open the shop for you.
Just so you know.
Hye Joo.
Grandma.
Grandma, Grandma.
What's the matter?
Grandma, I can no longer live like this.
I can't live with my mother-in-law.
My gosh,
you shouldn't run upstairs like this, though.
There's limit to insisting...
nonsense.
She says I convinced my father...
to open the shop for me.
What is she talking about?
I have no idea. I really don't know.
Whenever something comes up,
my mother blames me.
My goodness.
Oh, dear.
Hye Joo, don't cry.
Crying would make you even more upset.
Grandma.
Grandma, I...
I can't live here anymore.
I really want to move out, Grandma.
I am so bitter at Seong Hoon,
I don't get why I moved in with my parents-in-law.
There is no single day when my mind is at ease.
Dong Hui,
what are you doing?
Nothing.
You're so boring.
You're young, but you're not doing anything on Christmas Eve.
Does it even make any sense?
That's why I came to get you.
- Let's go. - Where to?
I'm opening my coffee shop today.
Gosh, really?
I'm throwing an opening ceremony and Christmas party in the evening.
I hope you can give me a hand.
Shall I?
What a cozy and cute place.
You think so, right?
I did all the dcor on my own.
Really?
Well, someone helped me a bit.
Is that so?
My goodness.
You should ask who it was. I'm dying to tell you.
- Who helped you? - There's someone.
Dong Hui, don't you like anyone?
I don't.
Right, there's no way a woman sitting on a rooftop on...
Christmas Eve has a boyfriend.
Do you have someone you like, then?
- Yes. - Who is it?
He'll be here later.
- Should I turn it? - Yes, let's work on the back.
Seong Joon, shall we have another glass of wine?
Let me pour it for you.
Thank you.
Let's have a toast.
Merry Christmas.
It's been a while since we spent Christmas Eve together, right?
Has it?
Here it goes again. You're so inattentive.
You're an inattentive man who can't remember a single memory.
- Mi Joo. - Why do you suddenly look serious?
Don't do that. I'm scared.
I'm not scared of my dad,
but I am scared of you so often.
Why are you scared of me?
It's because I like you.
People are normally scared in front of those they like.
I hope...
you won't be scared of me.
I hope you'll always be dignified...
and sure of yourself.
I hope you'll be someone like that.
What are you talking about?
- Mi Joo. - Stop it.
What are you trying to say?
We have...
seen each other for the past five years.
I know you better than anyone else.
You also know me well.
Seong Joon.
I told you once...
that I have a sense of honor.
I want us to stay as colleagues.
- Stop it. - I've wanted to say this for long.
It's my fault that I didn't tell you.
I feel sorry about that.
Does it mean you have never seen me as a woman?
Is that why you rejected my proposal to get married?
No.
It would be a lie to say that I've never...
seen you as a woman.
You're a beautiful...
and charming woman.
You said you have a sense of honor.
Is this all you've got?
I'm a woman who has loved you only all this time.
Rejecting me gracefully? Is it your sense of honor?
Seong Joon.
It's Christmas Eve, Christmas Eve.
Couldn't you tell me that after today?
Sure, pretend that I was the only one who liked you.
However, I've liked you for five years.
If you were faithful and compassionate,
you could have told me that after today.
Seong Joon.
Nice.
What is it this time?
You're here.
It's that way.
Please come this way.
Jeong Eun.
I'm sorry, but...
Jeong Eun is doing something in the storage.
Is that so?
Why did you call me for something small like that?
That's not small. It's a big problem for me.
Anyway, call an engineer next time.
I'll be going now.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Look. Can you stay here for a glass of wine?
Please, I beg you.
He's the man Jeong Eun likes.
Let me go.
Feliz Navidad
Prospero Ano y Felicidad
I want to wish you a merry Christmas
I want to wish you a merry Christmas from the bottom
Of my heart
I want to wish you a merry Christmas
I want to wish you a merry Christmas from the bottom
Of my heart
You better watch out, you better not cry
Better not pout, I'm telling you why
Santa Claus is coming to town
I had so much fun today.
I enjoyed your singing, Jeong Eun.
All right. See you. Goodbye, Dong Hui.
- Okay. - Goodbye.
Bye.
Wait.
Can you stay and help me out with this as well?
Do it alone.
Oh, my.
The lights went out. What should I do?
Oh, dear.
What should I do?
What's the matter with you?
Well...
Can't you stay for a little longer?
Why?
It's Christmas Eve.
I've been busy.
I still am.
I know.
It's Christmas tomorrow.
It is.
What is this?
I just bought it on the way here.
To like someone isn't a bad thing.
It makes your heart flutter, and makes you happy.
It's a blessing that...
you should be grateful for.
I'm an aspiring writer,
so I know how it feels...
better than anyone.
I also know how I'm feeling.
Dong Hui.
But...
more often than not, love is unobtainable.
It's unobtainable inside of novels, and also in reality.
I'm going to be a writer,
so I decided...
to give up one of them.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
He may be paralyzed below the waist.
What do you mean my son was drunk?
I did...
a bad thing today.
I forgive you.
I can't love you.
Do you have to treat me so coldly?
You ruined my life. How can you do this to your mom?
It's not a big amount, but it will be enough for you...
to move out and get a place to live.