(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
To like someone isn't a bad thing.
It makes your heart flutter, and makes you happy.
It's a blessing that...
you should be grateful for.
I'm an aspiring writer,
so I know how it feels...
better than anyone.
I also know how I'm feeling.
Dong Hui.
But...
more often than not, love is unobtainable.
It's unobtainable inside of novels, and also in reality.
I'm going to be a writer,
so I decided...
to give up one of them.
Dong Hui.
I decided to love...
just either in novel or in reality.
Why do you have to give up?
You can just love in reality...
like you do in novels.
You also know well...
that the reality...
is far different from novels.
Are you running away because you're afraid?
I am not afraid.
If I had been afraid, I wouldn't have been able to hold up this far.
We plan to move out of the house...
as soon as possible.
So I have no time...
to spare for anything else.
What do you mean?
To like someone...
is something very exciting,
isn't it?
It is.
You're right.
Thank you so much...
for listening to my story.
Everyone, we need to hurry today!
We must get everything done by this week.
- Yes, Sir! - Okay!
Sir, you're here.
I heard that you're having a year-end party here tonight.
We are. Thank you.
Please make sure you drink them after work.
Of course, we will drink them when we're done.
What are you doing?
It must be tough for you.
I am sorry. I'm not supposed to drink while on duty.
Well, it's a rough job, so many workers do that.
But you shouldn't drink too much.
I won't. I apologize.
Let me pour you a shot.
Please give me.
But... Sir...
- This will be the last shot, okay? - Okay.
Then, I'll drink my last shot.
Gosh, get out.
I said step aside.
- What's going on? - What happened?
- Gosh, he fell off. - Come quickly.
- Stay still. - My goodness.
- What happened to him? - This is really bad.
- Call 911 now! - Hang in there.
- Is he all right? - Call 911!
- Will he be all right? - Call an ambulance right now.
- Wake up! - Hello?
- A worker fell from a building. - Goodness.
This is really terrible.
I can't believe that you consider getting divorced in your 60s.
You've lived together for a long time.
It's time to think about how to spend the rest of your life well.
If you get divorced at your age,
who do you think will take care of you?
Mother,
I can live on my own.
He can live with our children...
and take care of them for the rest of his life.
That's where he finds happiness.
- What do you mean by that? - Hey! Be quiet!
Aren't you ashamed of yourselves in front of your grown-up children?
There are neither children nor grandchildren...
who would respect their parents or grandparents...
who got divorced in their later years.
Mother, it's no longer a matter...
of winning respect, but a matter of survival.
If you give them everything we have, we'll end up with nothing...
when we grow even older.
That's enough.
Don't you think that's too much?
Goodness. Did you just yell at me?
Do you think opening a shop for Seong Hoon is a good idea?
Maintain your dignity as their mother.
Stop such nonsense.
Do you think you can maintain your dignity when you become penniless?
You can have it only when you have money.
Then, let's just get divorced!
- That's exactly what I want. - Stop!
Stop nagging at your children.
You should be the ones who should move out of my place.
You two are shortening my life right now.
Who is it at this hour?
I don't know. Let me go and see.
Who... Who are you?
Isn't it Seong Hoon's place?
- It is. - Well,
Seong Hoon fell from the building at the construction site.
- Sorry? - Pardon? Oh, my goodness.
Pardon me?
Okay.
(Emergency Medical Center)
Seong Hoon!
- My goodness. - Seong Hoon, please wake up.
Seong Hoon, what happened to you? Honey, will he be all right?
You cannot come inside. Please wait here.
Wait a minute.
He's my child. He's my oldest son.
Sir, what is wrong with him?
Why are his eyes closed?
Seong Hoon. Please hold on.
He's my kid. Please wait.
We have to check his condition now. Please wait here.
- Please calm down. - This can't be true.
Seong Hoon. My poor son.
My son. What do we do?
My poor son. What do we do?
My poor son.
Save my poor son.
- Father. - You're here.
How is Seong Hoon?
They're doing an emergency surgery on him.
How is he right now? How is he?
We don't know yet.
Seong Hoon.
Turn the monitor.
What do we do, Father?
Father. What do we do?
I know. He's been studying his whole life.
How did he think he could manage to work at the construction site?
I don't know. I don't know what to do.
Please save my son.
What do we do?
What?
Did you say Seong Hoon was working at the construction site?
Yes, apparently he was.
He couldn't get a proper job, but he had mouths to feed.
So he must have worked as the construction worker.
Ms. Oh, I don't want to live like this.
I know.
How can this happen? Goodness.
I was going to follow the kids to the hospital.
They said I might faint and get hospitalized too,
so they stopped me from coming.
Why aren't they calling by the way? They have to tell me...
how he is to feel relieved.
Goodness. My heart and hands are trembling.
I can't do anything.
Goodness.
We just found out about Chang Soo and Ji Hoon.
And this happened to our eldest grandson.
Doctor, what happened to our son?
Doctor.
When someone falls from a high place,
shoulder or collarbone fracture usually happens.
Fortunately, his shoulders and collarbones are fine.
His forehead is slightly lacerated,
and he's complaining of pain in right arm and left leg,
so I'm suspecting minor fracture.
But what worries me more is...
that he keeps vomiting.
We have to check for cerebral hemorrhage and spine fracture.
What?
Cerebral hemorrhage and spine fracture?
What will happen, then?
We have to check him,
but if any of them happens,
he may be paralyzed below the waist.
Mother. Mother.
How can this happen to him?
Let's get an MRI scan first.
Mother. Mother.
Mother. Wake up, Mother.
Do not transport materials until we reinforce the handrail.
Okay.
What did you do to my son, you moron?
What did you do to make him like that?
Bring my son back!
Sir, please calm down.
How can I calm down?
He has two children, and he's about to die.
- Save my son! - Sir.
Please stop.
Let go of me. Let go of me!
Save my son, moron!
Save my son!
Please stop.
- Stop. - Let go!
Let go of me!
I'm going to sue all of you.
Sir, why are you putting the blame on him?
He didn't do anything wrong.
Come this way. Talk to me.
Come this way.
Look at this. This is the soju Seong Hoon's been drinking.
Who on earth would work after drinking?
What are you saying?
What do you mean my son was drunk?
He hid over there and drank about one bottle.
If you lie, I am going to put you in jail, too.
That doesn't make sense at all. My son would never drink.
So let's go to the hospital.
When we took him to the hospital,
they took his sobriety test.
Let's go and ask the doctor.
Bring my son back!
Welcome.
Hyun Woo, what brings you here?
I'm glad you're here.
Can you help me with this? This bulb is burned out.
Move.
Goodness.
You are MacGyver of Bangbae-dong.
It's not for free. I'm going to charge you for the service.
I don't have money.
I haven't sold any coffee yet.
Are you proud of that?
How can you pay back the loan?
Don't you know me? I was the goddess barista of New York,
Gold Cat.
Goddess barista? Right.
What?
Wake up. Here is your pay.
Eat. It's for changing the bulb.
Are you not going to eat it?
I will eat it. Apparently, it's my pay.
By the way, I've been curious about this for three years.
Do you have a story about cucumber sandwich?
All right. All right.
Your eyes tell me that I shouldn't have mentioned it.
I don't know what it is, but I won't get curious.
Instead,
blow on it and drink all of it.
Chamomile tea is good for calming your mind.
You look unusually tired today.
You're okay, right?
All right. All right. I won't ask anything.
Why do you keep giving me the angry eyes? Are you an actor?
You are Mr. Mystery.
I did...
something bad today.
Something bad? What is that bad thing?
Did you push a pooping child and drive a stake into a pumpkin?
Or did you...
cruelly step on an ant?
Or did you honestly tell an elder that she's fat and ugly?
Or did you tell someone wearing a wig that...
you can see that he's wearing a wig?
You are very bad.
You are just like David Lee of Golden Street I know.
You didn't hurt somebody, did you?
As long as it's not that, you're fine.
Still,
you have to pay for your sin if you want to get rid of bad luck.
I forgive your sins.
Hey!
Hello. Welcome.
What would you like?
- Can I have a cup of black coffee? - Okay.
What do you want?
I will have the espresso.
So you ordered black coffee and espresso.
Hello, I am from the headquarter.
I am Oh Dong Hui from Contents and Marketing Team.
- Have this. - Thank you.
I finished going over the documents. Thank you for your help.
Please drink some.
It's freezing outside.
Your cheeks are all reddened.
Thank you.
You visited all of these branches?
Other employees only visit the half of the list.
You are very productive.
It's my job.
This is the concept book.
This book will help the customers to dress nicely on a daily basis.
Fashion manners and practical tips can be found there.
I thought it would be helpful for the customers.
My gosh, you are good at your job.
A couple, wearing the jacket lies down side by side in the city.
Soon, the scene changes into the one from "Love Story".
Oh Dong Hui came up with...
the initial idea and the storyboard.
Oh Dong Hui did this?
Who knew she could pull it off? Because she is new,
her thinking is quite refreshing.
What do you think, Ms. Na?
I think this can be useful for viral marketing with social media.
The commercial will appeal to people in their 20s and 30s.
You think so?
We already signed the male model.
We decided to select the female model from our employees.
Regarding the nominees for the commercial,
we are taking votes through social media.
I voted for Ms. Na.
We need to wait for the result, but I think Ms. Na has a shot.
I see.
I'll be grateful for your help as a director of this company.
I will work hard.
I will do my best, Director.
Proceed with the viral marketing.
- Yes, Director. - Yes, Director.
My goodness.
Director Han Seong Joon.
Could we talk?
You are too harsh.
You don't even want to see me in private?
It's not that.
Do you have to be so cold-hearted towards me?
Okay, I will make it brief.
What is your reason?
Your reason for breaking up with me?
Explain it so I can understand.
- Mi Joo. - "I never wanted to break up."
"How can we break up if we never dated." Don't say these things.
When I said we should stay as colleagues,
I meant it.
I can't love you.
You are a great person, a great colleague, and a great friend.
I don't feel the same way with you.
It's always been like this from the start.
No, you weren't like this at first.
You have changed.
- Mi Joo. - It's been five years.
Everyone in the company thinks we are getting married.
They will say, "She heartily loved him..."
"for five years, but they broke up."
How will the people in company,
I mean, how will the people in this industry think of me?
Don't you feel bad for me?
Then, what should I do?
Pity me.
What?
From now on, I am going to beg you.
I will beg desperately and miserably.
I'm going to beg...
for your affection and love.
So pity me as I do so. That's all.
You're back, Director.
Yes, I am.
- Ms. Oh. - Yes?
Did you do this?
You told me to do it before.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Did you correct all of these?
I wouldn't say I corrected them.
I just wrote down strengths and weakness...
of each drama and strategy...
for the further storyline.
I'm sorry. I won't do that ever again.
Write down only your opinions and hand it in.
- Yes? - You studied writing, didn't you?
I could tell.
Yes, I studied by myself.
It looks like you studied scriptwriting for a while.
I studied it for six years.
I never learned at school.
I wrote my own scripts and transcribed.
That's great. Help me, then.
Summarize your thoughts.
I will give you the casting board. For each character,
write the introduction and revise them.
Okay.
Thank you.
You told me that you liked Ms. Oh's idea before.
How can you trust someone who has no experience in this field?
If our idea isn't good enough,
subcontract a company to bring in new ideas.
What made you change your mind so suddenly?
Nothing did. Hurry.
Okay, I will.
Also, let Ms. Oh to take over...
store management for a while.
Excuse me?
It will be hard for her to visit 400 stores all by herself.
So what? Do you have another opinion?
No, I don't. She should be lucky to get a task like that.
Okay, I will get going.
He's taking a CT and an MRI scan.
I'm just waiting here.
Where did you go?
Nowhere.
You must think I am a joke.
What do you mean?
I made a fuss because...
I didn't want to set up a shop for him.
After seeing him like this,
you must be laughing at me.
Aren't you?
Why would you say such a thing?
A mean mother is being punished.
Aren't you happy?
Seong Hoon isn't only your son.
Isn't he my son, too?
But still.
I'm being punished for being so harsh on him.
Don't you like that?
My goodness.
You know how I raised him for all these years?
He only studied.
All he ever did was studying and writing.
It breaks my heart to know that...
he worked in a construction site...
to raise his children.
It's breaking my heart.
Honey.
How did I...
Father.
Hye Joo.
The doctor finished his examination.
They moved him into a room.
Seong Hoon.
How are you feeling?
Mother.
Yes, Seong Hoon.
Look at you. What's all this?
I really have no idea what's with you.
I am sorry.
We have to wait for the examination results,
but the doctor said his spine and brain seem to be okay.
- Really? - Yes.
Thank goodness.
I'm relieved to hear that.
You're back.
What happened to him? Why didn't you call me?
Mother,
I had no time to make a phone call.
So is Seong Hoon okay?
He is.
He fractured his leg and arm. Other than that, he's fine.
Thank goodness he's safe.
Still, he has to stay in the hospital for a few days,
so Hye Joo is packing downstairs.
Then, who's at the hospital now?
Hyung Seop is.
Mother,
can I go downstairs and take some rest?
Of course. Go have some rest.
Ms. Oh, please don't worry too much.
Thank you.
Please put yourself together and sleep tight.
I'm worried that you might also fall ill.
Goodness.
I have to sleep over at the hospital.
Please take care of Ah In, okay?
- Is it really bad? - No, he's okay.
He just needs to stay there for a few days.
Mom, I miss Dad.
Come here, my Ah In.
You're such a good girl. He's all right.
Stop crying. Don't worry.
I need you to make kids dinner.
- Why do I have to? - Let's talk about...
our old grudges and our switched kids later.
Seong Hoon had an accident,
so I have to stay at the hospital.
Gosh, what happened to him?
I'll explain later.
Make dinner for Chang Soo, Ah In, and Ji Hoon, okay?
Hye Joo!
Mom.
I mean, Aunt.
I can't believe you are so peaceful right now.
Your ex-father is in the hospital.
How could you possibly enjoy that hot dog?
Is he in a hospital now?
I need you to take good care of Ji Hoon and Ah In, okay?
Mom.
- Where's Ji Hoon? - He said he doesn't want to eat.
What?
("This time, I'm a magician")
Ji Hoon.
- Yes? - Why are you not having dinner?
I'm not hungry.
Isn't it because you don't want to see me?
What book were you reading just now?
- It's nothing. - Give it to me.
- I don't want to. - Do you know what time it is?
You must be receiving your private lesson at this hour.
Why are you reading a useless book like that?
- Give it to me already. - I don't want to.
Is that why you wanted to live here?
You decided to live here so that you can waste as much time as you want?
Did you abandon your mom...
who raised you for 15 years for this?
Give the book to me!
I said no! You're not even my mom.
Why do you care about me?
What? Ji Hoon!
Ji Hoon, stop right there! Ji Hoon!
Ji Hoon!
How can you do this to me?
I put all my time and efforts for you.
I devoted all my life to you!
How can you change your attitude toward me this quickly?
Ji Hoon!
Ah In, stop crying.
Don't cry.
It's all right. Stop crying.
Grandma.
Gosh, you're here.
Here is my Ah In.
Grandma.
It's good to see you. My little girl.
Ah In kept crying because Mom and Dad are away.
- Grandma. - It's okay.
This is my cute Ah In.
My poor kids.
Dad, please go home.
Hye Joo will be here soon.
Please go home.
Did you drink?
Is that really true?
- Yes. - Why did you do that?
Well, I just had a little...
Why didn't you tell me earlier if things were that tough?
I cannot ask for your help any more. It's too shameless.
Still, I'm your father.
Father.
There's no need to feel shameless to your parents.
I'm sorry to trouble you so often.
I can't say anything, but I'm sorry.
You know what?
I think you're the worst one.
Father.
Aunt.
Chang Soo.
- Grandma. - You're back.
Seong Hoon had an accident, so the kids came up here.
Sorry?
It's all right.
My little Ah In is a good girl.
It's okay.
So...
I want you to go downstairs and take care of Seong Hoon's kids.
They must be in a daze now.
I will. Don't worry.
I'll stay over at the hospital, then.
Hye Joo and your dad are staying there.
There's no room for you.
Please just take care of the kids.
Okay.
Aunt, I can hold her.
It's all right. She wants to stay on my back.
Uncle, you're here.
Are you okay, Chang Soo?
I have no idea why things are going crazy.
We have one problem after another.
Goodness, you talk like a grownup.
- By the way, - Yes?
I need to go to bathroom.
Please let me hold Ah In. I will put her to sleep.
It's okay. She wants to be with me.
Ah In, let me hold you.
Uncle.
Come here.
Ah In.
Stay with me.
Okay. I will.
Dong Hui.
How have you been?
Good.
I just wondered...
if you've been doing well.
I'm good thanks to you.
I see.
Don't worry about Ah In.
I will go down often.
Good night.
Okay, then.
("Theoretical Love")
Children are children.
Children don't think about their parents.
Get out.
Go to your room.
How can I go to my room when you are crying like this?
You...
I told you not to call me mom...
because I'm not used to the fact that you are my son.
Okay, then. I will call you Aunt.
It doesn't matter to me.
Hold on. There's an eyelash.
Hey.
Get that hand off me.
Why don't you go...
and find my Ji Hoon?
Ji Hoon isn't home, right?
Go and look for Ji Hoon.
What a horrible child.
How can he torture you like this?
Should I hit him?
Be quiet.
Get me some more tissue.
Okay.
How is he?
He's with Hye Joo.
Is he in serious pain?
The nurse gave him painkiller.
How can he not feel pain? He fell off from the third floor.
President.
I'm here.
Cancel it.
Just like you told me,
cancel the pension and give it to Seong Hoon.
Honey.
My son is about to die.
What difference does money make?
Cancel it and give this to him.
I was worried that he would live longer than me.
That's why I was holding on to that money.
It wasn't just for me.
My son is about to die before me.
What different does it make?
Honey.
Cancel it tomorrow and give it to him.
We lived more than they did.
If we live longer than now...
or even if we go somewhere and die,
we wouldn't have any regrets.
Honey. My gosh.
People say it is "The Pain of Intestine".
The intestine of parents...
whose children die before them will break.
They will go blind because they cry a lot.
Even if it's not the intestine,
no pain will top the pain they feel...
when they see their children in pain.
Now their children are in a predicament.
Let us see what they will do...
to help their children.
How is it? Isn't it nice? Doesn't it energize you?
Do you know how good pickled ginseng is?
I want another cup of this.
Do you want more?
I need to bring warm water. Hold on.
How are you?
I am okay. How else would I be?
Don't worry.
He's going to be discharged today.
You don't need to worry any more.
I know, Mother.
Raising children makes you worry.
I told you it will continue until the moment you die.
I guess so.
You are right, Mother.
But why are you crying again?
You cried a lot already.
Just because...
Mother.
I just feel...
so pathetic of myself.
Who knew I would be in this kind of situation?
My goodness.
Hey, what are you doing? Your sister-in-law wants another cup.
I'm boiling the water now.
It's been a while. Why are you still boiling the water?
Because you look down on your sister-in-law,
she is still sad.
Do you know how tired she is nowadays?
My goodness. She acts too much.
You should be helpful if you are sister-in-law.
Hey, if you aren't going to be helpful, don't even come.
Seong Hoon, don't just lean on me.
Lean on Seong Joon. He's stronger.
If I can move my body as I wish, why would you be here?
- Lean on me. - Okay.
Here. Try to maintain your balance.
Okay, let's go there.
Be careful.
Hold on.
It's Hye Joo.
Tell her that I am home.
- Okay. - Seong Hoon
Try please.
Yes, Hye Joo?
Hi, Seong Joon. I was wondering how my husband is.
I should have been there, but I am at work.
Don't worry, Hye Joo.
Seong Sik and I were there when he was discharged.
We brought Seong Hoon home.
Is that so?
Seong Joon.
Hye Joo, I will call you later.
Okay.
Seong Joon.
Thank you.
- My goodness. - Okay.
- Yes, Seong Sik. - Hey.
- Help him from that side. - Be careful.
My gosh.
Walk slowly.
Be careful.
Stop exaggerating.
This really hurts.
Exactly.
How can you work in a construction site?
Do you think anyone can work there?
It's a specialized field.
It's only for those who worked there for 30 or 40 years.
How could you possible work there?
- Stop talking and let's move. - My goodness.
- We can't do this. - What?
How will you...
go down the stairs?
How will you walk up and down?
Seong Joon, we have no choice.
Let's move him back.
- To where? - I don't know. Let's just move him.
- Let's move back. - Please be careful.
- Gosh. - Be careful.
- Wait. - Watch out. Move slowly.
What are you doing?
Aunt, Seong Hoon was discharged from the hospital,
but he can't go downstairs.
Please try to stand more firmly?
Seong Joon, hold his arm tighter.
- Okay. - Hold on a second.
- Goodness. - Aunt.
- Aunt. Move slowly. - Lean on me.
- Gosh. - Be careful.
Wait, Jeong Ae.
- Aunt. - Watch your step.
- Goodness. - Walk slowly.
Good. Slowly.
Goodness, what on earth is going on?
Mom.
- Mom. - Jeong Ae, what's wrong?
You're such a useless brat.
- Stop. - Jeong Ae.
- You know he's ill now. - You really drive me crazy.
- I can't put up with you any more. - Please calm down.
- Relax, Jeong Ae. He's ill. - You're a worthless jerk.
My goodness.
- You're a disaster. - Stop.
Ji Hoon.
Can we talk?
Okay.
Can I ask what you're doing?
I'm studying math. I haven't studied for a while.
Really? You really are a good boy.
I don't even have to nag at you to study. You do it by yourself.
You're my boy.
Well...
by the way,
as you...
are well aware,
your dad is injured and staying on the second floor.
Right.
I don't think...
he'll be able to work for a while.
I know.
Sadly, we cannot afford you...
any private lessons like how your mom did.
I don't think we can afford you. I'm so sorry.
Do you and Dad want me to stay as the top student...
as I have done until now?
No way. We don't expect...
such a big thing from you.
- Then, what do you expect? - Well...
We've never expected or wanted anything from our children.
We just need you to stay healthy...
and happy.
Then, I don't need any private lessons.
- What? - I can study on my own.
If you don't want me to be the top student,
I can study by myself...
and become top 10 students.
Will it be all right with you?
Of course, I am.
We'll be more than thankful.
Being top 10 students is such an incredible thing!
Then, you don't have to worry about me.
I'm totally fine.
Really?
Okay.
Thank you, Ji Hoon.
Anyway,
come into my arms.
Let me hug you.
But I...
It's all right.
Parents and their children hug often.
My Ji Hoon.
Good boy.
I went down to the basement, and Ji Hoon was studying math.
So you don't have to worry about him.
Which part was he studying?
Do you think I'd know that?
So I also figured something out.
Obviously, I'm not a son...
who has met your expectations so far, Aunt. I mean, Mom.
So, I made a big decision.
For the first time, I'll study hard during this winter break.
Although I ranked 359th last semester,
I'll beat three students...
and rank 356th...
in the next year's first semester.
So, please don't be depressed...
- Hey. - Yes?
Are you joking me?
I know every student of your school. One of them...
flew to the States for golf match on the second day of the exam.
The other one got caught while cheating.
And the last one had to leave in the middle of the exam...
because his grandfather passed away.
Even with such advantages, you ranked the bottom.
You attended every class and took the exams, but ranked the last.
So how are you going to beat them?
Is that even possible?
I see.
And why do you eat uncooked food?
You should cook it first.
I was going to cook this for breakfast.
You're eating it at this late hour, and that's why you've become obese.
Who gave birth to you?
You know who did.
Dad, I really can go on my own.
You're still not well.
What if anything happens on your way?
Nothing will happen.
I'll just accompany you. It's cold.
Goodness.
- I'm okay, Dad. - Just stay still.
Dad, stop it and have a seat.
It's all right.
They have some tea. Do you want it?
No thanks. This is enough for me.
Please sit down.
I believe all of you are...
looking for a reliable business partner...
with a profound knowledge and competitive edges.
(Mustard Chicken)
(Sweet Chicken)
(Boneless Chicken)
Have a bite.
Have you run a business before?
Penguin...
I had a large business once.
This will be his second avian business.
(I love you Dad. Please get well soon.)
- Are you having fun, Ah In? - Yes, I'm having fun.
Please get well soon, Dad.
This is my little girl.
I will.
Is there anything else?
No, that's all.
I heard that beef bone soup is good for fractures.
I already ordered bones from the butcher's shop.
Okay.
I'll open the door.
Hello, Sir.
It's going to take forever.
This is driving me crazy. Dong Hui.
- Yes? - Can you revise these for me?
Can I?
The writer got fed up with revising, so she just left it to us.
She's gone off the grid now.
We have to fix it and come up with a complete script.
I think you can manage this.
But can I...
Can you do it or not?
I will give it a try, then.
Okay. Please do a good job.
You're here.
You're working late.
Yes, we're not done with the work yet.
Where did Director Han go? His phone is turned off.
He left for a meeting with a TV station director.
That's why he might be out of reach.
I see. Then please tell him to come to my office when he returns.
Okay, I will do that.
Dong Hui, can I see you?
Sure.
So what did you decide?
Decide what?
Last time you came here and we agreed that you will...
think about what you should do for Director Han.
So what did you decide to do?
Mr. Park was praising that you work very well.
I think you decided to stay here...
and work hard.
You should talk to me. What's wrong with you?
Director.
Yes, Dong Hui.
I...
I want to keep working for this company.
I will try my best.
You don't think about Director Han, do you?
Wouldn't it be uncomfortable for you?
Since I already started working here,
I want to work hard so that I can pay for my brother's debt...
and stop being nuisance to Director Han.
I am a little smart.
That sounds like you've chosen to ignore Director Han...
and to benefit yourself.
Can I consider it like that?
Can I understand it like that?
Yes. I want to work.
Okay, then.
A high school graduate like yourself...
working for our firm is as impossible as...
a camel passing through the eye of a needle.
You can't abandon that chance...
for royalty or sense of honor to your in-law.
It's not like you've known each other for a long time...
that you would be willing to take sacrifices for him.
After you got off at the apartment in Cheonho-dong,
I had an argument with Director Han.
I said your place looked haunted,
and he got so upset at me.
At the time, I didn't get why he was so upset.
After I found out that you were his in-law,
I understood him clearly.
Because you are his in-law, I feel bad for you.
I am sorry about what I said to you that day.
You don't have to be.
So I prepared something for you.
What's this?
It's not a big amount,
but it will be enough for you...
to move out and get a place to live.
Do you understand what I am saying?
I want you to leave Director Han's house.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Why are you doing this to me?
Do you like me?
Dong Hui, wake up.
Don't you think you're being too impudent?
Why would I go to the basement? It's too small anyway.
All right. Let's not see each other, then.
I won't see you ever again.
Are you laughing right now?
Should I cry, then?
Why are you so upset?
Cheer up.
Merry Christmas.