(Episode 16)
(Home of Angels)
Ma'am, I don't want to go.
I can't live with another family.
Hyun Woo, calm down and think about it.
It's a good chance for you.
What if Sang Woo comes back?
I should be here when he returns.
We're looking for Sang Woo with all our might.
We'll call your foster parents if we find him.
You should adapt well in the U.S...
so that Sang Woo can move there...
when we find him.
You know there's no way for you to live here...
with Sang Woo alone without your parents.
I still don't want to leave.
I'll just wait for Sang Woo.
Are you giving it to me?
Thank you.
In a little stream, there's a tadpole
Wriggle, wriggle, wriggles around
Hindlegs out
Forelegs out
Hoping, hoping
He became a frog
You're here, Mr. Lee.
Hello.
We're so thankful each time.
Don't mention it.
There are many people who do much more than me.
Still, we are always thankful.
The other volunteer brought a lot of snacks.
Do you want to have some before you go?
I'm okay. I have to go now.
Please don't refuse it. Please come this way.
Goodness.
Stay still.
You will get cold if you don't dry your hair in the winter.
We will eat together after you dry your hair.
- It's warm. - It's warm, isn't it?
You're so lovely.
You guys had a bath. How lovely.
Mr. Lee, please come in.
What brought you here?
Since when did you volunteer at Home of Angels?
I'm not sure.
At first, I sang there with my friends.
That was before the former director passed away. It was 10 years ago.
Why did it have to be that orphanage?
No.
Why did you start volunteering at an orphanage?
I can't stop going there...
because the kids are like me.
Why do you feel that they are similar to you?
I have a mother, but I don't feel like I have one.
And I never had a father.
That's why.
Why do you keep asking me these things?
Your life is so perfect, and you wouldn't understand.
Do I look like that? Do I look like I have a perfect life?
Don't you?
Stop.
I have to get off here. Get me off here.
Bye. It was unexpected, but I was happy to see you. Bye.
My guitar. My guitar.
Bye.
Hey, what are you doing?
Don't you want to come with me?
I know, too.
Know what?
I know how the kids at the orphanage feel.
Hey.
Yes?
I will give an answer.
I...
I like you.
You asked me if I like you.
It doesn't mean you have to like me.
It doesn't matter if I like you one-sidedly.
I am telling you this because...
I think you should know. No, I want you to know.
Anyway...
My mouth never does me any good.
Anyway,
I am sorry that I like you.
Bye.
Let me go. I am really embarrassed right now.
Let go of me. Please.
Do you even know how to get embarrassed?
You like me.
Why?
Like you said, I'm rude and arrogant.
Besides, I'm poor now.
I know.
I can't understand myself either.
Hey.
How can you make a slave of someone who likes you?
If you're not going to accept me, make me go home early.
If you're going to accept me, you should take me to a nice restaurant.
You're not doing either,
and you ordered me to make you a cucumber sandwich.
Are you saying you're going to use me as your servant?
Did you slice the cucumber in 1.5cm-thick slices?
Did you add three big spoons of mayonnaise?
Yes, I did.
Now you are complaining about food, too.
That's how my dad used to make it.
What?
He sliced the cucumber thicker than you did,
and he put a little more mayonnaise.
It's good.
It's almost there.
My mom died early.
So my dad...
raised me and my brother.
You said you have a little brother.
Yes.
My father used to make this for us sometimes.
All he knew how to cook was ramyeon and kimchi fried rice.
The only thing he made well was this cucumber sandwich.
What happened to your dad?
He died unfairly.
That's why I lost my little brother.
You lost your little brother?
- Yes. - How did that happen?
So?
So I eat this...
when I miss my father and my brother.
I eat it when I miss them, too.
I see.
My head...
You...
What are you doing here not sleeping at this hour?
I told you not to eat anything at night.
Perhaps, you ate at night because...
you didn't know how dangerous it is.
I will explain it to you why you shouldn't. Listen up.
When we sleep, melatonin which helps us sleep, secretes,
but if you eat, your intestines start to move actively.
And that movement wakes your nerves which decreases melatonin.
In conclusion, it causes insomnia.
You do know what insomnia is, right?
It doesn't matter how much you want to sleep because you can't.
You end up staying up all night for days.
I've never experienced that.
Our parasympathetic nerves in our body...
stores internal nutrients into our fat tissue.
When you eat late at night, you won't burn them off.
It will go straight to your body and it will cause you to gain weight.
That is how this sort of obese body is created.
Did you know that?
My body wasn't created drastically.
It's been turning into as it is slowly.
Shut it.
I can't let this happen.
Your body is an abuse.
Your former mother...
How can she let this happen?
Regardless of...
whether I accept you as my son or not,
I can't...
let this happen.
What are you going to do to me?
Han Chang Soo.
Yes?
From now on,
it's a war with the fat.
I am going to give you a hard training.
Happy New Year.
Hey.
Even before 2017 comes,
some of us got laid off.
My gosh.
I found this business card in his car.
(Lee Hyun Woo, Manager of Miracle Construction)
Call this person.
Hello?
Happy...
New Year.
Happy New Year.
Are you all ready?
- Welcome, Mother. - Okay.
You're wearing the traditional dress.
I only wore this twice a year although I paid so much for it.
It's a dress I feel so unjust about.
Is that so?
- Then give it to me. - Shut it.
Do you know how expensive this is?
Jeong Ae, are you cooking rice cake soup?
Yes, Mother. I'm cooking the soup.
Is it bland?
- Mom, I'm here. - You're here.
Hello, Aunt.
Look at you.
Why are you talking badly about my son?
I'm sorry to worry you.
Hello?
You're even spending the new year at someone else's house.
You two are fighting again. It's only the beginning of the year.
This mother and daughter always fight whenever they meet.
Have a seat. The floor won't collapse.
Jeong Ae, Ae Ri is here. Make plenty of soup.
I will, Mother.
My gosh. She is so excited.
Hye Joo, are you done with the eggs?
I told you to cook the eggs for garnish. What are you doing?
Hye Joo. My gosh. You're impossible.
I'm sorry.
How can you not know how to cook the eggs?
This is quite challenging.
What is not challenging for you?
You can't do it right. Move aside. I will do it myself.
Mother, should I call Hee Sook to come up?
Hee Sook is good at this.
My gosh.
You sent her a text message...
to come up so that we can cook the soup.
She must be ignoring your message.
How can she ignore your message? You're her dear mother-in-law.
- Hey. - Yes?
You can't even beat her. So stop it already.
Excuse me?
Hee Sook came up early morning to say her greetings for the new year.
She went to exercise since today's the first day of the year.
What? She went to exercise?
She's driving me crazy.
Get up.
I can't. I can't...
run anymore.
I told you to get up.
Aunt. No, I mean Mom.
I seriously can't run anymore.
When I realized your body fat, weight, and the height,
you need to exercise at least 2 or 3 hours.
Obesity is a cause of all diseases and will lead you to be bullied.
Do you want to live like this?
Han Chang Soo. In 2017, you will become...
a completely different person.
So get up.
Get up.
Hey.
Please save me, Aunt.
Please save me.
I think I'm about to die.
You call me Aunt when things are not going your way.
It's hard for me to adjust, too.
That's why you need to lose weight.
That's how it won't be difficult for you to run.
Run.
Run now.
You need to speed up.
Will you lose running at this pace?
I will just accept the cause of all disease...
and be bullied.
You must have some energy left.
If you do, then you need to run faster.
Run. Run faster.
This is childish and too old-fashioned.
What does that mean?
This isn't possible. It's hackneyed. It needs to be revised.
Delete the scene. What is this?
"Meanings make emotions."
"Cliches don't bring out emotions. I don't feel sympathetic."
"Everything must be changed."
My gosh. He completely ripped my script into pieces.
Then he should write.
We're home.
Moong Chi, you turned five years old.
You will listen to me this year, right?
Hey, Moong Chi.
What's wrong?
Aunt, they want you to come down.
- Uncle. You, too. - Okay. I will.
It's the morning of the new year, Ms. Han.
Did you have a good dream?
I didn't have a dream,
but it's nice to have everyone gathered here.
Isn't that so?
On a day like this, it doesn't matter if you are rich or poor.
The family with the most number of people is the best.
We raised them so hard because...
we wanted to get together like this. Aren't I right?
You're right.
On a holiday,
the family with a lot of family members is the most fortunate.
- Enjoy it. - Thank you.
Is it hot?
This is tasty.
Why isn't Seong Sik's family here?
Mother, Hee Sook went out to exercise.
I'm not sure if Seong Sik went with her.
My head aches.
It's about to split.
Honey.
Goodness.
Where... Where am I?
Who brought me here?
Why am I in a suite room?
Excuse me. Gosh.
What's all this?
I didn't order any.
Someone made an order in advance early in the morning.
Sorry?
You can also use the sauna for free after breakfast.
Of course, all the fees are paid.
Then, have a good day.
Wait, who did it?
Who is it?
Lawyer Han Seong Sik seemed to be very depressed.
Well,
it's understandable since he's fired from the TV show he loved a lot.
I told the director of Channel T that Lawyer Han will come back...
shortly.
There'd be no fun if we give him back right after we deprived.
- Every game has its own rules. - Then,
should I make an appointment with Floor Leader Kim Young Tae?
That sounds good.
Let's drag Lawyer Han into the political arena.
Every man is thirst for power.
I can't wait to see how chaotic his house will be because of his greed.
Yes?
Come over and have some rick cake soup.
Sorry?
My grandma told me to call you over.
Will you come or not?
You'd better maintain your reputation as a polite young guy.
Hurry up. I'll be waiting in front of the house.
Gosh.
Jeong Eun,
why do you talk on the phone in Seong Joon's room?
Why are you so startled?
- It's nothing. - Will Joong Ki come over?
Yes.
- Is Joong Ki our neighbor? - Yes, kind of.
Please come in.
Grandma, he's here.
Goodness, you made it quick.
It's good that our houses are very close.
- Hello. - Welcome, Sir.
Thank you.
I was worried that you might be alone. Welcome.
- Hye Joo, get the soup for him. - Okay.
Thank you for inviting me.
How gentle you are.
- Please come have a seat. - Okay.
It's not a big deal,
but we always gather and share rice cake soup...
on the New Year's Day.
You're so humble. You look great, and I envy you.
This is Ms. Oh, our in-law.
It's great to meet you.
- Welcome. It's nice to see you. - Thank you.
She's my sister.
I see. Hello.
Hello.
I'm Jeong Eun's mother.
Mom.
It's nice to see you.
Me, too.
- Why don't you bring some soup? - Okay.
Let me bring it.
- Please sit down. - Thank you.
Sit over there.
There she is.
- Here. - Thank you.
Please eat up, Mr. Lee.
I will. Thank you.
You really eat well. Is it good?
Yes, it's very tasty.
I wish I had a young daughter so that I can marry her off to you.
Goodness, how nasty.
Stop it. I'm sure no one would ever want to marry her.
Thank you. I'll take it as a compliment.
It is definitely a compliment. I like you so much.
By the way, how old are you?
- Pardon? - How old are you?
Why? Do you want to marry him?
Mom.
My family is quite raucous, isn't it?
Yet, it's way better than staying alone on the New Year's Day.
Why do you like me?
- Pardon? - It becomes unfavorable to you.
You'll expose your weaknesses.
You just enjoyed the soup. What's with that question out of the blue?
Anyway, thank you for inviting me to your family gathering.
I'm giving you an advice in return for the soup.
Do not like me.
That's for your own good.
My throat sores.
I won't give up here.
It took me so long to be a panel. I can never lose it like this.
There must be a plot.
I will discover the plot...
and get the panel position back.
Women viewers love me so much. How dare they give me...
such a preposterous excuse?
Mr. Han.
Hello. You look busy.
Lawyer Kim Jong Wook will join the show as a new panel.
My throat... What... What did you say?
He's so lame compared to me.
He has achieved nothing in his career.
He barely passed the bar exam.
He even ranked the bottom in the post-training course.
He'd never been able to stand by my side.
How on earth could he...
take my place?
Goodness. I guess you should grow up.
He has his father, who is Senior Secretary of the Blue House.
He has the greatest asset. What are you talking about?
Having powerful parents is the most valuable asset.
Don't you think so?
However, leading an ordinary life isn't that bad.
Ms. Jang already...
started flirting with Laywer Kim Jong Wook.
Yoo... Yoo Ra did?
I told you that she cares wealth and power the most.
Sir. Sir!
Let go of me! Sir!
Sir! I said let me go! Goodness.
Gosh. You jerks!
How can you do this to me?
You know how dedicated I have been to this broadcasting station.
I rather deserve an award for my contribution!
You pieces of trash!
Seriously.
Mr. Han.
That's enough.
Don't you think it'd only make you...
look even more pathetic?
What? Pathetic?
- Hey. - Yes?
Please stop being nerdy and try to be a cool man.
Look at yourself. You're not a child.
Isn't it too childish to make a fuss all over here...
because you're fired?
What?
Did you say I'm childish?
I did. Please...
don't come here. Okay?
Yoo Ra. Hey!
You will regret it. You will!
I will make you regret it, okay?
What do men do when they try to win girls' hearts?
Is it a movie from the 1970s?
Were you even born in 1970s?
Do I have to live in that period to know what's cliche?
What did you say?
Be quiet, Moong Chi. Dong Hui's upset.
Yes, I am upset.
How can you draw red lines on my script and...
leave comments like "It's childish", "It's cliche", "Fix it",
"Take it out", and "I don't get this"?
How can you be so mean?
You asked me to support you.
I was trying to support you.
What kind of a man says a pickup line like...
"I fell in love with you at first sight" these days?
That's what happened in 1970s.
Why? Should we ask the stars now?
He's a womanizer. He just dates girls without love.
That's why it's more cliche.
There's no man like him these days.
You know very well.
You've never dated, have you?
- What did you say? - It's too obvious.
Like it says here, you learned romance through writings
"Romance Learned through Books".
Hey. I may look like this,
but I made all the way to the final round of the script contest.
I submitted my script everywhere and now I'm waiting for the result.
Why is it so loud here?
What are you doing?
Are you fighting so that all the neighbors will hear it?
If you have something to say, you could go in and talk
Why would you talk here in this cold weather?
- What? - What?
Go inside.
You are embarrassing us.
People would think there's a fight in the house.
Come on. Let's go in.
The dog is all worked up, and the weather is cold. It's chaotic.
Why are you looking around?
It's my first time to visit a woman's room.
Hey, this is not a woman's room.
It's the room I share with my grandma.
You must relate everything to romance.
What's wrong with that? Can't I do that? That's my job.
- Do you want some tea? - No.
Then hurry up and sit.
Anyway.
What did she do so wrong to face the wall?
Just leave her there. Don't touch my thing.
I gave you that.
So it's mine now.
She's going to watch you...
and see if you write something cliche again.
What?
Okay. Fine. I have nothing to say about that.
It's so hard to make you understand.
I understand well now.
By the way,
isn't it funnier if it's intentionally childish?
Comedy becomes uncomfortable when you cross the line.
Also, it's not realistic at all.
Romantic comedy doesn't have any realistic side.
Besides, love is like mirage.
It's something unrealistic and old-fashioned as well.
You will be in big trouble if your script is old-fashioned.
Romantic comedy is the most stylish genre.
Stop getting so upset.
When you go to a store, people might mistake you as a tomato.
I am not upset.
You are upset.
Goodness. You get upset whenever I say something.
What did you just say?
Are you hitting your teacher?
My body hurts. My body is so sore.
I hope all the holidays...
in the world disappear.
Just disappear!
Kang Hee Sook didn't show up all day.
My legs don't move.
Stop being such a cry baby. Come in.
Will you continue being a cry baby?
I'm not being a cry baby.
Hey.
What are you two up to?
Where have you been?
Where did you go when you should be cooking rice cake soup?
Will you keep disappearing whenever we have...
a family event?
What's wrong? I went out to exercise.
So...
why are you trying to lose weight alone?
Is my body already beyond help?
Do you think...
I exercised to lose weight?
I don't have to lose weight. I'm already perfect.
Then?
It was for him.
It was for this boy.
It was for this boy, whom you raised...
for the past 15 years without thinking.
According to WHO's...
obesity classification, he has a third-level obesity.
It was for your former son,
who is at the critical stage.
I took him out for a morning exercise.
Do you get it?
Mom, save me.
I'm hungry.
Hey.
Go back there.
I know well that...
you are a betrayer and that you have no moral.
You are the boy who eats gourmet sausage from Germany...
and romantic bread made with milk produced by cows...
running in the fields of Hokkaido.
Move there. Okay?
Mom.
Come here.
Go inside the bathroom now.
Go take a shower. Quick!
Wash yourself well, okay?
Why? Do you feel bad for your former son?
No.
I don't feel bad.
I don't have any more lingering feelings for him.
He met the right person.
Of course. Who am I?
I am going to make him...
into a totally new person and show you.
Watch me and reflect on yourself.
What?
She's unbelievable.
By the way, Mom,
isn't that rice cake?
Can I have some?
I love rice cake soup, you know?
Who told you to come out? Go back inside.
Who...
just called me "Mom"?
Call me "Aunt" now.
Mom.
Our relationship is...
already over.
Live well with your new mother.
I will go cook the rice cake soup...
for my son who is the top of his class.
I will add beef and make it all delicious.
Are you teasing someone?
You two.
- What? - What?
I'm teasing you!
- Mom! - Hye Joo!
I hate her. Go back inside.
Go back inside. Now.
You're here.
You've been studying.
Yes. I think I wasted too much time in the morning...
eating the rice cake soup.
I'm going to study a little in the afternoon.
Ji Hoon,
you are truly amazing.
Don't say that.
What do you want to eat? Do you want some fruits?
No.
I don't eat anything when I study.
When blood goes to the stomach,
my head becomes dull.
I see.
Did you wash well?
Yes. I washed well.
Do you like the pajamas?
I couldn't care about the design as I had to look for the right size.
It's okay.
You saw your former mother...
looking down on you, didn't you?
I saw that.
She said that...
you weren't her son anymore.
Yes. I heard that, too.
Forget the past.
Okay. I will.
And don't...
humiliate me.
Yes. I won't.
That bean came from the Andes of South America.
It's considered the mother of grain.
This bean is good enough.
- Eat it. - Okay.
Where is Mother?
She goes to bed around 8pm.
That's right.
Your restaurant will open soon.
It seems like they started the construction yesterday.
I couldn't have done it without you and Mom.
- I'm sorry. - Don't be silly.
Do you really realize you should be sorry?
Jeong Ae.
You should pull yourself together.
Work hard and pay back the money you owe us.
Okay. I will.
Did you have to be say that?
- When are you removing your cast? - I'll remove it tomorrow.
- Is that so? - Shall I take you to the hospital?
It's fine. I can go by myself.
By the way, where is Seong Sik? I haven't seen him all day.
He should come upstairs and help his brother.
You're right. I haven't seen him all day, either.
Have you seen Seong Sik?
No, I haven't.
My goodness.
No matter how hard you try, it'll be all useless.
It goes the same for you, too. You just...
shine for a while, but that'll be all.
You are...
a gas lamp, right?
You will...
probably be replaced by...
an LED lamp that has good connections soon.
They say a great man can rise from a humble family,
but it's not like that these days.
My gosh. Poor you.
Goodness.
Why can't...
a great man rise from a humble family?
Why do I...
have to live such an unsuccessful life? Why?
- Gosh. - Lawyer Han Seong Sik.
You drink very often these days.
Look who it is.
Gosh, Mr. Lee.
- Yes. I'm Lee Hyun Woo. - Oh, dear.
You're my sweet and kind neighbor.
You're my kind neighbor who lends me an expensive car...
without any problem.
- Let me give you a kiss. - It looks like you drank too much.
Let's go. I'll walk you home.
Okay.
I'm so jealous of you, Hyun Woo.
I heard your uncle is rich.
You probably have nothing to worry about, then.
That must be great, right?
You have great parents, too.
Weren't you able to become a lawyer because of their support?
It's not their support that made me a lawyer.
I studied very hard,
and became a lawyer myself.
Your parents would be disappointed to hear that.
Let's go. We're almost here.
This is...
so unfair to me.
Kim Jong Wook, that jerk.
What's wrong with him? My goodness.
- Gosh. - What's going on?
Seong Sik. Why did you drink so much?
I'm sorry to intrude like this at a late hour.
What's wrong with him? Did you two drink together?
No. He was outside, and I was worried because it's cold.
My gosh. How could you stay out all day...
on a new year's day, and come home drunk like this?
You should've gone to your house. Why did you come up here?
- Mom! - Gosh, you startled me.
Why are you yelling?
Dad!
- Yes. What is it? - Why is our family...
so unfortunate?
- What? - What are you saying?
Why did you...
have such an unsuccessful life, Dad?
- Seong Sik. - Get off of me, you punk!
Oh, my. I can't believe him. What's wrong with you?
Why did you make me...
someone from a family with no money or connections?
Why did you...
make me someone who is from an insignificant family?
- Come here, you brat. - Let go of me!
Hey. Stop it right now.
- What on earth are you doing? - Think about what I've done!
I graduated from Seoul National University,
proudly passed the bar exam,
and brought...
a great joy to you two, didn't I?
But what have you...
ever done for me,
your proud son? What?
Honey. What's wrong with him?
What is he saying?
Seong Sik. Stop. Let's go downstairs.
- Go downstairs now. - Dad.
Why are you so incompetent?
And why is our family so insignificant?
Why are you so unsuccessful that you can't even back me up?
Dad.
Why are we living like this?
- Let's get him out of here. - Let's go.
Wait. Let go of me. Mom, Dad!
Something so unfair had happened to me today.
It was so unfair!
It's unfair!
Although my dad was an alcoholic who...
lived in a shabby room that didn't even had heating,
and had a low life which he lived from hand to mouth,
I never blamed my dad.
Even when everyone in town pointed their fingers at him,
and trampled all over him,
I didn't blame him.
My dad was a good person.
I blamed those who drove him into a corner instead.
I only resented my dad for...
killing himself...
and leaving me and my brother behind.
But children these days...
blame their families and even deny them.
Children don't realize that their parents are...
the only ones who wouldn't let go of their hands...
and who would give them hope...
when they're swept away in the strong current.
- What brings you here? - You didn't come to my cafe today.
Here.
It's my daily duty to give the landlord cucumber sandwiches.
There're two. My uncle isn't home right now.
It's not for your uncle.
It's for your brother.
He'd want to eat it as well since it's what your dad used to make.
From now on, I'll give you two sandwiches every day,
so you can eat it together with him whenever he comes back.
This is something my grandma said.
Mothers used to prepare an extra bowl of rice at every meal...
if one of their children is away from home.
They believed it would make them come back home sooner.
Also,
they wished their child wouldn't be starving somewhere.
I hope you'll find your brother soon.
I'll be going now.
Oh, I almost forgot.
And...
These are...
What are these?
These are movie tickets...
from the headquarter for opening the cafe.
It's tonight. Why don't we watch it together?
Come when you finish work.
I will buy popcorn and wait for you. I wanted to watch this movie.
I'm busy today.
That's why you can come whenever you finish work.
I will get going.
What are you doing, Chang Soo?
Where did he go?
This is weird.
I saw it this morning.
What are you looking for?
I can't find stir-fried dried squid and black beans...
cooked in soy sauce.
Those were all the side dishes I had.
I threw them out when I was cleaning the refrigerator.
You threw them out?
- Why? - It's because they looked old.
I threw out watery soybean paste, hardened spicy paste,
smelly dried lavers,
and softened vegetables. I threw all of them out.
They might look like that, but they are still edible.
No, you shouldn't eat them. You get a stomachache if you do.
Besides, Ah In is young.
Her immune system can't fight the viruses well.
She shouldn't eat food that's even slightly rotten or gone bad.
Is that so? What should we eat, then?
Han Chang Soo. You think I don't know you're here?
Hey.
Why are you looking for your son at my house?
Chang Soo isn't here?
No, he isn't.
Where did you lose your son and why are you looking for him here?
Let's take care of our son well.
Okay.
Gosh, she is so weird.
Then, why don't we...
eat the rice with spicy paste?
We will add sesame oil and eggs. It sounds delicious.
By the way, where did Chang Soo go?
It's because you eat like this...
you weigh more than 120kg.
Lose some weight.
Hey.
Don't talk to me because I'm hungry.
If you are going to get fat like a pig, then study.
If you aren't going to study, be slim and handsome.
What is this?
Eat a lot and get fat.
What did you say?
You little...
Han Chang Soo.
Mother.
You, two.
Who are you? What class are you in?
Why are you picking on him? He hasn't done anything to you.
Are you thugs?
Do you want to get scolded from me?
Hey, let's go.
Who's your homeroom teacher?
I will pay your teacher a visit. I won't let this go.
You.
Follow me.
Give me all of your money. Hurry.
I'm sorry.
I can't survive with a single bean.
From now on, you don't have any allowance.
Until you lose weight, live without money.
- Mom. - Shut it.
Sit down.
Out of all the desires you have as a human,
is eating your only desire?
Then what other desires would I have?
The desire to be acknowledged and to be loved.
Don't you have confidence or self-esteem?
I'm always hungry that I can't think about those things.
You need to bear it.
You need to endure the hunger and the difficulty.
That's how a person grows up.
Also, why are you so prone...
to hit others that easily?
They started it first. You saw it, too.
But still.
Don't you know whoever swings first is at a disadvantage?
They keep bullying me.
Why do you let them get into your head?
I can't help but to swing first when I'm angry.
- I'm sorry. - No, you shouldn't be.
This isn't on you.
This is all because of...
lack of the humanities.
Excuse me? Lack of what?
The humanities.
The difference between people and animals...
is that people can think deeply...
and can express it verbally.
In 1995, after there was a wave...
of the humanities in the States,
all the troubled children...
found a way to express their feelings...
without swinging their fist.
Books over bread.
Art history over curses. Instead of their fist,
the children started to study philosophical reason of life.
After that,
they began to change.
Excuse me? Why did they change?
This isn't acceptable. Starting today,
you will study about Shakespeare.
What? Shakespeare?
Who is Shakespeare?
Who does he do?
Seriously?
Seong Sik really said those things?
Yes, he did. It broke my heart.
Where is Hyung Seop?
He must have felt disappointed. He went for a hike.
Of course, he must have. That's enough to disappoint him.
You know how he raised them.
With his salary, he raised four children.
He sent them to colleges and married them off.
He did his best raising them. How can he say those ungrateful things?
My goodness. I'm going to talk to him. Is he home?
No.
He went out early in the morning.
Lock the door so he can't come in.
Do you think he can't come in because I lock the door?
This is why we shouldn't have been nice to our children.
This is how he treats us. We raised, clothed, fed, and educated him.
We even let him stay on the first floor. I don't even know...
what else he wants that desperately to talk to us like that.
Are you crying because of that?
This is breaking my heart, Mother.
What a punk.
When he comes home, I'm going to kill him.
To be honest, your script is good.
It's tightly constructed and the characters are vivid.
I feel as if the characters are real.
However,
do you think they need to go home before midnight like Cinderella?
What do you mean by that?
I'm telling you to let loose. Don't restrict yourself.
When I look at your script, I can see you in it.
Why aren't you confident about love?
You told me you can love confidently in your writing.
Okay.
Like I told you before, you have to change the title.
As you revise your script little by little,
you will think of a title you like.
Okay.
By the way, there is...
a book in my room that would be helpful for you.
Who can it be at this hour?
I'm not sure. Who is it?
Oh, my. Who are you?
Hello. My name is Bang Mi Joo.
Look who it is.
You're Seong Joon's girlfriend who was here the last time.
- What? - Yes. How have you been?
I've been great. Please come in.
You said you'd visit again, and you really did.
Say hello. She's Seong Joon's mom.
- Oh, I see. Hello. - Hi.
- Welcome. - These are for you.
Gosh. Thank you.
- Okay. - Jeong Ae. Where is Seong Joon?
He went to the rooftop to do something with Dong Hui.
You should go and tell him to hurry downstairs. His girlfriend is here.
What is he doing with Dong Hui?
Please come inside.
- Okay. - Goodness.
Please have a seat here.
- Did you say your name was Mi Joo? - Yes.
Gosh, you're so pretty.
Thank you.
What are you doing? Call Seong Joon.
Okay.
Mom. We're here.
Seong Joon. Hi.
You're here.
What were you doing with Dong Hui? Didn't you know she was coming?
No. I just wanted to meet Seong Joon's parents so badly.
I just came here to give you new year's greeting. He didn't know.
Hello, Dong Hui.
Hello.
Do you and Dong Hui know each other?
Of course. She works at our company.
Oh, my. Really?
Well... I should go upstairs now. Goodbye.
Gosh. You're a director?
Yes. That's right.
Her father is the chairman.
- Goodness, Seong Joon. - Mom.
But Seong Joon has helped me a lot since I was a new employee,
so I listen to everything he says.
- Mi Joo. - Charming men...
are those who have a firm hand.
Do you have any siblings?
I'm an only child. I felt lonely growing up without any siblings,
so I was jealous when I heard...
Seong Joon had two brothers and cousins.
I see. How long have you been seeing each other?
We've known each other for five years,
and we've been dating for three years.
- You should get married now, then. - Grandma.
My father is also...
watching Seong Joon carefully as his successor.
Oh, my.
You still can't take away my dear Seong Joon.
Of course. I'll move out of my house myself.
No need to discuss. You should get married now. It'd be perfect.
Since his brothers got married, there haven't been any weddings.
Now it's time to have one.
Jeong Ae. How long has it been since we had a new family member?
It's been 16 years because Chang Soo and Ji Hoon are 15.
But Mother. I just met her.
Talking about their wedding must be uncomfortable for her, too.
No, it's not. I met my husband...
for the first time at the wedding, but we had a wonderful marriage.
Really? Oh, my.
Grandma, Mom. She should go now.
I'm sorry she visited so abruptly.
- Why should she go? - I'm sorry.
Come on, Mi Joo. You should go.
I actually have things to do.
I'll visit you again next time.
Sure. I'll see you next time.
Let's have dinner together, then.
Seong Joon's dad isn't home right now.
The rest of the family isn't, either.
Okay, Grandmother. I'll see you next time, Mother.
All right. Goodbye.
I'm disappointed that you're leaving so soon.
I'll see her off.
Okay.
Gosh.
- What are you doing? - I'm going to go now.
Seong Joon.
I'm sorry. Please cut me some slack.
What am I supposed to do? I just like you so much.
That's why I went to your house.
I know it's mean and humiliating, but I went anyway.
I told you before.
I don't love you.
You're wrong. You can love me.
You'll just have to try.
Mi Joo.
I can't give you up. Never.
Seong Joon.
Do you think...
you can try to love someone?
During those five years that we've spent together,
I found you beautiful,
and reliable at times.
Sometimes I felt comfortable around you like we're friends.
But while we were seeing each other,
I always felt a burden on my heart.
It felt uncomfortable like you aren't really mine.
It confused me.
That confusion made us come to this far.
I'm so sorry.
I sincerely apologize.
But...
I can't love you just because I'm sorry.
I can't marry you just because I'm sorry.
It'd be deceiving myself, and it will also be bad for...
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
How did he become so smart all of a sudden?
- We study now. Let's go, Chang Soo. - Okay.
When Seong Joon gets married,
his mother will come, right?
I just thought it'd be good to have rich parents when things are hard.
Dad devoted his whole life for us,
and now you're calling him humble?
Be careful. You can't get swayed now.
Do you want to go out with me?