What are you doing? Do you still not get what I said?
Don't you know why I am doing this?
- Mi Joo. - I don't want to listen to you.
I like you, Seong Joon. I love you.
So don't try to persuade me with those words.
Just think about when you used to like me.
That's enough for me.
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
Do you have to do this?
Seong Joon.
What do you want me to do?
Do you want me to resign?
Is that what you want?
(Episode 17)
By the way, are you really the one...
who got me into the hotel?
I feel so sorry, and I thank you a lot for it.
I was glad to do it.
By the way, you don't have to be nervous today.
Okay.
I've been on TV countless times. I shouldn't get nervous.
But...
who exactly are we meeting today?
You will find out soon.
Let's go in.
Okay.
This is the room.
You're early. We apologize for arriving late.
Welcome. Take a seat.
Okay.
You are...
Mr. Lee, the chairman of Seonghan Group...
and Mr. Kim Young Tae, the floor leader.
He's a new face.
I told you to bring a former judge or prosecutor.
I guess you don't know him.
He's quite famous in media.
Am I right?
You are right. You saw him well.
Please trust my judgement.
Yes.
I am known as the handsome lawyer Han Seong Sik...
from Seoul National University.
What?
Did you study law at Seoul National University, too?
Yes, I did.
You and Mr. Kim went to same school.
Is that true?
What a pleasant surprise.
Indeed.
I am truly honored to meet...
the nation's most respected businessman and...
a fellow graduate from my Alma mater.
Please give me one large pop corn.
Ta-da. I arrived at the cinema.
If you follow what I said, I guarantee that you will...
avoid any legal problems.
Your eye for people is truly admirable.
You're too generous.
I'll pour you a drink.
Sure. Thank you, Sir.
By the way, you should open a private practice.
It hasn't been long since I quit my job in media.
Why would you quit? You should continue.
Yes. But...
I was laid off during the restructuring.
Is that so?
Mr. Kim,
shouldn't you help your handsome junior...
to continue working in media?
Of course I should.
I should make a call for you.
People have to play in the big water.
You should open a private practice first.
Of course.
You need a base to build your empire. Don't you agree?
After years of working in media, you should be ready to join politics.
Pardon me?
Politics, did you say?
I already ate half the bucket, and the movie already began.
Maybe he's not coming.
You're right. It's just like what you said, Sir.
- Is that right? - Yes.
He's very funny, isn't he?
I have another appointment to attend, so I'll leave first.
You should get going, then.
I hope you three will have a great time.
- Okay. - All right.
All right, then.
He's very funny.
- He surely is. - Isn't he, Mr. Lee?
Yes. I will serve you well.
He really didn't come.
This is what happens to me.
But he's too mean.
I should go now.
You're too late.
Let's watch movie another time.
Hey.
Do you want to go out with me?
Why aren't you talking?
Jeong Eun I know never stops talking.
Do you think I'm always talkative?
After making me wait for such a long time,
you suddenly appeared and asked me to go out with you.
So I am in shock right now.
Why?
Should we not go out, then?
No. That's not what I mean.
Why are you passing by it? I need to get off.
It's cold today. You should sleep in the house.
Sleep in the house.
A lady shouldn't be sleeping anywhere.
So this is your house.
It's my mom's house.
Your mom's at home, so you should...
sleep in your house from now on.
Okay.
Can I ask you a question?
Why do you want to go out with me?
I want to know too.
You're the most unsettled and the loudest person.
I don't know why I suddenly came up with the urge to go out with you.
I am curious about that, too.
I need to go home and think about it all night.
I'm going. Good night.
Wait.
Then this is our first day of being together, right?
It's our first day together. Right?
I'm going to count until Day 100.
I'm going to count until Day 300.
I'm going to count until Day 1,000, too. Be ready.
All right, then.
Bye, Hyun Woo.
Thank you for today.
Let's watch a movie together next time.
Good night.
- Yes, Atty. Han. - Hello?
Perhaps I'm being a nuisance. You must be busy.
No, you are not.
Did it go well yesterday?
I should have stayed with you.
Don't say that.
I'm thankful for introducing them to me.
I never imagined that I'd have the chance to meet those people.
I sincerely appreciate it.
I'm honored that I got to help you.
Don't say that.
Did you forget? I'm your fan.
Fan...
What is your plan now?
Now that you mentioned it...
Like what Mr. Kim suggested,
I think I should open a private practice.
I need a base to do something great.
I lost my job, and I have nowhere to go in the morning anyway.
Either to offer legal advices to Seonghan Group or join...
Mr. Kim's party, I need an office.
You're right.
So I thought...
I heard your uncle...
owns a lot of buildings in Bangbae-dong.
Do you think he can lease me a good place at a cheap price?
I am sorry.
I wondered if he could help me.
Don't you worry about it.
I will ask my uncle.
Will you really do that?
Goodness.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
I will call you again tomorrow.
Yes.
My mom...
has good sense of style.
What are you looking for?
Excuse me.
It's for a grumpy woman in her 60s.
It can't be the same as what other people wear.
How should I say it?
Is there something special?
He's no fun.
I lost my interest. He fell for it too easily.
However, it didn't cost you as much as it did...
when you acquired Jinsung Daily News.
Anyway, he's going to tell his family about it.
This is the copy of padded account for Kim Geum Ja's academy.
This suits well...
to close down the academy.
Thank you for your hard work.
Did you have a good time with Ms. Han at the theater?
- Yes, I did. - I hope you had fun.
What do you mean by it?
I mean you should enjoy it...
and you should also be careful.
People will open up when you give what they want...
just like you gave the honor and power...
to Han Seong Sik who sought for them.
What did she want from you?
Do you plan on...
including her on the list?
Of course.
Then, please be careful.
Give what she wants, but don't get swayed.
I'm only telling you this because you are still young.
I took off my cast.
Father.
Why are you incompetent?
And why is our family so insignificant?
Why did you make me...
someone from a family with no money or connections?
Why did you...
make me someone who is from an insignificant family?
Why are you so unsuccessful that you can't even back me up?
Mom.
- Get out. - Mom.
- I don't want to see you. Get out. - Mom.
Mom, I'm really sorry. I deserve to die.
- I don't need a son like you. - Mom.
- Get out. - Mom.
I had...
my reasons.
Please hear me out.
Reasons? What kind of reasons do you have?
Even if you did, how could you say those words to your parents?
You asked why we raised you the way we did?
- You little punk. - Mom.
Somehow, I...
got laid off from the program.
I felt like destroying myself.
So?
Why were you laid off?
I told you. I got laid off because I didn't have connections.
That isn't an excuse. How could you take it out on us?
I didn't take it out on you, Mom.
I was just stressed out.
I just remembered how you played favorites with Seong Hoon.
I was drunk.
That's why...
Ta-da.
Isn't this nice?
I bought this because I thought this would look good on you.
Don't buy me this sort of thing.
Don't disappoint us.
I've been holding grudges against you.
Be honest. Dad and you did...
discriminate me with Seong Hoon.
You babied him even if he did badly because he was the oldest.
You didn't compliment me when I did well because I was the youngest.
- My goodness. When did we do that? - You did.
To be frank, when we grew up together,
which one of us disappointed you more? Did he disappoint you more?
Or did I disappoint you more?
He disappointed you more than I did.
What are you talking about? Until now,
he never disappointed us. He was the perfect oldest son.
The perfect oldest son?
Mom.
Don't you really remember?
Mother.
I want to drop out of school and play rock.
Seong Hoon.
What? Play what?
I want to play rock.
Spirit of rock.
I want to express the symbol and resistance...
of youth in present time through rock.
What?
Mom. Mom!
Mom! Get up.
Get a hold of yourself.
Mom. Seong Hoon. Mom!
Father, what are we going to do with Seong Hoon?
That's exactly my point.
Please go back.
I've already left the secular world.
I will cut my ties to my family.
I would like to enter the stage of nirvana...
in order to find deeper happiness.
Seong Hoon.
Who told you to become a monk? You were to study for journalism exam.
You're doing this because you don't want to study.
Do you know what enlightenment is?
Goodbye.
- Seong Hoon. - Seong Hoon! Seong Hoon!
Don't do this.
Let's go down and have spareribs.
I can't approve of this marriage. I won't give you my blessing.
If you...
don't approve of us getting married,
I will disown you as my mother.
I will choose her...
over you.
What did you say?
Seong Hoon, don't say that.
Why do you like her?
What do you like about her?
She's pretty.
You, punk.
- Why don't we both die? - Mom.
- Mom. Stop it. - Let's die together.
- Mom! - What did you say?
- You little punk. - Seong Hoon.
- Mom. Mom. - My goodness.
- I'm so sorry, Mother. - Mom.
Think carefully.
Perhaps, you forgot because you've gotten old.
Seong Hoon troubled you a lot.
But your brother didn't get drunk...
and took it out on us.
Mom.
Mom. Don't be like this.
I think I should get an office for my practice.
Can't you lend me a little bit of money like you did for Seong Hoon?
What?
I think...
I should start my law practice again.
Which brings me to my next question...
- I can't believe this. Hey! - Mom.
You, come outside with me.
Come out.
Mom.
- You come here. - Seong Hoon, hold on.
- Mom. - Today, I will...
- Come inside. - Seong Hoon, let go of me.
- Let me go. - Come inside, you little punk.
My gosh.
How could you behave so rudely after you've been drinking?
Do you know how sad they were because of you?
So what?
That's why I bought a present for Mom.
Do you think that can smooth things over after what you've done?
Do you think you can be forgiven with that?
As I told Mom before,
you're the one who troubled our parents the most.
I vent a bit because I got laid off from the TV station.
To be blunt, when you are struggling,
haven't you wished that our parents were well connected?
Well, I have.
What I'm saying is It's hard...
to succeed on your own even if you are talented in Korea.
I'm saying a great man can't rise from a humble family now.
So you're saying...
our dad who has been living to raise us...
- for all his life is nothing? - I mean.
Well,
I didn't mean that.
What an ungrateful child.
How can you...
My gosh. You're sly like a snake.
- Goodness. - Hold on.
I'm going to teach you a lesson today.
Wait. Isn't anyone home?
Ji Hoon. Your father's about to die.
Ji Hoon! How dare you!
Gosh.
I'm going to die.
The poor second son who received nothing...
from his parents is dying!
We are back.
- Goodness. - Honey!
Honey.
Seong Hoon, what's going on?
- Dad. - Chang Soo,
I'm your dad. Come help me.
Let go of me.
Honey, what on earth is this?
Can't you see it?
Seong Hoon is beating me up.
- Goodness. - Mom.
Ah In, it's okay.
You little jerk.
Seong Hoon, how can you do this to him?
You can't use violence in front of the children...
even though he's younger than you.
This is really barbaric.
- Do you want them to learn this? - Hey.
You can't talk down to Seong Hoon in front of the kids, either.
- What? - Hey,
Seong Sik deserves a good beating, of course.
Why would Chang Soo...
Why would Ji Hoon's dad hit him, then?
- Hye Joo! - Enough!
Let's stop. The kids are here.
You'd be as good as dead if it weren't the kids.
Gosh. You're really something else.
- Get you! - Say that again.
Don't say anything!
Why do you provoke him?
Seong Hoon, please let go of him.
The kids are watching you.
- Wait. - Please calm down.
Let him go, Honey.
Living in the same house with this jerk...
is so stressful.
I am also very...
stressed out.
Honey, stop it.
- Let him go. - Goodness.
Seong Hoon, please let him go.
I love you, Hye Joo.
Gosh, get off from him.
Honey, stop!
You little jerk.
Stop it.
Hey, don't just stand there. Come pull your dad.
Please let him go, Seong Hoon.
How dare you?
He's trying to kill me.
Why are you just watching us?
Please stop!
Please stop fighting.
Honey.
Honey, we won.
We won!
Chang Soo, good job. Give me a high five.
- We won. Honey. - Okay.
Gosh, how embarrassing.
You should have controlled yourself.
But he was too rude to Mom and Dad.
You know he's always been that way,
Anyway, Ji Hoon and Ah In,
I apologize for making you watch such disgraceful sight.
Dad.
Come here, Ah In.
- I am sorry, Ji Hoon. - It's all right.
I think adults also need to be honest...
- with their own feelings. - Goodness.
Thank you for understanding me.
However, I don't think what you did...
wasn't a right thing to do as an adult.
What?
I can't believe that I was beaten by him at this age.
How humiliating.
You know he's ill-tempered. You should have been quiet.
- Why did you get on his nerves? - It's your fault.
- Why is that so? - I was busy working at the show.
You should have taken care of the family affairs.
You've lost your mind since we found out about the kids.
So Seong Hoon ripped Mom and Dad off...
and opened a restaurant with it.
Oh, boy. Excuse me.
My whole universe collapsed.
- Would a restaurant be a big deal? - I don't care!
We moved in to take care of Dad. Look what we ended up with.
Seong Hoon...
took our money and son.
He even...
beat me today.
How pathetic.
Why are you here?
Please stay still.
Here.
You still shouldn't have fought with him in front of the kids.
They learn from adults.
Please don't worry about me. I understand you.
What do you mean you understand me?
Like Cain and Abel,
brothers envy and compete against each other.
Once upon a time, there were Cain and Abel.
Cain was a farmer and Abel was a herder.
One day, Cain got really angry...
and killed his brother Abel.
What? He killed his brother?
Yes.
My goodness.
What's wrong?
How did he become so smart all of a sudden?
He studies hard these days. Chang Soo.
- Yes? - Get up. You should study.
Okay.
Calm down and stay here.
- Let's go, Chang Soo! - Okay!
Honey. Honey.
Seriously.
He wants to open his own office?
Goodness.
That's what he said. He asked to give him some money for that.
So what did you tell him?
Of course, I flatly rejected. I said we have no money left.
It's true.
Our children are no different from enemies.
Thinking about it,
I don't think...
Seong Sik is totally wrong.
- What? - To be honest,
we were busy taking care of Seong Hoon and Seong Joon.
So we couldn't fully support him.
Please stop that rubbish.
Is that a conclusion you drew after a day at the mountain?
You know how much he wants to stand out.
I'm sure he was discouraged by his colleagues from wealthy families.
I knew you'd think this way.
Frankly speaking,
he has no reason to be discouraged.
Some kids don't even have parents.
He had parents who fed him with food, clothes,
and a place to live in and study.
We sent him college and helped him when he got married.
How can he blame us for not being rich?
Do you really think we deserve that?
He said that...
because his life isn't easy. Don't take it literally.
What about you? Why do you climb the mountain...
almost every day, then? You even have a blister on your lips.
You're also very disappointed at Seong Sik,
aren't you?
This blister has nothing to do with Seong Sik.
I got it because the weather is too cold.
By the way, how will he open...
his office?
- Don't we have to help him? - Honey!
You scared me. Why do you yell at me?
He received the deposit for rent.
He can open the office with that. We're not his piggy bank.
Still...
Please stop it.
Let's go to Housing Finance Corporation.
- To where? - Housing Finance Corporation.
- For what? - Kim Bok Ja...
told me about it this morning.
They have a pension plan.
If we rent the second floor,
they will pay us pension every month.
As Seong Hoon...
doesn't seem to be able to pay rent to us.
He will also not going to move out easily.
So let's go and ask them if we can get this pension.
That's absurd.
Why is it absurd?
This is a really good plan to make money.
Do you have a plan for Seong Joon's marriage?
Did he say he'll get married?
He came with his girlfriend...
when you were away in the mountain the other day.
Really?
(Letter of Resignation)
(I'll be resigning as my role...)
Sir, they'll pay me for this, right?
You're such a greedy girl.
They won't pay you that much.
Does that mean they will pay me at least?
Do your best, okay?
Okay.
Director, she is the one.
Hello. I'm Model Oh Dong Hui.
I'll do my best.
But...
she looks different from the picture.
Pardon?
Anyway, get ready.
"Snow", "flower petals", "winter to spring", and "first love".
The concept is "beauty".
(Frustration, tiredness, daily life, reality)
These are...
These are all keywords from my project proposal.
How could you use someone else's idea?
That's strange. Maybe it's a coincidence.
We hired an agency to do that for us.
What did you say?
What are you doing? Get ready.
Let's talk later. Okay?
I'll go get ready.
I know it's awkward, but get a little closer.
Great. Look this way.
All right. Where are you looking at? Look here. Okay.
Let's lighten things up a bit more.
Could you make your smile bigger?
Again.
Come here, Ms. Na.
Dong Hui found out that we used her idea.
What should we do? Look at her face.
She's so scary.
Director Bang will take care of it.
I came to see how good she is.
Now... My gosh.
Miss.
What's wrong with your face? Are you angry or something?
No, I'm fine.
Now, smile. Put on a big smile.
Smile from ear to ear. Okay. Keep that smile.
Here we go. Keep that smile. Let's go.
Miss. Why aren't you looking at the camera?
Okay.
Doesn't she know how to smile?
Again.
This isn't working. Stop.
I can't work with her.
I told you to bring a natural beauty, not a bumpkin.
Are you a log? Why are you so stiff?
Pardon?
I knew this would happen.
Look. You should do it instead.
Me?
Thank you, Director. I'll do my best.
I'll go and change.
What will you do about my proposal? I messed up because I was so angry.
Look. We just did what we were told to do.
We can't afford to hire an agency,
and Director Bang told us to change the concept.
Director Bang?
Oh, boy. I shouldn't have said that.
Mi Joo.
Where is Mi Joo?
Mi Joo. What on earth are you doing?
You didn't come to work today. What do you think you're doing?
I didn't go to work because I wanted to take a rest.
What?
Please go out.
Listen.
Getting dumped by that jerk isn't something you should advertise.
Dad.
I lost face...
at the company because of you.
You told me to pick someone ordinary and smart.
I told you to pick one, not date one.
Here you go again.
It's not something you can control.
You can't control your feelings.
You can. That's what a business owner does.
Have you forgotten that thousands of lives depend on your hands?
You'll soon run a company.
And yet, you're lying in bed refusing to eat because of a guy.
This is important to me.
That's enough.
I just didn't want to give away my daughter and company to some guy.
I was going to let you marry a smart and ordinary guy,
and make him the chairman so I can control him from behind.
That's the only reason why I approved your relationship.
It's not because I like him that I let you see him.
Dad. Is that what you told Seong Joon?
Do you think he didn't know?
It all comes down to a decision in the end.
He can either be my son-in-law and bear the disgrace,
or he can keep his petty pride...
and stay in the lower class.
Dad!
If that was your plan, why didn't you just let me run the company?
Grandma is a woman, but she ran the company by herself.
Don't talk about your grandmother.
She's too weak and compassionate.
If it wasn't for me, our company...
would've been broken apart long ago.
Your own daughter is about to be broken apart.
If you keep doing this,
I'll kill myself.
What?
(Letter of Resignation)
The more I think about it, the more I get upset.
What are you going to do?
He's your son. It's not like you can kill him or anything.
Mother. Hyung Seop says...
he can understand Seong Sik.
He says Seong Sik is a poor kid who gave up things for his brothers.
My goodness.
Look. There is no one in this world...
whom Hyung Seop can't understand.
He should be scolding and yelling at Seong Sik.
How could he say he understands?
I just can't believe it.
As a father, he should be stricter.
He's just too soft.
When he gets older,
our children will all look down on him.
Don't worry. You have Seong Joon.
He will believe anything Hyung Seop says.
You only need one child who understands how you feel.
Don't expect all of them to understand you.
By the way,
what are we going to do with Seong Joon?
What do you mean?
What if he marries that girl named Mi Joo?
She's the only daughter of the chairman.
It should be different from how Seong Hoon...
and Seong Sik got married.
Goodness. You're right.
I guess we shouldn't be too happy that...
she's the chairman's beautiful daughter.
I know.
By the way, Mother.
When Seong Joon gets married,
his mother...
- will come, right? - What?
I've been holding it in...
for more than 20 years,
but I'm going to see her face...
when Seong Joon gets married.
Why would you do that?
You've raised him for over 20 years. He's your son, not anybody else's.
You're a woman, too. I'm sure you understand how I feel.
Of course I do. I understand how you must feel.
I don't know if anyone would, but I do understand.
You've treated all of your four children alike.
I know you must have wanted to hate him and be mean to him,
but you have been trying so hard not to.
Jeong Ae. That's why I've been always grateful to you.
Why would you want to see her face after all this time?
Why would you want to dig up the past?
I just want to know...
what kind of person she is.
She abandoned her child,
and never contacted us.
I know. I want to see her, too.
You know Hyung Seop isn't someone who would cheat on his wife,
but he cheated on you with that woman.
I want to see her, too.
But Jeong Ae. You should keep this to yourself.
If you dig it up, it will only hurt your feelings.
I don't know.
Anyway, I'm having...
such a hard time because of my kids these days.
I know. My goodness.
It's never peaceful in our house.
Hello.
Are you coming home from work?
Yes.
You got off work quite late.
I was busy at work today.
What line of work are you in?
Was that rude?
No.
I'm working at contents marketing team.
That sounds like a fancy job.
It may sound like it, but that's not really true.
But your father is so proud of you.
My father is proud of all of his kids.
But he seemed to have even more affection toward you.
It's because I'm the youngest.
Parents love their youngest kid the most.
- Your name is Seong Joon, right? - Right.
You're very different from your brothers.
You have a different personality.
You are very good looking as well.
No, that's not true.
My brothers are better than me.
Right.
Thank you for taking Seong Sik home...
the other day.
I should have thanked you earlier.
You're welcome. I just ran into him that day.
Usually, he's not like that at all.
I think he had some problem that day.
I understand. Don't worry.
Anyway, Seong Joon and my family...
owe you a lot.
Please let me treat you to a good meal someday.
Do you like drinking?
Yes, as much as others do.
Then, let's have drinks later.
Okay.
Good night, then.
It was nice to meet you.
Goodbye.
By the way, Jeong Eun is...
a soft touch.
Please be nice to her.
I was fired right away and didn't get any pay.
I should have written the scenario instead.
How can they steal my project proposal?
I won't just sit back. Tomorrow...
Should I write about it online?
Why don't you take some rest?
Why are you standing and murmuring in the middle of the room?
- It's nothing. - Did you have dinner?
No, I didn't and I won't.
Why not?
I'm busy. I will rather write the scenario.
Are you not studying with Seong Joon today?
We don't study together every day.
Writing isn't a team work.
By the way,
you work for the same company as Seong Joon, right?
How did you know that?
Of course, Ms. Hwang told me.
I heard that he brought his fiance home the other day.
He did.
You should have told me about it earlier.
Why didn't you tell me?
He's your boss after all.
I should thank him for helping you.
This isn't right.
I didn't tell you because I didn't want to make you feel uncomfortable.
Still, I should thank him, anyway.
I am sorry.
Dong Hui,
you can write more comfortably without me, right?
No, Grandma. You can stay here.
I'll just sleep downstairs.
Write as much as you want.
Why does she want me to sleep over these days?
Who is it?
Hello.
I was waiting for you.
Will you make a scene again tonight?
I won't.
I heard about everything.
I will thank you later. Have a good time.
- See you tomorrow. - Good night.
What made you so scary that you want to sleep with me?
I think I'm too stressed because of my grandchildren.
I fell asleep,
and the grim reaper was...
sitting right there.
It was really scary. Goodness.
Then,
you should have just followed him.
Why did you send him away empty-handed?
How can you say that?
Are you saying I should have died last night?
Let's not be petty.
We live with a lot of risks every day.
- The grim reaper is nothing. - What?
- What risks are you talking about? - Forget it.
Let's go to bed.
Fine, I am petty. I want to live longer. Is that wrong?
You're unbelievable.
You called me over for nothing.
You can't say it's nothing.
Aren't you afraid of death?
I'd rather die than keep living like this.
- What? - Look at me.
I still have to work hard at this age.
I don't have my own house,
so I'm living in my in-law's house with my granddaughter.
It's such a harsh life, so I'd rather be dead.
By the way,
I heard that Dong Hui is a writer.
She does. Seong Joon is with her.
I think they'll have a discussion over night.
Speaking of it,
why don't you live on this floor?
Pardon?
Writing requires a great deal of concentration...
and sensitivity.
If you stay with her and snore while she writes,
she won't be able to come up with good stories.
Excuse me?
Don't get mad and listen to me.
Dong Hui has to write the scenario,
and I am afraid of the grim reaper because I am petty.
So if you just live here with me,
it will be great for both Dong Hui and me, right?
("Fascinating Words")
You're good at making ramyeon.
- Is it good? - It is.
I really wanted to read this book.
I visited three libraries,
but none of them had available one.
Were you okay...
when Mi Joo came here?
Sorry?
I should be okay.
I have no other choice.
That's right.
I understand.
By the way, did something happen to you?
You look sad.
Dong Hui,
will you be okay...
if I quit the company?
Sorry?
What do you mean by that?
Hello.
You're my sunshine.
My only sunshine.
You make me happy.
When skies are gray.
You'll never know dear.
How much I love you.
Please don't take my sunshine away.
What do you think you're doing?
Good morning, Hyun Woo.
- This is what girlfriends do. - Girlfriend?
I strangely couldn't sleep well,
so I woke up early and opened the cafe.
Do you know what time it is? It's five in the morning.
Someone used to order sandwiches at three in the morning.
You're up now. Come and have breakfast.
I'll prepare some hot milk and a cucumber sandwich.
Hey.
Hello?
No, I won't take a shower
I won't wash my face.
Why are you so late?
I made your sandwich ages ago.
I reheated the milk several times, too.
Hurry. Sit down.
You have to eat and go to the construction site.
Here you go.
Eat your sandwich.
Welcome. Good morning.
What would you like?
- I'd like sweet potato latte. - Sweet potato latte?
Hold on please. Sweet potato latte.
Here you go. Please wait.
Hello.
Can I have the bubble tea?
- Here you go. - Thank you.
Okay.
Please eat.
My gosh. You ate the whole thing.
Good job.
What are you doing?
What's the matter with you?
We decided to date each other.
This is what girlfriends do.
I read it in a book. This is how to earn affection from boyfriends.
You studied about that?
What can I do? I have no experience in dating.
Please be understanding.
How cute.
Well done.
Don't go home tonight and wait for me here.
- What? - Bundle up.
I will be here at 10pm.
- Are we going somewhere? - Yes.
- Where? - Theater. To watch the movie again.
I'll get going.
Hyun Woo.
Hello?
I don't know how to thank you, Mr. Lee.
I am not certain if I can rent this place at a cheap rate.
Do you like the place?
Of course I do.
How did you have a place like this?
My uncle used to utilize the office temporarily.
He was looking for a new tenant. This all worked out well.
Good luck.
Thank you so much.
I will not forget your kindness.
Bye, then.
Hold on a second.
(Lawyer Han Seong Sik)
This is it.
This looks great.
Ji Hoon. What are you doing?
I'm studying.
What's wrong? He's studying.
Stay out of it.
Ji Hoon. Can we talk?
Okay, let's talk.
As you know,
Father will open a friend chicken restaurant.
Every member of our family is folding the calendars to pitch in.
You're the only one studying.
Doesn't this look unfair to you?
Should I help?
Of course.
You should.
Studying isn't everything.
What's wrong?
Stay out of it, honey.
We need to educate him properly.
I'm sorry. I will help.
Is there anything you know how to do except to study?
To be blunt,
you escaped from your former mother.
You should have fun. If you don't, it's all for nothing.
I only know how to study.
I don't know what else to do and how to have fun.
I don't know.
Seriously?
That's why.
Then...
This can't be right.
In order to educate Ji Hoon,
clear away everything here.
What are you going to do?
First of all, just put them away.
Ji Hoon, you too. Put away your books.
("Romeo and Juliet")
"Why does your name have to be Romeo?"
"Deny your father..."
"and refuse your name."
"If so, I won't be Capulet anymore."
"Yes, I will."
"My name isn't Romeo."
"Romeo, you are back."
"It's dangerous for you here. Please leave."
"No, I won't."
"I will be with you wherever you are."
"My goodness. My mother's calling."
"I must go."
"Please don't."
Can't you do better than that? Is that how you're going to read?
The play isn't fun. It's like soap opera.
What are they doing? Their families are enemies.
Do you think you read this for fun?
To do well on your essay part of the college entrance exam,
reading is the fundamental part of it.
How haven't you...
read "Romeo and Juliet"?
I saw it on TV.
Watching it on TV...
and reading the play...
as you appreciate the literature aren't the same.
How old are you?
Why do you think I'm reading this...
with you line by line?
Read the next line. Come on.
Okay.
- It's a small baby squirrel - It's a small baby squirrel.
- The squirrel is on a picnic - The squirrel is on a picnic.
- With acorns as its lunch - With acorns as its lunch.
Ji Hoon. You lost. Come here.
- Come here, Ji Hoon. - Come, Ji Hoon.
- Indian Bob. - Indian Bob.
- You're it. Run. - You're the tagger. Run.
Start.
What's wrong?
Why are you here?
Hye Joo, can't you keep it down?
What do you mean?
Chang Soo is reading now,
but you are too loud.
Chang Soo can't focus on his reading.
Hey, don't lie to me.
What?
What do you mean? Chang Soo doesn't read.
Stop trying to be funny.
Hye Joo.
I haven't seen him read...
in all my life.
You're just jealous because we're having fun.
If you want to play with us, then join.
What?
You.
I educated you the best I could.
Do you want to play a game like this?
I'm having fun.
- What? - Why don't we play it again?
- A squirrel in a mountainous valley - A squirrel in a mountainous valley.
- It's a small baby squirrel - It's a small baby squirrel.
- The squirrel is on a picnic - The squirrel is on a picnic.
- With acorns as its lunch - With acorns as its lunch.
What are you doing?
Let's go, Juliet.
Watch me. I'm going to kick you all out.
You, Ji Hoon. You're going to regret this.
(Letter of Resignation)
Hello?
Is this Oh Dong Hui?
Yes, I am.
(Letter of Resignation)
(Han Seong Joon)
Really? My script is a runner-up in the short drama section?
Yes.
Please bring your identification card and your stamp...
to the headquarter.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Seong Joon.
Dong Hui.
Something great happen to me.
I wanted to let you know first.
Seong Joon!
How could you do this?
Dong Hui.
I quit my job today.
I hope you'll do great even if I'm not here.
What?
Seong Joon.
All right.
What are you doing?
- What? - Are you going out?
- Yes. - Where?
I'm not sure.
What?
Sit down for a minute.
Why?
- On the day we had rice cake soup, - Yes.
A guy named Mr. Lee came over.
You like him, don't you?
My gosh. I knew it.
This is driving me crazy.
How did you know?
It's all written on your face.
Grandma and the rest of the family don't know.
They're all blind fools who can't see anything.
Listen to me carefully.
- I can't let you see him. - What?
Why not?
- What are you doing? - Gosh.
- I'm going out on a date. - Pardon?
You told me to give her what she wants.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
So where is my brother, Sang Woo?
He'd be around the same age as my cousin, Seong Joon.
I've wished...
you'd stay well and healthy all my life.
- Eat this. - My dear Ah In.
How would you feel if you have to live with me?
Please forgive me.
What is this?
Are we going to sleep here together tonight?
This is all for Seong Joon's sake.
I'm just an office assistant. Even if I talk to him,
it wouldn't make any difference.