Listen to me carefully.
You can't date him.
What? Why not?
You can't date someone who's tall, pale,
and have long limbs and fingers.
When did you check his fingers?
Cut it.
Okay.
You can't meet someone who is as handsome as him.
- It's dangerous. - Why?
You had a passionate romance with Dad.
I heard the entire town knew about it...
and that your love story still remains as a town legend.
I told you to cut it.
Okay.
You know that the handsome face comes with a price, right?
He's the perfect example.
Also, I don't like his eyes.
They look wicked and sorrowful.
You can't meet a guy with a difficult past.
They tend to pounce on every little thing.
And he doesn't own the house.
His uncle does, right?
He doesn't have his own place at his age...
and lives in his uncle's house as if it were his.
He seems like a playboy. I can't let you date him.
I can never do that, okay?
- He's not what you think. - What are you talking about?
You've already lost your head over him.
You'd better pull yourself together.
He flirts with you because you look like an easy fish to catch.
Mom!
You know how I ruined my life...
after I got smitten by a guy with a sweet voice?
You can't date him.
Understood?
You got here 10 minutes earlier than usual.
Why are you waiting outside? It's cold.
- Get in the car. - Where are we going?
You love sleeping outside.
I will show you what sleeping out...
- in the open is like. - Sorry?
What is this?
You really like sleeping out.
- I hope you enjoy it. - Gosh.
Are you serious?
Then, will we sleep inside the tent...
together tonight?
I'm just joking.
You learned all the bad things from books.
- I'm sorry. - Listen.
I'll sleep in the camping car. And you like sleeping out,
so you'll sleep in the tent. Okay?
- Pardon? - I'm joking.
You can sleep in the car.
How can a lady be so clumsy?
I am sorry.
It's wonderful.
This theater is just for two of us.
It's better than a real theater, right?
This is to make up for not being able to watch the movie before.
Did you really have boyfriends in more than 150 countries?
- Sorry? - Well,
I can't believe that none of them took you out...
and showed movies like this.
That's something you don't need to bother.
Stop talking to me. I'm watching it.
(Go back to where you were.)
Yes?
I found someone who knows Sang Woo.
What are you doing? Are you not going to watch it?
I'll be right there.
Did something happen?
I think I found my brother. I should go now.
I am sorry. Don't wait for me.
Sorry?
Hyun Woo. Hyun Woo!
- I am Hyun Woo. - Hello.
- I heard that you know Sang Woo. - That's right.
So I...
raised Sang Woo...
who has lost his memory for 20 years.
He was such a gentle and cute boy.
I loved him a lot.
So where is he now?
Well...
He's in China.
In China?
However,
he had a car accident...
and needs to get surgery.
He called me that he needs money for that.
He won't get the operation...
if I don't send him money.
I am sorry, Sir.
- It's okay. - There are so many con men.
I'm like a drowning man who needs a straw to catch.
By the way, where is Jeong Eun?
I thought you were enjoying camping with her.
Hyun Woo, you're back.
Did you wait for me all night long?
I told you not to.
But I felt like you'd come back.
What about your brother? Did you find him?
Actually,
I made you breakfast,
wishing you had found your brother.
Hyun Woo.
Are you okay?
You couldn't find him?
I see.
It's not the first time.
When I went there because they said they found my brother,
it was someone else.
Or it was a con man.
I see.
This is how I spent my last 20 years.
I could get tired of this.
Whenever they say they know my brother,
I end up rushing to the meeting like yesterday.
Anyway,
I apologize for abandoning you like that last night.
You didn't abandon me.
I let you go to find your brother.
You ought to find your brother.
You've been waiting for him for a long time.
Besides, even if he isn't your brother...
or he is a con man,
shouldn't you go by all means if it's related to your brother?
That's what I think.
I can't even remember my brother's face now.
A picture book he liked.
Cucumber sandwich we ate together.
These are the only things I remember about my brother.
It's been 24 years.
I might not be able to recognize him even if he's in front of me.
Then, how old is he now?
We were separated when he was seven years old.
He must...
be 31 years old now.
Then, he's the same age with Seong Joon.
Just like Seong Joon, he must be a healthy guy.
Maybe.
Even though 20 years have passed, I can understand...
why you want to find your brother.
How can you?
Didn't you happily grow up in a big family?
That's not necessarily true.
I also...
wander around to find my father.
I visited 150 countries in the world.
My mother...
was a single mother.
She was a single mother back then.
She is quite amazing.
Thanks to her, I grew up in secret.
You said...
your father's death was a wrongful death, right?
Yes.
May I ask under what unfair circumstance he passed away?
No, you may not.
But we are dating.
There are somethings that make your life difficult instead of...
easier when you know more things.
Don't try to find out.
It won't be helpful to you, Jeong Eun.
Okay.
You don't want to suffer me, too. Right?
However, after time passes by,
tell me your suffering.
Tell me how your father passed away unjustly...
and how you lost your brother.
We are dating.
(Director Bang Mi Joo)
You are not going home?
My grandmother wants me to stop by.
If I don't, she calls me all day long.
Where are you going? Are you going to the construction site?
I have to visit Home of Angels.
Then, let's go together later.
The tiles in the bathroom are all broken. The kids might get hurt.
It's urgent. Let's go together next time.
Say hello to the director for me.
Jeong Eun.
Seong Joon.
Hello.
Hi.
- We are meeting a lot. - Yes, we are.
Jeong Eun, where are you coming from?
I am...
I went camping.
Camping?
Yes.
But why are you home so early?
Did something happen? You don't look so good.
Nothing happened.
Anyway, let's go inside.
Bye, Hyun Woo. Drive safely and call me.
I will.
Let's go in.
Hurry up.
Do you know what you're doing?
How can I help you?
I'm here for a consultation about the pension...
regarding my house.
Okay. Please come this way.
Okay. Hurry.
A lot of families have disputes...
due to inheritance and support issues.
You can resolve these disputes through this pension.
That's true.
Children these days aren't shameful at all.
They don't want to support their parents,
but they fight over the inheritance.
I don't know why they behave like that.
Why would you...
tell him such things here?
What? Am I wrong?
How could you?
You're glad you came, right?
Since we found out about this,
we should prepare for our golden years.
It's a good system.
You're admitting that now?
Let's go.
He's so stubborn.
Yes?
Seong Joon.
Jeong Eun.
What are you doing?
I was just resting. I'm tired. Why?
Grandma asked me to help her.
I was on my way to her...
and I just wanted to talk to you.
Can you not...
tell the family what...
you saw before?
Jeong Eun.
Are you really dating him?
Yes.
Do you...
like him a lot?
It's a bit embarrassing to say this to you, but I do.
We aren't serious though.
If they find out,
they will ask me if I will marry him or not.
I want to keep it a secret for a while.
Okay. I will keep your secret.
Thank you, Seong Joon.
Who's home?
Uncle and Aunt. I'm here.
I see. I heard you moved back to your house.
Yes, I did.
Good job. You should sleep at your house.
Your mother's disappointed if you don't.
Yes, I understand.
You're home.
Why are you home so early?
You don't come home this early.
I was feeling a bit tired.
Mother and Father. I will get some rest.
Seong Joon. How about dinner?
I won't need it.
I'll get some sleep, Mother.
Is he sick?
Did something happen?
Jeong Eun, do you know anything about this?
No.
Really?
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
Dong Hui.
My dear Dong Hui.
I'm so proud of you, my Dong Hui.
Hye Joo.
She's my Dong Hui. Why is she yours?
Grandma, I raised her since she was six years old.
So she's my baby.
I'm so proud of you, Dong Hui.
Congratulations, Aunt Dong Hui.
Congratulations.
Thank you, Ji Hoon and Ah In.
When I win the cash prize, I will treat you something good.
- Yes! I'm excited. - Hey,
- will you be getting a prize, too? - Of course.
But because the contest is held by a cable television, it's not much.
Still,
Dong Hui's level has just gone up.
I know.
Then will you be debuting as a writer?
- I don't know yet. - Why don't you know it?
Even if I win, it has to be turned into a TV show.
And even if it gets turned into a TV show, I won't be recognized...
as a writer for just one short show.
That's why you should use this as your opportunity...
to write more shows for TV.
It's easier said than done, you know?
Anyway, good job.
I'm proud of you.
By the way, did you tell Seong Joon?
He's helping you with many things.
He should be the first one you should thank.
Well... I haven't seen him yet.
I think he came home early.
I was actually going to go down.
We should go down too, then.
Let's leave Aunt Dong Hui alone so she can write again.
Dong Hui, keep writing. Write with all your might. Okay?
- Let's go, Kids. - Okay.
Let's go down, Grandma.
Okay. Let's go together.
- Thank you. - Let's go.
Dong Hui.
I quit my job today.
I hope you'll do great even if I'm not here.
- Hello? - It's me.
Yes, Director Bang.
Director Han is at home, right?
I haven't seen him yet, but I think he is home.
I will go there now. I need to talk to you.
Hi, Dong Hui.
Hi.
Can you please change his mind?
What?
Don't you get it?
Why did he resign in the first place?
That's because...
we had a trouble while preparing for our marriage.
I hurried it a bit.
I think he handled it emotionally, and it is very unlike him.
As his staff, you know well...
that he's crucial to the company.
So please make him change his mind.
How can I do that?
Director Han made the call.
Do you think he will change his mind because...
an assistant tells him to?
Dong Hui, aren't you his family?
It's for his best interest.
You owe a lot to his family, so you could do this.
That is why I am saying that I don't have the right.
I think it's better if you approach him directly.
I'll get going now.
I tried. I tried everything.
But he won't listen to me. He doesn't even answer my call.
How desperate should I be to be asking you for a favor?
Can't you think of that?
Do you not care if Seong Joon falls like this?
If Seong Joon leaves the company like this,
he will have no place in this industry.
Besides, do you think my father will leave him alone?
So you have to persuade him.
Or help me so that he will meet me.
The number you're calling is currently unavailable.
It will be charged after the beep.
It's me.
I wondered if we could talk.
I'm with Moong Chi right now. I will wait for you.
Moong Chi, bark.
Why aren't you barking today?
Bark so that Seong Joon will come up.
It's good, isn't it?
- It's good. - What do you think, Ji Hoon?
I think it's good. It's slightly unsanitary, but...
Hey,
if it's good, just say it's good.
Stop being so picky.
Okay. It's good.
That's right, Son. You have to smile like that at your age.
Don't look so gloomy all the time. Okay?
Okay.
Should we go home?
- Let's go. - What is this?
(Fishcake)
Where did you get this?
You eat so much,
so I got rid of everything in the refrigerator except for beans.
Where did you get this? Tell me now.
I am sorry. I was too hungry.
So where did you get this?
Will you go down first?
Okay.
Let's go.
I went down to my old house...
and got it from the refrigerator there.
What?
Hee Sook,
do you want this fish bread?
What?
You loved it...
when you were working.
- When did I like it? - Anyway,
I want to give this to you.
It's not for him.
I will put it there. You should eat it.
Hye Joo, are you joking with me right now?
When did I like this?
Do you even know what Chang Soo...
stole from your place?
What did he steal?
Hey, what did you get from my house?
Fishcakes.
Fishcakes?
Stop crying. Stop.
How can you lose weight when you're so impatient?
If you eat junk food,
all the workouts you did become meaningless.
Be quiet. Be quiet.
- Stop. - Stop.
Hey, stop hitting him.
What if...
he eats a little?
How can a big boy like him survive without eating?
You should stay out of it.
Losing weight is good.
But you have to feed him, too.
It will be too tough for him if you make him drop weights fast.
He's not your son anymore.
So stay out of it.
- What? - Am I wrong?
You've been raising him...
with no discipline. You let him...
do whatever he wants. That's why he became like this.
He lost 3kg until now.
But he gained it right back after eating this today.
Stop eating the fish bread.
Okay.
Put on some clothes.
You will lose all the calories you took in today before going to bed.
Go and change into a training suit.
Okay.
Hurry up!
It bothers me a lot.
There's nothing we can do about it.
Hee Sook has her own way to take care of her kid.
We can't tell her what to do.
Still, she's too mean and harsh.
I'm sure Chang Soo is having a hard time.
I want to move out as soon as possible.
I think I'll feel better if Chang Soo is out of my sight.
My goodness.
Sure, I bet you would feel better.
I think you're right.
Try not to worry about Chang Soo for a while.
That's for your own good.
He's so silly.
He should have...
been nicer to me when I was his mom.
It serves him right.
How is Ji Hoon doing?
I don't know.
Hee Sook raised him too strictly,
so he hardly opens his mind to me.
He doesn't smile a lot, either.
All he does is reading books.
I think he has some issue as well.
I have no idea how I should raise kids.
I can't believe...
that my parents raised four of us this far.
I know.
By the way, I just want...
to grill a lot of pork belly,
so Chang Soo can eat it to his heart's content.
Don't be too harsh to him.
I'm not harsh at all.
Did you think he'd change overnight?
Ji Hoon was different.
Let's not talk about Ji Hoon anymore.
Honey!
Now all you care about is Chang Soo.
How can you never bother to take care of me?
How did the office contract go?
Don't you think you should have asked that earlier?
I signed the contract.
How?
My parents...
didn't even give me a penny.
So I found a cheap one through my friend.
So what will you do?
What do you mean?
I was falsely fired from the show. I will succeed by any means.
Wait and see.
I'll pay them back for the injustice...
and resentment I suffered because I didn't have wealthy parents.
So what should we do with Chang Soo?
Please give up on him.
- Honey. - Stop.
I'll succeed in my career and make a lot of money.
I'll have him liposuction surgery with money...
and appoint him a good post when he grows up.
So please give up on him and raise him into a healthy person.
What?
He has to lose weight to become a healthy person.
Goodness. Is that true?
It is.
My dear.
You must be very happy. Please take a seat.
I am.
My goodness.
- I am very happy. - I see. My goodness.
This rice cake is really tasty.
I never knew...
your granddaughter would become a writer.
Me neither.
Dong Hui really worked hard to become a writer for a long time.
I'm sure she did.
Being a writer is really difficult.
I want to ask writers...
how can they be full of great ideas.
When I write letters,
I write, "How are you doing? I am doing fine."
After that, I have nothing left to write.
So I just write,
"Please take care."
And that's the end of my letter.
My friend found my letter half-hearted and got upset with me.
Since then, she never calls me.
Really?
She was the closest friend...
from high school.
I see.
How can you be so mean? Why are you laughing?
What's the matter?
You always have a wooden face,
so it's hard to read if you're happy or sad.
You even told me that I shouldn't be petty...
and just have followed the grim reaper.
Didn't you say that so cold-heartedly?
And now your granddaughter has become a writer,
and you can't help but keep smiling.
It's because I'm too happy.
Elizabeth, please stop laughing.
This is ridiculous.
My goodness.
What is that?
Honey, come eat some rice cake.
Who brought it?
Dong Hui has become a writer.
- Really? - Yes.
So Ms. Oh brought this to celebrate.
That's great news.
Try some.
- It's good. - Isn't it?
Seong Joon taught her how to write recently.
I think it worked.
Right. Did Seong Joon go to work?
No.
Why not?
He said he's on vacation. He's in his room now.
Is he?
Seong Joon.
Dad.
Are you not going to work?
Wait.
Put your coat on and follow me.
Ma'am, here are your tasty coffee and cakes.
Thank you.
By the way, your cafe is so cozy and nice.
I know. I took care of it a lot.
Where is Ms. Kim? Doesn't she always hang out with you?
The one who owns Geumbit Academy.
She closed the academy...
and moved to other town.
Really? That's sad.
She has run the academy for about 20 years.
I know.
Anyway, I hope this cafe thrives.
Thank you.
Tell me if you want more coffee. You can have as much as you want.
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
By the way, will Geum Ja be all right?
I am so worried, too.
I never thought she'd be arrested.
No one knew it.
Goodness.
Who do you think tipped the police off...
about her fake account?
I don't know.
I feel very uneasy after I heard what happened to her.
By the way, did you hear...
that President Jo Moo Gyeom bought Geum Ja's building?
Are you sure?
Did he have a bad memory in Bangbae-dong or something?
Why does he buy up all the properties here?
That's what I'm saying.
The owner of Mina Supermarket and Geum Ja...
are the witnesses of the drunk driving accident, right?
What are you talking about?
That's nonsense.
Welcome...
Hyun Woo.
Is everything all right?
Yes.
I came to see what you're doing.
I'm working at my cafe.
I had two customers so far.
What's wrong with you?
It's you.
Hello.
I guess you're here for some coffee.
Yes. We just finished drinking.
She's right. We finished our coffee.
Thank you for the coffee, Jeong Eun.
- We enjoyed it. - Ma'am, what's wrong?
See you soon.
- We're leaving. - Okay.
See you later.
Goodness.
Do you want a cucumber sandwich and a cup of coffee?
Sure.
I saw your uncle and Seong Joon.
I think they were on their way to the mountain.
Really?
Why is he at home? Maybe it's his day off.
They seem to be very close to each other.
Of course, they are.
My uncle loves Seong Joon so much.
He's had greater affection...
especially toward Seong Joon for a long time.
- Why is that? - It's because he's handsome.
Besides, he didn't cause any trouble growing up.
He listened to them.
He was an exemplary son.
That's why he likes Seong Joon,
but...
Seong Joon likes Uncle more.
Is that so?
All he cares about is his dad.
He loves his dad a lot.
There's a reason why.
What reason?
I am not certain if I should tell you this.
But you told me your story, too.
Seong Joon was...
born out of wedlock.
Really?
It happened when he was seven years old.
I was only eight and it was hectic for me, too.
That's when he came to our house for the first time.
When I think back, that day was such a chaotic day.
My uncle doesn't look like...
he would cheat on his wife.
My aunt cried and screamed.
She said she was going to divorce him.
It was a total chaos. Somehow, they worked it out and...
it is what it is now.
Seong Joon grew up well.
Everyone's relieved that he did.
That's why Uncle and Seong Joon have...
a special relationship.
Your family story is quite interesting.
What are you thinking about? Your girlfriend is right here.
Do you want to have dinner at my house?
Really?
Come at 7pm.
I'm going.
Hyun Woo.
Good bye. I will be there at 7pm.
Are you not tired?
I climbed more mountains than you.
- Let's take a break here. - Okay.
- Do you want some rice cake? - What kind of rice cake is it?
Ms. Oh won...
some sort of script competition.
Is that so?
That's why her grandmother gave out the rice cake.
Your mom packed it for us. Try it.
Okay.
But why did you resign?
Just because.
It's because I wanted to be free.
That doesn't make sense.
I'm sorry.
Did they...
find fault...
with you because you were born out of wedlock?
No, they didn't.
Then, why did you resign? She visited us not long ago.
It doesn't seem logical.
- We are not getting married. - Then why did she visit us?
She wanted to.
She visited us because you led her on.
I'm repenting.
Even if that happened. But still.
If you resign like this,
putting aside the fact she's hurt,
what will happen to your subordinates who depended on you?
The same goes to the company who trusted you and gave you the job.
This is not how you should treat them.
I'm aware of it.
You are aware of it, but this is how you handled it?
I wished...
all my life that you'd grow up well.
I worried...
if you would turn out well...
or if you would turn rebellious.
However,
unlike your brothers,
you never caused troubles.
As I saw you matured into a decent individual,
I was grateful.
I'm going to feel grateful...
until the day I die.
Seong Joon.
- Yes? - If there's anything that will...
help you, I will do it no matter what it is.
I can sacrifice my life for you.
Father, why are you talking like this?
If you resigned because they rejected you...
since you were born out of wedlock,
if this is the case, it will break my heart.
Father, it's not true. I didn't resign because of that.
Then, why did you?
My son, Seong Joon. You are not under qualified
Why would you need to resign?
It's breaking my heart.
Father.
What a misfortune. This is a chaos.
We have a lot of work to do. How can he resign like this?
He took care of all the urgent assignments, though.
It doesn't matter. There's no one to lead the team afterwards.
I mean I do hate him,
but no one is as good as he is.
I only admit that image of him.
By the way, does it mean Director Bang and Director Han are over?
Writer Jo. Director Han is...
on a business trip overseas.
It's hard to get a hold of him.
- What are we going to do? - No, it's not true.
We will be able to reach him soon.
He's in Shanghai. We are in different time zones.
Anyway, I will tell him to contact you right away.
Okay.
What? Different time zones? It's only an hour difference.
What was I supposed to do?
She's saying that she will only work with Director Han.
- That you should have... - I was confused. I was lying.
This is driving me crazy.
Seriously, why did he resign out of the blue?
That's what I want to ask.
What are we going to do? We have to resolve this somehow.
Without Director Han, we are ruined.
Signing the writer and airing it on a TV station weren't the hard parts.
What follows is more challenging.
This is a problem.
Han Seong Joon resigned?
Yes.
How absurd.
Bring me his resignation letter. I will accept it.
I will destroy him.
We need to bring him back.
He's not worth it.
It's because I was stubborn.
He wasn't interested in a marriage.
That means all he cared about was work.
If we lose him, we will suffer a heavy blow.
Writer Jo said she'll terminate the contract if he doesn't come back.
There are many qualified directors who can replace him.
He's acting arrogant because...
you keep holding on to him.
You're right. I acknowledge my mistakes.
But saving the company takes precedence now.
I can't accept his resignation, Dad.
Please. Trust me one more time.
- You can't. - Dad.
How dare he submit a letter of resignation?
I'm going to...
bury him somewhere.
If you do that, then I will die with him.
- What did you say? - Why?
Do you think I can't?
I will die if you hurt him.
I'm going to die.
Is this all?
Yes, it is.
This is too light.
I don't have a mink coat that can't be crumpled...
or jewelries.
It makes sense I don't have a lot of belongings.
Where should I put these?
If you have a drawer, let me have one.
Please come this way.
Mom. I'm here.
- Mom. I'm here. - Yes, you are here.
I didn't know you were here, Ms. Oh.
- Yes, I am. Hello. - Hi.
By the way...
Mom.
- You can't do this. - Stay out of it.
My goodness, Mom.
You're already living with your in-laws in the same building.
Are you going to share a room with her now?
Dong Hui became a writer.
You should congratulate her,
but that doesn't have anything to do with this.
That old woman stays with Dong Hui.
Then she won't be able to write.
What is this about?
If she becomes a famous writer,
are you going to ask her...
to give you a job as an actress?
Why not?
If they need someone to play a woman Song Joong Ki falls in love with,
I'm going to do it.
What did you say?
- My gosh. - Besides, I'm scared.
You come by every evening,
but I'm all alone at night.
The grim reaper keeps showing up in my dreams these days.
Hey. Look at Ms. Oh's face. If the grim reaper comes...
and sees her face, it will run away.
How ridiculous.
What a jerk.
I asked him to backstitch it and he did such a bad job.
Also, she made a promise with me.
If the grim reaper comes, she will follow it instead of me.
So to speak,
she switched her ticket number with me.
Sometimes, when you go to a bank,
a busy person asks you to switch the ticket numbers.
Mom!
Why are you yelling at me?
Anyhow,
don't you live with her,
have a fight again, and call me.
Do you hear me?
You brat.
Seong Hoon. Please put it over here.
All right. Here we go.
Is your back okay?
Of course.
It hasn't been long since you removed your cast.
I'm worried.
Gosh. Don't you worry about it.
If I can help you become a good writer,
I wouldn't wish more.
Seong Hoon. Thank you so much.
I know things are hard for you, too.
Thank you for taking care of me.
Don't say that. Of course I should take care of you.
You're my only sister-in-law. Am I right?
Is this good enough to be your workroom?
I'm starving.
Chang Soo.
Ah In.
Eat this, Chang Soo.
What's this?
It's snack I got from the preschool today.
I didn't eat it because I wanted...
to give it to you.
Ah In. Thank you so much.
Hang in there, Chang Soo!
Ah In.
Aunt Hee Sook.
I don't want to scold you.
I'm sorry.
No. You shouldn't be saying that.
It's only natural that you want...
to help your brother.
- What? - However,
I don't have a daughter, right?
And I really...
adore you, Ah In.
I'm raising your brother, Chang Soo.
Maybe...
I should raise you as well, my dear Ah In.
What?
My dear Ah In.
How would you feel if you have to live with me?
Please forgive me. I won't do it again.
- Chang Soo. - Dad.
Here. Eat this.
Hurry up.
Seong Hoon.
"Anna Karenina", a novel by Leo Tolstoy is...
evaluated as the most artistic work...
of Tolstoy among his many other novels.
Is that right?
It's been so long since I read a book.
This novel depicts...
Russian aristocratic circles...
in 1870s.
And it is the background of Anna's love affair.
Do you know how the novel begins?
Look, Hee Sook.
Like I said, it's been so long since I read a book.
"Happy families are all alike."
"Every unhappy family..."
"is unhappy in its own way."
I see.
I'd like to change these words...
to something that reflects my situation today.
How?
Slim kids are pretty in their own way...
while fat kids are look alike...
for only one reason.
Excuse me?
Do you want Chang Soo to look like...
all the other fat kids?
No. I don't, Hee Sook.
If you had been my husband,
I wouldn't have let you off so easy.
I can't...
I can never be your husband.
I'm sorry. Forgive me, Hee Sook.
Are you...
going to give Chang Soo food again?
No. No.
I'll never do that again.
Thank you for inviting me.
I didn't know what to wear,
so I just wore this.
Invite?
It's not like this is your first time being here.
You came to my place so often as if it's your own.
Now you're thanking me for inviting you.
Still, when a man invites a woman to his place for dinner,
it must mean something more than just dinner.
Don't expect too much.
I just wanted to cook for you since I couldn't when we were camping.
Anyway,
the book said the first stage of a man and woman...
getting close is the man inviting his girlfriend to his house.
Throw that book away immediately.
Still, you brought me a nice bottle of wine.
Really?
- Do you like pasta? - Yes.
You don't have to come.
I'm good at cooking, too.
I know you are.
But you should just rest. You've been standing all day long.
Sit over there.
Okay.
By the way,
you look good in that dress.
Pardon?
You look good in that dress.
I see. Thank you.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Are you on a date with her?
I can talk.
Han Seong Joon handed in his resignation a few days ago.
I think we may have to change our plans.
Did you find out anything about his birthmother?
Actually, I couldn't find any information.
I think we should look into it from another direction.
Okay. Look into it further, then.
I hope you'll have a good time with her.
Listen, it's not what you think.
Oh, my. Why did you go into your bedroom to answer the call?
- It's nothing. - Are you hiding something?
My gosh.
It's delicious.
By the way, why did you get...
double locks on your bedroom door? I've been curious.
Why are you curious about that?
Besides, you have a model of our neighborhood.
It looked so real with the lights and everything.
Did you forget what I do for a living? I'm an architect.
I suppose.
I'm a neat freak.
I really hate when other people touch my things.
When I was in college in the States,
my roommate kept touching my things.
So I smacked him.
Both of us got kicked out of the dormitory because of that.
You should learn to control your temper.
Can't you be more easygoing?
Don't force it on me just because you can.
Anyway, the most easygoing guy I've ever known is...
Seong Joon.
But I guess Seong Joon must have been very lonely.
His mother and brothers aren't...
his real family.
No. It was never like that.
My family isn't that kind of people,
and Seong Joon has been a very good kid.
Besides, he's smart and reliable.
Anyway, he was just different from the beginning.
We understood each other. He has no mother, and I have no father.
He still must have been lonely.
But he didn't show it. That's what made me feel bad for him.
Do you know who his birthmother is?
No. We've never seen her,
or talked about her.
It's like a taboo subject in our house.
Come in. Be quiet, Moong Chi.
Don't bark. Stay quiet.
You're here.
Yes.
Why are you standing there like that?
Don't you have to work harder from now on?
You're now one step closer to your dream of being a writer...
who makes a lot of money and meets handsome actors...
every day.
Congratulations. I really mean it.
- Director Han. - I'm not a director anymore.
It feels so empty without you.
Everyone would feel that way at first.
I'm not talking about other people.
I'm talking about me.
I'm sure you can do great even without me.
I know I can.
But when you were there,
I felt like I had a reliable supporter. I just never told you.
Dong Hui.
You asked me what my dream was, right?
What's your dream?
I've been curious for a long time.
My dream is to make heartwarming dramas...
and show them to many people.
Why? Was that an unexpected answer from a producer?
No. I'm just happy.
You and I share the same dreams.
I don't write the scripts.
Of course. I don't produce dramas, either.
Are you going to give up your dreams, then?
Director Bang came to see me yesterday.
She asked me to stop you from resigning.
She asked me, a person with no power.
I see.
I know this isn't something I can stop.
But I'm just worried that...
you might never be able to work in this field if you quit now.
That's what I'm worried about.
I guess Director Bang told you about that stuff, too.
If you think about it, she's not wrong.
You quit before finishing the work you started.
You told me to be more confident,
and not to give up my dream as a writer.
What I can say to you is...
I mean...
What I can say to you as a friend who shares...
the same dreams as yours is...
do not give up.
Whatever the reason is, I don't think you should give up...
the dreams you have had for so long.
Also, I have a favor to ask of you.
You have to do this for me.
What is it?
I want to work harder from now on,
and become the greatest writer in this country in 10 years.
Would you produce my drama then?
If you do, it will be...
another memory between us.
How many women have you seduced like this?
- What? - It's fine.
I'm not someone who dwells on the past.
Didn't the book that you're reading say...
a couple shouldn't ask about each other's past?
Am I not supposed to? I haven't finished reading it yet.
I think I had too much wine.
I should try to sober up.
What should I do with those two?
The way I see it,
they like each other.
I hope things go well between them.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I actually have a brother who is around the same age...
as you, Seong Joon.
Is that so?
I think I can find your mother now.
Thank you so much...
for raising me and taking care of me so far.
- Are you here to eat? - Yes.
Mom. Please don't tell me to go out and play.
I don't think...
you're a very good person.