The way I see it, they like each other.
How do you know that?
Isn't it obvious?
I figured it out last Christmas.
Didn't you call them to hit on me?
It was for both.
You're supposed to more than one thing at a time.
Goodness.
Look at that idiot.
Nothing will happen if they just sit like that.
Dong Hui's no better.
I hope things go well between them.
But...
in-laws should not like each other, right?
There's no such rule in times like this.
Still, when adults find out about this, they will go crazy.
So I am going to keep Seong Joon's secret.
If all fails, I am going to get him money to run away.
Where would you get the money?
Goodness.
Seong Joon promised to keep my secret, too.
He will keep it a secret that I'm in love with you.
It's my mom.
Hide.
Hurry.
As you can see, it's designed in a way that makes it easier...
for the consumers to find the product they want.
With just one click, they will be transferred to the purchase page.
This page was also designed simply so that the product...
will stand out in the page.
Please take a look.
Very nice.
It's different from other companies' websites in a way that...
there are no advertisement banners...
and that only our products are exposed to them.
Therefore, the consumers will be able to concentrate on the product.
The shopping mall website looks...
as sincere as Mrs. Seo.
Thank you, Sir.
I'm late. Oh, dear.
Ms. Kim.
Upload the presentation on the company web database.
Report to me about the demonstration schedule within tomorrow.
- Okay. - Did anyone call?
Your family called many times.
I'm leaving now. Go home when you're done.
- Mother, this is it. - Is it?
- Goodness. - The location is good.
I think he will have many customers.
I know.
Hyung Seop, will Seong Hoon be cooking?
Of course he will. Go in.
- Please go in, Mother. - Let's do that.
(Toreore Chicken)
When are you going serve spicy fried chicken?
It's coming soon.
It's packed. Is there a table for us?
Goodness.
It's coming now.
Enjoy.
Grandma. Aunt.
Mother, Father. You're here.
Yes. Congratulations.
You're busy. Where's your wife? Why are you doing this alone?
You are not going there.
- What? - We are going...
there.
(Attorney Han's Office)
Follow me. Hurry.
Thank you, Sir.
Thank you for sending flowers to my humble office.
I am very grateful.
Like I said,
I will visit you tomorrow.
- Okay. - Honey.
Why are you just two? Where are the others?
They went to Seong Hoon's restaurant downstairs.
It's very nicely decorated.
- How about here? - I'm sure they will come up.
I will go pick them up.
You sit right there.
My gosh.
My head hurts from all the fried chicken smell.
Aren't they being too unfair to me?
Wait.
- Gosh. - Honey.
Goodness.
There's no table for us.
It's okay. Just watching it makes me happy.
- Gosh. - Goodness.
What's this? Why is everyone here?
Don't you know that I'm opening my office today, too?
Stop it.
Be patient.
Mom. Dad.
Here's garlic soy chicken.
- Hey, be quiet. - Still,
we can't just stand here forever.
- What do we do? - I don't know.
- What should we do? - I know.
You are too unfair. Okay?
- Where did he learn this? - What's this?
He cooks better than his mom.
- It's so delicious. - Don't give Hyung Seop wings.
He will have an affair.
Eat it. It's okay.
- Eat a lot. - Gosh.
Why are you eating fried chicken here?
What else can we do?
There's no table at Seong Hoon's restaurant.
How nice is it to eat here with just our family members?
This is not what I wanted.
Seriously, what is this!
What are you doing, Chang Soo?
Where did he go after coming back from the opening ceremony?
We came in together.
- Yes. Thank you. - Enjoy.
Thank you.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Please give me a lot of rice.
More.
- More? - Yes.
Thank you.
Honey.
- Yes? - How did you...
end up here?
Well, I ended up here because my parents were switched.
Your parents were switched.
Hurry up and eat.
Thank you.
Thanks to you, I was able to open my office so fast.
If you didn't introduce me to Senior Secretary and President Lee,
this would have not happened.
Thank you so much.
It's nothing.
I just introduced the two parties who needed each other.
Your future is in your hands now.
Don't you worry about it.
I've already won over...
Senior Secretary and President Lee.
I see.
Shortly, Hoin Industry and Seonjin Construction...
will request to work with you.
Pardon me?
Is...
Is that why they sent these?
They are my close acquaintances.
They asked me to recommend a good lawyer.
And I thought of you.
I appreciate it so much.
I will never forget this.
Seong Hoon.
Seong Joon, welcome.
- Congratulations. - Thank you.
- Please take this. - This?
Goodness. Thank you, Seong Joon.
Congratulations. You have to earn a lot of money.
I know.
Hello.
- Hello, Ji Hoon. - Hello.
Hello, Ah In.
I will go say hi to Seong Sik and then come back to help you.
Yes. You should visit Seong Sik's office.
He was so upset that nobody came to his opening party.
Okay. I will be back, then.
Hello.
I guess you are on the way to visit your brother's office.
Yes.
Well, then.
Seong Sik.
Seong Sik, my little brother.
Why are you so late? It hurts.
I'm sorry I am late. Congratulations.
- I hope you thrive. - Thank you.
You didn't have to bring this.
Why don't you have a seat?
You're the only one in my family...
who truly cares about me.
So many people sent me flower pots as you can see.
And even Director Han of FGC came all the way here...
to celebrate.
Did Senior Secretary send you the pot?
Seong Sik, do you know him well?
Of course, I do.
He counts on me recently.
Look, even Seonghan Group sent me a flower pot.
President Lee really likes me.
By the way, how did you get close to them?
Why? Is there a problem?
The collusive links between Minjeong Party...
and Seonghan have become an issue these days.
How timid you are.
Hey. Great politicians and businessmen...
all have little flaws like that.
Still, you should be cautious.
Hey, if you meet them in person, you'd know how nice they are.
And if they were that dangerous people,
Mr. Lee wouldn't have introduced them to me.
- Mr. Lee did? - Yes, the guy next door did.
Isn't he just running a construction company?
He does, but that's not all he does.
I guess it's because of his uncle.
He has got a lot of connections in various areas.
He even lend me this office almost for free.
I've already got many cases...
since he introduced me to everyone he knows.
I'll be extremely busy right from the beginning.
Seong Sik, you should be careful.
There's no such thing as a free lunch.
Why do you talk and think like a old geezer?
You're still very young.
Hello.
- Are you on your way home? - Yes.
I had to help my brothers, so I'm a little late today.
- There are things to celebrate. - That's right.
My brothers told me about you.
You're helping them a lot.
Neighbors should help each other out.
I'll treat you to a nice meal later for my brothers.
See you around.
Seong Joon.
Why don't we...
go for drinks now?
- Do you like drinking? - Although I can't drink a lot,
I like as much as others do.
Let's just talk casually.
I think we're about the same age.
You might find me boring.
Even my friends call me a nerd...
and don't want to have drinks with me.
Really?
I like you because you're polite and upright.
- I'll take it as a compliment. - I really mean it.
You really look like a good guy.
It's all thanks to my parents.
Actually,
I have a younger brother about your age.
I see.
I don't think I've seen him.
That's right. He's not here.
I see.
What do you do on your days off?
I usually read books I wanted to read...
or monitor the dramas of other channels.
Why don't you take time off from your busy life?
You can go clubbing and meet some girls...
before you get old.
That's what young people do, right?
I like it better.
I'm enjoying my life to the full.
Is it because you don't live alone?
Isn't it uncomfortable to live with your parents?
There's no reason to feel that way.
They've raised me so far.
Mr. Lee,
thank you so much for helping...
my brothers.
However,
I no longer want my family...
to owe you anything.
It wasn't a big deal at all.
I just helped them as a neighbor.
I didn't mean to offend you.
Still, I think...
my family members can take care of each other...
without other's help.
I guess you really love your family.
I received a lot of things from them.
I will never be able to pay them back...
for what they've given me.
You're such a nice son...
and a nice brother.
You might find me peculiar,
but my family is all I got.
They're what I care the most.
I see.
I already paid for it.
I wanted to treat you this time.
You helped my brothers.
Seong Joon! Hyun Woo!
Gosh, you should be careful.
Jeong Eun.
I'm so sorry.
Wait, is it already over?
It is. Let's go home.
No way. They serve great stir-fried chicken feet.
Let's just have one more dish.
Seong Joon, let's have just one more drink.
Come on.
Let's just go home.
How can a lady drink every day? Let's get going.
I want to drink, too.
Seong Joon, tell him to listen to me.
You can leave. It was nice to see you.
I'll take her home.
Okay. See you later.
- Goodbye, Jeong Eun. - See you, Seong Joon.
Seong Joon, let's drink later!
Gosh, let's go.
- Let's go for another round. - That's enough.
Go inside. Don't despair just because you didn't drink tonight.
Have a cup of milk and sleep tight.
Why do you smile like that?
I walked you home, then you should go in.
What do you want from me with that smile?
I want you to figure it out. You are not a child.
It hurts.
You read that book again.
I told you to dump that book right away.
Don't you ever feel embarrassed?
Life is too short to feel embarrassing.
Fine. See you.
Go inside. Come on.
Go in.
It's my mom. She'll kill me if she sees me.
A young couple in love...
Professor Song.
I got home safely.
You put me in a cab.
I'm in front of my house.
By the way,
The baritone singer tonight.
His voice was just charming.
As soon as he sang the first verse,
he caught my ears.
His tone was clear.
What a great singing ability.
His voice was so rich and he had perfect acting skills.
By the way,
is he married?
Then? Is he seeing anyone?
- She's embarrassing. - He was so attractive.
That song.
I was completed won over by it.
"I Don't Love You Anymore."
I won't love you anymore.
I guess...
you take after your mother.
She's unstoppable.
I guess she must have met an amazing baritone singer.
She still hasn't learned her lesson.
By the way...
Why are you looking at me like that? You're making me cringe.
I mean it's...
Go in quickly.
It looks like your mother drank a lot.
Okay, then. Get home safely.
Jeong Eun.
Yes?
Good night.
Okay.
Get on it.
What? How? How is this possible?
- What's wrong? - Isn't...
this broken?
You said you bought this from online yesterday.
Losing weight might not be possible,
but you worked out without eating.
Then you shouldn't at least have gained weight.
You.
Did you...
eat something without telling me?
No, I didn't. There's nothing to eat.
I don't have any money. You took all my money, Mother.
Something's fishy.
I'm hungry, Mother.
Okay. You're ready.
Ah In, Dad is busy with his restaurant.
He can't take you to your preschool.
So let's leave a bit early with me. Is that okay?
Yes, it is.
My cute baby.
Let's go.
Ji Hoon.
What are you doing? I'm leaving for work.
Okay. See you.
What are you doing this morning?
I'm studying.
Studying?
It's good to study.
You're on a winter break. You should have some fun.
I can't let this slide.
You. Here you go.
Take this money and don't come home until dark.
Why?
I'm telling you to go out and have fun.
What is this? You are supposed to go out and enjoy yourself.
You're studying during your winter break.
I don't...
have anyone to hang out even if I go out.
But still. You should go out.
Close your book. Close it.
Okay.
Today, you must go out.
I will.
All right, then.
"Our rooster was chased again today."
"It was when I had lunch and came out to chop the wood."
Han Chang Soo!
What's the matter, Mother?
What's wrong? When is the breakfast?
I'm hungry.
Since I was young,
I always had toasts and coffee for breakfast.
It was because my father was a high ranking official.
He often had his breakfast...
with foreigners.
That had an effect on breakfast at home.
After I got married, there was one time I ran out of coffee.
I couldn't go out to buy coffee because of my mother-in-law.
At that time, I could only get it at Hwapyeong department store.
I remember that I was in a jam.
Why don't you have toasts, too?
Why would I have that for breakfast? It will turn my stomach.
You can just drink this coffee.
I will drink this hot rice water. Enjoy your coffee.
How can we spend...
our last years together when we are clearly so different?
Why can't we?
All we have to do is respect each other's preferences.
So please adapt to my preferences.
- Ms. Hwang. - What?
Try this kimchi.
- Here you go. - What? Ms. Oh!
Where are you going this morning?
What do you mean where? I'm going to work.
Then, with whom will I spend my day today?
Spend it with her.
What?
When are you coming home?
Ms. Oh! My goodness.
Dong Hui. Are you on your way to work?
- Yes. - Okay. Have a good day at work.
By the way,
what will Moong Chi's brother do today?
Excuse me?
You said you are not a director anymore.
So I don't have to call you by.
I wondered what Moong Chi's brother will do today.
Don't worry about me.
I will go and get one step closer to becoming a writer.
Why don't you comb Moong Chi's hair...
since you are free?
What did you say?
Dong Hui. Hey.
- When's the breakfast? - I'm cooking it now.
It's fish.
That looks delicious.
Mother, can I have breakfast, too?
My goodness. You, men.
How will you survive without me?
Here you go. Dig in.
Thank you for the food.
Don't be like that for cooking us breakfast.
By the way, until when are you on your leave?
It is...
Why did you take a leave of absence from the start of the year?
I understand if it was the end of the year. This was so abrupt.
What do you mean by abrupt?
He worked hard for all that time. He can take a leave of absence.
It's hard for me when he doesn't go to work.
What's so hard for you?
I have to cook him three meals a day.
I can take care of it.
You are his mother. Can't you prepare his meals for him?
It bothers me to prepare yours, too.
What?
By the way, Seong Joon. Are you getting married...
with the lady who visited us before?
- Excuse me? - She came to visit us.
You should say either you will marry her or not.
It's not like you are young.
Mother.
Mi Joo is just a friend and a coworker.
- We are not getting married. - What?
Then why did she come to visit us?
It was because...
we didn't communicate well.
What?
Don't take what she said too hard.
I completely believe in your decision.
I'm sorry, Father.
Let's go out and have black bean sauce noodles later.
Isn't she being too petty about food?
- Cheer up. - Okay.
Hello?
Writer Jo, that's not true.
Director Han is on a business trip overseas.
What do you mean you will terminate the contract?
Writer Jo. Hello?
What will we do? Will she terminate the contract?
It's a serious problem.
She did wait for a long time considering her personality.
Ms. Oh. Please bring us the contract.
Where is Ms. Oh?
Ms. Oh. What happened with his proposal?
Did she go somewhere?
What is everyone looking for her?
Is she an important part of this office?
Okay. Look for Director Han instead of Ms. Oh.
We are about to be ruined.
She's coming in late today.
- Why? - Why?
Something amazing will happen to her today.
- What is it? - What is it?
- Did she catch Seo Cheol Min? - Is she getting married?
You are hopeless.
Oh Dong Hui, the writer of the runner-up.
Oh Dong Hui.
- From the script competition... - Thank you.
Hosted by Channel T, her script was selected as a runner-up.
- Here is the certificate. - Thank you.
Please give a round of applause.
This is it? Thank you.
(Channel T Script Competition Awards Ceremony)
- Ms. Oh. Please look this way. - Okay.
Ms. Oh. Please do a good job of it.
Yes, I will.
Only wealthy people live in this neighborhood.
A small mistake will cause a big trouble.
Yes, I know. I'm doing my best.
Hello, Dong Hui.
Grandma. I'm at the broadcasting company.
I see. Did the ceremony go well?
Yes, it did.
I'm sorry. I should've been there. I had to work.
Don't worry about it.
By the way,
Thank you, Grandma.
Thank you for raising me...
all these years.
Don't mention it.
Who would raise my baby if it's not me?
But still.
You raised me.
You took care of me. I sincerely thank you.
Why are you crying?
It's a happy day. Don't cry.
Grandma.
I even received the prize money.
My goodness. You did?
I received 5,000 dollars.
Gosh. My baby did well.
I'm so proud of you.
Grandma.
I've never earned this much money in my life.
I should write more diligently.
It feels good to make money, Grandma.
Welcome.
President.
Look who's here. Director Han's here.
How have you been?
Okay.
You look better...
since you rested at home.
Go upstairs.
It's a talk between two men.
So how does it feel to stay at home for a few days?
- President. - If you will talk nonsense, don't.
I didn't accept your resignation yet.
Keep your manner.
I'm sorry.
Writer Jo said...
she won't work if you resign. What are you going to do?
- Excuse me? - She officially sent a notice...
that she will terminate the contract.
She's temperamental and grumpy.
Tell her to do whatever she wants.
However, what will you do with...
the schedule you coordinated under her name?
If we can't deliver our side of the bargain,
we will have to stop our...
contents-related business forever.
You might think you handed in...
your resignation letter thinking you tied up loose ends.
From our perspective,
it seems like you ran away.
Thanks to you, our business will be ruined.
The employees in your department...
will lose their job overnight.
And...
are you going...
to keep being stubborn?
You're so arrogant.
He resigned from our company?
What will you do with him?
What do you mean what I will do? We will let him work.
Later I will find something on him...
and send him to jail.
All sorts of things happen when you produce a drama.
I'm going to teach him a lesson.
I'm going to put him to work...
and later, I will make sure that he ends up in jail.
That was arrogant of him.
How dare he act like that?
- Let go. - Com here.
You are pushing it. Get in the car.
- Hurry. - You're hurting me.
Get in.
- Please enjoy your beverages. - Thank you.
Jeong Eun.
Seong Joon, what brings you here at this hour?
What's wrong?
What's going on?
Seong Joon.
What do you...
like about Lee Hyun Woo?
Why are you bringing this up?
I was just curious.
I don't think...
he's such a good person.
No, he is a good person.
You got him wrong.
Actually,
this is a secret.
I met him in New York three years ago.
I've been watching him ever since.
- Really? - Yes.
At the time, he was the CEO of an investment bank on Wall Street.
He's now lost everything.
He's one of those people who instantly became rich...
with stocks and then lost everything.
But he's a good person. He's very good-hearted.
He treats me well,
and he rented me this place for a fraction of the cost.
Did he do that to you, too?
Yes. Why?
It's nothing.
I am sorry. I am sorry.
- You're here again. - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - You're here.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
I have to pick up Ah In. I'm late.
Ji Hoon.
Mom.
What are you doing here?
I...
Goodness.
Have you been here all day?
Yes.
You told me to play outside.
But I haven't done this before,
so I didn't know what to do.
I didn't know where to go.
Did you do this whenever I told you to play outside?
Yes.
Is it that hard to play?
I really don't know how to play.
I feel more at ease when I study.
Mom.
Please don't tell me to go out and play.
Okay?
What should I do with you?
What should I do?
- Please give me a lot. - Thank you.
- Eat a lot. - Okay.
Thank you.
- Please give me a lot. - Eat a lot.
- Are you here to eat, too? - Yes.
Stop right there!
Han Chang Soo!
Come on. Come on.
Hey, what's that about?
He went to get a free meal and got caught.
Free meal?
Yes.
- Who went there? - Who do you think it is?
It's the person who we both know.
Are you in your right mind?
Why would you go there to get food?
Stop hitting me. It hurts.
How can I not hit you right now?
Goodness.
I tried so hard to make you work out.
I got you those expensive beans...
and made you lose weight.
And how could you go to a soup kitchen?
Do you think it's where you can just go and get food?
That place is for people who can't afford to...
feed themselves. That's where they get free food.
It's not where you go because you can't control your appetite.
Do you understand?
Goodness. It's too much.
How can Chang Soo go to the soup kitchen?
Gosh. He's a clever boy, isn't he?
It's not the time to worry about Chang Soo.
What are you talking about?
Ji Hoon is just as in trouble, too.
Today,
I told him to play outside,
and he sat in the playground all day...
and thought about what to do.
What?
If I were him,
I'd think while riding the swing.
Honey,
Ji Hoon is in serious trouble.
Chang Soo got hungry, so he came up with the soup kitchen idea.
He can think creatively at least.
Is that something to be proud about?
No, but it's true.
Of course, Chang Soo's actions are quite off the wall,
but who would think like that?
Only Chang Soo can think like that.
But Ji Hoon doesn't even know how to play.
Don't you think that's a bigger problem?
So? Where did Ji Hoon go now?
I told him to go up to Seong Joon's room.
Why?
I told him to go there and think about what he really wants to do.
I told him to write a bucket list.
What list?
You know.
It's a list of all the things you want to do in life.
You. Listen carefully.
You are grounded from now on.
What?
You are grounded until the school resumes.
You can't go anywhere.
The only time you can leave...
is when you are exercising with me.
That's the only time. Okay?
Study now.
Mom.
Don't you ever think about escaping like in "The Shawshank Redemption"!
Sir.
Did you look for a place?
Is this about that child from Home of Angels?
Yes. I think I shouldn't ignore it.
Maybe you can make her the information desk clerk...
at Golden Street Korea Branch.
I will do that.
Is there any more information about Han Seong Joon?
Within the FGC Group, everyone knows that...
he is engaged to the chairman's only daughter.
But despite the rumor, he recently resigned.
He's got some nerve.
I agree.
Here are the documents from FGC Group...
regarding Han Seong Joon.
How did it go with Senior Secretary?
From my understanding,
he already contacted Attorney Han.
Han Seong Sik is an easy opponent,
but this man is the problem.
(FGC Personal Record Card)
Hyun Woo.
His front door was open. Where did he go?
So will you be...
at the construction site all day tomorrow, President Lee?
Yes. If nothing special comes up.
Oh, dear.
Aren't you Ms. Han Jeong Eun?
Yes.
Hello, Mr. Jo.
How did you get in?
The front door was open.
I didn't know you had...
plans today.
It's all right, Uncle.
I hope you'll have a good time, Jeong Eun.
- Why don't you join us for dinner? - No.
I can take a hint, you see.
Okay.
Uncle. I'll see you later, then.
Listen. I didn't hear him wrong, did I?
Mr. Jo called you "President Lee" earlier.
He helped me a lot since I was in New York.
He formed a habit of calling me that.
He still calls me that from time to time.
Are you saying he was your subordinate back then?
Well, kind of.
You were so rich and successful.
I'm sorry things turned out this way.
Why?
Are you sorry that I'm not rich anymore?
I didn't mean that.
I just don't want people to say that you are...
living off your uncle at least.
I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Let's eat kimchi stew today. The old-fashioned kimchi stew.
Do you know how to make it?
Of course not. I bought it from a great restaurant nearby.
I'll fix the meal today. All I have to do is boil it.
Oh, goodness.
What should I do? Oh, my.
Gosh, I'm so scared.
Oh my goodness!
Are you really scared?
Or did the book say you should pretend to be scared?
We picked a wrong movie today.
I easily get frightened.
You said the movie had a twist. You didn't say it was a horror movie.
My gosh.
If you get frightened so easily,
how did you go around the world and sleep out in the open?
That's different.
Oh, my. What should I do?
I'll get it.
What should I do? Why don't you just take it off?
- You should... - No, it's fine.
What? Are you going to say I'm being silly?
- No. - What, then?
Am I clumsy?
Look.
Are you always...
this careless?
Excuse me?
What are you talking about? You're offending me.
It looks like you believe...
everything people tell you like a little child.
Of course I believe what people tell me.
Should I doubt them first?
Once I decide to trust someone,
I believe whatever the person says, even if it's obviously a lie.
You have to be loyal.
What are you looking at me like that? We're alone.
You're not getting any wrong ideas, are you?
Oh, goodness. I should run away!
Gosh.
My goodness.
The starts are beautiful.
I really like this place although it's not as good as...
the rooftop of my grandma's house.
You said you were scared. Are you okay?
I have you, Hyun Woo.
My goodness. My mom is so cute.
She doesn't even look at me now that she's living with Ms. Oh.
It'd be good for me if I don't have to come here anymore.
Gosh. Is she out of her mind?
Aren't you cold?
- I'm cold. - Do you need a blanket?
I brought one.
That'd be great.
Jeong Eun.
Get down here.
I saw everything. You'd better get down here now.
Sit down. We have to hide. Hurry.
- It's too late. - You should come down, too.
Me... Me?
Get down here, both of you!
- You little... What are you doing? - Mom.
- What do you think you're doing? - Mom.
Why didn't that guy come down with you?
Mom. Let's talk when we get at home, okay?
Don't be silly.
Gosh. Just get in. Come on.
- Let go of me. - All right. Let's get in.
Let's talk at home.
Writer Jo.
Hello, Producer Kim.
How have you been, Writer Jo?
Good, of course. I've always been great.
- Hello. Welcome. - Hello. Welcome.
All right. Hello.
Hello. I'm Jo Jeong Sook. It's nice to meet you.
It's an honor to finally meet you. I'm Park Jin Sang.
Director Bang. Writer Jo is here.
Please hurry.
By the way,
your office is so messy.
I think it stinks a bit, too.
Open the windows. Open them now.
You're not ready to welcome me at all.
It's not that. It's just...
the air is polluted these days, so...
Hello, Writer Jo.
Oh, my. What a pretty lady.
By the way, where is Director Han Seong Joon?
I said I don't want to work with anyone but him.
Bring Director Han right now.
Now!
Oh, my. Director Han. You're here.
Gosh, it's been such a long time.
- It's good to see you again. - You, too.
How have you been?
What's your name?
Yes. It's Oh Dong Hui.
You look like a very nice lady.
- Thank you. - Thank you for the tea.
Sure. Thank you.
None of this makes sense.
We all agreed to work together. You should stick it out until the end.
If the staff suddenly changes in the middle,
it's hard to achieve the objective we set at the beginning.
- Don't you agree, Director Han? - I'm sorry.
We're not playing a game here.
Also, how could you try to dump me...
on some other guys?
I'm sorry, but Director Han didn't try to dump you on other guys.
I need you to stay out of this.
I really don't like you.
I am sorry.
Anyway,
we made a deal, so you should take responsibility to the end.
I won't let it slide just because you're handsome!
Okay.
I will fulfill the promise.
We are sorry.
Thank you for coming back, Seong Joon.
Before I decided to return, I made a few promises with the president.
Firstly,
my return doesn't mean that I'll marry you.
I know.
And...
I will lead the Contents Team...
and produce only good dramas not commercial ones.
That's what I want.
I will work with competent directors and writers...
regardless of their backgrounds.
I'll select only quality scenarios with literacy value.
Why don't you decide that after you finish Writer Jo's work...
successfully?
You're right.
I will put over the drama no matter what.
I know...
you and other staff members went through a lot because of me.
I'll make sure to make up for it.
I'm glad to hear that.
Mi Joo.
You were the best partner...
from the beginning.
And you will be.
I won't cling to you anymore.
I'll focus on my work now.
I, Mi Joo, you, Seong Joon,
and...
I don't want to mention her, but Dong Hui is the same.
We all should pull ourselves together and work really hard.
That's the only way to survive.
Seong Joon,
you must make it succeed.
This is terrific!
How about you, Ji Hoon?
It's amazing. I'm so excited.
That's great.
Ji Hoon, why don't we come out every day like this?
That sounds good.
- Ah In, hurry up! - Okay.
This is so much fun.
What are you doing? I told you to study.
How can you be sleeping?
Mom, I'm really exhausted.
I hadn't eaten anything. I'm studying all day long.
The vacation is almost over.
You must improve something before the semester starts.
But I'm so hungry and burned out.
I'm too hungry to focus on studying.
It's tasty.
Ji Hoon,
how can riding a bike here be included in your bucket list?
Goodness. Is it good?
Yes, it's so delicious.
I can't believe that your second wish is eating cup noodles.
My former mom never let me eat junk food...
like cup noodles.
She is...
too uptight and inhumane.
Wait.
Ji Hoon?
Ji Hoon.
Hello.
Aren't you Chang Soo's mother?
Sorry?
Ji Hoon, where's your mom?
Well...
That is...
Where are you going?
Why do you pull my pants down?
Gosh.
I haven't seen Dong Hui for a while.
I'm going to go see her.
She's doing just fine. I went upstairs and saw her earlier.
She's really busy writing the scenario.
Please wait here.
You're not a kid.
Come back as soon as possible. I'm scared to be alone.
You're asleep.
(Award Certificate)
I'm so proud of you.
Hello?
How have you been?
I'm doing fine.
Where do you stay?
I live in my in-law's place.
I apologize for not being able to help you before.
Did anything happen since then?
No.
Nothing special happened.
Right,
Dong Hui...
has become a writer.
Really?
That's good news.
She couldn't even attend college.
But she achieved her dream. I'm really proud of her.
Please wait a little longer.
I think I can find...
where she is soon.
Okay.
I will wait.
I hope that matter settles as soon as possible.
Hello.
See you.
Seong Joon.
- What happened the other day... - Forget it.
You don't need to explain.
I don't think...
you are really a good person.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
What if Seong Joon falls in love with Dong Hui?
Director is such an insignificant position.
What did you say?
Everyone returned to work?
Are you saying it's the curse of the dead driver?
He's not stupid like his brothers.
He won't be easy to handle.
Don't act like a tragic heroine. That's nasty.
They love and take care of each other...
in front of me.
And I can't stand it anymore.