Hello.
Where are you going at this late hour?
I'm on my way to buy digestive medicines for my mom.
Seong Joon.
Tell me if you are struggling to find a job.
You know BNC Production, right?
Someone I'm close to works for that company.
How did you know I'm looking for a job?
Jeong Eun told me that you quit your job.
Does she know that?
I've never told anyone in my family about it.
Did I cross the line?
You did...
a lot.
Have I done anything wrong to you?
I think you've raised your guard too high against me.
What happened the other day is...
Forget it. You don't need to explain.
I don't think...
you are really a good person.
There's no good will or kindness for no reason.
That's what you think, right?
That's right.
However, aside from that,
you've never made yourself clear.
I don't know who you really are.
Then, see you.
Did you find any clue?
No, there's no progress yet.
Why is there no record about Seong Joon?
I've tracked down the hospital records with his birthday,
but strangely, I couldn't find his birth mother.
I think his real birthday...
and the officially registered birthday are different.
I suppose it's meaningless to find records with the birthday.
What about Han Hyung Seop?
It's no different.
As far as I know,
there's nobody he had an affair with.
Let's shift the focus from his birth mother...
to Seong Joon.
Find every single person...
who's had connections with him and his father since he was brought in.
I need you to investigate them.
Where's Mom?
I think she's having lunch with Ms. Oh.
They really have a good chemistry, don't they?
There's one thing good about Ms. Oh's move in.
Mother doesn't bother me anymore.
Goodness. You're too mean.
Let's be honest.
People find it weird if they know about us.
I take care of Mother and Ms. Oh.
They say it's even worse than the worst.
What? What did you say?
It's good since Mother isn't lonely any longer.
We can pay less attention to her, so it's good for everyone after all.
My goodness.
By the way,
is your vacation over?
- Sorry? - Stop it.
Can't you see he's eating?
What did I say? All I asked is if the vacation is over.
Yes, it's over.
Your company is very weird.
By the way,
are you really not going to marry...
the lady you brought before? Are you sure?
He said he won't marry her.
You've asked it so many times already.
It's because she's too good.
What do you mean?
His brothers...
married women from ordinary families.
It'd be great if he marries a woman from a wealthy family.
Mom, that is...
Seong Joon, change your mind and get back with her again.
I'm sure she didn't visit us...
for no reason.
- Honey. - Please stay out of this.
Guys also...
need other's help in their lives.
Look at your brothers.
They ended up back in their parents' house.
If they had rich wives,
they wouldn't be living in the same house,
fighting every day.
They're living like that...
because they had no luck in choosing their wives at all.
Seong Joon,
please do not...
make the same mistake your brothers made.
Please consider getting back with that lady again, okay?
Seong Joon,
life is short,
and love doesn't last forever.
You need someone who can give you a helping hand in dire times.
If your parents are poor, you need wealthy parents-in-law at least.
Stop it already.
Gosh, why are you yelling at me at this early hour?
You keep talking total nonsense.
You never know what will happen...
to him later. I'm just telling him to marry a rich girl...
unlike his brothers.
Is it that wrong?
I bet Hye Joo and Hee Sook will be happy to hear that.
I'm sure they will.
My goodness.
Are you on your way to work?
You're also going to work, right?
Yes, I am.
Moong Chi's brother is going to work.
I didn't have a chance to talk to you.
Congratulations on coming back to work.
I thank you, too.
I won't forget about the time you teased me being Moong Chi's brother.
We'll see.
I heard your grandma moved downstairs.
She did so that I can write.
Then you must have a workroom. I would like to see it.
You can see it later at night.
Why aren't you heading to work?
Hello, Mrs. Han.
Hello, Dong Hui.
I'm here to see Moong Chi.
Why are you here?
I'm here to get some fermented soybean paste.
Your grandmother comes downstairs to have lunch.
She wants to eat soybean paste soup with dried radish leaves.
Where's Ms. Oh's soybean paste? She told me I could take some before.
It's in the right barrel.
This is it.
My goodness.
Aren't you going to work, Seong Joon?
You should go as well, Dong Hui.
- I will. - I will.
No one lives like me.
Who takes care of two mothers and cook three meals at this age?
I take care of all the family members.
What?
That's not true.
Why would you say such a thing?
What do you mean the kids are switched? That's not true.
Ah In. Let's go.
Who is this? I don't know this number.
Hello?
Is this Ji Hoon's mother?
Ji Hoon's mother?
Yes, I am Ji Hoon's mother.
I am Kyung Jun's mother. He was an old friend of Ji Hoon.
They've been friends since first grade.
Is that right? Nice to meet you.
Why did you call me this morning?
I wanted to know which English workbook Ji Hoon's using.
English workbook?
By the way,
how did you know that I am Ji Hoon's mother?
Who told you such a thing? What do you mean they are switched?
Ji Hoon said so.
What?
Min Soo met Ji Hoon at Han River.
He told me Ji Hoon was with your brother-in-law's family.
Min Soo called and asked him,
and Ji Hoon said his mother was switched.
That brings me to my next question.
Since you are not Ji Hoon's mother,
can you tell us which academies Ji Hoon is attending?
Excuse me.
I don't know which workbook he's using.
We haven't even met once.
Don't you think it's over the line? Calling me in the morning like this?
That's right.
I am not interested in my children's education,
but I got a top student at his school for free.
I am so excited and happy.
Are you happy?
- Mother. - Call me again. I'll finish you.
Yes, I am ignorant and Ji Hoon's mother. What do you want?
Han Ji Hoon. You, brat.
How can you tell what happened?
Is that something you're proud of? Is it?
- You little brat. - Hey. What are you doing?
Move aside.
You told your friends that you were switched and I am not your mother.
Did you tell your friends? Are you trying to spread the news?
How can you do this...
without talking to us first?
Is it not true?
Min Soo asked me what happened.
He wondered how I ended up at Han River.
It's because I never go such places.
He kept asking for an answer. So I told him.
Everyone will find out eventually. The school will start soon.
You won't come to school, Mother?
No, I will. I will go to school.
You will come to school, too. Right, Aunt?
Did you just call me Aunt?
Yes. Everyone will find out, then.
Why are you doing this to me?
Ji Hoon.
Tell I'll be late because my child is sick.
Hee Sook, let me go to work.
I am an office worker.
I am a manager of Planning Department for a cosmetic company.
You are being inconsiderate.
Hye Joo. Do you want to go to work now?
- What will I do if I don't? - The school will start soon.
We have to resolve this problem first.
How can we resolve it again?
What do you want to do?
How are you going to tell Ji Hoon and Chang Soo are switched?
What do you mean? I will tell the truth.
Hye Joo.
My goodness.
Don't you think about the children?
They will be teased when other students find out about it.
Don't you think so?
- Then what? - We have to pretend it's not true.
At home, our hands are tied...
and everyone is living at their own home,
but it will be chaotic if this news gets out to school.
It's his last year of middle school. He will go to high school soon.
So what?
Shall I be Chang Soo's mom while you're Ji Hoon's mom at school?
- Yes. - When they come home,
I am Ji Hoon's mom and you're Chang Soo's mom?
- That's right. - Hey.
You don't like my Chang Soo that much, right?
Who said I don't like him?
First of all, they will be teased.
It'll be hard for you to be Ji Hoon's mom...
and for me to be Chang Soo's.
It will be chaotic at school, too.
So for now, I will be Ji Hoon's mom...
and you will be Chang Soo's mom.
- Hey. - You startled me.
What did you say?
Don't you think I can see what's in your mind?
You are embarrassed of Chang Soo.
You were showing off as a mother of a top student.
Now you are a mother of a student who gets the lowest score.
That's why you are embarrassed and humiliated. Isn't that right?
I can't say I am not embarrassed.
What?
Put yourself in my shoes.
Wouldn't you feel the same?
Children are a mirror of their parents.
Hey!
I am not going to work today. I am not going.
I am going to teach you a lesson today.
Hey.
Will you only keep a good son?
Will you raise him when he's good...
and throw him out when he's not good? What kind of a parent are you?
You are jumping to conclusions.
If this is how you are going to handle things,
give me back Chang Soo. I will raise both of them.
I'm glad you brought this up.
Send Ji Hoon back to me.
Ji Hoon will go to high school soon. If you raise him,
he won't be able to get into a specialized high school.
My goodness. You're still out of your mind.
You are busy anyway.
I will raise both Ji Hoon and Chang Soo.
Send Ji Hoon back to me. Let me be his mother...
until he graduates middle school...
and starts high school.
What did you say?
Hey.
What am I going to do with her? What should I do?
Kang Hee Sook!
When are you going to come to your senses?
I want to throw you out. I do.
I seriously want to kick you out. You, witch.
Take out what's inside. Take out everything.
- We will. - We will.
(Geumbit Academy)
Ma'am, this can cause a big accident.
- You really have to get it fixed. - You should bring your car, then.
All the other drivers bring their own cars.
But you're using my car...
and you have so many complaints.
If you want to fix it so badly, you should pay for it.
Dad.
Hyun Woo. You're here.
You guys.
Is something wrong?
No, it's fine. I will fix the car quickly...
and treat you jjajangmyeon. Can you wait?
- Okay. - Okay.
- Smell this. - Goodness.
- You are gross. - How does it taste?
Stop.
What's wrong with this?
Move!
It's coming down.
Please support it.
What's wrong?
Guem Ja's building is getting torn down today.
I know.
Why did Guem Ja do that to get arrested by police?
She should have paid the taxes well. Why would she try to evade taxes?
She's too old to go to prison.
Who doesn't break the law like her?
The problem is who reported her to the police.
What do you mean?
There are a lot of problems in this town.
Mi Ja has been running a grocery store for many years,
and she recently bankrupted and got kicked out.
Guem Ja and her husband are about to go to jail together.
Besides, their children got laid off and became unemployed.
Mi Ja's son even got private loans.
Oh, dear.
So even their children are suffering.
I think...
it's because of that incident.
In the past, Guem Ja's driver...
drunk-drove and got into a car accident at the intersection.
I told you not to talk about that time.
My children almost died that time.
Why do you keep bringing that up?
I don't want to talk about it either, but look.
Both Guem Ja and Mi Ja got totally ruined.
What does that have to do with that incident?
Both of them...
are the witnesses of that incident.
Are you saying it's the curse of the dead driver?
I heard he had a son.
Perhaps his son came back to take his revenge.
What a nonsense.
That's a complete nonsense. His father was the one...
who almost killed many kids by drunk-driving.
How can he dare to show up here?
He might think his father wasn't drunk-driving.
What on earth are you talking about?
There were clear proofs.
Mi Ja sold him liquor,
and Guem Ja smelled alcohol from him several times that day...
and stopped him from driving.
And you tested his blood.
You tested his blood for blood alcohol concentration.
I did.
You are funny.
Still, if your husband...
didn't ask for a further investigation,
it wouldn't have been such a big issue.
What?
Why would you bring up my husband there?
He did that. Don't you remember?
He deserves to receive a criminal penalty.
An animal like him must be put behind the bars.
You moron. How can you drive when you're drunk?
It's not true. I didn't drink. I am serious.
You're still lying!
Mr. Han, stop. Will you calm down?
My child is dying. How can I calm down?
subtitles ripped and syned by riri13
You're just as bad.
How can you hire a drunkard like him as a driver?
- Dad. - Saving money is good,
but how can you hire an alcoholic like him as a driver?
Do you want to get sued, too?
No, I...
Drunk-driving is like a murder case. You're a murderer.
Everyone else might forgive you, but I can't forgive you.
I am going to make sure to put you in jail.
What are you doing? Investigate him more thoroughly...
and put him in the jail!
Goodness.
Calm down.
Dad.
(Geumbit Academy)
Let it go.
Let's load it.
Support it there.
It's you.
Did you get everything from the inside?
- Yes. - Yes.
Is something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
I was thinking about something else.
What were you looking at?
The academy.
Goodness, all my children went to that academy.
It's too bad.
The head of the academy shouldn't have done something so foolish.
I know.
Did your uncle...
buy this building, too?
Yes.
I heard the academy was going to close.
So I came to calculate the renovation cost.
You said you've been staying with your uncle...
since your parents passed away, right?
Yes.
My parents passed away when I was in elementary school.
I see.
You were...
way too young for that.
Yes.
That's why I've never...
forgotten my dad's death.
Mom.
Be quiet and come here.
- Mom. - Hey.
This is pretty. Try it on.
Mom, I'm not going there.
- You have to go. - Why?
Or I will go to his place and ring the bell.
Mom. Hyun Woo's not like that.
Be quiet. If you've seen one, you've seen them all.
You two got busted while secretly being on a date,
and yet he made you go down and face me alone.
I told him I'd go alone.
Hyun Woo wanted to come down with me and explain everything...
to you. He even wanted to introduce himself.
But your daughter Han Jeong Eun stopped him.
Are you siding with him now?
Mom, I'm not siding with him.
Be quiet.
Even if you said that, he should have come to me and greeted me.
Why would you be so royal to a coward like him?
Mom.
Anyway, just do as I say.
Or I will arrange for the three of us to meet.
Here. Go put this on.
Hurry up.
- Where is the fitting room? - It's right here.
Goodness.
She's so helpless when it comes to men.
She has no idea how hard I try...
not to make her end up like me.
She's such an immature girl.
How do I look? Do I look good?
I can't give you to that guy.
Mom!
My ears! Why would you shout?
Yes.
What are you doing? Are you at the site?
No, I went out for a while, and now I'm resting at home.
What's up?
If it's okay with you,
can you pick me up...
after 30 minutes?
What?
Hello.
Hello, Jeong Eun.
Just like what Prof. Han said,
you are...
beautiful.
Yes.
I heard you recently came back...
from a long trip you took...
to feel the music and the culture of the world.
Gosh, you scared me.
Because you're a daughter of someone who enjoys arts,
your life is very unusual, too.
By the way,
do you have to laugh like that?
- Pardon me? - Your laughter is so special.
It's just that my voice is quite unique and special.
Shall we order first?
For an appetizer,
they have great beef carpaccio...
with fresh wild rocket...
and white truffle.
I think Italian vegetable soup...
with rich aroma of basil will be good.
Well, I'm not picky at all.
No, no.
Fine ladies like you must eat the finest food.
You can't just eat anything.
I want Italian vegetable soup...
and beef carpaccio...
for this beautiful lady.
I also want a bottle of wine.
Look who's here.
You should pay back the money you borrowed from me.
I am sorry. Please forgive me.
Do you think I don't like traveling around the world?
You borrowed money and traveled around the world.
It's about time to pay me back.
Do you think I cut you some slack...
so that you can enjoy a date with such homely guy?
Jeong Eun, who is he?
- Well... - You mean me?
I'm a moneylender.
Can't you see it?
If you have no money to pay back,
you should work for me.
Follow me.
Come now!
Wait...
I'm sorry. I'll do whatever you tell me to do.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
You were so good at it. Did you learn acting before?
"If you have no money, you should work for me."
Where did you learn such a lame line?
- Goodness. - Jeong Eun.
I have no idea what I've done.
You did exactly what I needed.
Now he thinks I have a lot of debt and won't get close to me ever.
You did just great as I told you.
- You're such a cute boy. - Gosh.
Let's eat ramyeon.
It's a bit sad I had nothing at that fancy restaurant though.
I'll make ramyeon.
This is how I work for you.
By the way,
who is that brat?
He's a professor of Seojung University. He's a baritone.
Your mother loves baritones, doesn't she?
She'll kill me if she finds this out.
She even bought me clothes for the blind date.
You can go back to him if you want.
That's not what I mean.
She doesn't like me going out with you.
Why not?
You're not her type.
You have fair skin.
You're tall and have long legs and fingers.
Isn't that a compliment?
Of course.
But my mom hates guys like you.
Then, what kind of guys does she like?
Guys like that baritone.
- Sorry? - She likes short guys...
with a short neck, curly hair, projecting teeth, and a sweet voice.
That's peculiar.
Still,
do you have to meet the guy she likes?
She's trying to live vicariously through me.
What do you mean?
Never mind.
And she strongly believes that I should get married...
before Seong Joon does.
She hates to lag behind others.
And if Seong Joon gets married,
I'll be the only one in our family who's not married.
Seong Joon seems like a stubborn guy.
Gosh, no way.
Seong Joon isn't that kind of guy.
He's so nice and has a warm heart.
Literally, he's a gentleman.
It's nothing.
Don't mind me and keep reading.
I wish I had a son like you.
I see.
Great.
Guys, don't you think you're too mean?
Dong Hui is staring at you.
Why don't you just let her read Writer Jo's scenario?
She's a temporary worker.
Dong Hui, please prepare for a meeting with...
the Planning Department. It will be about new products.
Sorry? For new products?
Is spring coming already?
Yes, spring is coming.
- Don't just stand there. Move on. - Okay.
Dong Hui, I need a cup of tea.
Sure, Director Bang!
What's with you? Did something happen to you?
No, nothing happened.
I'll go make some tea for you now.
Does anyone know what's the matter with Dong Hui?
So what do you think?
Well, the producer wants the romantic relationship,
so we can't just get rid of it.
Director Bang,
these two don't love each other in my head.
How on earth can they have a romantic relationship?
Then, I'll talk to the producer about it.
However, I think their love story...
will attract more viewers from different age brackets.
I also believe that you're capable of adding it naturally to the plot.
Regarding it, I agree with Writer Jo.
I think you should talk to the producer face to face.
Do you think so?
The meeting was very fruitful.
We've made a lot of progress.
Director Han, we should go for some drinks with Writer Jo.
I'll go pull out the car.
I and Director Bang will visit the president and be right there.
Excuse me.
I'm a huge fan of yours.
Can I have your autograph, please?
Sure. What's your name again?
I am Oh Dong Hui.
Are you an aspiring writer?
I am. My work was selected as a runner-up in the recent contest.
I see.
I really enjoyed watching "Sons of Pharmacist Kim".
It was a great work.
I also think...
I wrote a great masterpiece.
I'm sorry.
I'm struggling with the scenario I'm working on,
so I'm about to lose my mind because I'm so stressed out.
Many writers suffer...
from sever mood swings like me.
So you should never be a writer like me.
You must be a writer who's way better than me.
I will. Thank you so much.
- Hello, Ma'am. Are you going out? - Yes.
- Excuse me. - Yes?
What's wrong, ma'am?
Nothing.
Please make sure the floor is dry.
It gets frozen easily since the weather is cold.
Okay. I will.
Don't worry about it, ma'am. Goodbye.
Okay.
Where are you now?
I'm about to go home.
When are you coming home? You are coming home early, right?
I have a company dinner tonight. I might be late.
Why do you have so many company dinners? Just come home.
I can't do that.
This is an important dinner.
Dong Hui. Let's go. Everyone's waiting.
Yes, Writer Jo.
Grandma, I will try my best to come home as early as possible.
Let's get going, Writer Jo.
Dong Hui. Dong Hui!
Let's shake and dance!!
I have to dance.
- This is great. - Make some noise. Scream.
Are you okay, Director?
Are you drunk?
Hey, Oh Dong Hui.
Do you think you're the only one who has a hard life?
My life is also hard.
Don't act like a tragic heroine. That's nasty.
That's nasty.
Welcome.
- Reporter Han. - Look who's here.
- Have you been well? - Yes, of course.
Long time no see.
What a nice place.
Thank you.
- Here you go. - Sit down.
This is for you.
Anyway, congratulations on starting a business.
Thank you.
What?
Everyone got reinstated?
Yes.
When the new owner took over,
whoever wanted to get reinstated got their jobs back including...
employees on the waitlist and who voluntarily resigned.
Then...
why wasn't I reinstated?
I heard that you already had a job at that time.
Where did you work?
Woori Daily News?
No, I didn't.
But...
who is the new owner?
I don't know much about him.
He doesn't come to the company. His proxy comes often.
Is that so?
Mr. Han.
Mr. Lee.
Wait.
- You're here to pick up the food. - Yes.
- Sun Mi. - Yes?
- Here you go. - Thank you.
I'm always grateful for your help.
Don't mention it.
The workers at the construction site...
always praise your fried chicken.
- Goodbye, then. - Goodbye.
- Take care. - Goodbye.
So I have a question.
When you were working at the company,
you were investigating about corruption...
between Senior Secretary and Seonghan Group, right?
- Yes. - Do you have the materials?
I still have the files on my computer. Why?
Can you give me the files?
I got reinstated.
I should make a mark in order...
for me to strengthen my position.
Reporter Han. Please let me have the files.
This is expedient,
but if you liquidate your existing company,
you may be able to avoid charges against the company.
Is that so?
I see. I didn't know I had an option.
The president of Seonghan Group will certainly like this.
How about the compensation for the victims?
You will compensate them, right?
That's up to the president.
All you need to do is to inform us about the loopholes.
Okay.
I will...
nominate you in the upcoming election.
Pardon?
Are you serious?
How can you live with only a lawyer office?
Men must think of the big picture.
So all you need to do is do what I ask you to do.
Yes, I will.
I will be loyal to you...
with everything I have.
I like your office,
but I keep smelling food.
It smells like friend chicken, doesn't it?
Take care.
Okay. Reporter Han. Take care.
Don't forget what I asked you, please.
Take care.
I will visit you soon.
Okay. Take care.
Thank you. I will.
Goodbye.
My gosh.
What are you doing?
Goodness.
Why are you saying goodbye so slavishly?
I can't live because of you.
- What? - Do you want to...
fry chickens when your brother is having the most important moment?
What would I do if I don't fry chickens?
Don't go overboard with it.
I'm trying to make a living just as much as you are.
Why are you talking to me like this?
Look. I am going to do something big.
Then I am going to get rid of your fried chicken restaurant.
No, I will buy the whole building.
I'm going to kick you out. Did you get that?
What?
How dare you talk to your brother like that?
I'm going to tell Mom on you. I'm telling Mom.
Okay. Do that. Tell Mom on me.
Tell on me. Tell her.
- You, little brat. - Seong Hoon, let me go.
- What do you mean? - Why don't we...
- I'm going to rip off your ears. - You're going to hurt my ears.
Are you not going upstairs to check on your granddaughter tonight?
She will come home late since she has a company dinner tonight.
- Is that so? - Yes.
That means Seong Joon will be late as well.
I guess so.
Good for them.
What do you mean?
They live in the same house and work in the same company.
They go to work together and come home together.
They won't be bored. How nice.
Isn't it?
Ms. Hwang.
Why are you so bored?
Is being bored your talking point these days?
What?
If you are bored,
why don't you accompany when I go to clean the staircase?
I'm saying this...
because I am jealous of...
Seong Joon and Dong Hui.
In addition, she now has a workroom.
They will be chatting away in that workroom.
That must be a lot of fun.
You go out early in the morning and come home late at night.
Then go and ask them to let you join them.
When I was young, I lived in the countryside.
On the way home from school,
there was a house that raised a big dog.
It was so scary to pass by that house.
As soon as I stepped out of school, I started to worry about it,
but I still had to pass by that house.
At that moment,
a boy from my class was standing there.
- So? - So I asked him...
to take me with him.
Every day since then,
that boy...
stood there at that time.
What's your point?
We walked back together for about six months.
After the six months, he confessed his feelings.
He said he intentionally stood there at that hour...
because he had a crush on me.
Goodness, it turned out that his home was on the opposite side.
But he did that just for me.
My goodness.
What if Seong Joon falls for Dong Hui?
What?
We can't predict young kids these days.
That shouldn't happen. My daughter-in-law will be mad.
She will go crazy.
She thoroughly planned to marry him off...
that millionaire girl who visited us the other time.
Hey! Stop talking nonsense.
Why would you yell? You really surprised me.
What's wrong with my Dong Hui?
When you get to know my Dong Hui,
you will see that she doesn't lack anything.
He's just a director anyway.
What did you say? "Just a director"?
It's smaller and cozier than I thought. It's nice.
Is this Hyung Seop's work?
Yes. He worked hard on it.
Now you just have to write well. Right?
Yes, just like Writer Jo.
Right. You have to be like her, too.
Well,
anyway, you have to write well,
stay healthy, and be happy.
Yes, I should.
By the way, I saw...
a totally different side of Director Bang.
She was singing and playing tambourine.
I've never seen her trying so hard to please someone.
I thought she doesn't know how to do that.
That's Director Bang's strength. We should learn that from her.
- What? - She doesn't...
always stay arrogant and stuck-up like other rich girls.
She's a professional when she works.
That's Director Bang's big strength.
Yes.
It's freezing. Why did soy sauce have to run out at night?
I need it to marinate meat.
Dong Hui.
- Goodnight. - Bye.
Write a lot, too.
Okay.
Seong Joon.
Why are you coming out from there? You should've come home.
Mom.
I dropped by because Dong Hui got a studio.
- Yes. - Still, how can you visit...
a lady's room at this hour?
I came here before to check her writing.
Stop it. It's so embarrassing.
Even though you are in-laws who live in the same house,
you shouldn't enter a young lady's room in the middle of night.
You're just as bad. You should have asked him to come during the day.
You work in the same office. Why didn't you ask him at the office?
Why would you call him to your room? I think this is wrong.
I am sorry. I will be more careful next time.
Rumors travel fast in this town. Please be more careful.
- Okay. - Come on down, Seong Joon.
Okay.
Good night.
What? So what did you say?
What do you think? I said I am going to teach her a lesson.
Goodness. She's not wrong though.
- What do you mean she's not wrong? - Hey.
Put on some more.
Frying chicken is not easy.
Did you think it was going to be easy?
Like what she said, the kids might get bullied.
This is something that only happens in dramas. It's a mess.
I agree with you on that.
Like what Hee Sook said, you should be Chang Soo's mom for now.
Tell Hee Sook to continue being Ji Hoon's mom.
- Honey. - We just have to do well at home.
It doesn't matter.
And send the kids to different high schools.
Then you can be Ji Hoon's mom again.
That's better.
Do you think so?
What did you just say? Where did you say you're going?
To a church.
Are you out of your mind?
Your school resumes soon. You should study a little more...
and think about getting better grades next year.
Why on earth do you want to go there?
I made a promise a long time ago.
We're going to have a charity concert at the church.
- No. - Mom.
I said no.
You are the unfortunate person, and I should be comforted.
That's going to be counted as extra credit on the third grade.
What?
Goodness.
He always thinks about a way to avoid studying.
Yes. Hey.
I was wondering if you're coming to the moms' get-together.
I told you I can't go. I'm not feeling well.
I can't join today.
And starting this year, I won't be the leader. Choose another one.
You should at least come today.
You have to settle the fees from last year and hand it over.
What?
Are you crazy? Why would you get an exorcism?
What's wrong with you?
Don't do that.
Try to relax.
Hello? Hello?
Mal Ja. Mal Ja.
What's wrong?
- It's Mal Ja. - What's wrong with her?
I'm glad you came. Have a seat.
Mal Ja is causing me much trouble.
Because of what happened to Mi Ja's store...
and Guem Ja's academy,
she thinks the spirit of the driver who died 20 years ago...
after the drunk-driving incident cursed our town.
She's on the way to meet an exorcist.
What?
I've never heard that kind of hideous story.
We didn't push him to die.
We didn't.
And it's not such a pleasant memory to bring up.
Many things happen in life.
Why would she associate everything with that?
I should stop being friends with Mal Ja.
She lost her mind when she got old.
(Yerang Church)
I will follow him.
Follow him where ever.
He may go.
And near him
I always will be.
For nothing can keep me away.
He is my destiny
I love him, I love him, I love him.
And where he goes I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow
I will follow him.
Follow him where ever he may go.
There isn't an ocean too deep.
A mountain so high it can keep.
- Keep me away - Together, together.
- I will follow him - Follow him.
Follow him where ever he may go.
- There isn't an ocean too deep - Too deep.
- A mountain so high it can keep - A mountain so high it can keep.
- Keep us away - Keep us away.
- Away from his love - Away from his love.
- Oh yes, I love him - I'll follow.
- I'm going to follow - True love.
- He'll always be my true love - Forever.
From now until forever.
- I love him, I love him - Yes, I love him.
And where he goes I'll follow, I'll follow, I'll follow.
- My love - He'll always be my true love.
From now until forever, forever, forever.
- There isn't an ocean too deep - No ocean.
A mountain so high it can keep.
- Nothing can keep me away - Keep me away.
- Away from his - Away from his.
- Love - Love.
You promised to feed Chang Soo fried chicken as I'm joining you.
Make sure Ji Hoon completes his English workbook within this week.
- You still haven't changed. - Let's go.
- Hello. - Hello. You're here.
It's good to see you.
Our children are now in their third grade.
No matter what kind of high school they may want to go,
we, mothers, should put our heads together...
and work out a strategy to help them get into...
the school they want to go.
The admission process of specialized high schools...
is expected to remain the same this year.
However, we must not get manipulated by the schools' announcements...
or the instigation of the press...
that the level of difficulty will remain unchanged.
Now, we have to come up with an original...
learning strategy that will be shared only with...
us and our children.
We should be fully prepare our children,
so that they can get the best score...
under any circumstances.
Speaking of which,
I invited Mr. Kim Tae Pyung,
a teacher at a famous academy in Gangnam...
to join us next week.
- Really? - That's wonderful.
That's really great.
Thank you.
Look, Chang Soo's mom.
- Yes? - Yes?
Why did you answer me at the same time?
We actually live in the same house.
We sometimes get confused.
- Is that so, Ji Hoon's mom? - That's right.
What are you two doing? Just explain about the rumor.
There is no rumor.
The kids were just joking around. It's hardly a rumor.
My son, Chang Soo is very insensible.
Ji Hoon is under a lot of stress because of studying.
I knew she was not just any ordinary woman...
when I first saw her.
- Me? Why? - Gosh.
I heard you were a manager of a department at a big makeup brand.
Also, you graduated from Seoul National University, right?
- Oh, my. Seoul National University? - Seoul National University?
I think there has been a misunderstanding.
Chang Soo really is my son.
No wonder Ji Hoon is so smart.
- What? - I knew it.
We thought it was strange, too.
It didn't make sense that a son of...
a Seoul National University graduate got the worst grades.
It's unnatural.
- Look. - Kids get as smart as their mom.
They get the grades their mom got,
and go to the university their mom went to.
People who graduated from a bad university...
only write the name of their graduate school on the paper.
I guess they think it can cover the university they went to.
- Look. - Someone here turned out to be...
a local university graduate,
but she could put on airs thanks to her fake son.
Hey! Don't you think you're going too far?
Please stay seated, Hye Joo.
- She's right. - Please sit.
What do you think you're doing?
You're being too harsh!
- You're such shameless women. - Hye Joo.
Stop.
That's right!
Han Chang Soo, the one who...
gets the worst grades is my son.
I'm Chang Soo's mother. What are you going to do?
(Lee Jae Cheol)
How have you been?
I just came by to see you.
Dad.
You're here, you brat.
Why did you drink so much, Dad?
You should stop drinking.
Put it back.
Why can't I drink as much as I like? You brat.
Dad.
My goodness.
- Hey. - That hurts.
You're my son, you brat.
Since you're here, do you want to have a drink?
I'm fine.
Have a drink.
My gosh, Dad.
- Have a drink. - All right.
- Is this your glass or mine? - That's yours.
- Is this mine? - It is.
Dad. Be careful.
I'm all right.
I'm all right!
You shouldn't have drunk so much.
You punk. I'm going to kill you today.
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Saying sorry won't cut it, you jerk!
I'm sorry. Forgive me.
- Get up, you punk. - He deserved it.
I didn't do it on purpose. Please believe me.
- No one will believe you! - You deserve this!
- He needs a good beating! - What a jerk!
- I'm sorry, Seong Joon. - What?
- Seong Joon. - Okay.
I must be heavy. Put me down.
I'm fine.
Dad. I'm carrying you on my back, and...
You're asleep.
I'm too tired.
Let's stop.
Sir.
I can't take my revenge...
this way anymore.
They look after each other, care for each other...
and enjoy themselves.
I can't watch it anymore.
Let's just destroy Seong Hoon and Seong Sik,
break down their house,
and go back to the States.
I cannot...
contain my anger any longer.
Sir.
Before we do, there is something you should know.
What now?
Han Seong Joon, the youngest son of Han Hyung Seop...
isn't a child Hyung Seop had with another woman.
He brought Seong Joon from an orphanage.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Chang Soo. Let's just stop making our lives so hard.
They're better off without you as their father, you jerk.
Excuse me, Ma'am. Don't you recognize me?
No matter what you say, I will make sure Seong Joon...
marries a decent lady.
I'm saying he is very talented to be an opera singer.
Excuse me? What did you say?
Did you say Golden Street is still in business?
That's not possible.