BioskopKeren
Be careful.
Watch out.
What's wrong with my mother?
It's a long story.
Look at you, calling her your mother.
Do you know what I did...
so that I can feed you a fried chicken?
Forget it. Bring me a glass of cold water.
Okay.
Hey. Sit down.
Hey, Hee Sook.
Why are you so disheartened? Don't let them bother you.
Don't.
You shouldn't care about...
what they said about you.
If you care, it's your loss, not theirs. Okay?
Hee Sook.
Kang Hee Sook. Wake up. Come on, Hee Sook.
Kids get as smart as their moms.
Someone here turned out to be...
a local university graduate,
but she could put on airs thanks to her fake son.
That's right! Han Chang Soo, the one who gets the worse grades...
is my son.
I'm Chang Soo's mother. What are you going to do?
It's late.
Why isn't he home?
Is he still on his hike?
- Seong Joon. - Yes?
Seong Joon.
Yes?
I must be heavy. Put me down.
I'm fine.
Dad, I'm carrying you on my back, and...
You're asleep.
Sir! Please.
Please forgive me this one time.
I have two young children.
- I can't go to jail like this. - My goodness.
They will starve to death.
Hey, you let someone else's child die.
And you're worrying about your own children?
They are better off without you.
What a scum.
Father.
Go home.
Go home. Until the result comes out,
wait at home and think about what you did.
You are an alcoholic scum.
Sir. Sir.
Sir.
Father.
I'm fine.
Let's go home, Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo.
You can take a good care of Sang Woo, right?
Yes, I can.
Okay.
Don't leave him behind next time.
Understood?
Yes.
Don't look. Close your eyes, Sang Woo.
Hyun Woo, what's wrong with Dad?
I can't see anything.
No, you can't. You can't look at him now.
Don't look at him, Sang Woo.
- Sir. - Let go of me. Let go.
What's wrong with you?
It's over. Everything's over now.
I won't let it stand.
I'm going to destroy everything. Let go of me.
Sir. Sir!
Hyun Woo, I am here.
- Sir. - Let go!
Hyun Woo!
What's going on?
Hyun Woo.
Jeong Eun.
Hyun Woo. Hyun Woo!
- Hyun Woo. - Jeong Eun's here.
What's wrong with him?
Why is he so upset?
Jeong Eun's here. Calm down. Calm down!
Your foot is...
bleeding.
Jeong Eun.
Will you go to the pharmacy?
Yes, I will.
Please, sir.
Get a hold of yourself.
Jeong Eun saw what happened.
What are you going to do?
I'm too tired.
Let's stop.
Sir.
I can't take my revenge...
this way.
They look after each other, care for each other,
and enjoy themselves.
I can't watch it anymore.
Let's just destroy Seong Hoon and Seong Sik,
break down their house,
and go back to the States.
I cannot...
contain my anger any longer.
Why aren't you talking?
I said we will destroy them and return to the States.
They killed my father.
I can't watch them living a happy life.
Sir, you came up...
with this plan first.
I wanted an elaborate and brutal plan.
I wanted to destroy them one by one.
That's why...
I gave you clues.
Just like Gatsby who moved into a house across his lover's house,
I helped you move into the house across Hyung Seop's house.
That's driving me crazy.
I have to witness how happily they are living,
while I am all alone.
My father's death...
and my brother's disappearance.
I'm about to go crazy with the nightmares...
I have every night.
How can they be so happy?
The harder I drive them to the corner,
the more they love and support each other.
You should swallow your anger.
I can't.
I want to kill them right now.
Sir.
Before that, there is something you should know.
What now?
Han Seong Joon, the youngest son of Han Hyung Seop...
isn't a child Hyung Seop had with another woman.
He brought Seong Joon from an orphanage.
I heard it today.
What?
What I find weird is the fact...
that they adopted him.
They adopted him when Sang Woo had gone missing.
What do you mean by that?
I don't want to believe it,
but we should consider every possibility.
I found out where the orphanage is.
I'll visit there tomorrow morning.
Jeong Eun will visit you with a medicine and a bandage.
She'll treat you.
Please be nice to her like her real boyfriend.
We're almost there.
Please be patient a little longer.
I'll be leaving.
I will not ask you anything.
I won't ask why you did something you'd never done before...
or if you have more secrets you're hiding from me.
I'll ask nothing.
Still,
I want you to tell me about it later.
I want to know...
how your father encountered the wrongful death,
how you'd lost your brother,
and what happened to you tonight.
Tell me about these later.
It's done.
Do you want me to stay with you?
No. You can leave.
I want to be alone.
Okay. I'll go, then.
Honey.
Are you okay?
What happened?
Why did you drink so much?
Did something happen to you?
I'm so worried.
Are you going to work?
Yes. How is Dad?
Spare me some time.
We need to talk.
Follow me.
Why did...
your dad drink so hard yesterday?
- Do you know why? - I don't.
He called me, so I went to pick him up.
I really have no clue at all.
He hadn't drunk like that for the last 10 years.
He got dead drunk when he voluntarily retired from work.
Since then, he'd never drunk so heavily like yesterday.
And he even kept screaming all night long...
and apologizing to someone.
Last night was an utter nightmare.
Really?
Does anything come to your mind?
So I slept on it.
Nothing special happened to our family these days.
Seong Hoon and Seong Sik opened a restaurant and an office...
respectively.
And Ji Hoon and Chang Soo...
got used to their new lives.
There's nothing...
your dad would be worried about.
If there is,
it should be you.
- Me... Me? - Yes.
I think it's about your marriage.
I asked you to get back...
with that rich lady the other day, and your dad yelled at me.
He told me to just let you handle it on your own.
Right.
Maybe,
he thinks...
he should find your birth mother before you get married.
- Mom. - Seong Joon.
I don't mean to hurt your feeling.
But we all know the truth,
so let's make it clear this time.
Have you ever...
tried to find your birth mother?
I haven't.
Why not?
It's you who has raised me so far.
So,
I have no plan to find anyone else other than you.
That's what I think and I won't change my mind.
Okay. I am sorry.
I guess it was a meaningless question.
But...
as your brothers moved back in,
and you've reached a marriageable age.
I'm confused with all the complicated thoughts.
This time, your father came home heavily drunk.
So...
I feel heavy with unnecessary worries.
I'm sorry.
You'd better leave now.
- Really? - Yes.
They are such evil women.
Why do they talk about which college others went to?
That's what I'm saying.
Moms who love their kids too much are so problematic.
That's why people point fingers at them,
calling them selfish moms.
You're totally right.
Mothers must change in order to make the better world.
Think about it. The ones who give the greatest affection...
to their children are parents.
Don't you think so?
But fathers go to work and come home late at night.
Then, who would the kids spend the most time with?
Of course, it's their mothers.
Exactly. But those mothers...
are so emulous and selfish.
They pay too much attention to their kids...
and even tell them to become the best...
and even to trample others to succeed in life.
Imagine what kind of people they'll grow into.
Our future will be so gloomy.
You've learned a great lesson...
from other mothers of the moms' get-together.
- Honey. - Yes?
- I'm in trouble. - Why?
- I'm the president. - What?
I'm the president of the moms' get-together.
Why did you say yes?
You just criticized them harshly.
I don't know. I had no choice because Ji Hoon is the top student.
What should I do?
Goodness.
Don't let it get you down.
Just let them make fun of us and speak ill of us.
They'll forget about it in a few days.
We're doomed.
What do you mean?
We should move...
- to other town. - Stop such nonsense!
Where would we move?
I don't care if it's Gangbuk,
Gangdong, or Gangseo.
Let's just leave Gangnam.
I can't...
go back to that school.
No!
I have things to do here in Gangnam.
What do you have to do?
Are you going to get into Seoul National University or what?
Are the schools all you can think of?
What is Gangnam famous for?
It is the heart of politics.
It's the center of new trends.
What do you mean?
I am...
going to get into politics.
I'm going to be nominated for...
the Seocho district special election.
- That's nonsense. - It makes sense.
Who will support you?
There is someone who is willing to support me.
So stop obsessing over your child...
and pay more attention to your husband.
I can't make you the mother of a valedictorian,
but who knows? Maybe in 10 years,
I will make you the first lady.
Stop the nonsense. Who's going to vote for you?
Why wouldn't they vote for me?
I'm a lawyer, and I have experience in broadcasting.
I'm the perfect candidate.
Do you think they won't dig your private life?
They will find out that our child was switched...
and also that he ranks number 359 in his class.
Who would vote for you?
You are unbelievable.
Why are you so obsessed with your child?
If you are so worried about Chang Soo,
you can find his other talent.
What talent does he have?
What talent do you think he has?
I don't know.
What if he doesn't have a talent?
Make him play Korean wrestling.
Then he would at least have a nice body.
He can be a Korean champion wrestler.
Goodness.
What?
The color looks amazing.
Thank you, Dong Hui.
- And congratulations. - Thank you.
So we're getting this because...
your script got chosen.
- Yes. - Let's clap for her.
- Thank you. - Let's try this drink first.
I am going to eat the rice cake, too.
Maybe, he thinks...
he should find your birth mother before you get married.
Have you ever...
tried to find your birth mother?
- Director Han. - Rice cake.
Eat some rice cake.
I'm okay. Enjoy.
Dong Hui...
bought it because her script got chosen.
What are you doing right now?
Dong Hui brought us these homemade omija drink...
to celebrate her win on a drama script contest.
It's very delicious.
This is for you.
It's slightly more than ours.
- Did anyone talk to Writer Jo? - I talked to her.
She said she doesn't want to be bothered because she's working.
But she was supposed to pass us some documents.
Did she say anything else?
No, she didn't.
Is that right? Okay.
Ventilate the room after you're done eating.
You shouldn't eat in the office.
By the way, where did Director Han go?
Didn't you meet him? He just left.
Is that right?
- Okay. - Director Bang.
Please take the drink. She brought it for you.
Okay. I will take it.
But please don't ruin the atmosphere...
to celebrate something personal.
She's so mean.
Why can't she just take the gift?
Dong Hui.
This omija drink tastes great.
Does your grandmother make things like...
soy sauce, doenjang, gochujang, too?
I mean, with her own recipe. Does she make?
Yes. She used to run a grocery store,
so she makes everything.
Is that right?
Can you bring me some?
My wife always feeds me store-bought doenjang.
I miss the taste of homemade doenjang.
Okay. I will get you some.
(Orphanage)
I clearly remember him.
Because of some traumatic experience,
he couldn't even remember his age and name.
When the police brought him over,
his voice was hoarse from crying so much.
How soon did he get adopted?
He was adopted within a month.
As soon as he came,
he chose that boy and signed him for adoption.
It was as if he was taking a boy he used to know.
Which police station was he sent from?
It says he was sent from Seocho Police Station.
Is that where you lost the boy?
Yes, Sir.
He was sent here from Seocho Police Station.
I need to find the person who first found him.
- Please look for him. - Okay.
What's wrong?
Is something wrong?
Is this a woman problem?
No.
Then what is it?
The woman problem is the only problem that should...
make you look that grim at your age.
Jeong Eun.
Yes?
Do you remember...
when I first came to the house?
What?
When what?
I asked if you remember...
the first time I came to our house.
Seong Joon.
Why are you asking that all of a sudden?
It's just...
I thought you might remember something.
I don't remember anything special about that time.
One day, Uncle Hyung Seop brought you on his back...
and said that you were his son.
Grandma and aunt collapsed,
and the house was a mess.
I remember that, too.
- Seong Joon. - But...
I don't remember...
anything else.
I remember a few scenes,
but I don't know if they are real.
I feel frustrated.
What's wrong with you? You've been doing so well.
Is something really wrong?
Hyun Woo.
How's your feet? Are you okay?
Yes.
Give me some coffee.
I will. Please wait...
Hello.
Can I sit with you and drink some coffee?
Did you...
return to the company?
Yes.
I could have introduced you to...
a better job.
- Hey. - You don't like me.
Didn't I tell you before?
Don't hate me too much.
You never know what will happen in life.
Hey, Ji Yeon.
Is that so?
Hyun Woo.
Ji Yeon said she's doing well at her work.
She asked if she could come and see you at night.
Tell her she can.
Okay. He said you can come.
My goodness.
You saw her in front of the motel. Her name is Park Ji Yeon.
She grew up in the orphanage, Home of Angels.
When the children in the orphanage turn 19 years old,
they have to leave the orphanage...
with 500 dollars from the local government.
With that money, they can't even rent a room.
That's how most of them end up working in bars and clubs.
They are again bound to face misfortunes.
Misfortunes will repeat.
Eventually,
misfortunes will be passed down.
I apologize if I misunderstood you...
and this is a heartbreaking story.
However,
what's your purpose of telling me?
I just wanted to.
I just wanted...
you to know how I felt.
What's wrong with you two?
Nothing.
Jeong Eun, I will get going now.
Seong Joon.
Hyun Woo.
What's going on? What were you two talking about so seriously?
It's nothing.
I'll come back later.
Hyun Woo.
Let's talk later.
Hyun Woo!
Hey. Jeong Eun.
If you have something to talk about, talk to me tomorrow.
I even closed early because I'm tired.
What did you do to Professor Park you met the other day?
I told you that I didn't want to go on a blind date.
Do you know how talented and smart he is? He comes from a good family.
Of course not, but...
Your status has been falling since you're dating someone like him.
If you date someone who works at the construction site,
- you will have a hard life, too. - Mom.
You didn't like him because of his occupation?
Yes. That played a part.
It didn't play a part. It's solely because of it.
- What? - You lived like a princess...
all your life.
You only played the piano and didn't do anything else.
You lived in that world of classical music for all your life.
What did you say?
Do you think I introduced him because he plays classical music?
- His personality is... - Don't lie.
You just...
wanted to introduce someone who resembles Dad.
What?
It doesn't matter if you deny it.
You can't let go of him all your life.
On the outside, you pretend you hate, despise, and are mad at him.
But you've been in his shadow all your life, Mom.
That's why you introduced that baritone singer.
What a terrible wench.
You shouldn't say somethings to your mother even if I am your mother.
You know what kind of life I had.
How could you say such things?
I'm so bored.
Why isn't she home? When will she come home?
Hold on.
Seriously.
You're not a kid. Why are you acting up?
Anyway, I am hanging up.
I will be home. I will try to finish work as soon as possible.
What a baby.
- Excuse me, Ma'am. - Yes?
Don't you recognize me?
Well, I am not sure.
How could...
an old grandma like me know a rich lady like you?
By any chance,
didn't you work as a cook at Hwashin Company's President's house?
Aren't I right?
My goodness. Ms. Oh.
How can you quit so suddenly?
I'm sorry. I've got a situation.
- I'm sorry. - Ms. Oh. Ms. Oh!
My goodness. Ms. Oh. Are you okay?
Stay still.
I have to put the ointment so that it doesn't leave a scar.
When we go out...
with the bruise like this, people think that we will die soon.
What do you mean?
Both of our husbands are dead.
The bruise couldn't have come from them or a fight.
They will think it happened because...
you are old and your legs gave way.
That's why they will think you might die soon.
The age spots don't come from anywhere.
They come from bruise like this.
I told you to come home early and hang out with me. Listen to me.
Don't move. Stay still.
Mom.
What's going on?
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
I can't live because of Jeong Eun. She's breaking my heart.
Ae Ri.
Mom. She deeply...
hurt my feelings. She said hurtful words to break my heart.
Mom, I am so disappointed.
What? I'm going to talk to her.
How dare she hurt my daughter?
Ae Ri, don't cry. If you cry, then I'll be sad, too.
Mom.
Ae Ri. Calm down.
Let's calm down.
- You're home. - Hello.
By the way, this is for you.
An employee gave me this. You can have it.
Thank you.
What are you doing?
I was looking at pictures of Grandmother.
- Why? It's so out of the blue. - It's not.
I always have her pictures in my room like this.
You told me to be responsible and do my duties as an owner.
That's why I was looking at the pictures.
She built the company all on her own as a woman.
With her energy, I want to be evaluated as a capable director...
this year although I won't be as capable as she was.
- Why? - It's nothing.
I was just wondering how you were getting along with Director Han.
We are fine.
We agreed to focus on work and not to pressure each other.
That's what you should have done.
Don't worry.
Okay. I won't worry about it.
I'm so disappointed.
I can't live because of Ae Ri and Jeong Eun.
Sometimes, Ae Ri comes and bothers me.
Sometimes, Jeong Eun comes and bother me.
Now they have an argument and come to me.
They start crying in front of me. That really bothers me.
My goodness.
There are worse things than that.
What do you mean there are worse things?
Children are so bothersome.
You should never live so close to your kids.
No matter how angry I am at them, I can't help crying when they cry.
I feel sadder when they are sad.
For me, my daughter is...
much more important than Jeong Eun.
She knows how her mother suffered after she was born.
I won't let it slide this time.
Please calm down.
Just leave her the way she is.
Your children have grown up so well.
You should appreciate it.
Why do you keep talking things unrealistic...
like a saint?
You may not know, but there are...
much more terrible things happening in the world.
Sorry?
Things we have never imagined are taking place these days.
Children...
threaten and drive their parents out.
They even neglect and abandon their parents easily.
That's what's happening these days.
Dong Hui.
Yes?
Director Han's cell phone is off.
I see.
I have something to tell him urgently,
but I couldn't meet him today.
Can you put him on for me?
Sorry?
Now?
Please hold on a second.
Come in.
Please take it. It's from Director Bang.
She called me because your phone is off.
Hello? What is it?
This is unbelievable.
Please don't turn your phone off, Director Han.
Officials like us are destined to keep working...
even after we get home.
Okay.
I'm going to have dinner with Director Seong Min Soo.
I'll brief on the result tomorrow.
Okay.
Then, see you tomorrow.
Ms. Bang, have a good evening.
I'm sorry, Dong Hui.
I turned my phone off.
It's okay.
By the way, did something happen to you?
What makes you think so?
You didn't look happy at the office all day.
Nothing happened.
Right.
How is "Romance Learned through Books" going?
Didn't you say you're working on the 5th and 6th episode?
- It's almost done. - Then, you should let me read.
- Do you want to read it? - Sure.
I'll read and revise it for you.
But if the scenario makes a hit,
the half of the copyright belongs to me.
Hello.
Ms. Moon.
See you later.
This way, please.
Okay.
Mr. Han.
Come here.
Okay.
It's good to see you.
Sir,
how are you?
This is Lawyer Han Seong Sik. I plan to recommend him...
for the Seocho-gu's by-election.
He is a competent lawyer...
that even President Lee of Seonghan Group recommended.
I see.
He's the one who won the lawsuits...
of Seonghan's conflict with their temporary workers...
and Daeyoung Group's demolition plan in the redevelopment town.
I'm sure he will be of a big help to all of you here.
Please introduce yourself.
Hello. I am Han Seong Sik.
It's great to meet you all.
Come have a seat.
Okay.
I've seen you on television. You're on a roll these days.
Thank you.
I see.
That is not all
I will have my heyday
In the near future
Do you know him?
No.
What are you doing here?
You look even better after you left the program.
Well...
I'm doing fine.
By the way, how do you know the people...
you were with?
You mean Senior Secretary, the vice president of Mijin Co.,
and the chief secretary of Seonghan Group?
Why?
- Did you say Seonghan Group? - Yes.
It's such a nice office.
Have a seat, please.
I just opened it a while ago, so it's a little messy.
Did President Lee...
of Seonghan Group send you the flower pot?
What?
Secretary Park said...
the president ordered him to send it to me.
I'm working with them these days.
By the way,
what is it you want to tell me in my office?
Please go ahead.
It's about my brother.
He runs a factory that manufactures semi-conductors.
He wants to work with Seonghan Group again.
Really?
I wonder if you can help him.
Well...
I am not so sure.
To be honest,
his company is...
under financial strains.
He supplied the products...
to Seonghan Group until last month.
But...
the contract is terminated this month.
Wait. Please don't cry.
Please stop crying.
Actually,
I dress up every day,
but my family isn't so rich.
So without me and my brother,
my family...
will fall into poverty.
I never knew you've gone through a lot.
Yes.
- Do you want some chicken? - Gosh.
You have a client.
Who are you?
Well...
Hey! I'll pay you later.
Please get out now.
- Hey. - Get out of here.
- What's the matter? - Just leave.
Get out.
Well,
the restaurants in this building suffer from low sales recently.
Seong Sik!
Ms. Jang.
This isn't a good place...
to talk about things like that.
Why don't we go out...
and have a constructive talk with some cocktails?
What is this? Who would...
send it to me by express delivery?
Mom!
My dear Ah In.
- Where is Ji Hoon? - He went to the stationery.
Stationery? Why did he go there?
I don't know. He was...
making that, then he went out.
What is that?
Ah In. Look at your face.
Go and get washed up before dinner.
- Okay. - Okay.
What is this?
What? Who would send me this?
- Hello? - Hi, Hye Joo.
I'm Gyung Joon's mother.
- Hi. - Did you get the delivery?
Did you...
Yes. I sent it to you.
Why?
Why else? I wanted to make a good impression on the new president.
Pardon?
Also, I want to send my son to a specialized high school...
together with Ji Hoon,
so please help us out.
Look, that's not...
Don't forget to take the vitamins I sent you.
We should stay healthy to send our kids to good schools.
- I will see you later, then. - Hello?
Are you there? Hello?
What was that?
What should I do now?
- Mom. - What is it?
What are those things on the dining table?
- It's your dinner. - What?
I couldn't go to get groceries, so I ordered them.
Shouldn't I try to lose weight?
Forget about it.
Chang Soo.
Let's stop making our lives so hard.
I'm going to the supermarket.
I should buy groceries for tomorrow's breakfast.
Just eat those. Okay?
Okay.
Why did you come out? I told you to eat.
I ordered your favorite food.
You're not feeling well. I didn't want you to carry heavy things.
What?
Give them to me.
I know you're upset because of me.
It's not like this is the first time.
I know I embarrass you.
I didn't say you embarrass me.
You don't say it, but I know you do.
I thought about what I should do...
to make you and Dad proud of me in the past few days.
And?
I don't think I can get good grades...
just like Dad said.
Mom.
Should I become a Korean wrestler?
- What? - I'm big.
Maybe I'll be a good Korean wrestler.
Hey.
I can't believe this. Do you think it's easy?
Do you know how hard wrestlers train and exercise?
If you think you can be a wrestler just because you're big,
it'd be an insult to the wrestlers. Do you hear me?
I see.
I just...
wanted to make you feel better.
This is fine silk. Gosh.
Oh, my.
Oh, goodness.
You look gorgeous, Hye Joo.
I guess I didn't look good because...
I didn't own a classy scarf like this.
Gosh, it looks great.
Gosh, this feels nice.
I can already feel my body getting healthier.
Mom. What are you doing?
Hi, Ji Hoon.
Why are you wearing that on your head?
Oh, yes. It's nothing.
I was just cold.
Since this is a basement,
the cold wind gets through.
Well...
I have something I want to tell you.
Sure. Go ahead.
You know, school starts tomorrow.
That's right. It starts tomorrow. Hey.
Since you brought it up, let me ask you.
Do you think you can top the class this year, too?
What?
Well...
I've been thinking.
You're now in your third grade.
Wouldn't it be nice to keep up the good grades?
You said I could just stay in the top 10 students.
Gosh, you brat.
You're a guy. Don't just settle for being in the top 10.
If you're going to do it, be the top student...
as you always have been. You can play in your spare time.
I'm not going to do that.
What?
I'm not going to a specialized high school.
Which school do you want to go?
I want to go to a regular high school.
Also, I'm going to...
- become a magician. - What?
A magician?
Yes.
I don't know. I'm not going to care anymore.
Chang Soo.
Thank you. I can achieve my dream thanks to you.
- What do you mean? - You don't have to know.
I will repay you for this whenever I can. Okay?
Here is the fatty, you're a fatso
- You got your mom switched, right? - Do you want me to punch you?
- You punk. - Chang Soo!
Chang Soo. See me in the music room.
What are you doing, Ji Hoon and Ah In?
I brought you some fried chicken.
What are you doing?
Please look at this. Watch.
In 1, 2, 3.
Gosh, it's snowing!
It's like flowers are falling! Yes!
- Sure. - What's going on?
What happened to our house? I can't believe this.
You're right.
Yes!
This is so cool, Ji Hoon.
Mom.
What?
My school resumed today.
I know.
My teacher wants to see you.
Then I guess I should go.
I'm sure your teacher wants to see me...
to talk about your bad grades.
It's not my homeroom teacher.
The music teacher wants to see you.
What?
Did you... By a chance...
Did you break the piano in the music room?
How do you do this, Ji Hoon?
You can create a special device for it.
Ji Hoon.
When will it stop?
We have a little more.
- I see. - Yes.
Why are you crying?
Ji Hoon wants to become...
a magician instead of going to specialized high school.
What? Magician?
He saw this...
on the video, "Secret of Magic".
We have Harry Potter in our family.
Mom, sprinkles keep falling from the sky.
I know.
It keeps falling, doesn't it?
It's nice.
Why?
Are you going to get enormously drunk again...
when you come down from the mountain?
I'm not.
When did I drink that much?
What's going on with you these days?
Was I so wrong for saying that about Seong Joon's marriage?
That's not it.
I just wanted him...
to marry a better woman than his brothers.
I didn't mean anything else.
I know.
But still, you came home drunk because I said that in the morning.
You made me take care of you.
I am sorry.
No matter what you say,
I'm going to marry Seong Joon off well.
That way he doesn't have to struggle like his brothers.
I'm going to marry him off to a family that would...
believe in him and support him.
You may point fingers at me for being a materialistic person,
but I can't help it.
Gosh, I told you it's not about that.
If you come home drunk again,
and I'm going to change the gate lock password.
What did you say?
What did you...
just say?
Why don't you...
get Chang Soo a vocal lesson?
- A vocal lesson? - Yes.
Oh, dear.
I appreciate your suggestion,
but doesn't he need to be born with a gift for that?
You can't pursue music,
especially classical music,
unless you have an unbelievable talent.
Ma'am,
Chang So has an unbelievable talent.
- What? - He's got the qualities of...
top 0.001 percent as an opera singer.
What?
What did you say?
Did you say...
top 0.001 percent?
Sir.
I brought the man who found Sang Woo that night.
What's up, Sun Hwa?
What time is it in New York?
What? You're getting married!
Congratulations!
You kicked me out every night to be with him...
and made me get a job.
You're marrying him, aren't you?
How am I?
I don't know if I have a boyfriend or not.
I'm depressed because my boyfriend is giving me a hard time these days.
My boyfriend?
You will be shocked when you hear the name.
Remember the company Golden Street?
It was in front of your sandwich shop.
That night,
I went to Han River to do some night fishing.
I wasn't catching any fish, and it kept getting cold.
So I wrapped up early and headed home.
And I saw one boy...
who was crying loudly.
I looked around, but there was no adult.
It was very late, too.
He was wearing only a thin coat.
He was wearing sneakers, but he wasn't wearing any socks.
I thought it was strange, and I asked him.
I asked him why he was crying.
I asked him if he had lost his mother.
Then he suddenly cried,
"Brother! Brother!"
He was calling his brother so sadly.
What? Did you say Gold Street is still in business?
That's not possible.
He lost everything.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I doubt a person like him would have raised my brother.
Was it that happy?
If you get blinded by money,
power, and honor, you might get into a big trouble.
Until when do we have to wait?
Do you think she's even alive?
You didn't forget your proposal to me, right?
- Happy New Year. - Happy New Year.
They look like a newly married couple.