That night, I went to Han River...
to do some night fishing.
I couldn't catch any fish,
and it kept getting cold.
So I wrapped up early and headed home.
On the way, I saw a crying boy.
I looked around, but there was no adult.
It was very late, too.
Brother.
He was wearing only a thin jacket.
He was wearing shoes, but he
wasn't wearing any socks.
I thought it was strange, so I asked him.
Darling.
Why are you crying?
Did you lose your mother?
Then he suddenly cried,
Brother!
He was calling...
his brother so sadly.
What?
Did you say Golden Street
is still in business?
That's not possible.
He lost everything.
Perhaps you are mistaken.
Okay. Take care.
Congratulations on your marriage.
Welcome.
Hyun Woo.
Is something wrong?
Who is...
your uncle, Jeong Eun?
Pardon?
My uncle?
Why do you ask that?
He's too different...
from the one I know.
Who is my uncle you know?
Did you know...
my uncle even before?
No.
That's not it.
Hyun Woo.
Are you curious about my uncle now?
You were curious about Seong Joon
last time, and it's my uncle now.
Why are you so curious
about my family, Hyun Woo?
Are you not going to tell me?
Is it a secret again?
My uncle is...
a really nice person.
He's the man who would
live even without the law.
He gives his everything to his children,
and for that he gets into
a conflict with my aunt.
But I've never...
seen someone greater and
nicer than my uncle.
Is that enough?
Don't be upset.
I apologize...
about what happened that night.
I'm really curious about what
happened on that night...
and about why you came and had
a conflict with Seong Joon.
But I won't ask anymore.
Instead,
like I always told you,
please tell me when you want to.
I will wait.
Eat. I got you coffee and
cucumber sandwich as always.
Welcome.
What would you like?
Sure. I'll prepare a cup of warm Americano.
Please wait a little.
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
- You're well, right?
- Yes. Thank you.
- Hello.
Hello, Min Ji.
Where are you going?
Tell him where you're going.
We're going to a theme park.
You must be excited.
Get yourself something good. Have fun.
You didn't have to do that.
It's nothing.
- Say thank you.
- Thank you.
You're so adorable.
Take care.
- Sir.
- He's a nasty and cheap man.
A man like him could not
have raised my brother.
He destroyed another person's
family for his family.
He wouldn't have raised the son of
the man who almost killed his sons.
You have to think rationally.
We don't know yet that Han
Seong Joon is your brother.
23 years ago,
he looked straight into my eyes.
Crying while holding my dad
who was lying on the floor,
I looked at him with eyes
filled with resentment.
And he...
looked straight into my eyes too.
Still,
if Seong Joon is your brother,
it will be a good thing.
Seong Joon is not Sang Woo.
You saw how he treated me.
If he's Sang Woo,
he would have recognized me.
You heard the man who took
Sang Woo to the police.
He was calling for his
brother, not his mother.
There's no way...
Sang Woo wouldn't recognize me.
But I still hope Seong Joon...
turns out to be Sang Woo.
It would be a good thing
that he grew well...
like Seong Joon.
You have to remain cold at times like this.
I requested the police for the case record.
Everything will become clear soon.
I told you I'm not David Lee.
So why do you spread rumors?
Do you want to get hurt?
You are right.
I lost everything.
Every penny I had.
Will you be at the construction
site all day tomorrow, Sir?
Yes. If nothing special comes up.
What do you like about Hyun Woo?
I don't think he's such a good person.
Gosh, this is killing me.
My goodness, it's so heavy. My back hurts.
Mother. Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay. I thought my
arms were going to fall off.
We have so many people in our family.
Why do we have to buy groceries
for the holidays by ourselves?
Where did all the men in this family go?
None of them volunteered
to carry these for us.
What are you doing?
Where on earth have you been?
- You're home, Father.
- Yes.
Goodness. Why are you yelling at me?
I just went hiking.
Did you have to go today? We had
to buy groceries for the holidays.
I didn't know you had to
buy the groceries today.
Can't you tell?
The holidays are marked on the calendar.
You should have thought
to stay home and help me.
That's what you should have done.
Father, Mother. Give it to me. I'll do it.
Why would I look at the calendar?
It only makes me upset
that I'm getting old.
You always make up excuses.
Do you want me to move those things?
Father, please leave them. I'll do it.
Hurry and bring them over here.
I'll help you, Hye Joo. You came
home early from work today.
Yes.
Hye Joo.
Let Hyung Seop do it. You should go
downstairs. Hee Sook said she was...
going to Chang Soo's school. If
she's back, bring her up here.
It will take a long time to
just organize all these.
Okay, Mother. I will.
Chang Soo has an unbelievable talent.
- What?
- He's got the qualities of...
top 0.001 percent as an opera singer.
What?
What did you say?
Did you say top 0.001 percent?
He has an amazing and powerful voice.
Especially, we call the singer's
body "sound box" in vocal music.
His body is three times
bigger than other students.
Having a body like Chang Soo's is...
the same as having the
best musical instrument.
Look at that. Hee Sook.
What are you doing here?
Your aged mother-in-law...
and I, your sister-in-law who
will soon reach menopause,
worked so hard to buy the
groceries for the holidays.
You're a young woman.
You're actually the youngest one.
Why are you just sitting here?
Look, Hee Sook.
Hey! Should I teach you some lesson again?
Hye Joo.
Why are you looking at me like that?
You look scary.
- Hey! What are you doing?
- Just come here.
Why did you drag me down
here to tell me something?
We have a big problem.
What? What's the problem? What is it?
Did they say our sons
haven't been switched?
Hye Joo. That's something
I really hope for.
Anyway, what is it?
Please keep this to yourself for now.
- Chang Soo...
- Chang Soo?
Chang Soo... I mean...
I found out that Chang Soo has...
an amazing talent.
- A talent?
- Yes.
Does he have a talent?
Is it related to food?
Goodness, Hye Joo.
You're underestimating your former son.
Come on. It just feels too
awkward to hear all this.
I just can't put together the
word "talent" and Chang Soo.
That doesn't matter. What kind
of a talent does he have?
For music.
- For music?
- It's even classical music.
What? Did you say classical music?
Yes, that's right!
My goodness! You just spat on me.
Chang Soo and classical music?
Hye Joo.
What classical music? Is it...
a giant drum?
Castanets?
Or cymbals?
Hye Joo. Is that how much...
you value your former son?
No. That's not what I meant.
He doesn't have a talent for music,
let alone for classical music.
My husband and I don't know a
thing about classical music.
You and your husband also don't know
anything about classical music.
That's why I'm saying this, okay?
Chang Soo has potential to
become an opera singer.
An opera singer?
He's even got qualities of a top
0.001 percent opera singer.
What?
Who said that?
The music teacher at Chang Soo's school.
He asked me to come to the
school, and told me about this.
Is that true?
I'm telling you it is.
Anyway, whom should we...
consult with regarding this matter?
That's what I wanted to ask.
Do you know anyone who
studies classical music?
Wait. Let me think.
Who can there be?
All the people I know are office workers.
Seong Hoon's friends are all reporters.
Your husband's friends are all lawyers.
I know.
- You're just a housewife.
- Stop.
There is no one. What should we do?
Hye Joo!
What? What is it?
Do you know Mr. Jeong Myung
Hoon's phone number?
- Hey!
- My goodness.
What's all this?
I can't believe her.
Hey, Ae Ri.
Ae Ri!
You're here, Mom.
What do you think you're doing?
What's wrong with you?
How many bottles of wine have you had?
- Did you finish them all today?
- No.
In three days.
Are you saying you've been
drinking like this for three days?
Yes. Gosh, this feels good.
This is why artists should
do nothing but practice art.
They would be fools to love
someone or have children.
They are the most happy
when they do nothing...
but perform art all day every day.
Will you stop drinking?
Are you trying to drive me insane?
Mom.
You should think about it.
I don't even have...
a husband at this age.
My only daughter doesn't listen to me,
and I couldn't become a
world-class pianist.
How ridiculous.
My life is totally empty.
The only thing I can do is drink.
- Don't you think, Mom?
- Stop drinking!
Ae Ri.
No one stopped you from
becoming a world-class pianist.
You couldn't study abroad, and
you became a single mother...
because you met that jerk and got pregnant.
It's not because I told
you to live like this.
Mom.
They say you must tell the truth
no matter what the situation is.
You can't blame anyone.
You can't blame your daughter who
grew up well without a father,
and you can't blame me who
told you not to date that man.
Stop it, Mom.
Do you have to be like this in front of me?
You'll soon be in your 60s.
Do you have make your aged
mother see you live like this?
How can you do this?
I haven't said anything so far
because I knew you'd be upset.
Even when you and Jeong Eun were
having fights, I thought...
you would know how I felt since
you had a daughter like yourself.
That's what I thought, but what is this?
You locked the door for three days...
and drank day and night?
Is this how a person lives?
Do you call yourself my daughter?
Then, what other choice do I have?
This is so hard on me.
What am I supposed to do?
I'm having a hard time because I
think my life has been a waste.
I feel this is so unfair for me and
I am so furious. What can I do?
Are you the only one who's
having a hard time?
How about your daughter and me?
Don't you think it's easy for us?
Why did you have to set her
up with that baritone singer?
You should have learned your
lesson with baritone singers.
Are you still clueless?
Is that why you introduced
him to your own daughter?
As soon as I heard it,
I wanted to scold you.
You are so shallow.
- Mom.
- Shut it.
Don't come on the day
of the Lunar New Year.
I don't want to see you drunk.
All you do is complain...
and pick a fight with the family.
I don't want to see any of it.
Please just stay here and enjoy...
your own company like the
artist you call yourself.
What's wrong, Dad?
What do you mean? I'm just
wondering when you will be home.
Is there something wrong?
My gosh. Your mother told
me to peel the chestnuts...
since it's Lunar New Year's day tomorrow.
It's so hard to peel them.
I wanted you to help me with them.
I will finish soon since the
holiday starts tomorrow.
Leave them to me. I will
peel them when I get home.
I wouldn't say this to
you if it weren't hard.
Since your brothers are not here
and I am the only one here,
she's making me work.
Okay. I will be home soon.
I always forget something
whenever I go grocery shopping.
Can you peel these balloonflower roots?
You should have bought peeled ones.
They were sold out. I had no other options.
It's not easy for me.
I am not even half way
done with the chestnuts.
So will you peel them or not?
Okay, I will.
What's gotten into you this morning?
Excuse me.
When you are going home, take this home.
This is a present from me
for the Lunar New Year.
It's the traditional
fermented soybean paste.
- Isn't it?
- That's right.
Did you end up bringing it?
This is really authentic.
It smells wonderful.
It stinks. Close the lid.
- My clothes will smell like it.
- My gosh.
This is why I don't like
the younger generation.
They don't know nothing
about their hometown.
This is authentic indeed.
Did you Grandmother make it?
- Of course, she did.
- Thank you, Dong Hui.
Thank you. I will enjoy it for sure.
What is the smell?
It's the fermented soybean
paste from Dong Hui.
Is it fermented soybean paste this time?
Why do you keep doing this?
I didn't mean any harm.
I guess your family will like
it since it's the holiday.
Is there one for me?
Why don't you finish up your work?
Let's call it a day today.
Please hurry if any of you
are going to your hometown.
Those who aren't going should still
spend the time with your family.
- How nice.
- Great.
Please have nice holidays.
I hope for a safe return.
Everyone, Happy New Year.
- Happy New Year to you, Director.
Director, please have this.
Just like the previous time,
yours is slightly bigger.
I guess now she has caught on how
to be sociable in the company.
From now on, you don't need
to give me things like this.
Director Han, can we go over some
documents before you go home?
My goodness, Chang Soo!
Chang Soo!
Ji Hoon.
Until when do we need to do this?
I'm sorry.
I have to practice until
I can do it perfectly.
I...
can't...
understand you, kids.
One of them wants to be a magician.
The other one...
Hye Joo. Hye Joo!
Hye Joo.
What brings you here?
What is going on here?
It's nothing. Nothing.
Mother, I will go to a stationary store.
Ji Hoon. I'm coming with you.
Let's go.
Okay. Don't trip on the way.
Okay.
Hye Joo. Something has happened.
What now?
What is it this time?
Can you take a look at this?
- Chang Soo, what are you doing?
- What are you doing?
Hey. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
It's the thigh band. I'm just trying it on.
- Why?
What's wrong with you, two? Why
are you repeating each other?
Well, there is...
a reason to it.
Yes, there's a reason to it.
I want to try Korean wrestling. Can
I attend Kyung Woon Middle School?
Why?
I heard there's a Korean wrestling team.
I want to do my best there.
I should be good at something. It's
how I will make you and Dad happy.
Well, Chang Soo.
Well...
There's something I want to ask you.
What is it?
How do you feel when you sing?
When I sing?
Well,
you volunteered at the church
and the nursing home before.
That brings me to my question.
I'm asking you how you feel when you sing.
I'm also asking you the same question.
When I sing?
It's hard to explain.
Well, it feels like...
I feel like my body is
being sucked into space.
Did you say "space"?
Yes, my body feels like it's
being sucked into space...
and I float around in space.
All of a sudden, I feel like
space and I become one.
Then, space and I disappear...
and only the song remains.
- Do you mean it?
- Yes, he means it, Hye Joo.
Yes, I do.
Then...
I can't see anything since
it's pitch-dark in space.
From somewhere, I can hear a song.
But...
I don't think if the
voice is from angels...
or from me.
Why do you ask?
Anyway, I want to transfer
to Kyung Woon Middle School.
I will do Korean wrestling.
How do I look? Doesn't it suit me?
It doesn't?
What brings you here?
I'm here to get that
fermented soybean paste.
Why don't I get anything?
You didn't give me omija
or rice cake last time,
and you didn't give me
fermented soybean paste.
Why are you discriminating?
Dong Hui, aren't you supposed to...
flatter your boss?
You're flattering Director
Bang because she's above me.
Come with me. I'll get you some.
But first, show me your script.
Hurry up.
You talk as if I owe it to you.
Yes, you owe it to me.
Give it to me.
I need to check first if
you've been working hard.
I'll print it out. Please wait a little.
Okay. Go ahead and print it.
- I'll make some ramyeon.
- Pardon?
How can he touch her here?
She has never even held
hands with a man before.
Besides, she went to him to ask for help.
How can he touch her immediately?
Don't be so violent, Miss Writer.
He didn't touch her immediately.
Besides, he hardly touched her.
He just grabbed her hand to take her.
Nobody would think he was touching her.
But he hugged her shoulders.
You created that man, you know?
You made him the womanizer.
Until when will you make him stay pure?
Still, how can he hit on
his client like that?
You read the synopsis. He's the man...
who never hits on his client.
Yeon Hee is very desperate.
She mustered her courage and went
there to win Woo Hyeon's heart.
When they met for the second time,
Jun Sung already started to...
have feelings for her.
No way.
No way? But it's true.
You're too old-fashioned.
If you make a drama like this,
it will have a bad rating.
You are behind the times.
Never mind. I won't show it to you anymore.
I'll just review it myself. Give it to me.
- What's wrong?
- Give it to me.
If I keep taking your advice,
the story will be spoiled.
Give it to me. Give it to me.
Don't move. Stay still.
This is it.
When a man and a woman meet,
they just need to go for it.
Stop arguing logic and etiquette.
You said you want to be a writer.
You have to come out of yourself
and get ahead of the viewers.
Like this, the viewers won't wait for you.
This is my taking revenge on
you for dumping me to write.
Preserve it with honey and
make juice every morning.
Yes, Ma'am.
Why would you bother yourself to
visit me every Lunar New Year?
You are an adult too.
I may be old too, but I am
still like your little sister.
This omija is nice. It's not too sour.
It tastes just like omija I
used to have in your house.
Right.
Do you remember the lady who
used to be your helper?
When we were in high school,
we used to gather...
with Kwang Woo to study at your place.
And that helper made the most
delicious snacks for us.
I still remember her.
I think she cooked very well.
- What about her?
- That lady...
was cleaning our building just recently.
I wasn't sure at first.
But it was her. I'm sure it was her.
Didn't she quit your house because
she had to take care of...
her grandchildren after
the death of her son?
Yes. I think that's what happened.
It's been too long though.
What about that anyway?
It's nothing. It's just that...
your family started struggling...
after she left. That's what I thought.
What are you talking about?
Think about it.
Kwang Woo's family died of accident,
and the chairman went missing.
Until when do we have to wait for her?
Is she really still alive?
What? Why would you bring that up?
We need to find out whether
she is still alive or not...
for you to become the largest shareholder.
This is why the stockholders...
look down on you.
You're here.
- You're here, Mi Joo.
- Hello, Mi Joo.
You've gotten even more beautiful.
You should get married soon.
Don't you agree?
She has to learn the work a little more.
But she's a daughter.
You should get a son-in-law
first and train them together.
You're here, Mi Joo.
Please take this.
- What's this?
- One of my employees gave it to me.
Open it in the kitchen. It will smell.
Okay.
It must be homemade
fermented soybean paste.
That lady made...
the best fermented soybean paste.
Which lady are you talking about?
Goodness. Take it easy. It
will get dusty in here.
I want to get rid of the
disgusting dust from 2016.
You must be happy that
you lived to greet 2017.
Why would the dust be disgusting?
You're such an understanding person.
You're even wearing a cast today.
I know.
I fell very lightly, but it hurt too much.
So I went to see the doctor, and
it turns out my bone is cracked.
That's why you should have
just hung out with me.
Why do you do that cleaning job?
I won't go anymore.
My kids are making a big
fuss because of my arm.
They gave me a harder time.
Of course you shouldn't go.
You still work at your age
and support your children.
But that's all useless.
Stop being so mad at your daughter.
But I can't help myself.
I tried so hard to educate her.
Do you know how expensive it
was to get her piano lessons?
The lessons were so expensive
and I paid the tuition, too.
I worked so hard to make
her good at playing piano.
But she fell in love with
that useless vocalist.
I shouldn't be telling you this,
but she got pregnant and had
to give up her studies.
She's still depressed because
of that, and I'm always upset.
That's how she lives.
When I went there the other day,
she was playing the piano
loudly like a mad woman...
and drank unbelievably a lot.
When I see her, I don't even
feel the joy of living.
But still,
that's no reason to take out
all your clothes at this hour.
It's just that I can't control my anger.
I think I will feel calmer
only when I organize things.
By the way, why do you keep this?
People call you an oldie because
you keep things like this.
Don't touch that. Why
do you touch my things?
Goodness. What's this?
Goodness. Don't touch it.
My goodness, look at this.
Give it to me.
Isn't that the key to your safe?
- Do you have hidden fund?
- No.
Why do you have so many secrets?
- I don't.
- Goodness.
You are so secretive.
Hi, Reporter Yim.
I sent you the confidential report about...
the corrupt relationship of Seonghan
Group with Senior Secretary.
Yes. I hope...
you will fulfill your duty...
as a reporter.
Okay. Good luck.
I took care of the problem very
perfectly again this time, Sir.
I'm sure you handled it well...
since you took care of it yourself. Right?
Thank you very much.
So, you said you wanted to
introduce someone to me.
Do I have to wait?
Oh, yes.
She'll be here soon.
Hello, Senior Secretary.
You're Jang Yoo Ra, the famous anchor.
I see you recognize her.
Thank you for recognizing me, Sir.
It's nice to meet you.
Thanks to Seong Sik who
appears on TV shows,
I was able to meet a beautiful anchor.
This is great.
I'm flattered.
You don't have to worry about that.
I will talk to President
Lee about it myself.
Would you really do that?
Thank you.
Thank you so much, Sir.
My goodness.
You didn't need to get so serious
to ask me something like this.
Aren't we too close for that?
Are we?
Anyway, take this.
What...
is this?
Why are you so surprised?
Seonghan Group could escape
the crisis, thanks to you.
Their son could avoid the imprisonment too.
This is a small present from the president.
I'm honored,
but how can I accept this?
Just take it. He's just
showing his gratitude.
By the way,
I can still smell the fried chicken here.
I heard fried chicken restaurants
aren't doing well these days.
I guess that restaurant is an exception.
Yes, well...
The owner isn't good at everything else,
but he's famous for making
great fried chicken.
I wonder whom Seong Sik is meeting with.
The preparation for the
by-election is going well, right?
I'll expect to see you join our party soon.
Yes. I got it, Sir.
Isn't that Senior Secretary?
No, you don't need to.
Okay. Goodbye, Sir.
Goodbye.
What is that brat up to?
Please get in.
Lucky me!
Seong Sik.
Go away. My goodness.
That brat...
That crazy punk.
- What do you think?
- I like it.
Do you like it?
All right, then.
Yoo Ra.
Shall we go in?
Let's go.
- Grandma, Dad, Mom, Ms. Oh.
- Happy New Year.
My gosh. All right. How nice!
Aren't you happy, Ms. Oh?
Yes. Of course.
Grandma. I hope your arm
will get better soon.
All right. Thank you, my dear Ah in.
- Grandma!
- Yes.
- All right.
- Her arm hurts. Let me hug you.
All right. I wish...
all of you great happiness...
and great fortune this year.
You two should stop having fights.
- Okay.
- Mom.
I never do anything wrong.
Seong Hoon always picks
on me for no reason.
Be quiet. You should try to be
a better son to us this year.
Mom. Please don't worry.
I will be the one to take
care of our family...
this year.
My gosh. He's all talk and no action.
I'm serious, Grandma.
You two should try to get along.
- Gosh, Mother.
- Mother.
- We're on great terms now.
- We're good now.
- Isn't that right, Hee Sook?
- Of course, Hye Joo.
- By the way, Mom.
- Yes?
I don't see Ae Ri.
I told her not to come.
- Why not?
- She's not allowed in this house.
From now on, those who is
self-indulgent on the excuse of...
being an artist can't enter this house.
If any of you...
bring the food that...
we prepared for the
holidays to Ae Ri today,
you will pay for it. I will
give you a good scolding.
Ms. Hwang. Please stop.
You shouldn't be like that
on a happy day like this.
By the way, where is Dong Hui?
Isn't Dong Hui here yet?
There're so many people
here, so I didn't notice.
Seong Joon isn't here, either. Seong Joon.
You should do a head count.
- Why can't you get everyone here?
- All right.
I'm sorry.
You look so pretty, Dong Hui.
Thank you.
Come on. Do the New Year's bow.
Mom. I can't button the shirt.
- It's done.
- Okay.
Seong Joon. You look like a new groom.
Seong Joon. Give them a bow.
- Yes.
- Dong Hui, do it with Seong Joon.
- All right. Do it together.
- Come to this side.
Grandma, Ms. Oh, Dad, and Mom.
Happy New Year.
All right.
Okay.
Both of you look so good.
You look like the bride and groom.
I know, right?
My gosh. She looks beautiful.
Magpie's new year's day was
Yesterday
Our new year's day is
Today
Pretty pigtail ribbon
I put it on myself
A new pair of shoes
I put it on myself as well
Pack some Korean pancake and fruits.
I've already packed fruits. I'm
packing Korean pancake now.
Aren't you going to give us any food?
Yes. I'm coming.
Wherever you are, I will be there
What are you and Hee Sook talking about?
You two are not that close.
What are you talking about, Seong Hoon?
Hye Joo and I are very close now.
Gosh, don't mind them. It won't last long.
Here. Let me pour you a drink.
Drink up.
Where are you
My dear
His voice sounds so powerful.
Goodness. Chang Soo is quite a singer.
Of course. He's my grandson.
That was so hard.
Hey. How could we have
forgotten about Aunt?
I know, right?
Sometimes, you don't see what
is right in front of you.
Hee Sook, let's get going.
By the way,
what's wrong with you?
Your hanbok is so gaudy.
Hey, you should be grateful that
I'm wearing hanbok at least.
I'm too fat to wear the one I
bought when I got married.
So I borrowed it at 80 dollars yesterday.
I was a little, and this was the last one.
Still, your hanbok is too garish.
What do you mean it's garish?
Your former son might
major in classical music.
Please maintain your dignity.
Hey, wait for me.
I said wait for me.
The one who visits your office often
recently by the black sedan...
is Senior Secretary Kim, right?
Didn't you see the flower pot he sent?
We graduated the same college.
Hey, are you close to everyone
who went to the same college?
You shouldn't be close to anyone like that.
What's wrong with you?
Now are you trying to pick
on the connections I have?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- My gosh.
Why do you hit me on New Year's Day?
Do you think you're still a journalist?
You're the owner of a chicken restaurant!
How dare you!
It doesn't matter what my current job is.
I'm telling you this because
I'm worried about you.
Then, tell me what makes you that worried!
Are you worried that I might
become too successful?
It's silent now, but Kim Young
Tae and Seonghan Group...
They are involved in many problems.
A naive guy like you is likely
to be framed up in the end.
Your breath smells of liquor.
Are you drunk? Stop it.
How can you be so ignorant?
Seong Hoon, you drank too much.
Please stop drinking.
If you become blinded by money,
power, and fame like now,
you'll end up in a terrible fix.
You'd better mark my words.
Gosh, I'm so fed up with you.
Don't try to pick a fight because
you don't want me to succeed.
Hey, what are you guys doing
in the beginning of the year?
Didn't you say you'd stop fighting?
What on earth is this?
- Answer me.
- Mom, Seong Hoon...
hit me like this again.
- You little jerk...
- Seong Hoon, let's go downstairs.
- Go downstairs right now!
- Mom,
- he just hit me.
- Leave already.
Thank you for washing dishes.
You can leave, too.
- Okay.
- Get out.
By the way, where are Hye Joo and Hee Sook?
Why did they leave the silly ones alone?
There's a way to eat holiday
dishes even if she forbade me...
from vising her house.
How is it, Aunt? Is it good?
It's a little salty.
Well, we're so sorry.
We should have been...
more careful.
By the way, did you say...
Chang Soo will major in classical music?
That's right.
- Are you serious?
- I am.
Well...
Aunt.
Aunt, please stop laughing.
We're really serious.
My dear.
So every man for his own trade...
Goodness.
Aunt, he really has a talent.
- Gosh.
- She's right.
His talent as an opera singer is...
within top 0.001 percent of all.
Within top 0.001 percent of all.
Come to think of it, Chang Soo
has an extraordinary voice...
and a firm body.
I think he should be a tenor...
- with his voice.
- Tenor...
- Tenor?
- Yes.
Males' voice types can be broken down...
into a tenor, baritone, and bass.
To be more specific, the
types can be classified...
as a sopranist,
countertenor, alto,
tenor, tenor-baritone,
baritone, baritone-bass,
and bass.
Considering his voice,
I think he should be a tenor.
However, the tenor voice
type is divided into many.
Lyric tenor.
It is a graceful voice.
It's the best voice for
young innocent guys...
who fell in love.
The next is spinto tenor.
The spinto tenor has...
a young and bright voice
with a heavier vocal weight.
It's a perfect voice...
for Commender Radames from "Aida" of Verdi.
Dramatic tenor.
This is my favorite.
The dramatic tenor has an emotive...
and powerful tenor sound.
It's a ringing and heroic voice.
So what Chang Soo should do from now on?
What do you mean?
He needs to receive lessons
from Professor Park.
Professor... Professor Park?
Yes. He's a great singer.
I'll make an appointment for you.
Visit him with Chang Soo.
Really? My goodness.
This is so great.
Why the police? Why haven't
they contacted us yet?
It's been 23 years. Please wait.
- Still, if they kept the records...
- Sir,
It's even longer than two decades.
I have a few things to
report while you're waiting.
Seong Hoon handed over information...
about the secret funds of
Hanseong to Jinsung Daily News.
Seong Sik sent back...
the car you lent him
only after three months.
Seonghan Group gave him
a luxurious sedan...
to muzzle him.
I guess Seonghan isn't fair game, either.
I think they plan to
completely destroy his life.
I think so, too. So we're not hundred
percent sure about Sang Woo.
So I'd like to ask you suspend your plan...
regarding the Han brothers for a while.
Yet, they're the family
who has raised Sang Woo.
Where are you going?
- To give New Year's greeting.
- Sorry?
They've taken care of Sang Woo.
Then, I should go make a bow to them.
Who would it be? Who is it?
- Hello.
- Goodness.
- You're here, Mr. Lee.
- Yes.
- Please take this.
- You didn't have to bring a gift.
- Hello, Mr. Lee.
- Hello.
- I'm here for New Year's greeting.
- Welcome.
Let me make a bow, Sir.
There's no need to do it.
Still, you're an elder
of this neighborhood.
I wish your family peace and happiness.
I hope so, too. But things
don't always go as we want.
Mr. Lee, please have this.
You didn't have to do this for me.
Please don't say that. I can't
let my guest leave empty-handed.
Please enjoy.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- Please take your time.
- Okay.
We were in the middle of playing go,
so we'll continue this round.
We put money on this.
Sure. Please go on.
What are you doing? It's your turn.
Okay.
Wait, why did you put your stone there?
Dad, I did to win.
No way. Please undo it just once.
Dad, that's not fair.
Seong Joon, come on.
Just once.
I can't lose like this.
I was going to put mine there.
No, I can't undo it.
Gosh, it's me who raised
you into a smart guy.
Dad, please stop it.
Just surrender and give me 10 dollars.
Just give me 10 dollars.
Please just let me take back a move.
No. I can't let you do that.
You're here.
You should be wearing it.
It looked good on you.
It's a bit uncomfortable.
You should rest today. Why did you come up?
If we rest just because it's the
holidays, when will you be a writer?
Pardon?
You have to be a writer...
so that you can put an end
to your love in your drama.
That's how your love in reality can start.
Please excuse me.
I'm here to see Director Han Seong Joon.
I'm sorry to barge in on a holiday.
I think Seong Joon is on the rooftop.
Who are you?
Thank you. I will introduce myself later.
Who was it?
It was a lady. She hurried
inside and asked for Seong Joon.
A lady?
Do you want some coffee?
Are you running away again?
- Excuse me?
- I don't need...
coffee.
Let's talk about your script.
You haven't forgotten...
your proposal to me, right?
What proposal? I made a proposal? When?
You promised you'll be...
the most famous scriptwriter
in Korea in 10 years.
When you do become one,
you made a proposal...
that I should produce your drama.
What were you thinking?
Okay. I got it. So let's work hard.
I think we stopped here.
Let's start revising.
Your mother didn't come today.
Yes, she didn't. She had a big
argument with Grandmother.
Are you angry at me?
Yes, I am angry a bit.
You left just like that and
didn't leave me a message.
It's because...
I know.
Something urgent and hard
must have happened to you.
I just...
waited for you for some time.
I got tired of it and
that's why I am angry.
Why?
I didn't take...
a good care of you lately.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
I'd feel weird if someone was
trying to take care of me.
- Jeong Eun.
- Let go of me.
What's gotten into you?
You...
are certainly a bad man.
By the way, Hyun Woo.
Who are you?
What sort of person are you?
What do you mean?
I don't know anything about you.
I thought at least I would
know the most about you.
That was my mistake.
- Jeong Eun.
- Aren't we...
lovers?
Aren't we dating?
Our history goes back to three
years ago when we met in New York,
but why do you hide so many things from me?
Why don't your actions add up?
You're so brutal.
Do you want to...
know more about me?
After my father passed away,
my brother and I were sent to an orphanage.
Sang Woo was seven years old.
After I went to school,
he always waited for me in
the yard of the orphanage.
On that day, I ended later than usual.
I couldn't bring the school
supplies I was supposed to bring.
So I had to stay late to clean by myself.
My brother who waited for
me, left the orphanage...
since I didn't come.
He wanted to look for me.
He only had a light jacket.
After that day, I couldn't find my brother.
After some time,
I was adopted by an American couple.
I am an adoptee.
An adoptee from an orphanage.
And a brother who's looking
for his younger brother...
whom he lost 20 years ago.
That's who I am.
Hyun Woo.
After 20 years have passed,
I think...
I can find my brother now.
Excuse me?
I think...
I can find my bother now.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I wish Seong Joon can
marry into a good family.
I am not certain if I
am talented in singing.
Why wouldn't you be talented?
I raised my Chang Soo for 15 years.
I didn't know what he likes
or what he is good at.
Where did you get this
fermented soybean paste?
I was wondering if you remembered
anything before you were adopted.
Do you have memories like
your old neighborhood...
or your father and brother?