I am an adoptee.
An adoptee from an orphanage.
And a brother who's looking for his younger brother...
whom he lost 20 years ago.
That's who I am.
Hyun Woo.
Why?
Do you feel better now?
I am sorry.
I didn't know.
I didn't know you had such a painful past.
I'm sorry for being so immature.
After 20 years have passed,
I think...
I can find my brother now.
Excuse me?
I think...
I can find my bother now.
Really?
So please trust me and wait a little.
I will never make you sad...
or hurt you again.
Please bear with me...
until I find my brother.
Okay.
I will wait.
I will bear with you.
Also,
I will trust you.
You're no longer the wild girl I used to know.
The neighborhood will thank me for it.
You made it happen.
Director Bang.
What are you two doing right now?
What brings you all the way here?
Seong Joon, I mean Director Han.
Do you know what's happening at the company?
How can the director be out of reach?
I am sorry. I left my phone downstairs.
What's going on?
You two are unbelievable.
Director Bang.
Writer Jo won't work with us.
What?
Do you know who she is?
She's the girl who came the other time.
Who is that?
She's Seong Joon's fiance.
Honey.
Seong Joon said she is not his fiance.
Honey!
What's the reason?
There's a problem with her previous employee.
She's contracted to write 10 more episodes for them,
so we were going to return them the money for those manuscripts.
But they claimed the priority right and decided to resign with her.
No way.
Where is Writer Jo right now?
She's at the writing room. Her agent is coming too.
We're going to have a meeting there.
Hurry up and get ready, Seong Joon. You don't have time to play house.
Seong Joon.
Where is she?
Mom, I have to go to the office. There's an emergency.
I am sorry.
Seong Joon. Seong Joon.
I'm in a hurry, but I have to ask you a question.
Yes, Director.
What were you two doing?
We were studying the script.
Did you say you were studying the script?
Yes.
Dong Hui,
I shouldn't meddle with the family...
getting along so well,
but I hope you will not get carried away by something personal...
like this and let it affect your work again.
Okay.
You're here.
My guess was right.
I knew it was you.
We have an emergency at work,
and Seong Joon wasn't picking up his phone.
Did something bad happen at work?
No, it's nothing bad.
It just needs to be addressed right away. That's all.
It turned out he left his phone downstairs.
Only if Seong Joon...
had his phone,
I wouldn't have ruined your holiday.
I am sorry.
You were just doing your work. I understand.
I will get going now then.
Seong Joon must be waiting for me downstairs.
Sure. Go ahead.
I'll visit you again next time.
Okay. Take care.
Dong Hui, do you have time?
I do.
If I knew they were going to leave so soon,
I wouldn't have brought up tea.
Since I brought up two cups of tea, we should drink it together.
Sure.
It's decorated quite well here.
Yes. Seong Hoon helped us a lot.
I see. Seong Hoon...
cares a lot about his in-laws.
By the way, you are always busy writing.
Don't you want to get married?
Do I want to get married?
I am sorry.
You are quite old now.
It's time to think about settling down with someone, you know?
I don't know. I haven't thought about it yet.
I've already married off my two sons,
and now there's only Seong Joon left.
That's why...
I want Seong Joon...
to marry better person than...
his brothers.
That's how mothers feel, you know?
Rather than marrying a poor girl who is kind,
I want him to marry a wealthy and educated girl...
who was brought up with much love.
I want that kind of a girl to be my daughter-in-law.
That will make his marriage life easier too.
Of course.
I'm sure...
you are a clever girl.
You're a writer too, so I'm sure you understand...
mother's feelings well.
Yes.
I hope you marry well too.
You didn't say anything strange...
to that girl, did you?
I didn't get to talk to her.
Something came up at the office, so they rushed off.
Instead,
I had some tea with Dong Hui.
Why did you have tea with Dong Hui?
I just warned her a little.
What is there to warn her about?
Ms. Oh...
educated her children so well.
She's flawless.
She is hardly flawless.
She spends all day with Seong Joon in that small space.
They don't even come out for hours.
So how can I not warn her?
What are you imagining?
I smell something fishy.
I think there's something going on between them.
- Honey. - You don't know anything.
Young people are different.
They don't care if they are in-laws.
You are unbelievable.
And you know Seong Joon.
He's just like you. He has a soft spot for the weak.
So you're saying Seong Joon...
likes her. Is that what you're saying?
That can't happen. They are in-laws for crying out loud.
That's why I am taking precautionary measures.
Anyway, you should...
warn Seong Joon too.
Stop it.
We lost her after all.
I haven't had the faintest idea that this could happen.
How can they sign 10 more episodes? Their contract already ended.
She came to us first because she took care of it.
This is how businesses in this field run.
We only have us to blame. We should have been more careful.
I will try my best to...
avoid cancellation of the air time we already acquired.
However, we must find her replacement right away.
What is the agenda of the meeting of the shareholders?
The biggest agenda is regarding...
Contents and Marketing Department's performance.
My gosh. How idiotic.
I shouldn't have put them in charge in the first place.
They are still young.
- What else? - The more important agenda is...
the disappearance of the former president, Park Chang Wook.
They are so brutal.
Why are they so anxious to declare his death?
And...
how many are on my side?
It's more than majority,
but the opposing side is requesting...
to disclose the president's will.
My goodness. Nothing is going my way.
- Okay. You can go now. - Yes, Sir.
I heard the contract with Writer Jo was nullified.
How did you find out?
It just happened this morning.
Since you are looking down on me,
that is why Director Han is...
not afraid of me.
I'm glad it happened. The shareholders didn't like...
Director Han and Contents Department.
Now you can disband the team.
- Dad, I can't do that. - And...
Fire Han Seong Joon now.
This is when you accept his resignation letter.
We are not supposed to fooled by him like the previous time.
- Dad. - It's the end of our conversation.
Dad, give me some time to regroup.
We can manage this crisis. please?
Your pleading won't make any difference.
How are you going to handle the meeting with the shareholders?
Do you think the shareholders will...
let him off easy?
What brings you here?
Do you have any business with my family?
Are you coming home now?
Are you here to see Jeong Eun?
No, I am not.
Then, why are you here?
I can't seem to figure you out...
why you are acting like this.
- It's... - Please go back home.
It's not a good sight to see.
- What are you doing? - Stay still.
You must be neat. The professor will see you soon.
First impression is very important.
There.
- Are you ready? - Mom.
So today is...
the day I decide if...
I will sing or do Korean wrestling?
Why did you bring that?
I am not certain if I am talented in singing.
Why wouldn't you be talented?
There isn't any reason why you should stay as a bad student.
You are not the one to judge your ability.
The professor is the one to judge.
Chang Soo.
Just like I said, be comfortable.
You should sing just like you usually sing. Did you get that?
But still. I am nervous, Mom.
Don't be nervous. It's all right, Chang Soo.
I'm here for you. Let's cheer up, okay?
- You can do it. - Okay. I can do it.
Chang Soo, it's your turn. Go in.
- Come on. Hurry inside. - Please don't push me, Mom.
I'm scared.
Go in. Hurry inside.
A water bird dances in the blue sky
Hey, hey
Row the boat, I need to find her
My youth is on the floating boat
The sunset in Hwangpo River
It is red
Excuse me.
Professor.
How is he?
Well...
Professor?
Can you step outside? I need to talk to your mother.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait for me outside.
Mom, what did the professor say?
Chang Soo.
My gosh.
Mom. Thank you so much.
Good job, my Chang Soo. Well done.
Great work, Chang Soo. Let's go.
Okay.
- Really? Here you go. - Thank you.
- Are you serious? - Yes, I am serious, Hye Joo.
The professor in one of the best university of music...
recognized Chang Soo's talent.
My gosh.
I'm throwing a party at home. So please come home early.
Goodness. I'm so proud of you, Chang Soo.
Thank you.
- How do you feel, Ms. Oh? - I feel so happy.
I had no idea that Chang Soo would have a talent like that.
Exactly. Who knew? Every man for his own trade.
Mother, he just started.
Congratulations, Chang Soo.
I didn't know you could sing so well.
Nor did I.
You ought to put all your effort into it now.
Of course. Since he started,
you will be the best opera singer in the world, okay?
Yes, I will.
Everyone. Look at this.
- My gosh. How pretty. - What is that?
- Goodness. - Grandmother.
This is a celebratory cake for Chang Soo.
- My goodness. - It's so pretty.
- Gosh. - Everyone.
Please sing for Chang Soo.
- What song? - Please clap.
In 1, 2, 3.
- Congratulations - Congratulations
- Congratulations on our happiness - Congratulations
- Congratulations - It's for Chang Soo's new life.
- Congratulations on his new life - Congratulations on his new life
- Congratulations - Congratulations
- Chang Soo. Blow out the candles. - Okay.
- My proud Chang Soo. - He's so powerful.
This is why he sings well.
Hye Joo, when did you get here?
Hello, Mother. I just arrived.
Why are you standing there? Come take a seat.
It's okay, Grandma.
All right. Grandmother, Father and Mother.
Chang Soo will cut the cake now.
Go ahead.
Chang Soo, cut it nicely.
My goodness. Father, Mother.
Did you see how nicely Chang Soo cut the cake?
Mom, thank you so much...
for preparing a cake for me.
Thank you, My son.
Please give him an applause.
Why did she make us to sing the same song so many times?
Of course, I am also happy Chang Soo discovered his talent,
but my arms are so tired now.
She even asked us if we saw how nicely Chang Soo cut the cake.
Is that something to be complimented?
You know he cut cakes well even when he was little.
Mom, please understand Hee Sook.
She did that because she was so happy.
You know her heart was broken...
when she sent Ji Hoon to Hye Joo.
I'm sure she's extremely happy to find out about Chang Soo's gift.
She's right.
Please understand her.
So you mean...
Hee Sook now has a new goal, right?
Exactly, Mom.
I guess she won't bother us anymore, then.
She will no longer be depressed with a long face...
or go into hysterics toward us.
Since we found out that kids were switched,
I've been stressed out...
because of Hee Sook.
Mother, I've been the same too.
Really?
Of course.
It's spicy.
Honey, this is the new sauce. Do you want to try some?
Maybe later.
This was totally unexpected.
Who on earth would have known if Chang Soo was such talented?
Have you ever thought he'd study vocal music?
Honey.
What's the matter?
Why are you crying?
Hye Joo.
For the first time in my life,
I thought it was a good choice...
to send Chang Soo to Hee Sook.
What do you mean?
You know what I mean.
I've raised him for 15 years,
but I didn't know...
what he likes or what he is good at.
All I did were...
nagging him into studying...
and yelling at him to stop eating.
I really don't deserve to be a mother.
Don't be so harsh to yourself.
But this is the reality.
Hee Sook found...
Chang Soo's talent just in three months...
since she started taking care of him.
But I have been too indifferent to him...
since I gave birth to Ah In.
Saying I was busy,
I didn't take care of him well.
Honey,
you know finding and developing talents are Hee Sook's specialty.
That's nothing but a mere excuse.
I'm also a mother just like her.
And...
I had been his mother for the last 15 years.
By the way,
do you have any plan...
to marry Dong Hui off?
Pardon?
She has reached a marriageable age,
so I just wondered if you have any plan.
What's with that question out of the blue?
What in the world are you talking about?
Seong Joon also has a girlfriend who I think he'll get married to.
Dong Hui is also about the same age as Seong Joon,
so I just asked if she also has a boyfriend.
Well,
I should marry her off someday.
Why did you ask her such question?
What's the matter?
Don't you know she doesn't have much money?
She's staying in the rooftop room in her in-laws' house.
How can she afford to marry Dong Hui off now?
You mocked her in front of the family.
We need to talk later.
Goodness.
Mother, I didn't mean to offend her.
As I'm considering to marry Seong Joon off soon,
I just wondered if Dong Hui also has a plan.
Why do you even bother to care about her?
Put yourself in Ms. Oh's shoes.
She must have thought you were telling her...
to marry Dong Hui off...
and move to a nursing home because they're bothersome.
Hee Sook isn't the only drama queen, but you are too.
You two are no different from each other.
That's not what I meant. I asked it for a reason.
For a reason?
Stop it already.
Why are you yelling at me? Why?
Grandma.
Hello, Dong Hui.
What are you doing here? It's cold outside.
Well,
I just thought you'd be writing.
Please come inside. It's cold here.
Sure. Let's go in.
- Please drink some tea. - Okay.
How is your arm?
I think it will take a while to recover...
since I'm old.
Why did you take the cleaning job? You don't have to work.
If I don't, how am I going to help you when you get married?
Grandma,
I'm not going to marry.
What are you talking about?
I want to live with you like now.
You know I can't live forever.
My scenario will be dramatized soon.
I might become a sought-after writer when it's aired.
I will just keep writing...
and live happily with you, Grandma.
Do you...
have a boyfriend?
Sorry? No, I don't.
Then,
do you have any man...
of your heart?
I don't. Why are you asking such things?
I feel sorry for you.
I couldn't send you to a college,
so you are working...
and writing every day.
You can't dress up and hang out with your friends.
It breaks my heart...
to see you working.
Please don't say that, Grandma.
I'm really happy now.
Grandma, why are you crying?
Where is she?
Ms. Oh.
How longer should Dong Hui wait?
She turned 27 already.
You really have to do something with her now.
Please wait a little longer.
It's almost done.
Please hurry up.
You know my days are numbered.
Are you not going to sleep?
What are you doing here?
Nothing.
What do you mean it's nothing?
- Never mind. - You really smell fishy.
Ms. Oh, do you have a boyfriend?
That night,
I went to Han River...
to do some night fishing.
On the way, I saw a crying boy.
He was crying so hard.
Hyun Woo!
- He was wearing only a thin jacket. - Hyun Woo!
He was wearing shoes, but he wasn't wearing any socks.
Hyun Woo!
Yes, Sir.
Did you get any calls from the police?
I am sorry, but none yet.
You shouldn't do that.
- You will get scolded. - Really?
You should be busy preparing for your wedding.
Why do you keep calling me?
Did you ask your boyfriend about Golden Street?
It's true, isn't it?
Never mind. I am not going to ask him.
I'm sure he had his reasons.
Why do you keep denying that it's him?
David Lee is still the CEO of Golden Street.
- When I went there the other day... - Seon Hwa.
Maybe he's afraid that...
once girls find out that he's super rich...
they won't love him sincerely.
What?
I will be killing 2 birds with 1 stone if that's the case.
I will pretend I'm sincerely in love with him,
and later when I find out that he's rich, I will get rich too.
How nice would it be? Right?
Good luck with your wedding.
How can they be so selfish and think about only their interests?
This is just way over the line.
This is the Contents Department of FGC.
I called to find out when Writer Kim's contract will be over.
You have a lot of other writers.
We're asking you to release one writer early.
She's not even assigned to any project yet.
It's not that we don't want to go there.
We have an emergency here, so we're asking to delay the meeting.
Can we have a meeting, please?
I will call you back.
I appreciate the Marketing Team for helping us out.
Thanks to Director Bang, we didn't lose the airing right.
As long as we find a writer and a project,
everything will go as planned.
So don't be too disheartened.
This crisis...
might turn into a better opportunity.
As you must know, the Contents Marketing Department...
will be removed if anything goes wrong.
The general shareholders' meeting will be held soon.
That meeting will determine the fate of this department.
That's why I will never waste this last chance.
It's for all of us.
This is our last chance.
Let's make it work.
- Yes. - Okay.
Producer Kim, please distribute those.
Yes.
These are the scripts we've been collecting.
Please read them thoroughly and choose good ones.
I've collected the scripts of both experienced and new writers.
To make the selection process as fair as possible,
we have eliminated the names of the writers.
Isn't it better to go with an experienced writer's script?
It's easier for us to do business if the writer is experienced.
When we analyze the trend of successful replacement programs,
we can see that the programs reviewed as being new and...
original and received higher ratings were...
often the works of new writers.
All right. Please read them by tomorrow,
and we will talk again.
- By tomorrow? - Please do.
You're late.
- What now? - Seong Joon.
Can we talk?
Are you upset that I brought you here without asking permission?
What is it?
I felt bad for making you pay last time.
You don't have to feel bad.
What is it that you want to tell me?
I have something to ask.
I heard you were adopted when you were very little.
I was wondering if you remembered anything before you were adopted.
- Please stop. - Do you remember where you lived?
Or do you remember your father?
No.
Do you remember your brother?
- What are you doing? - Please don't be upset.
If you remember anything, please tell me.
I beg you.
Seong Joon.
Who are you?
Why are you going after me?
Seong Joon,
please calm down and listen to me.
Who are you? Why are you so interested in my family?
- Seong Joon. - I warned you.
I told you not to meddle with my family!
What is he doing?
It's Mr. Lee.
Seong Joon, what are you doing?
Leave him alone!
- Dad. - What are you doing?
Are you all right, Mr. Lee?
What's going on, Boy?
It's nothing.
- It's my fault. - Dad,
let's go home.
Let's go home.
(Scene 8, Ji Won's House)
Were you writing?
Yes.
It's cold outside. Can I come in?
Today's been a long day for me.
Please give me a warm cup of tea.
Wait here. I will go outside.
Is something wrong?
No, nothing is wrong.
Well then.
Here.
Everyone is reading these.
You should read them...
and see which one is good.
Is it okay for me to read them?
I trust your judgement.
Okay. I will read them.
It's late. You should go down now.
You should go down now. The elders are expecting you.
Dong Hui.
What's wrong with you today?
Since you brought it up...
I think it would be better if you don't come up here from now on.
- Why? - You must be tired from work.
I will write on my own from now on.
Something happened, right?
No, nothing happened. It's just...
I think I didn't think about...
your situation because I was only thinking about myself.
You must have a lot of things to do besides teaching me at night.
That's...
my favorite thing to do.
Teaching you.
But still,
please don't come here anymore.
Dong Hui.
I will give you a report tomorrow at work.
Hyun Woo!
- Sang Woo. - Hyun Woo!
Sang Woo!
Sir?
Are you all right, Sir?
You drank a lot last night.
I did.
I did drink a bit.
Did you meet Seong Joon?
I did.
You need to get a hold of yourself, especially in times like this.
How could you meet him?
I knew it was a mistake.
But I couldn't stand it. I was so anxious.
You were too hasty.
Then what do you think I should do?
I'm about to lose my mind.
He grabbed me by the collar and despises me,
and he might be my brother.
What am I supposed I do?
You should go.
I will be in here.
My goodness.
You're here.
I hope I am not intruding.
You are not.
I was about to have some coffee.
- Were you? - Yes.
Could I join you then?
- Of course. Please wait. - Okay.
I don't know why he did...
such a thing to you last night.
I hope you can be understanding and forgive him.
I asked him why he did it,
but he didn't say anything.
No, it was my fault.
It's very unlike him.
He's very kind.
He was...
so different from his brothers ever since he was young.
He is considerate and thoughtful.
He is mature too.
I feel like...
he's the oldest son.
You saw him the other day.
He didn't go out even on a holiday...
so that he could play go with his father.
When he was about eight years old,
he didn't go out...
and always hover around me.
So I taught him how to play go.
Is that so?
I could only win against him until he was 12 years old.
After that, I kept losing.
That's how smart he is.
I guess he is smart indeed.
I really like him a lot.
Parental love is...
one-sided, isn't it?
That's why...
I'd like you to give you this Korean traditional sweets and cookies.
I received it over the holidays. It's quite expensive.
It goes well with coffee.
Please don't. There's no need, Sir.
Please accept it.
This is all for my son.
He would never do anything like it.
I think he must be under a lot of stress at work.
Please forgive him this one time.
This is delicious.
Are you teasing me?
All we need to do is check the fact.
The police has to officially check just one line.
Your hard working of 23 years is about to be...
summarized into one sentence.
I know waiting can be difficult.
How about doing something else while you wait for it?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about Jeong Eun.
To you, she is just as important as Seong Joon.
What are you implying?
She's the only person...
who trusts and waits for you...
even though you're not her family.
Whether you admit or not,
I believe I am right.
Have some.
This is good.
Mom.
What's wrong with you?
Do you really have to ask?
Are you still mad at me?
Don't mind me. Just keep going where you were headed.
Mom.
Stop drinking. Please?
You told me to stay out of your life. Why are you butting in mine?
It looks like you are going on a date with that guy.
Don't be impatient. Just go.
I won't get involved in your life.
Children don't listen to their parents.
I don't want to fight with you, Mom.
Don't think you are all alone and you are lonely.
Can't we get along?
All we have in this world is each other.
Since you've been dating, it sounds like you know everything.
Fine.
Let me see how long that will last.
Love?
It's nothing.
Don't you think I was in love once?
Mom.
You.
Chang Soo started learning to be an opera singer. Did you know?
Really?
Yes.
Chang Soo is learning to be an opera singer.
It's funny.
I avoided singers all my life.
There's another man who sings in our family.
By the look of it,
I won't be able to avoid men who sing.
Does it remind you about Dad?
No, it doesn't.
Go now.
You should live your own life.
Don't worry about me.
What? Music?
Yes.
What have you been doing lately?
Chang Soo is about to be an amazing opera singer,
but you are not even interested in your own son.
You come home late all the time now.
How can you do this to me?
I didn't know...
Chang Soo had a talent for singing.
- Honey. - I'm busy too.
Do you know how much work I have?
To put it bluntly, if he wants to become an opera singer,
who's going to pay for all those lessons? Are you going to pay?
I have to pay them eventually.
Then I must go out and work. Should I just stay at home?
Honey. In times like this,
we have to separate our jobs more clearly.
You are in charge of our son's education.
I am in charge of making a lot of money...
so that we can raise Chang Soo well.
I should also expand my influence.
Mark my words. I will do my best...
so that Chang Soo can sing the...
national anthem at the President's inauguration after 10 years.
I'm going to the gym.
Honey. Where are you going?
- Honey. - Hold on.
What was that just now?
Doesn't he know that having small muscles is in trend now?
Mr. Han. Here.
Why are you so late? I was waiting for you.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you finished with exercising?
No, I'm a work out buff.
I haven't done far from enough.
I'll move to that area. Please follow me.
Okay.
You should pull it like this.
Please keep up.
You're unbelievably weak.
My goodness.
- Try it again. - Okay.
What's all this?
Can't you see them?
These are a CD, a book of opera scores, and an opera textbook.
These are autobiographies of great opera singers.
And these are English and math workbooks for Ji Hoon.
Why are you giving these to me?
You should become a good mother too.
You should thank me.
If it weren't for me,
you would have never been able to discover Chang Soo's talent.
You didn't even had time to visit your kids' schools.
- You still don't have time, right? - So what?
I will be even busier because of Chang Soo.
It's crucial to find a good instructor.
What about Professor Park you met the other day?
It's illegal to receive lessons from college professors.
I see.
It's not easy to find a good teacher.
Although I know nothing about classical music,
I will find the best teacher for Chang Soo by any means...
with the skills I've earned when I took care of Ji Hoon.
- How will you do that? - I already contacted some.
You're really amazing.
So I need you to listen to this CD...
and study opera music...
while I am away.
- Hee Sook, I... - Don't you want...
to raise Chang Soo into a great opera singer?
- Fine. - And...
you also need to take care of your own son,
not just other's son.
Tell Ji Hoon to finish these in a week and bring them to me.
- Hee Sook. - Or I won't be able...
to completely pay attention to Chang Soo.
Okay. I will.
Have him to read them thoroughly and meticulously.
Okay.
I will come late tonight.
I will find a good instructor...
in a couple of days no matter what.
- Hye Joo. - Yes?
Please make kids dinner and clean this floor.
I also need you to wash Chang Soo's clothes.
What?
I'm counting on you.
Hee Sook.
Hee Sook!
I think I can master classical music.
This isn't hard.
My jaw is dislocated.
Ji Hoon, what are you doing?
Why did you turn the fan on?
I'm just trying a new way.
Ji Hoon.
Will you really not finish these workbooks?
I'm doing this for you.
You don't have to do it.
Your former mom said...
she will get me...
if I fail to have you finish these in a week.
It's you who said I don't have to study hard.
You can't keep two tongues in one mouth.
He's driving me crazy.
Hee Sook will kill both of us...
if he doesn't finish these.
Grandma, I can do it.
- It's okay. - Let me do it. Your arm isn't well.
Gosh.
Let's eat.
Eat a lot.
Eat up and work harder.
Then, you will become a good writer soon...
and get married too.
- Grandma. - Eat up.
I came up here...
just to make you lunch.
- Okay. Thank you. - You're welcome.
Dig in. Eat a lot.
Grandma, it's really good.
Your soybean paste stew is the best ever.
Thank you.
Where is Mi Joo?
She said she'll come late.
No matter how hard she works,
the Contents Team will never be able to revive.
Excuse me,
where did you get this fermented soybean paste?
Mi Joo said one of her colleague...
gave it to her.
- Her colleague worker? - Yes.
It's beautiful.
It's awesome.
- Do you like it? - I do.
It's even more beautiful than the cabin in Quebec, Canada.
Quebec?
You exaggerated too much.
I mean it's truly amazing.
Gosh. You scared me.
Let's go.
- After you. - Thank you.
It's so pretty.
It's so wonderful to be on a trip by ourselves.
Was there anyone else when we went camping before?
I think I spent the night all alone.
You're right.
You are not going to leave me again, right?
It's a little scary since we're deep in the forest.
Don't worry. I'll be with you.
- Pardon? - I'm hungry.
Let's go eat something.
Okay.
Do you have anything you want to know about me?
Why?
Will you tell me everything then?
No. I will tell you exactly as much as you tell me.
I've never played hard to get.
I think I should change this time.
Then let's be fair to each other.
Let's answer honestly to each other's questions.
Is it like "Truth or Dare"?
You can call it if you want.
That sounds great.
When and who did you fall in love with for the first time?
Pardon?
I liked a girl in my class when I was 14.
She had brown hair and green eyes.
She had freckles on her face and British accent.
You still remember every detail.
Was there anyone else?
It's countless.
Stop showing off!
It's your turn now.
Who's your last boyfriend?
What?
You should tell the truth.
I've dated a man for three months.
I met him at a music band...
before I go on a world travel.
He dumped me.
It was a get-over travel then.
You must have liked him a lot.
You dated him for 3 months and traveled around for 3 years.
When did you feel sad the most?
When I found out I don't have a dad.
Why do you like me?
This is the most important question.
If you don't answer this,
I'll dump you this time.
Because you're attractive.
It seems that you can do many kinds of things very well.
You cook well, you handle logs well,
you make fire well,
and you listen to my song well.
I've had such a hard time...
listening to someone sing all along.
What?
The children in the orphanage...
envy those who are adopted.
They can have parents, a new house,
and a new family.
Above all, they can leave the orphanage.
I can understand.
However, the adopted children...
get to face a fierce life.
What do you mean?
They wonder...
whether they are not good enough for new parents.
whether they are shameful for new parents.
They also wonder...
whether they might be abandoned again.
I was like that too.
So I had to be the top in everything...
and I had to be...
the best in everything.
I tried my best...
not to lose favor of the foster parents.
So I got to do everything well.
It's not that I was born that way.
I had to survive.
Hyun Woo.
Anyway, I'm disappointed...
that you like me for such a reason.
In fact,
just because.
I don't have any reason.
What?
I like you with no reason.
What if I'm the worst man in the world?
I don't care.
I trust you.
And...
I can also feel...
your pain.
I sincerely hope you can find...
your brother...
that you've been looking for such a long time.
Everything will be all right.
You'll find your brother soon.
Because...
I truly wish...
you can be happier.
Why can't you open your eyes?
What if you fall down?
Never mind.
You're being childish.
I want you...
not to talk to me by the time we arrive home.
Can you?
Yes, uncle.
What?
(Seocho Police Station)
We had such a hard time finding him.
Is he the child?
Yes, he is.
It's my brother, Sang Woo.
Sir.
I'm glad that he's the one.
He was sent to a nearby orphanage according to the record.
A man who went for the fishing found him.
Sang Woo.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Just go, Hyun Woo.
You should call your brother's name at least once.
Who is Sang Woo?
He's my brother.
So, have you found your brother?
She's not a millionaire's daughter.
How are you?
Ma'am!
Who's the writer?
The writer is...
Do you think this company exists for your dating?