(Episode 24)
We had such a hard time finding him.
Is he the child?
Yes, he is.
It's my brother, Sang Woo.
Sir.
I'm glad that he's the one.
He was sent to a nearby orphanage
according to the record.
A man who went fishing found him first.
Sang Woo.
What did you just say?
Did you call me?
I think so.
What is your reason behind
your actions towards me?
Seong Joon.
What are you doing over there?
It's nothing, Father.
What were you doing?
Were you talking to someone?
No, I wasn't. Father.
- Are you throwing out the trash?
- Yes.
Let me.
Gosh, it's cold.
Let's go in, Father.
President.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
Congratulations.
Your effort of 23 years has
brought you a fruitful result.
I am not so certain.
I am not certain if this
is something to celebrate.
What do you mean?
Sang Woo...
Sang Woo is with that family.
I have to bring the family to its ruins.
Would you like to revise your plan?
No.
I won't.
No, I will never revise it.
That man destroyed our family.
He drove my father to death.
He caused me to be separated
from my brother for 23 years.
Just because he raised Sang Woo,
should I forgive that man?
However,
you might harm Sang Woo. Not just
harm, but you might destroy him.
Don't you think it's possible?
Imagine he discovers that the
father, who has raised him...
for 23 years, drove his
biological father into his death.
How will Sang Woo cope with that pain?
That was the despair I felt tonight.
I couldn't even hug my
brother even if I found him.
I couldn't tell him that I was his brother.
He still has my brother.
To him, I am just a
strange and pathetic man.
I don't know how to approach him...
and how to resolve this matter.
I am clueless.
Just think about one thing tonight.
Sang Woo grew up as a fine individual.
Don't you think so?
Yes, I think so.
He did indeed.
President.
Just think about that for tonight.
Moong Chi, let's eat.
Dong Hui already fed you breakfast.
Dong Hui.
Should we go to work?
No, I will go by myself.
I will see you at work later.
Dong Hui.
Sang Woo.
Did you call me?
I think so.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui.
- Yes?
- Can you give me a cup of coffee?
Come in.
Why do you treat me like this?
Excuse me?
You know in a drama,
a woman is angry at a man.
She doesn't tell him why she's angry.
When the guy asks her why she's mad,
instead of answering, she asks him
if he doesn't know and gets angry.
How can that guy know if
she wouldn't tell him?
Why are you asking me that?
Dong Hui, aren't you angry at me?
You seem angry, but you wouldn't tell me.
You're pushing me away again.
Aren't I correct?
- No, you are wrong.
- Am I wrong?
Yes, you are wrong.
Then, why are you so distant?
What do you mean?
You said not to visit you in the workroom.
I asked you to go to work together,
but you ran away. Even now,
you were about to leave like a stray
cat after you served me coffee.
So I am certain that you are mad at me.
Are you telling me you're not?
- What?
- Don't pick a fight in the morning.
Excuse me?
If everyone's here, let's
start the meeting.
- Where's Director Han?
- He came in a while ago.
Seong Joon.
What are you doing?
Hello, Director. I'll get going now.
You're here.
- What are you doing today?
- I'm visiting the branches.
Okay. Work hard.
Ms. Hong. Pull down the blind.
The meeting with the
shareholders is next Monday.
I reckon in that meeting,
they'll discuss whether to maintain
Contents Department or not.
Before that, we must find
Writer Jo's replacement.
Not to lose our airing time, we must
submit a groundbreaking synopsis.
Did you pick three synopses
you'd like to recommend?
- Yes.
Can you give your recommendations
first, Director Han?
I won't partake in this.
- Why is that?
- To make sure, it's chosen fairly.
I know the titles and the
names of the writers.
Okay. Why don't we start with
you first, Mr. Park Jin Sang?
- Tell us your recommendations.
- Yes.
Seong Joon went to work early.
He said he was busy with work. He
didn't even get to have breakfast.
Did he? I guess Dong Hui
went in early as well.
I told you not to bring her up when
we are talking about Seong Joon.
Why do you talk about them together?
They work at the same company.
Even if they work at the same
company, Seong Joon is a director...
and she is just a mere employee.
How can you put them in the same
group when you talk? You're his dad.
Do you think I'm devious like you?
I didn't mean anything by it.
Anyway, watch your tongue.
Whatever you say might come true.
My gosh. Where are you going?
I'm going downstairs. Seong
Hoon didn't go to work yet.
I'm just going to give him
some beef bone broth.
How about mine?
There's none.
Okay.
Goodness. My head hurts.
Gosh, my head hurts so much.
My goodness.
I think I drank too much
with the Senior Secretary.
Honey.
Honey. Get me some water.
My head.
I'm dying. Is it water with honey?
Honey. Can you get me my clothes?
I have to leave early, but
look at what I'm doing.
My gosh. I have to stop by a sauna.
Who are you?
It's me. What?
Seong Hoon?
Seong Hoon.
Why are you dressed like a wolf
in "Little Red Riding Hood"?
What? A wolf in "Little Red Riding Hood"?
Sure. I am a wolf, dressed
up as a lady. So what?
Get up. Do I need to give you water
with honey and your clothes?
Why are you flaring your nose?
Eat.
Seong Hoon, what is this?
Do you have to ask? It's leftover
fried chicken from yesterday.
But still, Seong Hoon.
Who serves leftover fried chicken
from the day before as breakfast?
Hey. Be grateful that I'm feeding you.
Our children went to school
without having breakfast.
Seong Hoon, you can't serve this.
This is ridiculous.
What are you talking about?
Where is Hye Joo?
Of course, she's at work now.
Then, what about my wife?
How on earth would I know?
What are you doing here?
- Hello, Mom.
- You're here.
What are you doing?
Well...
Mom, actually...
Mom, well...
Oh, boy.
Seong Hoon!
These are the survey papers
for the demonstration.
Summarize them and make a report.
What about the spa tickets?
Find out what happened and
make a report about it.
I will.
I got a lot of calls from your family...
when you were in the showroom.
I know, my phone kept ringing.
You can leave.
Hello, my dear mother.
How are you?
Are you joking me?
Sorry? I am not.
Why did you ignore my phone calls?
I didn't, Mother.
Don't try to fool me.
I'm sorry. I was working.
You don't need to explain. What
do you think you're doing?
Pardon? What do you mean?
Don't ask me. Just come see
what your husband is doing now!
Seong Hoon, please take this
apron and this scarf off.
Wait. I'm didn't finish the housework yet.
What?
How can you do this to my son?
Mother,
I am sorry. I was too busy this morning.
Still, you can't make him wear
an apron and a scarf like that!
- Come on.
- Stop it.
Mother,
guys also wear an apron.
Mine is worn out,
so I made him wear Hee Sook's
Doesn't he look good in it?
He looks like a doll.
What? A doll?
Are you trying to mess with me?
You're living in the same
house with me, his mother.
How can you do such a
barbaric thing to my son?
Sorry?
A barbaric thing?
I've never made him do housework...
while raising him.
That's why he's grown into...
a mother's boy.
A mother's boy? Did you just say that?
Say that again.
Well...
Actually, Hee Sook...
Speaking of Hee Sook, where is she now?
What is she up to these days?
The house is chaotic.
Right, Mom. Ask her where my wife is.
Stay out of it.
Just take these off now!
Mother,
Hee Sook is extremely busy these days.
Why? Why is she that busy?
Let's say...
she's regained the joy of life.
Please do not stop her.
Please don't look for her.
It won't be easy.
What on earth are you talking about?
This sikhye is too sweet.
- Let's drink iced coffee.
- Okay.
- I'll go get it.
- Sure.
It's all right. Please go sit down.
Hello.
Please sit down.
It's nice to meet you.
I bought a lot. Why don't
you share with me?
I saw the news that the egg price soared.
And it really did.
Please have an egg.
Please enjoy.
And this is the iced coffee...
you've wanted to have badly.
By the way, who are you?
Aren't you...
mothers of the 10th-grade
students who study vocal music...
in Seoul Munhwa Art High School?
My son also studies vocal music.
Your son is In Seok,
the winner of the recent
Inha Competition, right?
No, he's not.
My son took the third place.
Sorry?
The mother of the winner is not here.
Then,
where should I go to meet her?
Thank you for the flowers.
I'm sure you will be blessed.
Thank you so much.
By the way,
I don't think we've met before.
I'm sorry I don't recognize you.
It's all right.
It's not been long since I came to church.
I heard...
that there's a great singer
in this church's choir.
That's my youngest son.
Really?
He's the winner of Inha competition...
which is the largest one in Korea, right?
Isn't he?
No. My son got the second place.
Sorry?
The winner isn't here.
I see.
Where is he?
(3000 bows)
3000 bows...
My goodness.
Gosh.
All right. Let's draw a conclusion, then.
Let's start from Producer Kim.
Which one do you want?
I like the third one.
As the life is rough,
even I feel exhausted when I read...
complicated and serious scenarios.
I think choosing a light one
is strategically good as well.
No way. Only young people will like it.
I like the first one the most.
It's about adults' passionate love.
"Way to Incheon Port". The
title is fascinating.
What did they do on their
way to Incheon Port?
They wouldn't just stop at a
service area and have some snack.
But I don't like adultery.
I like the third one like Producer Kim.
I just feel like...
people will like it.
I like the third one, too.
I think the writer is talented.
It's very fresh.
The issue is whether it will
pass the censorship or not.
I also like the third one.
"Romance Learned through Books."
I like it.
If the quality of the script is
as good as that of the synopsis,
it will be a hit.
This is a new writing style. Director Han,
is it written by a budding writer?
Yes.
Still, the writer doesn't
seem like a complete novice.
It's good since it's not awkward
while it's fresh and unique.
Then, I'll leave the negotiation to you.
We'll go with this one.
What's the name of the writer?
Hello, I'm from the headquarters.
I'm here for the assessment.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
- Aren't you cold?
- I'm okay.
Do you want some hot tea?
Yes, please. Thank you.
Director Han, who's the writer?
Why are you silent?
Director Han.
Well,
the writer is...
Oh Dong Hui.
- What?
- Pardon?
Dong Hui?
You mean Dong Hui in our office?
Yes.
Yes, Assistant Dong Hui wrote the scenario.
Do you mean the Dong Hui...
who's visiting stores outside now?
Yes.
Are you out of mind?
This is your workplace.
This place isn't for your
romantic relationship!
- Director Bang.
- I said we should focus on work.
I said you and Dong Hui
should focus on work.
Do you have to do this...
in the same office with me?
What are you talking about?
Do you think I'm a fool?
Did you think I wouldn't
notice if you stayed silent?
Is this why you two were in
the rooftop room together?
Is this what you did there?
Do you want to make your precious
Dong Hui become a writer...
even by using such a dirty means?
What...
What did you just say?
Do you think I showed you her scenario...
because I love her?
Then, why did you do that?
Do you really think I'm such a scum?
This is my job and my career.
And the future of the staff members
is riding on this project.
And...
you think I showed you the script
just to flirt with Dong Hui?
Do you think her scenario is
good enough to be selected?
You already recognized her writing.
You said that her scenarios
is better than the rest.
Director Han!
I need you to calm down and
read the scenarios over again.
After that,
you can choose the one you like the most.
We need your approval after all.
And I won't push ahead with the
scenario you didn't approve of.
(Lee Jae Cheol)
Dad,
I found Sang Woo.
But things are bad.
What should I do with him?
Did you know about this from the beginning?
Why didn't you do anything?
Why on earth did you...
let the evil guy raise Sang Woo?
What should I do now?
Why am I the only one left
with difficult choices?
Answer me.
I didn't mean to offend you.
But I think...
family can help each other out...
better than others.
You really love your family.
I owe a lot to my family.
It will take forever...
to repay their kindness.
My family is all I have.
They matter the most to me.
Wait, why did you put your stone there?
Dad, I did to win.
Gosh, it's me who raised
you into a smart guy.
Hyun Woo!
What are you doing here?
Where have you been?
I went to the construction site
because you didn't answer the phone.
I gave some coffee and a
sandwich to the manager...
because it's really cold today.
Wait here.
Making a heart shape with this isn't easy.
Surprise! Do you like it?
I made it for you.
What is this?
Sweets are the best remedy for the blues.
Have some.
How is it? Isn't it tasty?
Did something happen?
I was worried as I couldn't reach
you after you went to the station.
Did something...
go wrong with your brother?
I found...
- my brother.
- Really?
Did you really find Sang Woo?
Yes.
That's so great. I'm happy for you.
How is he doing? Has he been well?
Where has he been? Did you meet him?
I guess...
there's something bad again.
Is my guess right?
No, it's not.
Is Sang Woo...
leading an unhappy life?
No.
He seemed very happy.
Then, go tell him that
you're his brother...
and you'd been looking for him.
Apologize to him for taking so long.
I can't.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
I don't know if it's a good idea...
to show up in front of him.
What are you talking about? You've
been waiting for that moment.
You're right.
This is the day I've been waiting for.
I overcame all the hardships...
only for this moment.
I thought I'd want nothing more...
only if I could find him.
But if I tell him that I'm his brother,
he'll be unhappy.
That doesn't make sense at all!
I really have no idea what to do.
I don't know what choice
I should make for him.
Poor Hyun Woo.
You don't need to think that way.
Please don't.
You've long yearned for him.
Please go see him.
You should meet him and call
his name at least once.
This is unexpected.
Her scenario was selected as a runner-up.
She must be good.
Well, there are good budding writers.
Don't pretend to be cool.
We cannot...
let such an amateur become a
substitute writer of our company.
I think Director Bang and
Han are having a fight.
I bet they already had a big fight.
I'm sorry for being late. There
was a problem at a store.
Writer Oh, welcome back.
You're back, Writer Oh.
What's going on?
Dong Hui, you're very canny.
- Sorry?
- Dong Hui, go to Director's office.
Okay.
("Romance Learned through Books")
What are you doing?
Get out. I need you to leave
our company right now!
Still, you can't throw things like that.
What is it again? Fine. Just tell
me the reason before I leave.
You're such a foxy witch.
You played the victim all the time
as if you were the poorest girl...
in the world. Did you think you
could hide it from me forever?
Do you think this is your playground?
I have no idea what you are talking about.
Just get to the point.
And I neither played the victim
nor hid something from you.
It's you who make me
feel as I'm the victim.
Anyway, you are fired as of today. Leave!
I am asking what the reason is. Tell me.
Explain why you treat me like this.
I know you coaxed Director Han
into selecting your script.
You're working at the rooftop of his
house, saying you're an in-law.
You even flirted with him by
asking him to help you write.
Isn't making him select
your scenario your plan?
- My scenario? - "Romance
Learned through Books".
Isn't that yours?
How do you...
(Self-statement for nomination)
"Have you bought a property..."
"with the information you learned at work?"
I barely make my both ends meet.
How can I afford a property?
"No."
Why isn't Ms. Jang calling me?
I took care of her business well.
So she should call me first and thank me.
I left her so many text messages.
The number you have dialed...
What's going on?
Is not available at this moment.
Is her family celebrating the occasion?
Gosh, Ms. Jang.
You should still answer the phone.
"Have you ever been involved in
a rumor for an immoral act..."
"including sexual harassment?"
I would never sexually harass someone.
I only dated Ms. Jang.
"No."
The number you have dialed is
not available at this moment.
Where did you go, Ms. Jang?
Why won't you pick up the phone?
Gosh.
Yes.
Where are you, Honey?
Mother yelled at me this morning,
so I came home early.
You didn't have to do that. You
should focus on your work.
I told you not to care too
much about what Mom says.
How am I supposed to do that?
Try being her daughter-in-law for 20 years.
Even 20 years isn't enough.
By the way, where are the kids?
I'm going to feed them dinner here.
Here are the new dishes.
This is spicy, so you should eat it.
Ah In, you should eat the sweet one, okay?
Okay. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You sweetie pies.
You should just take a good rest.
I should clean the house then.
All right. Bye.
Bye.
Let's eat.
Seong Hoon! Seong Hoon!
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
Did you call me?
Did I call you?
How can a restaurant owner
not pick up the phone?
Why did you call?
I was trying to order
fried chicken for dinner.
Hey,
why do I have to deliver fried
chicken to your office?
Why not? You should if
you want to earn money.
- What did you say?
- Hey,
the kids are watching.
Calm down. Okay?
Sit next to them and eat
when I say it nicely.
Okay.
Hello.
Long time no see.
Yes.
How have you been?
You're studying well, right?
- What?
- Be quiet and just eat.
All right.
I need that.
Otherwise, my hand will get dirty.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
I have to do house chores
after I come home from work.
Where on earth did Hee Sook go?
Hello.
Why are you smiling like that?
Hey, what are you doing?
What?
Did you just...
Gosh, I can't believe this.
What's up with your hair and clothes?
And what's that pretentious behavior?
My mother told me that the student
studying classical music...
must dress neatly, classy,
and behave elegantly.
Goodness.
My mother thinks about me all day,
so she bought me the
entire outfit in no time.
In the past, I used to wear
a cheap t-shirt on top,
gym shorts on the bottom, and no socks.
Now, I am wearing a dress shirt, a belt,
well-ironed trousers,
and socks that are carefully
selected to match the colors.
So?
I'm just saying.
Hey!
Why are you yelling?
You are just unbelievable.
You constantly surprise me.
You should watch and reflect on yourself.
You should reflect on yourself.
I knew you were immature,
how can you stick so closely to
your mom when I'm just downstairs?
How can you appear in front of
your former mom in this outfit...
and tell me to reflect on myself?
Is that an appropriate behavior for
someone who was once your mom?
Is it?
Also, hey,
what's the point of dressing so nicely?
You are just going to eat a lot...
and get Kimchi all over your shirt.
It's going to get covered in food.
Don't you think I know you?
I no longer...
eat too much.
What?
My mother said I should have
class to study classical music.
I have to sing, so I don't
have to lose any weight.
But she said I shouldn't
gain any more weight.
So?
I've decided to drink this
refreshing iced barley tea...
for dinner.
Then I will get going then.
Hey.
- Go inside your room fast.
- Don't upset me more.
Be patient. My mother said I shouldn't...
act rashly if I were to do classical music.
Chang Soo!
My head hurts.
My head hurts. What's wrong with my life?
Why did our children have to be switched?
I really want to move. I want to move.
It's killing me.
Hey, where are you now?
I don't think I can go
home today, Hye Sook.
Why not? Where are you?
I'm at a Buddhist temple.
Why did you go there?
I have to bow 3,000 times today.
So please take care of the kids.
Please prepare a suit for my
husband tomorrow morning.
What?
Hee Sook!
Thank you, Hee Sook.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Did you come for your son?
Yes. My son is a musician.
I am praying so that he will
do well in a competition.
I see.
My son is a musician, too.
He has to...
go on a competition, too.
I see.
Moong Chi, I feel sad. Don't bother me.
I am going to bite anyone...
who bothers me today.
So don't bother me.
Pour me a drink, will you?
Do you mind if I join you?
Let me.
I'll pour you one.
This is unexpected.
I thought you hated me.
I still don't like you very much.
I feel like you're
hovering around my family.
I still have doubts about you.
But...
I thought maybe you have
something you want to say to me.
I think...
you called me that night.
Do you think so?
Yes.
Did I hear it wrong?
No. I called you Sang Woo.
Sang Woo...
Who is Sang Woo?
He's my brother.
- Hi, Mom.
- Where are you?
- I'm at a place near our house.
- Have you had dinner?
How are you going to eat dinner?
You should tell me how you'll eat dinner,
so I can know whether I
should fix you dinner or not.
You don't have to. I'll
go and do it myself.
I made kimchi stew today.
Come and eat it before the meat gets cold.
Okay. I will. See you soon, Mom.
I'm sorry.
If you haven't had dinner
yet, you can order some food.
No. My mom says she made
kimchi stew at home.
She must've worked hard to make it.
I should go and eat it.
- I see.
- That's right.
You said your brother's
name is Sang Woo, right?
Yes.
Didn't I tell you before?
I have a brother who is around your age.
I lost him when I was seven years old.
His name is Lee Sang Woo.
He's the same age as you.
I see.
I moved to this neighborhood to find him,
and I found out...
you've been adopted.
That's why I...
I'm sorry.
I asked you a question about
a sensitive matter abruptly.
That's what happened.
I didn't know.
I'm sorry, too.
Not at all.
I've been hoping...
my whole life that Sang Woo would have...
grown into a healthy and decent
man with a loving family...
just like you.
I guess...
that's why I called you
Sang Woo without realizing.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know that was the reason
for your kindness and interest.
So,
did you find your brother?
I'm sure you will find him.
I'm also sure...
he would've grown into a
better man than I am.
- Seong Joon.
- Yes?
Are you happy with your family?
Of course.
Is there anyone who is not
happy with their family?
To me, my family is...
more valuable than my own life.
I'm sure that...
Sang Woo would be as happy as me.
Don't worry.
I think...
I lost.
What do you mean, President Lee?
I think Hyung Seop has...
defeated me.
Gosh, it hurts.
Hee Sook, what on earth...
I made...
I made 3,000 bows at the temple.
- Hee Sook. Are you okay?
- Gosh.
I think I'm going to enter nirvana soon.
You can't enter nirvana. Hold on.
My goodness.
By the way, Mother is very upset, Hee Sook.
I don't care.
Here. Look.
What's this?
(Mr. Kang)
He's the best vocal music teacher there is.
He's the best teacher in this country.
How did you get his number?
After I made 3,000 bows at the temple,
I thought I was going to die, Hye Joo.
You know I hardly make bows...
to anyone.
I do know. You're an arrogant person.
Gosh, Hye Joo.
I really...
made 3,000 bows at the temple.
- My gosh, it hurts.
- Really?
By the way, is this 6 or 8?
I think it got smudged by your sweat.
- What did you say?
- Here.
Why are you crying, Chang Soo?
Mom. Kids at school make fun of me.
Why? With what?
They say my face looks
bigger with this hair.
What? Who said that?
Who said my son's face is big?
The kids at school.
I will go and teach them a lesson.
Gosh. My son doesn't have a big face.
Don't cry.
Your face isn't big at all. My goodness.
My poor baby.
Goodness.
I should really move out of this house.
No. I must be crazy.
I guess I'm still crazy. No.
Aunt.
Yes. Hello.
Chang Soo. Come and say hello.
- Hello.
- Hi, Chang Soo.
Come and have a seat.
Here. Let's sit.
Oh, my. Hee Sook. What's wrong?
Well... It's nothing. I'm fine, Aunt.
Goodness.
Chang Soo. I heard that you
study vocal music now.
- Yes.
- My gosh.
I've never imagined that
you'd study singing.
That makes two of us.
That's right. Have you found a teacher yet?
I don't think Professor Park can teach you.
You're right. That's why...
I think I will let him teach Chang Soo.
I was wondering if you know him.
Well, he's not such a great teacher.
Wait. Why not? Among other parents,
he's considered as the best teacher.
It was so hard for me to get his number.
People like you who don't know him well...
would think that he is a great teacher.
But the way I see it,
everyone is just mediocre except for...
one man.
One man? Who is that?
He was...
the best singer I've ever known.
Oh, my. Who is it?
Just someone I know. Stop asking.
It's painful to talk about him.
Just let Mr. Kang teach Chang Soo.
"It's painful to talk about him"?
If Chang Soo is going to
work as a singer in Korea,
Mr. Kang won't be a bad teacher.
I just have high standards.
Aunt. Who is that man?
Tell me more about him.
Forget it.
Gosh, Aunt. Come on.
Who is the man you just mentioned?
Could you please tell me? Please.
Stop bothering me.
I'm listening to music. Be quiet.
Aunt. Please tell me who he is.
Hello?
Can I see you for a second?
I'm surprised that you let
me come into your workroom.
How...
could you do such thing without
discussing it with me?
- Dong Hui.
- You know better than anyone...
that I've worked so hard to write...
each and every word of it.
How could you do such a thing?
Why did you use my script
without asking me first?
Why did you sell my baby
without my approval?
How is it...
just your baby?
I also helped that script grow.
Even so,
you didn't have to do that.
Now people say I'm debuting because
of you, not because of my work.
Are you complaining about it?
I chose good synopses among...
the ones I had, and gave
them out to the team.
We took a vote, and your work was chosen.
I never forced anyone to pick yours.
I'm asking why you included
mine along with those...
great synopses.
They picked yours without
realizing that it's yours.
If they had known, they
wouldn't have picked it.
They know they shouldn't.
What did you say?
Why are you so insecure
about your own work?
You call it your baby. How could
you have such little trust in it?
- Look.
- Also,
who says I helped you make your debut?
Does that mean I helped
you debut because...
I want to get on the right side of you?
Why would I?
Why do I have to try to be in your favor?
What did you say?
This is so insulting.
What do you all take me for?
I'm confident that I'm
a competent producer.
Even if they give me 100 beautiful
actresses like Scarlett Johansson,
I would never trade it...
with one great script.
- Do you get it?
- My gosh.
Anyhow, I will never do it.
I wanted to let you know.
Forget it, then.
You're kicking away your own fortune.
A great opportunity comes
along, but you don't take it.
Suit yourself, then.
Hey!
Did you just yell at me?
Yes, I did. What are you going to do?
My gosh. Hey!
What?
Aren't you going to eat lunch?
I'm just going to take a rest.
Are you getting ready for the
stockholders' meeting tomorrow?
Please get out.
Lunch is ready, Sir.
Gosh. It's bean paste stew again.
I like bean paste stew very much.
How long have you been
working in our house?
It's been five years.
It hasn't been that long.
We once had a housekeeper who
worked here for 20 years.
She made...
such delicious bean paste stew.
President Bang.
Yes.
So, how did it go?
Is that so?
I said I'll fold it for you.
Just eat your tangerines.
I'll fold my own laundry.
I know that you're bothered
that I'm living off you.
I can imagine what you're going to say...
if I ask you to fold my laundry.
Why would I hear that?
Is it because of what my
daughter-in-law said the other day?
Forget about what she said.
She didn't mean it in a bad way.
She was just worried that
Dong Hui should marry...
That's my point.
Why would your family worry about...
whom my granddaughter will marry?
They're not just my family.
You shouldn't say that.
We've been living in the
same roof for months now.
People don't even treat
their dog so coldheartedly.
Are you likening Dong Hui to a dog now?
Like your dog, Moong Chi?
Why do you always get upset whenever...
we talk about Dong Hui?
My goodness. I don't understand.
Forget it. Forget I said anything.
By the way, you said Dong Hui was...
the granddaughter of your brother, right?
His son and son's wife suddenly died...
in an accident.
You said that's why you
started to raise Dong Hui.
Why are you so interested in Dong Hui?
What do you want to know
about my dear Dong Hui?
Why are you getting so angry?
I just thought maybe I can
fix her up with someone.
If you want to fix someone up,
you should fix up your
60-year-old daughter.
What did you say?
Are you attacking my weak spot?
I'm only saying this because you keep...
talking about Dong Hui.
We have a man and a woman who
are at a marriageable age.
Isn't it natural that...
we talk about their marriage?
Dong Hui isn't...
someone I can give away to
anybody just because...
she's old enough to marry.
You shouldn't...
treat her this way just because
she doesn't have parents.
It's not like she's from
a rich family. Gosh.
Whether you have parents or not,
you marry someone eventually.
Why do you think Dong Hui is so special?
How ridiculous.
Anyhow, don't speak inappropriately
just because we live together.
My goodness. Why don't you stop
being inappropriate first?
Excuse me? What are you talking about?
Why am I being appropriate?
Did you think I wouldn't know?
You're seeing a man.
What?
It's true.
Do you think I don't know about it?
Gosh, every night,
you hide and talk to a guy.
You are so secretive about it...
that you won't even introduce his
friend to your lonely friend.
You enjoy it alone.
I shared everything with you,
no matter how small it is.
Do you know that?
What did you say?
They say sorrow reduces to half and
joy doubles when you share it.
I still can't get my head around...
about why men find you so charming.
You always say you won't marry off
your daughter-in-law to anyone,
and you lock her in a
room in her prime time.
Yet you always talk on the
phone with your boyfriend.
I wouldn't care if you worked
at a building as a cleaner...
or if you went to a skating link...
and broke your arm.
What did you say? How dare you?
- Gosh, I am so upset.
- Goodness, Mother.
Why didn't you invite me to lunch?
- Goodness.
- Did you not eat yet?
- Have a seat, Mother.
- Nobody gave me food.
Have a seat, Mother, I
will serve it to you.
Why didn't you have lunch with Gui Boon?
Don't even mention her to me.
I really don't like her.
Did something happen?
I offered to match her granddaughter,
and she yelled at me saying
that her granddaughter...
won't marry just anyone.
- What?
- Is that true?
It is. Does she think her
granddaughter is precious,
and my grandson is not?
Is that what she thinks?
I hate old people who think their
grandchild is the most precious.
I really think that way of
thinking should be eradicated.
Didn't you say that Dong Hui had
a rather unfortunate childhood?
I think that's what I heard.
I heard she's the child of...
Gui Boon's brother's son.
The family got into an accident,
and only Dong Hui survived.
That's why Gui Boon raised her.
Goodness, did that really happen?
Yes. That's why Gui Boon
is overprotecting her.
She thinks her granddaughter
is the most precious one.
I hate her so much.
Calm down and have some sujebi.
Dong Hui's born with a
life fitting for a writer.
Her life is full of stories.
- Stop it.
- What?
- Hello, Madam.
- Goodness.
Mom!
Mom, it's me, Bang Jin.
It's been such a long time.
You look the same, Mom.
Sir.
It's ready.
Sir?
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Sir, it's Jeong Eun. What should I do?
Let's just go.
Hyun Woo.
Are you home, Hyun Woo?
Where did he go? He's not
picking up his phone, either.
(Han Jeong Eun)
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Hyeon Jung?
It's the late Gwang Ho's daughter.
- Hello.
- How dare you come here?
- Is Seong Joon well?
How much did it drop?
I don't think I can get
away from Mom, Uncle.
I was truthful.
I treated you sincerely.