(Episode 25)
Sir.
Sir, it's Jeong Eun. What should I do?
Let's just go.
Hyun Woo.
Are you home, Hyun Woo?
Where did he go? He's not picking up his phone, either.
(Han Jeong Eun)
I bet she repented of her wrongdoing while I was gone.
She always takes her granddaughter's side.
Just because I rely on her out of loneliness,
she mistreats me.
Ms. Oh.
Did you have lunch?
I had sujebi for lunch downstairs.
Where did she go?
Hold on.
Hey, Gui Boon has disappeared.
Excuse me?
Gui Boon has disappeared.
I don't think she's disappeared.
I'm sure she stepped out for a moment.
What do you mean? Where would she go with that injured arm? She said...
she won't go out due to the icy road and until her arm's healed.
She's not even answering her phone.
A woman keeps telling me she's unavailable to pick up the phone.
Please wait a bit.
You just said that you didn't like her and yet,
you look for her when she's gone for a minute.
You'll see when you are my age,
the person sleeping next to me, keeping me warm is the best...
instead of my own children.
Hold on.
Is it because we mentioned Dong Hui was at an age to get married?
Could it be that we hurt her ego talking about it?
Could she have run away from us?
I don't think so, Mother.
What do you mean? We didn't hurt her ego.
Please come in. Come in.
Please sit down. The house won't collapse.
How is it? Doesn't it look just the same?
Why don't you take a look around?
Why did you bring me inside? You didn't have to.
Mom, that hurts my feelings.
Why do you act so distant?
You left as soon as I was accepted into a university.
So how long has it been?
It's been 30 years.
When you left like that,
didn't you miss us?
Why wouldn't I miss you?
Your mother was very good to me.
Then, how come...
you didn't...
contact us for all those years?
My son and his wife died in an accident.
That's why I quit my job here.
They had two children.
Taking care of his children after my son had passed away,
took all of my time.
My gosh. You suffered a lot.
Why didn't you call my mother...
to ask for help?
After that time, I've never...
met with the president.
Is that true?
Of course, it is.
- Dad. - Hey.
You have a guest.
Yes, I do.
Come and say hello.
She's like a mother to me.
Hi.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
She will follow in my footsteps.
Is that so?
Excuse me, but who is she?
I'm not sure.
I just heard that she used to work here before.
Before?
Since we met, let me ask you.
Why don't you come and work here again?
I'm too old to be a cook.
My food doesn't taste the same anymore.
Why would you say that?
Your bean paste tastes the same.
What do you mean by that?
Your granddaughter, Oh Dong Hui.
What...
about Dong Hui?
She works at my company.
You didn't know?
Mom.
Have you...
really never met up...
with my mom? Not even once?
Have you really...
never met my mom...
over the last 30 years?
You haven't met her at all?
I said I haven't.
What do you want from me?
Then, do you know where Hyun Jung is?
Hyun Jung?
Who is that?
The late Gwang Ho's daughter.
You know he had a daughter just like me.
Really? He had a daughter?
I can't believe you didn't know about it.
Both you and President...
had more affection toward Gwang Ho than me.
What are you talking about? That's not true.
Is it really not true?
Stop such nonsense.
Don't pretend you know nothing.
You and President cherished Gwang Ho only.
And it really saddened me.
Do you really not know who Hyun Jung is?
I don't. I haven't heard of such name.
Mom,
please take care.
I will visit you more often.
I hope you get better soon.
Take the medicine every day. I'll send you another box later.
- Elizabeth. - You scared me.
Where have you been all day long?
Who are those guys?
Why did they take you home?
Did you have a date today?
Don't talk nonsense.
Take this medicine and go home.
Gosh. Elizabeth!
Elizabeth!
Grandma.
We need to talk.
You went outside today?
What's the name of the company you're working for?
It's FGC. Why?
FGC?
It's not Hwashin Group?
Hwashin Group?
They changed the name more than 15 years ago.
What?
It changed its name from Hwashin to FGC.
Grandma, what is this about?
It's nothing.
Please tell me.
I need you to leave the company right away.
- Why? - You...
Do you know that Jeong Ae is worried...
because you spend too much time...
with Seong Joon?
I do.
You should've behaved yourself not to cause such worry.
I can't hold my head up because of you.
I am sorry.
Quit your job immediately.
- Still... - And...
- we will move out soon. - Sorry?
It's all decided. Do not go to work from tomorrow.
Okay?
Are you really not going to work?
- No. - Dong Hui.
Right.
Please take this.
What is this?
It's a resignation letter.
Dong Hui.
I guess this is a good thing about living in the same house.
If you are done talking, leave. This is my workplace from today.
Is this really necessary?
It is. I won't work for the company any longer.
Why? Is it because of the rumor that I helped you secretly?
That's right. There's more.
I can no longer work with a thief who stole my scenario...
and the mean Eliza who trapped herself in her own imagination.
It's you who gave me the scenario for proofreading.
Stop calling me a thief.
And who's Eliza?
Haven't you read the classical romance novel "Candy Candy"?
An obnoxious girl with curly hair...
harasses Candy in the novel.
That's Eliza. She's exactly like Director Bang. Okay?
I guess Director Bang said something to you.
- What did she say? - Forget it.
Dong Hui.
Please leave. I no longer work for that company.
Fine. I don't want to work...
with someone who writes scenarios on the side.
- What did you say? - However,
(Letter of resignation)
I need you to hand this in yourself.
I don't think it's something you can submit by proxy.
Moong Chi, stay quiet.
Moong Chi, I said be quiet.
Or I won't feed you today.
Chang Soo, you have a great voice.
But I want you to lower your phren and open your throat wider...
as I taught you.
- Okay. - This part of face...
is called Maschera in Italian.
Imagine that your voice is coming from your front head...
instead of from your throat...
and try again.
Okay.
Hello.
Is it Ji Hoon's mom? How are you?
Oh, it's you.
How have you been?
I called you because of Ji Hoon.
Did something happen to him?
Well...
Is there a problem?
His grades dropped sharply.
So I thought something happened to him during the vacation.
Relax and make a sound from your front head.
How many points has it dropped?
Let's do it again.
Pardon?
Ji Hoon! Ji Hoon!
Ji Hoon!
This is unbelievable.
What? He ranked 10th in the school?
10th?
I'm trying to raise Chang Soo into the best artist.
How can she make Ji Hoon...
become the 10th student?
This is ridiculous.
I won't let it slide this time.
Why is it here?
This isn't Ji Hoon's handwriting.
My goodness.
Did Hye Joo do this for him?
Gosh. No way.
This is crazy.
What is that?
What is this? Oh, boy. What's all this?
What on earth is this?
Han Ji Hoon.
What's happening to you?
Mom.
What on earth are you doing?
Let's eat something delicious for dinner.
Why aren't you saying anything?
What have you been doing?
What's going on?
You should hurry to the basement.
- Ah In. - Why can't you answer me?
Why?
Ah In, stay with Chang Soo for a while, okay?
Ji Hoon.
Are you really not going to answer me?
You're not my mom now.
Do you still think that I'm going to be hurt by that?
It doesn't affect me at all now.
I've decided not to care whether or not...
you are my biological son.
Once a Marine, always a Marine.
Once a son, always a son.
That will be my life motto from now on.
Hee Sook.
You should kneel down beside Ji Hoon, too.
Me?
Why me? What did I do?
I told you to make him study.
And you are studying for him.
When did you see that?
Hye Joo,
don't you think you've gone a little too far?
I'm working hard day and night to make Chang Soo...
a world-famous vocalist.
I even bowed 3,000 times at a Buddhist temple!
And you are...
studying for Ji Hoon.
How can it be so unfair?
She did that only because I didn't want to do it.
So why wouldn't you study?
I don't want to study.
You lost your mind when your mom changed.
Hey.
Why do you care?
Why are you doing this to my son?
Be quiet!
Also,
that.
What is that switch?
Don't touch that.
What on earth...
is...
happening in this basement?
His class rank dropped to the 10th.
And you are studying his book.
I came down to the basement after a while,
and I found that thing.
So what can that be?
That's...
the magic device I created.
What?
Magic?
Yes!
What's wrong with this?
What's wrong with it?
I will...
become a magician instead of going to college.
Stop, Ji Hoon.
What?
A magician?
It should turn off. I think it's broken.
Hyun Woo.
Sang Woo.
Seong Joon.
Let's go in, Dad.
Sir. Sir?
Yes.
What are you thinking about?
It's nothing.
By any chance, are you regretting it?
No.
I'm not regretting it.
It's already been decided.
I won't regret it.
You are so determined,
and that worries me even more.
You left the house...
even without the final check.
If it has to be broken off,
it's better to break it off firmly.
I can't even come forward as his brother.
It's hard to just look at Sang Woo...
when he's right in front of me.
I will stay here until I leave.
I brought the investment proposal.
Please take a look.
Thank you.
Then...
what do you plan to do...
with Jeong Eun?
Welcome.
What are you doing?
What is it? What are you doing?
You are bad.
You are so bad, Hyun Woo.
About that rubbish romance dictionary you're reading...
What about it?
It talks about what it means when a man suddenly disappears.
It said there's a type of man who suddenly disappears...
without even saying goodbye when he gets tired of you...
and when he's done with his business.
You fit right into that type.
Did you think I disappeared?
Didn't you?
I am sorry.
Something came up.
Was it related to your brother?
Yes.
Did you meet your brother?
What happened? Did you tell him that you're his brother?
What is it?
Was there anything else...
in the book that you wanted to do?
What?
We will take these.
No.
They are not engagement rings, so these will be good enough.
We will take these.
No.
I will put it on you.
I'm okay.
Stay still.
I can't wear it alone.
It looks lovely on you!
It's beautiful.
It looks good on you.
Time flies, doesn't it?
It feels like it was only yesterday that you confessed...
you were David Lee of Golden Street here, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
A lot of things have happened between us.
Don't you think so?
Even on that day, a lot of things happened.
You got completely drunk...
- and slept on my sofa. - Stop it.
You said I shouldn't ask you about the past.
From now on, don't drink too much.
Don't just sleep anywhere.
Okay, I won't.
Actually,
I'm going to stop drinking.
This is nice.
Today is the last day I will drink. Starting tomorrow, I won't.
Go home even if you have a fight with your mother.
Listen to your mother even though you might not want to.
It's all for your own good.
I'm aware of it, too.
Gosh, you are acting strange today.
Why are you nagging me like an old grandpa?
And stop getting hauled into the police station.
Until when are you going to visit the lockup?
Don't follow strangers.
Even when I first brought you here, you got into my car without asking.
What if I were a bad person? What would've happened to you?
Hyun Woo.
What's wrong? What's going on?
You sound like you're going somewhere.
Why are you talking like that?
I am...
going back to New York.
What?
I've found Sang Woo.
I took care of businesses in Seoul, too.
This can't be.
You should live with your brother.
My brother...
should live as he's been living so far.
I think it's better for him that way.
So I should...
return to my place.
Then, what about me?
What about us?
What happens to us?
What about me? Did I mean anything to you?
To be honest,
I lied to you.
I am still the president of Golden Street.
So I can no longer stay in Korea.
Did you already know?
Does it matter?
It didn't matter for me if you were the president of Golden Street...
or a manager at a construction site from the start.
I'm sorry.
Are you...
breaking up with me...
today?
You can just say you will be gone for a while...
because you have your company and your stepparents.
It only makes sense that you will be gone for a while,
but...
why do you sound like you will never be back?
Why do you sound like you're breaking up with me?
I can't stand to watch that man...
taking care of Sang Woo...
while he drove my father to death.
Why aren't you saying anything?
Why are you acting like this?
When are you leaving?
I will leave as soon as...
I finish my business here in Korea.
Will you come back?
- Jeong Eun. - Let go of me.
Are you kidding me?
Were you playing with me?
What is this, then?
What is this?
How can you leave me like this even if you were playing with me?
I understand I can be loud and a handful,
but I meant everything.
I took you seriously.
- I know that. - Yet, this is how you treat me?
Hyun Woo.
I am so disappointed in you.
You are such a bad guy.
Don't ever show your face again.
I am going to curse the fact that...
I liked you for the rest of my life.
Hey. What's wrong?
What happened?
Goodness.
Hello.
Okay. I am going to hand in...
my resignation letter myself.
Writer Oh. You're here.
What's wrong with you?
You come to work later than the president now that you are a writer?
You even took a day off yesterday.
My gosh. You're all grown up.
It's not what you think. I had a personal issue.
Dong Hui. Or should I call you Writer Oh now?
- It feels so weird. - Excuse me?
Don't pretend you're clueless. Tell us you're happy if you are.
My gosh. Shouldn't you switch your seat with her, Ms. Hong?
Don't mind me. I'm fine.
- Ms. Hong. The truth is... - Dong Hui, I don't know...
if you got promoted to a writer in Contents Department,
but you didn't get promoted in our Marketing Department.
Let's clearly divide our task.
Assistant Dong Hui.
You're selected to help in the stockholders' meeting.
- Go and work hard. - Mr. Park.
The reason I cam here today is because of this.
The meeting is about to start. Wasn't she supposed to go and help?
I was about to send her.
Then, why don't we start our meeting?
Director.
I almost forgot.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui.
Submit a storyline for the concept of this season's new products.
- Excuse me? - Why don't you all come in now?
- Okay. - Okay.
Dong Hui, what are you doing? Go and help out in the meeting.
(The 1st Stockholders' Meeting of 2017)
Why didn't we pull out our business in the contents industry?
Just because they got the airing time, doesn't mean it will be a hit.
It's been three years.
Isn't it matter of Director Han Seong Joon's competence?
How can it succeed in only three years?
We've already invested in the business.
Shouldn't we observe for two more years?
Don't you think, Director Bang?
I think so as well. Businesses we had in China for last three years...
will start to show results, starting this year.
We already acquired the airing time in Korea. If we stop now,
we won't be able to retrieve our investments on the contrary.
It implies that we will suffer great losses.
Let me be clear. Starting the first half of this year,
our contents businesses will make profits.
I heard your contract with Writer Jo Jeong Sook has been nullified.
Yes, that's true.
- However, - Even with her, it won't be easy.
Do you plan to increase its risk by replacing her with another writer?
Do you even have a synopsis to replace hers?
Do you have a writer who will take her position?
We've already finished choosing a synopsis to replace hers.
There's no need to worry.
- We will sign the contract soon. - Is that true?
Will it go off without a hitch?
Yes.
I'm sorry to you all, but I'm afraid...
I have to excuse myself to take care of an urgent matter.
All right. You can go.
Is there a problem in the contents team again?
Contents team is the one causing all kinds of trouble.
President Bang.
Director Han. I just need your signature here.
Okay.
Excuse us, Producer Kim.
Sure.
You even play dirty tricks now.
What are you talking about?
I got a call from Director Park.
How could you send him Dong Hui's synopsis...
without telling me?
What? Did you say I sent him her synopsis?
Do you want to push ahead without my approval now?
What are you talking about? You're my boss.
I clearly said that I would follow your orders.
Then why did you send Dong Hui's synopsis to Director Park?
Well...
What are you still doing here, Producer Kim?
Director Bang.
Director Park kept asking me when we would send him the synopsis,
so I...
I sent it to him. I thought you had already discussed it.
What did you say?
- What? - I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Why did you do that when it hasn't even been confirmed yet?
I'm very sorry.
We can't...
leave the chairwoman as a missing person forever.
What else can we do?
We don't even know if she's alive or dead.
Do you want me to report her as a dead person?
We can't wait around forever...
to see what her will says.
Wait.
Are you saying I should report...
my own mother...
as a dead person just to see her will?
Is that it?
You're such coldhearted people. I can't believe you.
It's been 20 years,
but I'm sure that my mother, Chairwoman Park,
has not died yet.
I have firmly believed it...
ever since the day she disappeared. Okay?
I'm sure...
my mother is still alive somewhere.
Mother!
All right. We've already agreed that...
we would wait until he is ready to do it.
Even so,
he didn't seem to be reluctant to report the death of...
Bang Hyun Jeong, the former largest shareholder.
Why do you keep putting off...
the report of the chairwoman's death?
Reveal her will as soon as possible.
Is it even true...
that Bang Hyun Jeong is dead?
My goodness.
Tell us the truth!
Where is Bang Hyun Jeong right now?
Gosh, those persistent people.
The stockholders' meeting is over. They'll be quiet for a while.
All right.
Did you find out about the thing I asked before?
Like Ms. Oh said, her son and his wife died.
She has been raising their children ever since.
How is she related to Oh Dong Hui, then?
Dong Hui is Ms. Oh's brother's granddaughter.
What?
Her brother was raising Dong Hui by himself, but died.
Ms. Oh took Dong Hui and started...
to raise her, too.
Is that so?
Chairwoman Park...
wouldn't have left her precious granddaughter...
to such a lousy family.
Those two senile women...
won't stop giving us trouble.
It's the scent of herbal tonic.
It smells fantastic.
My goodness. She received it from some guy...
and tried to drink it by herself.
She is actually quite good at getting men.
Let's see. Shall I drink one more pack?
Yes.
I'd like to work as a live-in housekeeper.
As long as you could provide me...
a room where I can stay with my granddaughter,
I'm fine with receiving less salary.
Yes. I see.
Ms. Oh.
All right, then. Goodbye.
You always stay in this room.
I was talking to someone on the phone. Don't you ever knock?
Stop having secret phone calls, then.
I didn't have secret phone calls.
Didn't you?
My goodness.
Where do you think you're going?
Dear me. What are you doing?
Tell me the truth.
About what?
Who is that man?
Who is the man who dropped you off yesterday?
I'm talking about the man with gray hair who looks...
not so handsome, but rich. Who is he?
Who is the man that got you these herbal tonics?
It's none of your business.
Are you dating that man?
Excuse me? What did you say?
I guess I hit the nail on the head.
Ms. Oh came back home right away.
Mother is so unbelievable.
Every little thing makes her worried now because she's old.
Why would she be worried?
Her children are right here protecting her.
It's not the same thing.
Why not?
She just picked on me because she thought...
Ms. Oh had gone missing.
Anyway, you should watch your words when you're living with elders.
Gosh.
You never know how your words might hurt their feelings.
People say that...
everything upsets you when you get old.
I'm old, too. I get upset, too.
I'm upset because Mother picks on me...
at every chance she gets.
My gosh. Stop. That's enough.
I think Mom and Ms. Oh will be okay now.
You're no help.
What?
A magician? Really?
That's right.
I can't believe this.
What?
Dad.
Yes, my dear Ah In.
- And? - Look at that.
She made a big fuss before you came.
Seong Hoon. I think I might do something to Hee Sook soon.
Please stop me.
Dad. Aunt bought me...
a workbook, too. It's this one here.
(Chinese Characters for Children)
Where is Ji Hoon?
He ran outside crying.
What?
Seong Hoon!
Seong Hoon.
How could you do this, Seong Hoon?
What?
How can you be willing to let Ji Hoon become a magician...
without sending him to college? How could you do this?
That's what he wants.
You can't let kids do whatever they want.
What's a parent's job?
It's to guide your children, so they won't take the wrong path.
Listen, Seong Hoon and Hye Joo. Do you still...
not see Ji Hoon as your own son?
Seong Sik.
Seong Sik!
We're working so hard to properly...
raise Chang Soo.
You're being lousy parents to Ji Hoon.
I can't have this!
Lousy parents?
Are you done talking?
No.
We're not done talking yet.
You'd better go back upstairs now.
I didn't want to say this,
but I'm afraid...
I'll have to raise both Chang Soo and Ji Hoon.
- Excuse me? - What?
I don't think...
you have what it takes to raise children at all.
You're so busy with your own business that you're not...
interested in their education at all.
Hee Sook. It's not that we're not interested.
Children these days are different from us.
We didn't need to study much to go to college.
But now, kids can't even dream about going to college...
without their parents' support.
Being the graduates...
of good colleges yourselves isn't enough.
You have to do your best to educate our children,
so they won't have to live...
in a basement like this in the future at least.
Hey. Hee Sook.
I can't take this anymore.
That's right. We live in a basement. What are you going to do about it?
It's even a basement in my parents-in-law's house. So what?
We're still not the parents our children are ashamed of.
We don't do bad things, embezzle money,
or prey on the weak to get our children better things.
Isn't that enough?
Ask children...
if they want kind and righteous parents...
or wealthy parents who can fully support them.
- What? - Children don't want...
to lead the same life as their parents.
They want a better life.
They want more decent life than that of parents.
Then, education is the only solution...
in this country.
We should make...
our kids go to better college than other kids.
She's right. That's how we raise our kid.
I can no longer stand...
this situation.
I will take care of the education of the children from now.
I need you to work and make money.
Sorry?
Let me take care of Chang Soo and Ji Hoon.
And I want Ah In as well.
She plays too much.
Mom, Dad!
Ah In, did you study Chinese letters...
with the book...
I bought for you?
Do I have to give some scolding to you?
- It's okay. - It's all right.
I failed to submit the resignation letter in the end.
But I'll make sure to hand it in tomorrow.
Do you want to leave the company that badly?
When did you get here?
I just got here.
I was watching you...
staring at the letter pathetically.
- Director. - I'll get straight to the point.
It won't take long.
What is it you really want to do?
Number one.
Working like a slave in the FGC Content Marketing team...
for 16 years and 8 months.
Wait, three months have passed.
So it's 16 years and 5 months.
Number two. Working as an assistant in the FGC Content Marketing team...
and dream of becoming a writer someday...
only to grow old.
- What? - Number three.
After quitting FGC Group,
you spend the rest of your life with 200,000 dollars of debt...
as an incompetent writer...
who lacks endurance.
- Excuse me. - Number four.
Working hard as an official writer of the FGC Content Marketing team...
and becoming a renowned writer with your efforts.
- What is this for? - I am serious.
I need you to face the reality.
It has just begun,
and you've got a long way to go.
Your scenario ended up...
in a broadcasting station before I knew it.
- Sorry? - They found it very interesting.
You're the only one...
who doesn't recognize the value of your scenario.
How did it...
Please sleep on it and make the right choice for yourself.
You can submit your resignation letter whenever you want,
but such opportunity would be rare.
You'll choose to face the reality...
or to run away only to keep your pride.
It's all up to you.
I'll leave, then.
Right.
I also read "Candy Candy".
But I like neither Candy nor Eliza.
- Sorry? - Both of them aren't my type.
Well... Wait.
Did your parents die?
How can you cry in your bed for such a long time?
Mom, please leave me alone.
Please leave!
Why are you crying for such things like I did when I was young?
Let him go if he wants to. And do not wait for him.
Because men who walk away never come back.
If you're crying like this when I get home from work,
you will be as good as dead. Okay?
Do it again. Lower your phren and open up your throat.
Let's start over.
Sir.
- I'm exhausted. - Come on. Tighten your stomach. Go.
Why do kids always break their parents' hearts?
This is...
No way. This can't be him.
That arrogant and cantankerous guy...
will never sing Korean songs.
He's such a sassy jerk who sings arias only.
If he turns up in front of me,
I'll rip him to pieces.
I'm hearing things now because I'm so stressed out...
about Jeong Eun.
Let's calm down.
Goodness, that was fantastic.
I can't believe you still have such a great voice.
My voice isn't as young as before.
Please don't say that. You're the world-renowned baritone.
The world-renowned baritone?
By the way, do you plan to live in Korea?
I haven't decided yet, but I think I will.
I traveled around the world...
and sang too many foreign songs.
Now I want to sing...
Korean folk songs with Korean lyrics.
It's also about time that I repaid what I owe to my country.
And...
I will release a cross-over album soon.
That's one of the reason of my return.
I'm so happy for you.
We haven't met for too long, right?
Right.
- It's been about 30 years. - I know.
Do you remember that you, I, and Ae Ri...
spent a lot of time together when we were in college?
Gosh. I am sorry.
Professor Son,
- has Ae Ri been well? - Yes.
(Professor Han Ae Ri)
Did they really make these for human?
Whatever. Let me wipe my hands.
- Ma'am, can I have ramyeon? - Yes.
Please add an egg. Please cook it nicely.
All right.
It's so delicious.
Thank you.
Gosh, I didn't know cabbage was so delicious.
I'm so glad I came here to eat.
It's so good.
Ae Ri!
Who are they?
They're from a global investment company.
It's the best one in the industry. It has great financial status...
and credibility.
Why would they...
want to make investments in our team, then?
We haven't decided which show we're going to produce,
and everything is still uncertain.
Why do they want to invest such a large sum of money in us?
I don't understand.
You're the reason.
- What? - They're investing...
their money in you, Seong Joon.
Sure.
There he is. That's Director Han.
Hello.
I'm Han Seong Joon, the director of Contents Marketing team.
Gosh, Director Han. You should introduce yourself more properly.
He is David Lee, the president of the global investment company,
Golden Street.
Nice to meet you.
You've made a wonderful decision.
Contents business will be the most profitable business in the future.
You're right.
That's why my company is making this investment.
I suppose you've already learned it through your analysis,
but Director Han is...
one of the most recognized producer in the industry.
I already know.
I also know that you've been having difficulties...
producing a new drama series.
Yes. That's right.
By investment, do you mean...
you want to invest in our new drama series?
Yes.
I want to invest in the drama series...
you're planning to produce.
The writer we hired was signed with another company,
so our contract has been nullified.
That means...
we haven't selected a writer,
or a scenario yet.
Yes.
I'm aware of that, too.
May I ask...
why you want to make an investment despite all that?
Director Han.
I've watched you for a long time. I trust my instinct...
and your ability.
Excuse me?
This is my principle.
70 percent of my decision is based on data,
and the other 30 percent...
is based on my instinct.
My goodness.
No wonder you're a president of a global company.
You're very magnanimous.
I'm sure you must've looked into our company already,
so I won't explain further.
Our branch in Korea will handle the contract...
and other details.
I see.
I think I should get going now.
All right. Sure.
Come on.
I'll be at the head office overseeing the process.
Okay.
Golden Street...
believes in your ability, Director Han.
That's why we decided to make an investment.
I hope...
your new drama series will be a success.
Hello?
What happened?
I'm sorry.
I found it out when I was reviewing the documents.
We had two boys here that day.
They were around the same age.
What?
The report says that both of them didn't know their names or ages.
They both stayed here for two days,
and they were sent to that orphanage.
One of them ran away from the orphanage.
May I see his picture again?
This boy...
died.
These are pictures of the articles he left behind...
after the accident.
It looks exactly the same.
Hi, Hyung Seop.
- It's nice to see you. - What are you doing?
How dare you come here?
What's wrong? Why can't I come here?
Is Seong Joon well?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
You are Seong Joon.
I can't recognize you.
Don't you know who I am?
Don't be afraid. I'm here for you.
Is madam even alive?
Who is the woman you met...
in the afternoon?
Does it have to be Dong Hui? Can't you give up?
Sir? Sir!