BioskopKeren
(Episode 26)
- What happened? - I'm sorry.
I found it out when I was reviewing the documents.
We had two boys here that day. They were around the same age.
What?
The report says both of them didn't know their names or ages.
They both stayed here for two days.
They were sent to that orphanage.
One of them ran away from that orphanage.
May I see the picture again?
This boy...
died.
These are the pictures of the articles he left behind...
after the accident.
President. Wake up. President!
President. Please hold yourself together.
How are you, Sir?
I think...
I should visit that orphanage one more time.
I think you might be better off resting.
Wait. Sir?
You are right.
We had one more boy.
According to the record,
two boys were sent here from Seocho Police Station,
and one of them was adopted by someone.
Then where is the one...
who remained here?
(Adoption records)
He left the orphanage a day after he was sent here.
And Seocho Police Station reported...
us about his death.
After he left the orphanage,
he was heading to the downtown.
This is the road...
where he got hit by a dump truck that was running from there.
I heard that he died on the spot.
After the funeral,
his ashes had been kept at a charnel house...
in a nearby park for 10 years.
However,
the ashes were scattered in the national cemetery.
I am really sorry,
Sir.
I came too late...
for Sang Woo.
You did everything you could do.
I guess he's with my father now.
I had no idea what happened to him,
and slept and ate well.
I led a comfortable life alone.
You have never felt at ease even for a day.
I'm the only one who has been alive...
and breathing...
for the last 23 years.
My whole life is in vain.
Do you remember anything that happened before you were adopted?
Do you remember the town you lived or who your father is?
Or...
anything about your brother?
Who are you?
Why did you dig up my past?
Sang Woo.
We believe in your ability, Director Han.
I hope...
your new drama series will be a success.
Please slow down.
Hurry up.
What was that?
You've become much wilder.
Hyung Seop.
I mean...
Mr. Han, you grew old a lot.
Are you out of mind?
How dare you come here?
I came to see how my youngest son...
is doing.
Why did you come back?
Do you want to destroy my family?
Don't yell at me.
I also have the right to meet Seong Joon.
What?
What do you want from me this time?
Now that I came back,
I plan to open a store in this neighborhood.
Listen,
you don't need to run a store in this town.
Where should I go, then?
This is my hometown. I was born and raised here.
I can have many regular customers...
if I visit the old neighbors and tell them about my business.
No way.
The realtor told me that older son opened a chicken restaurant...
and the other an attorney office.
The whole town knows...
that Seong Joon has become a director of FGC Group,
one of the largest firms in the nation.
By the way, how is Ms. Moon doing?
Is she still ill-tempered?
What?
Stop it already.
I am so sorry, Mother.
I was busy taking care of the kids.
- You've always been that busy. - Let me do it.
I am sorry...
I couldn't care about you so far.
You lose your mind...
whenever the kids are in trouble.
I'm sorry. Still, I need to take care of them...
as they are young.
Fine. We're withered old people.
Don't forget to bury us after we die.
Mother.
Please don't be mad at me.
What are these?
Mother,
these are beans for Chang Soo.
This is for Ji Hoon.
This is an organic milk for the children.
And I'll make salad with these for them.
Why do you buy only organic ingredients?
They're too expensive.
Just buy cheap ones.
Don't worry.
Organic foods aren't so expensive these days.
Wait for me, Mother.
How much is it?
It's 110 dollars.
Although I don't buy much, it easily exceeds 100 dollars.
Pay for yours.
Okay.
Gosh.
No way.
- This can't be right. - What's wrong?
Mother, I forgot...
to bring my wallet.
This is bad.
Mother, I am sorry,
but can you pay for mine, please?
I pay for yours?
Yes.
I will pay you back at home.
When will you pay for these?
- Please, Mother. - I'm sorry.
Please.
I will pay.
I'll pay with this card.
Where should I put the toilet papers?
Just leave them there. I'll put them in the bathroom.
Okay.
Should I put these...
- in the kitchen? - Yes.
Mother, let me take that, too.
Are you organizing the fridge?
Yes, Mother. It's done.
Thank you. You can leave, then.
- Okay. Good night. - Goodbye.
Hee Sook, stop there.
Yes, Mother?
I'll go with you.
- Why? - I just want to help you.
It's okay, Mother. I can carry these by myself.
It's too heavy. Let me help you.
Let's go.
Okay.
Mother, you didn't have to do this for me.
You are almost...
taking care of both Ji Hoon and Chang Soo.
Of course, I should lend you a helping hand.
Goodness, your fridge is...
very neatly organized.
Hye Joo needs to learn from you.
You know she's busy.
It's done.
Thank you so much, Mother.
You're welcome.
I'll go back now.
Okay, Mother.
What is it?
Well...
It is...
See you, Mother.
Why doesn't she pay back the money?
I even went to her house.
Wait. How much was it?
She bought a lot of stuff.
It was 79 dollars.
Why on earth doesn't she...
give me the 79 dollars I paid for her?
Thank you.
Gosh. I didn't know cabbage was so delicious.
It's so good.
Ae Ri!
Ae Ri! Ae Ri!
- Are you all right, Professor? - I am fine.
What just happened?
Why is he in Korea?
Why is he at my school?
What's happening?
I am going back to New York.
I've found Sang Woo.
I took care of businesses in Seoul, too.
This can't be.
You should live with your brother.
My brother...
should live as he's been living so far.
I think it's better for him that way.
So I should...
return to my place.
Seong Joon.
Hyun Woo went back to New York today.
Were you already aware of this, Jeong Eun?
Yes.
He left today.
Did you break up with him?
Well. I think that's what happened.
- Jeong Eun. - But...
how did you find out?
I saw him at a hotel this morning.
- Why? - He invested...
a lot of money in the business I am in charge of.
Really?
You knew that he didn't go bankrupt and that he was still...
the president of Golden Street, right?
- Yes. - Jeong Eun.
He had his reasons. He didn't mean any harm by it.
He did it in order to find his brother.
So did he find his brother?
His brother's name was Sang Woo, right?
- How would you know that? - So what happened?
- Seong Joon. - Please tell me.
As I told you before,
he said he found his brother.
He looked for...
his brother for such a long time.
He had a painful experience...
and spent a difficult time doing so.
Even if he did find his brother,
he said he planned to leave without letting him know.
Why?
He said the family that adopted his brother, looked more...
like a real family than himself.
He said...
it might be better for him...
to live as he's been living so far.
That's why he left.
But why do you ask?
It's just that...
I thought that he knew me from a long time ago.
What do you mean?
He knew you from a long time ago?
It's just a thought.
Seong Joon.
Strangely,
I keep thinking about him.
I remember how he was overly nice to me and my family...
and the way he stared at me.
Out of the blue, he invested in my business.
I can't understand it. I can't connect the dots.
Anyway,
I can't seem to be at ease.
Just like I said before,
I feel like I knew him from a long time ago.
I mean...
I feel like he knows me better than I know myself.
I can't understand this.
Seong Joon.
My goodness.
Seong Hoon.
Are you trying to pick up some cash from the street?
- What? - It looked like you were.
You are funny, Seong Hoon. I wasn't trying that.
I should be the one who's trying to pick up some cash from the street.
- Are you doing the delivery? - Yes.
As you can see, I am. Go home and stop trying.
Okay. Seong Hoon.
Come on. Don't be like that. Please help me.
Let go of me. I can't help you anymore.
Go. Leave now.
Is this how you are going to play it?
My neighbors are walking by.
Isn't that Father?
- What's going on? - Please help me one more time.
- Let go of me. - My goodness.
Father.
What's going on?
Seong Joon.
Goodness. You are Seong Joon.
I can't recognize you.
You grew into a handsome man.
Who are you?
Me? Who am I?
Don't you know who I am?
What are you doing?
- What are you going to tell him? - What's up with you?
- Come here. - Goodness.
- Father. - What's wrong with you?
- Go home. - Seong Joon. Seong Joon!
Please sleep on it and make the right choice for yourself.
You can submit your resignation letter whenever you want to,
but such opportunity would be rare.
You'll choose to face the reality...
or run away only to keep your pride.
It's all up to you.
Who is it?
- Why are you here? - Why do you ask?
Seong Joon can come in, but I can't?
So you should've picked up my calls.
Goodness. You are certainly acting like a writer now.
What is your reason of visiting me?
Please tell me and leave.
What is this now?
Sell your synopsis.
- Excuse me? - I will buy your synopsis.
Just sell your synopsis and steer clear of my business.
- Director Bang. - You got lucky. A director who...
likes to revise terrible synopses like this, has turned up.
The director wants to film "Romance Learned through Books".
- Really? - But you are not confident, right?
- About what? - You are not confident that...
you can turn this synopsis into a 16-episode drama. Aren't I right?
Just because you were a runner-up at a competition,
doesn't make you a writer all of a sudden.
So what is your point?
How many times do I need to tell you?
Just sell your synopsis and stay out of this. You'll only cause trouble.
What if I say I won't?
Isn't that a better opportunity for you if you sell...
your synopsis and witness how your synopsis turns into a drama?
Who do you think will consider scripts that...
are written by a nameless writer?
Even if that's the case, I won't sell it.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui. Do you not take me seriously?
Do you think I came here to play with you?
Then, Director. Do you plan on playing with my writing?
- This is an insult. - My wish to buy it isn't an insult.
What is it then, if it's not an insult?
I mean to say I will purchase it fairly by paying you money for it.
But I won't sell it. No matter what happens, I won't sell it.
So please leave.
All right. I will go.
But think carefully.
Is it better to let your script come into the light?
Or is it better to let the result of your hard work...
rot away to never see the light of day?
Why are you drinking when you should be writing?
Let me join you.
Is something not going well?
Do I get to slack off only when things are not going well?
So you were slacking off.
I didn't know.
Is something wrong?
Today,
our drama got funded.
Goodness.
That's good news. The board was so unhappy...
with the Contents Team.
But why do you look so depressed?
Didn't everything turn out well?
I don't know.
Everything is all muddled up.
We got the funding,
but the investor worries me.
What do you mean the investor worries you?
It's complicated.
Also,
we got the funding,
but we have neither a screenwriter nor a script.
Nothing has been decided yet.
By the way,
what's wrong with you again?
I don't know.
I have a lot to think about, too.
So stop worrying and work with me.
Director Han.
Don't be afraid. I'm here for you.
Still, I don't have the courage.
I'm a rookie who just wrote one short drama.
It's not like I got an excellence award for it.
It was an honorable mention.
Do you know what that means?
I looked it up in the dictionary.
It means it's not as good as the winning work,
but it's a little good. It means it's a little good.
Did you know that?
Stop.
Being a little good is enough.
It could've been really bad.
Anyway, I don't have the confidence.
Let's do it. I'll help you.
No, I'm not doing it. I don't have the confidence.
I'm going to be humiliated...
and looked down by the entire nation.
I might be on the wanted list for not writing well.
Everyone will point fingers at me.
They won't.
You can do well, Dong Hui.
No. No. I will do bad.
You have to do it one day.
Aren't you going to be a writer?
I think...
I need to do it after about 10 years.
Dong Hui.
Anyway, I won't do it. I won't.
I said I'm not going to do it. Why do you guys keep pestering me?
Dad, it's me, Seong Joon.
Come in.
What is it?
Dad, is something wrong?
No. Why do you ask?
It's just...
Who's the woman...
you were with a while ago?
She knew me, so I was wondering who she was.
She's...
She's a former colleague. I knew her from my work.
So of course she knows you.
When you were young,
I took you with me to work,
and she saw you there.
Seong Joon,
why are you looking at me like that?
I'm telling the truth.
Okay.
All right.
Come again.
When did you come?
Just now.
Why did you come? I can handle it alone.
You can go home and rest. You can watch the kids.
I don't have any kids to watch.
What do you mean?
I lost all my kids.
To whom?
Who do you think?
I'm telling you for the last time.
I decided not to care about our biological relation.
Once a son, always a son.
Got it?
Remember that.
Now, stop talking about that magic nonsense...
and start studying hard again.
Do you understand?
What if I don't want to?
You still have to do it.
You will study hard again like you used to.
I will make sure that happens.
I'm going to rip all my books!
Okay. Rip them all you like.
Rip them if that will help you relieve stress.
As long as you will study hard again like you used to,
I will gladly buy more than 1,000 books.
Why don't you keep ripping them?
Keep ripping.
I will come back in exactly 10 minutes.
Ah In, are you done, Darling?
Yes. Here.
You did very well.
Ah In, you are much better than the boys.
Really?
Thank you.
Ah In, you studied 50 words.
Should we study 50 more words?
- Okay. - You can do it, right?
You have to write 50 words 10 times, so that's 500 words.
Mom.
You're home, Son.
Yes.
Was it not too cold outside?
It was a little cold.
Right. Ah In needs to study.
Shall we go to your room and talk?
Sure.
Ah In, keep going.
- Okay. - Okay.
Let's go.
I am sorry I had to take care of Ji Hoon and Ah In...
and I couldn't go with you.
Did you give your teacher the lesson fee?
Yes. My teacher said...
only little kids come with their parents,
so I should come alone from now on.
No, I need to go...
to check how much you've progressed.
We will go together next time, okay?
RIght. How was today's lesson?
I practiced vocalization all day again.
Mom, honestly, it's too tiring and boring.
No, Chang Soo.
The strongest person is he who endures boredom.
You have to endure repeating the same things...
and practice everyday.
Only then, you can be a great vocalist.
- Okay? - Okay, Mom.
I am so proud of you, my son.
Go take a shower.
You need to get good grades to enter the art school.
Why don't you study with me?
Sure. Mom,
I feel like I'm destined to sing and study.
Really?
You're such a good boy.
That's my boy.
How lovely you are.
Do you think that's what I wanted?
I tried to stop her, saying this is nonsense.
Then, what?
But Hee Sook...
lost her mind and fiercely yelled at me.
I couldn't fight with her in front of the kids, so I just left.
Gosh. She completely beat you.
She told me not to come home before midnight.
Really? You did a great job.
- And... - What is it?
she asked if you can sleep in the restaurant and not come home.
- What? - She said the kids can't...
sleep tight because of your snoring. And they can't study well next day.
So she wants you to live here.
- What? - This is unbelievable.
Honey, what should we do with her?
We can never defeat her at all.
What do we do now?
I have a headache.
Chang Soo, are you studying?
Yes, Mom.
- I love you. - Me, too.
Ji Hoon, did you tear the book apart?
I bought three more copies for you.
What happened to Ryu Myung Jin?
It's him who sang songs in your room, right?
Gosh. How did you know that?
I ran into him at the faculty cafeteria. What's going on?
Why is he in Korea now?
That's enough. He's Jeong Eun's dad.
He's not my daughter's dad. I don't know him.
He'd disappeared for 30 years. How can he be Jeong Eun's dad?
Tell me why he's here.
I will wait just three months,
and if I can't still get over him,
I'll move to New York, too.
Welcome.
Dad!
How have you been, my daughter?
- When did you come back? - It's been a couple of days.
Let me see...
if you've become more beautiful during the last six months.
You've become more handsome.
Do you think so?
Dad.
Goodness.
This is espresso, your favorite.
Please try it. It is as good as the ones you had in Italy.
It's great.
Anyway, why did you return to Korea?
You didn't tell me you'd come back.
You appeared...
in my life one day out of the blue.
Is it because I visited you when I was traveling?
That's right.
I needed some time to cancel the operas...
scheduled to be held in Italy and France. That's why I came late.
I see.
Have you...
met with Mom?
I have.
What did she say?
Didn't she hurt you or something?
I'm sure she didn't just let you go.
She dashed away.
You should've talked to me first before you went to see her.
You shouldn't have met her alone that recklessly.
Dad, you are in danger.
You really are in danger.
I know. It's been about 30 years.
- Dad... - Right, Jeong Eun.
- Why don't you come to my concert? - Sorry?
Come with your mom.
(World-renowned Baritone Ryu Myung Jin, Comeback concert)
Dad, I can be there, but...
You must bring your mom, too.
Dad,
she might set off a bomb...
at the concert hall. Then, it will ruin your concert.
That's what I want.
- Pardon? - I loved Ae Ri with all my heart...
in my vigorous youth. If it's her who detonates a bomb,
I am more than willing...
to die.
Dying on the stage while singing...
by the lady I love...
is so dramatic, isn't it?
That's what my lifetime dream is.
Dad...
Espresso has an aroma of men.
What? She didn't give you the money back?
No, Mother. I can't tell her to pay back...
since I'm her mother-in-law.
How much is it?
It's 79 dollars.
That's too little. Just think you paid for her this time.
Mother, it's a lot to me.
I don't get pension, and my sons do not pay rent.
I barely make my both ends meet with the money I saved...
with the pension.
So 79 dollars is a large amount of money to me.
That's the amount we can live a week on.
Do you think she has no plan to pay back?
Yes. I went to her place for that money,
but she just said,
"What brings you here, Mother", blinking her eyes like this.
I couldn't tell her to give me the money, so I just left.
- Dear me. - What should I do?
I'm really on a tight budget.
It's not embarrassing for children...
to ask their parents for help, while parents cannot even ask...
their kids to pay back the borrowed money.
It is so unfair.
You're right.
What should we do to make her pay it back?
What are you doing?
Don't talk to me. I'm counting money.
Actually,
I have something to tell you.
What is it?
What? What did you say?
Why...
are you yelling at me?
You just made me yell at you.
We don't have that large amount of money.
What do you mean?
We got the deposit back from our house in Daechi-dong.
We already spent one-third of it.
What? Where did you spend that much money on?
You haven't made money for a while, have you?
You were fired from the television show and took money for your office.
I still took take care of Ji Hoon.
Now we have Chang Soo.
Do you know how much his tutoring costs?
And Ji Hoon needs to resume the private lesson.
Why do we pay for his private lesson?
If we don't, Hye Joo won't let him take it. Is that okay with you?
And I will buy a piano for Chang Soo this week.
What? Why does he need a piano?
Those who study vocal music all know how to play the piano.
He has to pass the piano exam to enter Seoul National University.
What?
He needs to take a piano lesson...
and a sight-singing and ear-training session.
It costs a bomb.
Goodness.
Things have become terrible since they were switched.
Don't say that ever. I will make Chang Soo...
a world-class singer by any means.
What about me?
I join Minjeong Party today. I have to make a donation,
and I have to pay 20,000 dollars for the by-election.
What am I supposed to do?
Stop with the politic nonsense.
What?
Just work hard as a lawyer,
and make money. Okay?
What... What did you say?
Give me money, too. Give me money!
- Let it go. - You tore it. Give it to me.
- You're tearing them. - Let it go!
Ouch. My goodness.
- Oh, dear. My back hurts. - Gosh, my money.
My back hurts.
Grandmother, I'm here. Where are you?
We're in here. Come inside.
Grandmother. Did you want to see me?
- Come on in. - You're here, too, Mother.
Oh, my. What are you doing?
Let's play cards.
- Cards? - Yes.
Jeong Ae and I wanted to play,
but we were short one person. So I called you.
Oh... I see.
You brought some money with you, right?
No, I didn't.
Let's just start playing,
and if you lose,
go downstairs and get money. Okay?
If I lose, of course I will do that.
By the way, how much is the stake money?
Let me do it.
Here. Grab some.
I'll take one of the Bright cards.
There we go. I'm so lucky.
- I have nothing to take. - Discard one, then.
Oh, I have this.
Grandmother, you're unlucky with your second cards.
I've got three Red Ribbon cards.
Now, this will get me...
3 Red Ribbon cards and 3 Blue Ribbon cards.
Shall we continue? I call the second go.
- Oh, dear. - Goodness.
I have nothing to take. Where did they all go?
- There. - Oh, gosh.
I call the third go.
Why can't you take any cards, Mother? Look at this.
Now, Grandmother owes me nine dollars,
and Mother owes me five dollars.
My gosh. If you keep this up,
I'll have to sell my land. Here.
I don't have five dollars.
This is all I've got left.
How much is that?
It's 4 dollars and 30 cents.
Oh, my.
- Look at her. - Now,
this is our final game.
Here we go.
My goodness. I didn't know she was so good at this.
Don't cry. Why are you crying?
I don't believe you.
You said you will help me win 79 dollars from Hee Sook.
I've lost 15 dollars, let alone winning any money.
I didn't know she was so good at playing cards.
She won all our money. How can she leave...
without giving us some winner's tip?
What do I do now, Mother?
Hee Sook didn't pay me for the groceries, and I lost money to her.
You should pay me that money yourself.
Fine. I'll pay you.
Stop crying!
Is Dong Hui absent again today?
Yes.
Gosh, I can't believe her.
If she doesn't want to become a writer,
she should keep working hard as an office assistant.
Look at our office now with her gone.
Our office is a big mess.
Producer Kim. What are you going to do?
Leave her be. Let her quit.
- What? - She's so ungrateful.
So many people want to become a writer,
but she refuses to become one when the director loves her script...
and our company is backing her up.
Leave her be. Let her work as an office assistant forever.
Aren't you being too harsh?
Maybe Dong Hui is just afraid.
There's nothing to be afraid of. She's just acting to be weak.
Is Dong Hui absent today as well?
Yes, Ma'am.
She must be very sick. She says she can't move at all.
You don't have to cover for her. I saw her and she was fine.
Pardon?
I guess Dong Hui didn't say anything to you.
What are you talking about?
I thought you would rush into my office...
and lash out at me again.
I went to see Dong Hui yesterday and asked her to sell her synopsis.
What?
What else could I do?
We already got investments, and the TV station wants her synopsis.
Dong Hui is a rookie. I didn't have any other choices.
Did you really do that?
That's why I offered her a handsome amount.
I haven't even offered that kind of money to any experienced writers.
That's not what I was asking.
Does it have to be Dong Hui?
Can't you just give her up?
This is work. I'm not doing this to take her side.
Our team's existence depends on this.
That's why you should convince her to sell her synopsis.
Tell her to decide whether she will make a waste,
or make use of it and gain a foothold.
It's not a bad offer for her.
Mi Joo.
It's been a while since you called me by my name.
We don't have much time.
The broadcasting station is rushing us to set up a meeting.
Seong Joon. Please convince her.
How can you draw red lines on my script, and leave comments like...
"It's childish", "It's cliche", "Fix it", and "I don't get this"?
How can you be so mean?
I was trying to support you.
Romantic comedy is the most sophisticated genre.
The new trend is that the drama either has a fantasy...
or fully reflects the reality.
Give it to me.
Don't move.
This is what I'm talking about. When a man and a woman meet,
they should confront each other...
without caring about reasons or courtesy.
You said you want to become a writer.
You should free yourself and be ahead of the viewers.
At this rate, the viewers won't wait for you.
Hello?
It's me.
Yes. Go ahead.
There are people who have been following me since that day.
I don't know what to do.
I can't move out, but I can't stay here, either.
Also, the company that Dong Hui works for...
is Hwashin Group.
Its name has changed, so I didn't know.
What should I do?
If something goes wrong...
I don't know what I should do.
That's bad news.
Please find Chairwoman Park as soon as possible.
Where has she been for the past 20 years?
Not once...
has she ever contacted me. How can she do that?
Is it even true that she's still alive?
How did it go?
Yes.
Ms. Oh Gui Boon's everyday life haven't changed much since then.
Is that so?
She didn't show...
any signs of moving out or disappearing.
She didn't meet anyone particular, either.
What kind of work...
is Dong Hui doing at my company now?
She was hired as an office assistant,
but her synopsis recently got...
an honorable mention at Channel T's contest.
She may be the writer of the new show of contents marketing team.
Writer?
Yes, Sir.
What's wrong, President Bang?
Nothing. I'm okay.
I just...
miss my sister-in-law who passed away.
Your sister-in-law?
My sister-in-law...
wanted to be a writer...
before she married my brother.
I...
miss her very much today.
Yes. What is it?
- Can I see you? - I'm busy, too. What is it?
I'll wait for you.
What is it?
What do you want? I'm a busy person, too.
If you have something to say, fire it away.
You didn't come to work today, and you just stayed home.
How can you tell your boss to come to you?
Do you think of me...
- as some kind of a pushover? - I will do it.
- What? - I will give it a try.
I'll write the screenplay version of "Romance Learned through Books".
I won't sell my story to anyone.
I won't let someone else write my story.
I won't shove it in a dark corner of my room.
I will give it a try and write it.
It's my child, so I will write...
and make it see the light.
- Dong Hui. - Are you happy now?
So don't talk to me so bluntly like,
"What is it? I'm busy, too."
I'm glad you came around. Thank you, Dong Hui.
Wait.
Stay still.
Let me hug the writer who will soon become the greatest writer of Korea.
But...
honestly I am not confident about it.
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
You trust me, don't you?
I do.
We just have to keep doing what we have been doing.
We can do well.
Trust me and trust yourself.
Okay.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Dong Hui.
What did you just say?
Why are you yelling?
Hey, how can I not be upset?
What did you just say? Repeat what you just said.
I did my calculation in the office.
And I realized that we've spent...
a substantial amount of money...
while raising Ji Hoon for 15 years.
The money spent on his food and clothes is okay.
But the problem is...
the money we spent on his education.
It adds up to a substantial amount, you see.
So what?
So I was thinking...
I just entered politics,
and I'm a little short on money. Can't you return...
a small portion of the money...
we have spent on Ji Hoon's education?
What?
Please?
Here you go.
- Take that and get out of here. - Hey!
No matter how desperate you are,
how can you ask to return the money you spent on your child?
We are really struggling these days!
Then you should pay for Chang Soo's vocal lessons.
Fine. We will pay for Chang Soo's education.
So send him back to us.
You said it. You're really going to pay for...
- Chang Soo's education, right? - I just said that!
- Come here. I will kill you. - Why are you...
- threatening me with a chicken? - Come here!
Come here!
- Gosh! I will get back at you! - Hey! Come here.
I am going to tell mom that you hit me.
Go ahead and tell her, you idiot!
I avoided it! How's that?
Gosh, he's unbelievable.
Goodness, I am sorry about this.
- Can I still get fried chicken? - Of course you can. Come in.
Which one would you like to order?
Actually,
I don't care about the chicken.
You are Hyung Seop's eldest son, Seong Hoon, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
- Let go of me. - You're Seong Joon, aren't you?
- Seong Hoon. - You're here.
Why did you want to see me?
I wanted to talk to you in private.
What is it?
What? Are you serious?
Yes.
What did that woman tell you?
She didn't say something else.
She mentioned Seong Joon and asked for money.
She said she wanted to open a store.
Did you give her the money or not?
Gosh, Dad. I don't have that much money on me.
Dad,
I am really sorry to ask,
but who is she?
Is she Seong Joon's biological mother?
Hello.
I am the handsome lawyer, Han Seong Sik.
I am the new blood of Minjeong Party, Han Seong Sik.
Thank you.
You look like a politician now, Attorney Han.
Your infinite faith in me made everything possible.
Good luck. You should use this opportunity...
- to catch more people's attention. - I will work hard.
Attorney Han,
- congratulations. - I will remain royal forever!
- Let's do it! - Let's do it!
Let's do it!
Sir?
Sir!
Sir.
Why are you so surprised?
What is it?
Did you think I killed myself or something?
Like my father?
That's half right...
and half wrong.
I will never become like my dad.
I sat here for four days...
and tried to understand my dad.
I tried to think about how he would've felt...
and in what state he would've been in.
What should I do now?
What do you want to do?
Seong Joon.
Isn't this your phone?
It's you, Mr. Lee. Where are you coming from?
Yes.
President Lee. Why don't you go inside?
Goodbye.
He's a bit strange today.
What are you going to do now?
I'll do everything as I planned.
People in this town slandered my father which led to his death.
Hyung Seop's family...
made my brother die...
on the cold street in the end. I must punish them.
I'll do it as I planned.
It will greatly affect this neighborhood.
I don't care.
I'm not going to forgive them.
Inadequate forgiveness results in a tragedy.
People don't change. They can't defeat the truth.
All people are selfish.
They have to lose things they cherish and see them get destroyed.
That's when they regret their wrongdoings.
How is it going with Seong Sik?
He already joined Minjeong Party.
I think...
he will soon be nominated for the by-election.
How about Mal Ja's clinic?
It's still in operation.
Is that so?
I see.
President Lee. What are you doing?
Are you okay?
I'm going to the clinic.
Okay.
(Yoon Surgery Clinic)
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
You were fond of me.
Why are you trembling?
You're a doctor. I'm sure you've done this a lot.
No. I'm not trembling.
I just have been on edge lately.
By the way, when did you become a doctor?
Why?
Why are you asking?
No reason.
I was just curious.
Why would you be curious about that?
As far as I know, you were the doctor at the emergency room...
of Seorin Hospital at the intersection 23 years ago.
How did you know that?
You should pick up your tweezers.
Come on.
You should change them.
You're not going to use that to treat my wound, are you?
Why did you do it?
Do what? What?
Your friend, Ms. Kim Geum Ja...
ran an academy called "Geumbit Academy".
When their bus driver had an accident while drunk driving,
why did you fabricate the story?
Why did you fabricate...
the blood test result of the driver?
What are you talking about?
I don't know about that.
Did it break your heart...
to see your precious children suffer a little wound?
Is that why you thought the man who were treated as an alcoholic...
can be treated like that forever?
Mr. Lee.
Who are you? Tell me who you are.
You took your anger out on the driver,
and that poor man hung himself.
One of his sons...
was hit by a dump truck and torn apart.
Mr. Lee.
Are you...
the driver's son?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Dad. Please do what she wants,
and end things with her for Mom's sake.
Producer Kim and Ms. Hong, please say hello.
Hello. I'm Choi Jin Kyung.
Is she my birth mother?
Seong Joon. I'm here.
Dong Hui doesn't look like her grandmother at all.
I'm really scared.
Quit everything and marry me, then.