Would you like to order?
(Episode 27)
We will have two cups of this.
Okay. I see.
Here are your beverages.
This is so pretty.
It's delicious.
Thank you. Please enjoy.
Yes, Seong Joon?
Jeong Eun. It's me.
I have something to tell you.
What? Are you certain Hyun Woo is back?
Yes, I am.
Jeong Eun, I thought about him a lot.
Something's fishy about him.
I can't figure out who and
what kind of a person he is.
He certainly said he
will return to New York.
He even invested in my
company before leaving.
He came back this morning.
What's the reason behind his return?
Jeong Eun.
He didn't get in touch with you at all?
No, he didn't.
Something's off about him. He
seems like he's playing us.
Seong Joon. Calm down.
Let me look into it. I'm sure
there was a reason for it.
I will find out.
Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo!
Mr. Lee.
Who are you? Tell me who you are.
You took your anger out on the driver...
and that poor man hung himself.
One of his sons...
was hit by a dump truck and torn apart.
Mr. Lee.
Are you...
the driver's son?
"As you sow, so shall you reap."
You thought you won't
face the consequences?
Do you think...
karma doesn't apply to you?
Does this mean...
you were behind Guem Ja's
arrest and kicked out Mi Ja?
Mr. Lee. Please forgive me this once.
I wasn't doing so well at that time.
Guem Ja said she would pay me.
That was the only time.
Please, I beg of you, Mr. Lee.
Please forgive me this once.
How can I forgive you?
The incident was...
already settled as drunk-driving
of an alcoholic driver.
I just came...
to tell you that I was very disappointed.
After 23 years, I wanted...
to tell the neighbors that in
many ways, I was disappointed.
I came back to tell you that.
Mr. Lee.
May you spend...
the rest of your life well.
Mr. Lee.
Ms. Yoon Mal Ja.
Please accompany us to the station.
Get up.
What are you doing?
- What's going on?
- Ms. Yoon Mal Ja.
You're charged with illegal practice,
issuance of false diagnoses,
unlawful rebate, and illegal
sale of medication.
You need to come to the station with us.
You have the right to remain
silent and to consult an attorney.
Anything you say may be used
against you in a court of law.
Let's go.
No. It's not me.
- I didn't do it.
- Get in.
- No!
- Let's go.
My goodness. What happened to Doctor Yoon?
I am not sure. I wonder what it's about.
- What did she do wrong?
- Exactly.
- What's happening?
- What a mess.
(Han Seong Sik's candidacy is confirmed.)
How do you feel as you have
officially entered into politics?
I was too excited to get any sleep.
I'm honored to contribute...
in making the world a better place.
Please say a few words before we wrap up.
First of all,
I would like to show my gratitude to...
the members of my party who trust in me.
From now on,
my dear and respectful citizens,
I leave it to you.
I am the candidate of a dignity and...
a noble standard which you deserve to have.
I can assure you, I am the
only reliable candidate.
All you need to do is enjoy
the fruit of my labor.
I, Han Seong Sik, will do all the work
Hello. I am Han Seong Sik.
Hi.
Did you announce your candidacy?
You're working hard in this cold weather.
I am Han Seong Sik who
will save Korean politics.
Hello, Ma'am.
I am the handsome lawyer, Han Seong Sik.
The carrots look very fresh.
Hello.
I am Han Seong Sik from Minjeong Party.
Who is that?
- Isn't it my dear Seong Sik?
- I am Han Seong Sik who...
- will save Korean politics.
- Why is he on TV?
That is him.
Why is he saying hello to people?
He went to the market.
Why did he go?
Did his mother want him
to go grocery shopping?
I don't think so.
Hey. Why would you eat that
without cleaning it first?
Is your grandson running for...
a seat in the National Assembly?
What?
A seat in the National Assembly?
Jeong Ae. Hyung Seop.
Did Seong Sik mention that
he was running for office?
No one's here.
Where did everyone go?
I always forget at least something
when I go grocery shopping.
Last time,
I forgot to buy this spring onion.
I'm the same, Mother.
I forgot to buy spinach I was
going to cook for the children.
I think I should buy some more
dried laver and shrimp sauce.
I will buy some snacks...
and oatmeal for the children.
Are you sure?
Sorry?
I mean, I think that's a good idea.
Buy more. I will, too.
Okay, Mother.
I'm so glad that I can come
shopping with you often like this.
Same here.
How much is it?
It's 80 dollars.
Is it 80 dollars?
Wait a second.
Goodness. No way.
- What's wrong, Mother?
- I forgot my wallet today.
Seriously.
This is unbelievable.
I am sorry. Please wait a moment.
It's not in here.
Hee Sook, I need you...
to pay for mine today.
Mother, this isn't good.
What is it?
I forgot to bring my wallet...
again today.
Dear me.
What?
I apologize, Mother.
What's gotten into you?
You're not as old as I am.
I can't believe you forget
your wallet so many times.
Mother, actually, I used this same bag...
the other day I came here with you,
and I forgot to put my wallet
in here in the first place.
I should've remembered to bring it today.
- I'm so sorry.
- Goodness.
Mother, Father is here.
Father, we are here!
Hee Sook.
Why are you here? I called
Seong Sik, not you.
Mother, I called Father.
- I'm sorry.
- Why did you do that?
Come on. You know Seong Sik
is too busy to come here.
This is ridiculous.
It's 160 dollars in total.
I will pay it with this.
This is total nonsense.
Why did you pay for all?
How could I tell Hee Sook
to pay hers herself?
This isn't her first time
making me pay for her.
It doesn't really matter.
How could a parent neglect
her in such situation?
And you know she forgot her wallet today.
I'm saying she does this all the time.
Don't be too mean to her.
She's your daughter-in-law.
This is ridiculous.
- I can't stand this anymore!
- You two are back.
- Mom, you're here.
- Mother, Hee Sook ripped me off...
again at the market again today.
Stop it.
I told you Hee Sook is too
clever for you to deal with.
- Mother...
- Please be quiet. By the way,
is Seong Sik really going to run for
the National Assembly this year?
What do you mean?
I just saw it...
on television earlier, so I thought
you two already are aware of this.
Seong Sik runs for the National
Assembly by-elections.
Sorry? By-elections?
Yes, Dad. I also saw it on television.
What's gotten into him?
Politics isn't something
that anyone can do.
Dad, don't worry too much.
I'll visit his office right
away and talk to him.
It might ruin our whole family.
Tell him to give up now.
I will. I'll call you later.
Seriously.
What's wrong with him?
(Han Seong Sik, Minjeong
Party's official candidate)
Excuse me.
Hello.
What will you do?
I need you to resolve it.
Seong Hoon, did you talk to Seong Sik?
Hello. I told you we'd meet again.
How dare you come here?
- Dad.
- Get up already.
- What do you think you're doing?
- Dad.
Stay out of this.
- Get out of here.
- Goodness.
Dad.
Don't ever come back again.
If you come here again,
I'll call the police.
Sure. Go ahead.
I can't believe you just said that.
Get lost now.
I will leave now,
but I'm coming back.
I'll make sure to come back soon.
Wait for me.
What a wench.
Dad.
Dad,
you need to tell me so that I can help you.
I'm afraid to tell you...
that I don't want anything that
breaks Mom's heart to happen again.
If she's Seong Joon's biological mother,
please just give her what she
wants and let her walk away...
for Mom's sake.
Please don't just keep sighing.
Mom shouldn't find this out.
It took 10 years for her to
accept Seong Joon as her son.
Seong Joon came to us when he was seven,
and she first hugged him when he turned 17.
- This will perturb her again.
- Seong Hoon.
Yes, Dad.
Can you just help me...
without asking anything?
Hyun Woo!
Why are you here?
When did you come back?
Will you stay here, then?
You didn't come back because
you forgot something, right?
You'll stay here forever, won't you?
I'm so glad you are back.
I also have good news.
My dad is back. He said
he'll live in Korea.
I returned to take care of a few things.
I will leave again soon. Please go.
Hyun Woo.
- What's the matter?
- I need you to leave now.
Nothing will change even if
I came back permanently.
Now leave.
Hold on.
- Did something happen to you?
- Nothing happened.
We're not together anymore.
You also said we are finished...
and you'll blame me for
the rest of your life.
Do as you said.
Don't try to find me.
Hyun Woo.
Hello, Mr. Lee. How are you?
- Hello.
- Why don't you go inside?
Goodbye.
Get out. Leave already.
That's enough, Mr. Kim.
Are you joking with me? Do you
think anyone can be a writer?
- I'm sorry.
- Dong Hui,
sorry doesn't cut it.
Do you know we had to do extra
work while you were away?
I made coffee for others and
even had to clean the office.
That's enough, everyone.
She's here after all.
It's good you mentioned it.
Why are you back?
We've already suffered
enough because of you.
- Well...
- What's going on here?
Good morning, Director Bang.
What brings you here, Dong Hui?
Who is she?
Let me introduce her to you.
You know Writer Choi Jin Kyung, right?
Pardon?
She wrote a miniseries called,
"Icarus's Wings: the Golden Times".
Hello. I'm Choi Jin Kyung.
Where is Director Han? We have
to sign a contract today.
Director Han. Please say hello.
This is Writer Choi Jin Kyung.
Hello, Director Han. I've
heard a lot about you.
I'm sorry,
but I was aware that I was to
write the scripts on my own.
It's about the same as writing
the scripts on your own.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui wrote the synopsis.
We scouted you for a writer...
who will write even better scripts.
I hope you wouldn't be offended.
I never agreed to sell my synopsis.
Are you telling me that you will
write the scripts all on your own?
Director Bang.
Then, what is your plan?
Writer Choi, please help us.
Producer Park insists on
directing this drama.
I can't depend on Ms. Oh Dong Hui
since she's an inexperienced writer.
We have no other way around it.
So do you mean that I have to co-write...
with a rookie like her?
I also do not wish to co-write
my drama with another writer.
What?
How old are you? How many
dramas have you written?
Director Bang. How can you
handle business like this?
This is also an insult to Writer Choi, too.
Fine. Then, I will make a
suggestion to both of you.
Writer Choi, if you help us out this time,
we will sign you for the next drama.
And for you, Ms. Oh Dong Hui.
Since you won't sell your synopsis,
I'll treat you like a writer, then.
However, it will only air after you
have proved yourself as a writer.
What do you mean?
We will go ahead with her synopsis,
but both of you will write the
scripts based on the synopsis.
We will go with the scripts
that seem to be written better.
How can that be possible?
Director Bang. Is this how you handle...
I am aware that I may be
asking a bit much from you.
However, don't worry since a
rookie writer like her...
can't defeat you.
Now the decision remains
solely on your hands.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui.
This is a good way for you to
squash any rumor that claims...
you became a writer by someone's
help, not by your own merit.
What do you think? Are you not confident?
If you are not, then stay out of it.
Why did you willingly
accept her suggestion?
If not?
She might think I'm running
away because I'm scared.
You should have protected your synopsis.
How can you compete with another
writer with a synopsis you wrote?
If I don't, she won't
acknowledge me as a writer.
If I say I will write
the scripts on my own,
do you think she would approve?
You're right, but...
This is just too sad.
I can't do anything about it even if it is.
All I can do is win.
Dong Hui.
Please leave now. I'm going
to start right away.
Do you think this is some
sort of a game or a trick?
How can two writers
compete with each other?
Why? Did I hurt your feelings?
Drama is like a living creature.
It's hard enough for one writer
to come up with the scripts.
How can they alternate episodes and write?
Who said they will alternate
episodes and write?
Goodness. You are confident.
What do you mean?
Writer Choi has an experience
of 10 years in scriptwriting.
Do you think Dong Hui can
write better than...
Writer Choi even if it's just one episode?
Bang Mi Joo!
Whether Writer Choi wins or she does,
it won't hurt our team in any
way since we will be airing...
the episodes of better written scripts.
Isn't that enough?
Don't worry too much.
You said she is a good writer.
Then, she will win.
Anyway, you usually turn off
your phone when you go home.
I'm grateful that you're calling me now.
Well, then. Good night. Bye now.
Moong Chi, be quiet. Don't
you know I'm writing now?
This is very important to me.
I have to win.
Be quiet!
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I have to meet someone.
Who are you meeting at this late hour?
I'm meeting a coworker.
I'll be back.
Come home early.
Okay.
How's Father?
I saw him at home before I left.
What's going on?
Why do I have to keep
this a secret from him?
Seong Joon.
I'm sorry to bring this to you.
I think Father is in trouble.
What kind of trouble?
He won't tell me what it is.
You know the woman with Father you
saw on the street the other day?
Let go of me. I can't help you anymore.
Go. Leave now.
You must be Seong Joon.
Don't you know who I am?
I remember her. What about it?
We shouldn't...
mention at home that we met her, okay?
What do you mean?
I just called you just to make
sure you won't make any mistake.
We didn't see anything.
Let's be careful so that we
won't make any mistake at home.
Why?
Who is she?
I think she is an old coworker of Father.
Seong Hoon.
I am not clueless.
One day,
when Mother brought up about marriage,
she asked me if I looked
for my biological mother.
Seong Joon.
By any chance,
is she my biological mother?
I don't know, but...
Seong Hoon.
You are worried about Mother, right?
You are worried she might be hurt again.
- Seong Joon.
- If you know her phone number,
please let me have it.
Seong Joon.
Let me have her phone number.
Are you doing your best?
Yes.
I am doing my best.
How about you, Ah In?
I am almost done.
Excellent. After we finish all of it,
I will give you a ride to
your school and preschool.
I am going to take the bus.
Hey.
Han Ji Hoon.
What did I tell you?
Once a son, always a son!
Did you forget that?
You might be better off just taking
the ride when I tell you nicely.
Goodness.
It is quite comfortable since she
took all the children with her.
I have a plenty of time in the morning.
Just because you took them away from me,
doesn't mean they are yours.
Do your best, Kang Hee Sook.
Fulfill your wish.
It's never quiet because of
Hee Sook and her husband.
Besides,
you, Han Seong Sik. You are
going to be a politician?
You are running for a seat
in the National Assembly?
You're going to put your life
on the line for the citizens?
That is enough to make a cat laugh.
You were chasing after pretty girls...
while using the protest as an excuse.
Who are you trying to kid?
- You can't.
- Grandmother.
Do you think anyone can be a politician?
I've witnessed many people...
who destroyed their families
because they got into politics.
Grandmother, that's a very
negative opinion of your grandson.
It's not a negative opinion of you.
I'm basing this on my
experience and the statistics.
Aren't you going to proud of
me if I become a congressman?
I'll be so proud and happy,
but you might ruin your life over that.
- Just don't do it.
- Dad!
I agree with your dad and grandmother.
I don't really know it well,
but I know it costs a lot of
money to become a politician.
Mom!
Are you stopping me because of money?
Are you worried that I
might ask you for money?
- Hey.
- Stay quiet, Seong Hoon!
You've used up all our family's money.
That's why Mom and Dad
are stopping me from...
entering the election! They think
I might ask them for money.
- What did you say?
- Goodness. That fool.
Just stick to your job as a lawyer.
What's the matter with you?
A man should be ambitious and dream big.
Why should I settle for
running my own business?
- What?
- Being a lawyer is just a business.
I want to go into the bigger
world, Mom, Dad, and Grandmother!
My goodness. You've gone totally insane.
Get up. You and I should talk.
What are you doing?
- Get up, you brat.
- Gosh. Mom! Dad!
Grandmother! Help me!
- Let me go. What are you doing?
- It's never peaceful in this house.
- Stop it! Let me go!
- My goodness, you punk.
What's wrong with you?
Didn't I warn you?
I told you to be careful with
Minjeong Party and Seonghan Group,
but you've joined that party. Now
you want to run for the election.
Who's backing you up?
- Who's sponsoring you?
- Don't you know that?
Mr. Kim Young Tae is backing me up,
and Seonghan Group is sponsoring me.
What are you going to do?
Don't you worry. I won't ask
our family even for a penny.
Whether you get help from our
family or not isn't the issue here.
You're going to be in big trouble!
If something happens during
the election period,
you will totally lose your
social standing in this society.
You might lose your license, let
alone losing all the TV shows.
The way I see it, your
life is in bigger trouble.
Are you going to keep
selling fried chickens...
until you become an old man?
When you and Hye Joo become an old couple,
your children might look down on
you saying you're old and smelly.
- What did you say?
- Just stay quiet.
If you do,
I might hire you as my spokesperson later.
- Seong Sik.
- Let go of me.
Let me go. My goodness.
Seong Sik.
Seong Sik!
That brat.
Yes.
Please deliver it today, then.
Yes. All right.
Hey. What are you doing?
What? I just dropped the
kids off at school.
Gosh. This is driving me crazy.
Although I'm grateful that
you drop my children off...
at school and pick them up every day,
- isn't that tiring?
- It's not.
I have to go out to buy
collections of German songs...
and Italian songs for Chang
Soo later in the afternoon.
You're a natural. You have talents for it.
Don't pick a fight with me.
Just go to work.
Hee Sook.
Pay more attention to your husband.
He wants to be a politician.
What are you going to do now?
There is nothing to do. He's not
going to be elected anyway.
You're not interested in your
husband at all, are you?
I'm not interested in a grown-up.
The ones I'm interested in...
are growing children. I have
no interests for others.
It's good that I ran into you. Hye Joo.
I think you should move
this chest of yours.
- Why?
- Just move it.
You can't ask me to do that.
I told you this is what my parents left me.
No. Absolutely not.
Besides, we moved downstairs
on the condition that...
I can place this here. Have you forgotten?
Just move it.
I bought a piano for Chang
Soo, and it's coming today.
- A piano?
- Yes.
Don't you want...
to raise Chang Soo to a
world-class opera singer?
I speak
With trembling lips
My poor
Words of confession
My shy
And bashful face
I feel
My heart fluttering
I take courage
Hidden deep in my heart
I speak
My poor words of confession
He must be crazy.
Why does he want to meet me now?
I will see him and have
it out with him today.
That jerk. He's a total jerk.
Why does he want to see me after 30 years?
You're a dead man.
You're as tall as ever.
- You're as short as ever.
- How have you been?
Is that how you want to
greet me in 30 years?
You're still beautiful.
You look so pretty.
Please don't wear high heels...
next time we see each other.
Next time? Gosh, I can't believe this.
Why would I see you again? Are you insane?
Listen to me carefully. The
reason why I came here today...
is not because I missed you...
or because I wanted to see how you changed.
During the past 30 years,
I always wanted to know how you were.
Not me. I never wanted
to know how you were.
Since the day you left for Italy,
I've never thought about you.
I've never even dreamed about you.
So from this moment on,
don't ever call me.
Don't show up in front of me.
Just stay out of my sight.
I came to say this.
Let's clear up the misunderstanding.
Misunderstanding? There
is no misunderstanding.
I dated you because I was young and stupid,
and we broke up. That's
the end of the story.
Do you think I'm a woman who would wait...
for a guy to return for 30 years?
Don't be ridiculous.
I'm sorry.
No. You don't need to be.
Why are you sorry?
It's not like you hurt me,
made me waste my time, or humiliated me.
I've been just fine. I've been happy.
My point is...
Don't you ever...
show your face again from now on.
- Ae Ri.
- If you really...
loved me by any chance,
please do this for me.
I don't want to see you ever again.
Ae Ri. Ae Ri.
Ae Ri.
Ae Ri. Ae Ri!
Welcome, Director Han.
Hello.
Hello. We meet again.
He came to check the contract himself.
What are you doing? Take a seat.
I wanted to check the office atmosphere...
as well as get some things done.
Is everything going as
planned, Director Han?
Yes. Thanks to you, the
production is running smoothly.
We will sign a contract with a writer soon.
I see.
I have no doubt...
that you will handle things well.
If this investment turns out as a success,
I plan to expand the investment...
in Korean drama production.
Is that right?
Of course, I'd appreciate it
if Director Han is involved.
This investment will be a success.
And the next project will
be influenced by it.
You've made a right choice.
I think so, too.
Mr. Lee.
What's going on?
What do you mean?
Don't you know why I came here?
No, not that.
Can I ask you why you decided to come back?
I realized...
that I had unfinished businesses.
That's why I came back.
But I don't plan to stay too long.
Anyway,
I wish you good luck, Director Han.
What are you doing here?
You're home.
How did you get in here?
Did you forget?
We used to be a couple. I
know your gate password.
I heard you came back, so I stopped by.
Get out. Get out now.
You should've cleaned the house
as soon as you came back.
Even if you are only
staying for a short while,
you should make the house liveable.
I got groceries in a hurry, so I
couldn't get too many things.
I will make a few side dishes first.
Please go now. Please.
Then...
help me understand the situation.
Or else, I will never be able
to accept this situation.
Tell me why you suddenly came back.
It's understandable that
you suddenly came back.
Just tell me why you've changed.
Jeong Eun.
Are you stupid?
We broke up.
But you came back.
What difference does it make?
What did you say?
Does that make any difference
to the fact that we split up?
It's okay for a man and
a woman to split up.
Are you being all clingy because
of your lingering feelings?
Did you say clingy?
Did you say lingering feelings?
What happened?
What happened to you?
Why are you doing this to me?
Please leave...
when I ask nicely.
Don't do this. You don't
have to be this mean.
Without you,
a week felt like a year.
I don't know what happened
to you over the week,
but you don't have to be like this to me.
Nothing happened.
I just...
don't have...
a place for you in my heart.
Hyun Woo.
So please leave.
I don't want to talk more.
How can you do this to me?
Then...
what were you doing with me all along?
Were you playing with me?
Yes.
I was playing with you.
What?
I had a little fun with you.
Do you get it now?
Where are you going at this hour?
I'm going up to the studio.
The studio?
Do you mean Dong Hui's studio?
Why are you going at this hour?
Mom.
How many times did I tell you?
We are family, but you shouldn't
go up to Dong Hui's room so often.
- People will talk about it.
- Mom.
Dong Hui's my staff.
And she will be writing the
new drama we're producing.
Stop it. I don't know those things.
Just don't go up.
What's wrong with you?
Dong Hui.
Are you asleep?
Aren't you going to write?
Dong Hui?
Dong Hui.
Dong Hui, what's wrong?
Are you sick? Is something wrong?
What's wrong?
Dong Hui!
What's wrong? What is it?
I am scared.
I don't think I can do this.
No matter how much I think about
it, I don't think I can do it.
I think it's better...
to ask Writer Choi to write everything.
Tell her she can write the
script using my synopsis.
Give me the blanket.
I'm scared, and I need to put it over me.
I'm embarrassed, too.
Dong Hui!
She's a veteran writer with
10 years of experience,
while I'm literally a novice writer.
How on earth do you think I can beat her?
I'm no match for her in the first place.
You are very silly, Dong Hui.
You're right. I am silly.
I know I was too reckless.
So please leave me alone.
- Follow me.
- Sorry?
- Where are we going?
- Get up now.
What are you doing now?
- Just buckle up.
- Pardon?
Please tell me where we are going.
Why? Are you afraid that I
might sell you to someone?
I won't be able to sell you
at a high price, anyway.
No one would buy a novice
writer who cries out of fear.
What did you say?
Just tell me where we are heading.
- You'll see soon.
- I have no time for this.
I have to hand in my
script by this Wednesday.
Didn't you say you gave up and
you'll leave it to Writer Choi?
Be quiet and have some sleep.
Dong Hui, we're here. Wake up.
Where are we?
Just get off.
Isn't this amazing?
I didn't know there's
such a place in Korea.
I love this smell of books.
- These aren't mere books.
- Sorry?
These are the fruits of the
writers who have overcome...
dreadful fear of creation.
This is Ernest Hemingway's.
Hemingway once said this.
"There is nothing to writing."
"All you do is..."
"sit down at a typewriter and bleed."
He rewrote the last part...
of "A Farewell to Arms" 39 times.
Do you like Haruki Murakami?
Murakami...
gets up at three in the
morning and writes...
until noon every day.
In the afternoon, he runs...
to maintain his good condition for writing.
How does it feel like to find
out other writers' efforts?
I'm sure no writers wrote their works...
very easily without any
pain or hardworking.
All the great writers have gone
through the torment of creativity.
How would you think you'd
be able to avoid it?
Did you think you could write it overnight?
I never said that.
I am afraid. I'm scared to death.
What about the writers of all these books?
They have felt the same.
Everyone is afraid of unknown paths.
But if you give up and stop moving forward,
you'll never be able to find
out the beautiful things...
waiting for you at the end of the path.
All you need to do...
is take the first step.
Did you say you're scared? Everyone is.
You just have to overcome it.
Will I be able to do it?
Of course, you will.
What if I fail?
You just made...
what I've said so far meaningless.
I'm seriously afraid.
Then, give up everything and marry me.
Pardon?
What on earth are you talking about?
I was going to listen to you as
you said a lot of great things.
- And what's this?
- Then, just keep writing.
Stop whining like a baby.
You should know so many writers
desperately want to write like you.
Why are you yelling at me?
I do know how to yell just like you.
This is ridiculous. You're something else!
This is great.
I was stressed out anyway.
Let's get nasty, then.
You won't be able to write a line.
Stop nagging at me.
Why don't you go start writing
and see if it works as you want?
Do you think I'd be here shouting
like this if it was that easy?
Please...
take it easy and keep writing.
I know you can do it. I got your back.
I'll be by your side so
that you won't feel afraid.
Okay?
What was that?
Stop making excuses and keep writing, okay?
Come with me. I'll show
you my favorite book.
"I sat and watched her
sleep, a little troubled,"
"deep down in my soul,"
"but kept holy by the clear night
which has never given me..."
"other than beautiful thoughts"
"Around us the stars continued..."
"heir silent march,"
"obedient as a mighty army."
"I fancied that one of these stars,"
"the most delicate, the most lustrous,"
"had missed her way..."
"and had come..."
"to lean upon my shoulder, and to sleep."
("The Stars" by Alphonse Daudet)
(FGC personnel records, Oh Dong Hui)
(Agreement for writing scenario
and transfer of the copyright)
Hello?
Mom, it's me.
It's me, Gwang Jin.
You sound so surprised, and
I feel bad for calling now.
Right. How are you doing?
Have you finished the herbal medicine?
I still have some.
You shouldn't trouble yourself
with those things now.
Don't say that.
By the way,
I am looking at your
granddaughter Dong Hui's resume.
What?
But...
she doesn't look anything like you
She looks like her father.
Did you call to say that?
Of course not. I wanted to tell you
that you've brought her up well.
I see that she's a writer.
What do you mean?
She started out as an
assistant at our office,
and now we are signing a
contract with her as a writer.
How did it...
Director Bang brought it
to me for a final confirm,
and it turned out...
it was your granddaughter.
What a coincidence!
She's very pretty, too.
I need to meet her first.
After that,
I will sign the contract with her.
Only then,
I will get to see you...
and your granddaughter for a long time.
Take care then.
Did you sleep well, Sir?
No.
Is it because of Jeong Eun?
I don't want to talk about it.
You should've slept well.
Only then, you will get to...
read the morning paper with a clear mind.
(Jinsung Daily News)
(Seonghan Group evades tax!)
Han Seong Sik will start going down today.
Goodness.
Gosh, why are there so many things...
happening to Seong Sik...
and Dad?
(Seonghan Group evades tax!)
Seonghan Group?
(Attorney H gives them
advice on avoiding tax.)
(They sought to avoid the
prosecution investigation.)
(They closed down their subsidiaries
without proper compensation.)
(Seonghan Group, tax evasion
of Seonghan Group, Attorney H)
Where are you?
Where would I be? I'm at my office.
Good thing you called.
I've been busy all morning with
the women's society meeting...
and the alpine club meeting.
And I'm starving now.
Please cook me some chicken.
I'll get half-and-half. I want
a lot of pickled radishes.
It's not the time for fried chicken.
Should I eat there? I guess
it will smell if I eat here.
I will go down now. Okay?
Hey, don't come. Don't come.
Seong Sik! Seong Sik!
Gosh.
The number you have dialed is
not available at this moment.
Why aren't you picking up your phone?
Seong Hoon.
What is it?
What's going on?
Is it true that you provided
illegal advice to help...
Seonghan Group evade tax?
Are you Attorney H who got a
large sum of money for...
providing the illegal advice?
Did you get nominated as a reward?
Seong Sik! Seong Sik!
- Seong Sik!
- Seong Hoon!
What's going on here?
What's going on?
Move!
No! No!
Cover your face.
Please say something.
- What's going on?
- Please say something.
Move!
Welcome.
Seong Joon.
Here.
I can't even recognize you now.
You grew into a handsome man.
You understand me well
because you are young.
Take that...
and don't bother my dad anymore.
I never bothered him.
Don't show up again.
You are so mean.
Do you know who I am?
I don't care.
What?
I just want to...
protect my dad.
You want to protect your dad.
Yes.
Seong Joon, you are so naive.
You're too nice.
Goodness. What did he do to him?
Do you really not remember anything?
What is it that you want to say?
All right.
Since you gave me money,
I will give you a crucial information.
Your dad...
is not your biological dad.
He told the orphanage that he
is your biological father.
But he is not.
He's a silly man.
He fooled you completely.
I guess you needed to believe that
you were related to one of them.
Only then, you would've
endured your time there.
What...
What are you saying?
I'll tell you one more thing.
You shouldn't...
admire your father so much.
He's...
not so admirable after all.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Dong Hui should be writing a script.
I told her to come to the office.
So why are they saying...
that I provided illegal counsel
to help them evade tax?
- You are mad!
- Honey!
- I am divorcing you.
If you don't want to see
Director Han lose his job,
you should think carefully.
Are you...
my mother?
Everything I believed is gone.
It's killing me.