(Episode 28)
How about Seong Joon?
I don't know. He hasn't woken up yet.
Really?
- I will go check on him. - No, I will go.
Seong Joon.
Father.
What are you doing? You didn't answer when I called you.
What were you thinking so hard about that you didn't hear me?
It's nothing.
You are sweating a lot. Are you sick?
No. I am fine.
Look at you.
I am not sick. I'm fine, Father.
Are you certain?
Of course I am.
Come out and have breakfast. Mom's worried about you.
- All right. - Come out quickly.
I will.
Yes, Seong Hoon.
Seong Joon. Get the morning paper. Get the paper.
What?
We have already located Attorney Han Seong Sik.
Okay. I understand.
Get the newspaper so that Father doesn't read it.
My goodness.
Someone's calling me. I'll talk to you later.
Reporter Yim. What happened?
Did you have breakfast?
I am about to have it.
- Did you have breakfast? - Yes, I had some bread.
I came downstairs to have some coffee.
You could drink your coffee while we have our breakfast.
I guess I can do that. Here's the newspaper.
I always tell them to deliver well,
but they sloppily throw it.
Thank you.
Didn't you go to work yet?
I should get going soon.
Jeong Ae. Give me a cup of coffee, please.
- Okay. - Come.
All right.
Why are you reading the paper in the middle of your breakfast?
She's right. It's distracting. Put it away.
What is this?
What is it?
What's the matter?
Isn't this Seong Hoon in the picture?
What is going on?
My goodness. Isn't this Seong Hoon?
That's Seong Sik next to him.
- Why are they in the picture? - What on earth is going on?
Why are both of my grandchildren in the newspaper?
Mother. Please calm down. Let me read what this is about.
"Popular attorney who was involved in the collusion..."
"of Minjeong Party and Seonghan Group..."
"is revealed to be ex-presenter, Han Seong Sik."
"He is scheduled to be questioned by the prosecution."
Goodness.
Hey. Seong Joon.
What is all this? Were you aware of this?
Yes.
I just got a call from Seong Hoon.
- What did he say? - What did he say?
Well...
Seong Joon.
Where are Seong Hoon and Seong Sik? Are they home?
Mother.
- What's wrong? - Mother.
- Jeong Ae. - Honey.
- My goodness. Hey. - Mother.
- Mother. - Jeong Ae. Hold on.
Let's get her to her room quickly. What are we going to do?
Is she going to be okay?
Honey. Are you all right?
Jeong Ae. My goodness. What's wrong? Jeong Ae!
So where are you? I asked where you are!
Where do you think I am? I am in the office.
I am with Seong Hoon.
Reporters are camped outside the office,
so I can't leave.
Honey.
I am sincerely sorry.
Well...
But Honey,
I feel so dirty.
Can you bring me new underwear?
Hey, you jerk.
Do you want to change your underwear at this very moment?
You don't have to hit me though.
I am a human being. I am entitled to have clean underwear.
I can't stand you, jerk.
I told you...
not get involved with Seonghan Group and Minjeong Party.
Seong Hoon.
Please don't hit me. Whatever you do, don't hit me.
You never listen to me.
What are you going to do with all those reporters?
How are you going to handle the investigation by the prosecution?
Seong Hoon.
Don't bring up such a thing.
An investigation by the prosecution...
I am really terrified.
- Hold on. - Hey.
Hee Sook. What are we going to do with this mess?
I think I should go to the office.
How can you? There is a gang of reporters there.
I will find a way. Hye Joo.
Please look after the children. I'm going now.
Hee Sook. Hee Sook!
What should I do?
Han Seong Sik. I knew this would happen when he got into politics.
Hey. What's going on?
- Father. - Where's Hee Sook?
What is this all about?
Hee Sook just went out to see Seong Sik.
Is it all true what the article said about him? Is it true?
Well...
Seong Hoon said it probably is.
Goodness. How are we going to handle this?
Mom.
Ah In.
What is this nonsense out of the blue?
Please stop being upset.
I am so upset that I can't live.
How are we going to manage this?
Please calm down. Children are here.
Please go upstairs.
My goodness, Seong Sik.
Mother. What is going on?
Don't worry. It's nothing.
Then why is Great-Grandmother crying?
Trust me. It's nothing.
What are you doing? Shouldn't you get ready for school?
I will take you to school today. Get ready now. Hurry.
- Hurry. - Okay.
Gosh. What am I going to do?
How are we going to survive this?
Yes, Father.
You can put Ah In on the yellow bus from the preschool.
The same bus will drop her off. You can just pick her up there.
Okay, Father. Thank you.
Hold on. What is this smell?
Did one of you put on your father's toner?
What is it?
Did you put on your father's toner?
Yes, I did. What's wrong with it?
I can't stand smelling both of your hair product and the toner.
Don't open the window.
Cold wind will be damaging for my throat.
What?
Mother told me to be careful of the cold.
She said opera singers' greatest asset is their body.
My goodness.
Hey. Han Chang Soo.
I do want to congratulate you for working hard to be an opera singer.
Enough is enough.
You pooped your pants recently.
Aunt!
- You scared me. - Stop talking about my past.
I'm no longer who I used to be.
Is that so?
Fine. Just live as you please.
- Here it is. - What is this?
It's a list of Germany and Italian song books I need.
My mom went to buy them, but they were sold out.
I'm sure you'll be able to find them at the bookstore today.
I have no time to go buy these. Why don't you buy yourself?
I have a lesson right after school.
- What? - Please buy them for me. See you.
Wait. Chang Soo!
I'm super busy today. Goodness.
Ji Hoon, what are you doing? Get off.
Are you not going to school?
Mom, will we not going to move out?
What? Why are you talking about it out of the blue?
You know why. We live in the same house as Chang Soo,
so my former mom still meddles in my life.
- Ji Hoon. - I really want to move out.
Now there's no point in having a new mom after all.
Ji Hoon, I've also been troubled with that matter.
Please find a way to move out as soon as possible...
or I'll suffocate to death.
Darn it.
What? Did he say, "Darn it"? Fine. Darn it.
Chang Soo, wait for me.
He's also a little kid...
who doesn't know how hard his parents work.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh, my back aches.
Why? Do you have something to talk to me about?
Who are you?
Do you want to know who I am?
I work at the tea house,
I mean, at the cafe...
on the second floor.
I'm Madam Jeong. Why?
I see.
I'm just back from a trip. And what's all this fuss about?
I have to open the cafe from today. Why are you so crowded here?
Why don't you...
have a cup of coffee?
No thanks.
Okay. Fine.
Move.
It was dangerous. It is because of my foolish husband.
Mr. Kim,
please count me out this.
I gave you the advice personally...
without expecting anything in return.
Why do newspapers say it was an advice on tax evasion?
How pathetic.
I know...
the collusion between Minjeong Party and Seonghan has been revealed,
but I have no idea why I am involved in that.
I have been nominated because they found me competent.
It has nothing to do with the advice.
Am I wrong?
How silly.
I will stay in my office and avoid the reporters.
Please handle this well and save me.
Okay.
I will not go outside for a week.
I will. Please call me. Goodbye.
Seong Hoon,
Senior Secretary Kim said he'll take care of this.
He just wants me to stay in...
and not see any reporters.
Staying inside won't settle anything.
Senior Secretary Kim will resolve the situation.
I'm sure he's also in trouble like you.
He is very...
- Who... Who is it? - It's me.
This is your wife.
Goodness.
- Honey, I missed you. - Hello, Hee Sook.
You're totally useless!
I told you not to enter the political arena.
- Honey. - What will you do now?
Tell me what your plan is.
If you lose your title as a lawyer because of this,
how will we make a living? Tell me!
Stop it!
It will be all right!
It will be settled soon!
I told you to just work hard as a lawyer.
Why did you meddle...
in broadcasting and politics? Why did you overstep your bounds?
- This is terrible. - Stop.
Hee Sook,
do you want some ramyeon?
Seong Joon gave this pot to every one of the mountaineering club,
and this is highly likely to be considered a bribe.
- Why you... - This is unbelievable.
- It's all done! - Honey...
- Let's get divorced. - Honey.
We should get divorced.
So tell us honestly now!
Did you get anything in return for raising illegal fund for Seonghan?
I didn't. I'm not lying.
Then, how were you nominated by the Party's members?
They voted for me only because I'm competent...
and popular among the public.
You're still out of your mind.
Stop hitting me!
It hurts! It hurts so bad!
There's a possibility for you to be arrested...
along with the officials of Minjeong Party and Seonghan Group.
Is that true, Seong Hoon?
Tell me the truth.
- Did you ask them for help? - Well...
It's about my brother.
He runs a semiconductor manufacturer,
and he wants to work with Seonghan again.
Really?
I wonder if you can help him resume the trade with Seonghan.
Gosh.
I didn't. There's nothing like that at all.
Are you sure?
I am.
Fine. You neither asked them for anything nor received anything.
Right.
- Exactly. - Don't be ridiculous.
Gosh, it hurts so much. Darn it
Then, why are you hiding now?
- It's just for... - Tell us already!
Are you sure? Are you really innocent?
I am! I am really innocent!
Why do you hit the same spot? It aches a lot.
- Dad, it's me. - What is it?
How is Mom?
She's the same.
I'm relieved since Seong Hoon...
and Hee Sook are with Seong Sik in his office now.
But I'm still worried about how things will turn out.
Don't worry too much. Seong Sik is an honest person.
It will be all right, Dad.
- Do you feel better now? - Sorry?
You were sweating this morning. Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come home early. I'll make you invigorating tea.
Okay.
You want to protect your dad.
Goodness. What did he do to him?
Do you really not remember anything?
What is it that you want to say?
Your dad...
is not your biological dad.
He told the orphanage that he is your biological father.
But he is not.
He's a silly man.
He fooled you completely.
I guess you needed to believe that you were related to one of them.
Only then, you would've endured your time there.
What...
What are you saying?
I'll tell you one more thing.
You shouldn't admire your father so much.
He's not so admirable after all.
What is it, Director Bang?
Please come in, Director Han.
- Hello. - Hi.
How have you been?
Please sit down, Director Han.
President Lee came to discuss a few things with us. Please sit.
All right.
You...
want to include a secret behind the character's birth?
Why? Will it be a problem?
Many Korean viewers like a plot with a secret behind someone's birth.
Some may think it is out-dated,
but we can't deny the fact that they do like it when it's in the plot.
Besides, in order to export this to every country in Asia,
this plot twist is an essential factor.
Don't you think so, Director Bang?
Yes, I agree with your assessment.
However,
this may be a bit over the line.
Over the line?
Yes. I believe so.
As you know, the genre of our drama is...
romantic comedy.
I am fully aware of that.
However, this isn't an unreasonable demand.
You can change the plot slightly.
There are some things that...
we can not give up on our end for the quality of the drama.
If we ask the writer to do such a thing,
you will put the writer in confusion.
The whole storyline might go wrong.
I personally believe a talented producer...
creates the highest profits...
without changing the writer's intention.
Don't patronize me.
- Pardon? - President Lee. What he meant...
I am not trying to patronize you.
In producing dramas, we have the upper hand from you.
I meant you would trust us regarding the production of the drama.
I understand where you are coming from.
However, right now you are not making any profits.
Isn't it better to make profits...
by all means for your team...
and for an investor like myself?
Please add in a secret behind the character's birth...
or I will personally meet the writer.
President Lee.
Why are you doing this to us?
I don't understand what you mean.
You said you would trust and leave it to us.
Of course.
That's why I have invested in the production.
However, once I start investing the money,
I tend to worry in advance.
- But still. - Do you think I am interfering?
Yes, I think so.
I'm sorry to hear that.
From my perspective, under the contract,
I'm merely exercising my right as an investor.
I'd be grateful if you can understand.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui. Did you make the presentation for this?
No, it's not done.
This is urgent. How could you have not finished this already?
Hold on one second.
- Mr. Park. Here's your coffee. - Thanks.
I will finish it before I go home.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui. Please finish your assignments in a timely manner.
Don't you know we're busy with new products for the upcoming season?
What's wrong?
Director Han. You are here.
Hello, Sir.
Ms. Oh Dong Hui. What are you doing here?
- Sorry? - Why did you come to work?
Shouldn't you be writing at home?
Well...
Director Han. We are very busy, too.
New products will be launching soon.
It doesn't matter. She is a writer who has to write scripts.
How can you make her do work like this?
We didn't mean any harm.
I told her to come to work.
Whether she is a writer or not,
the fact that she is our assistant hasn't changed.
Director Han. Can we have a moment?
What is it this time? Did something happen?
I have no clue.
I heard the investor came to visit.
The investor?
We have to comply with his demand.
I can't allow it.
So we are not going to accept any demands from the investors?
We can't bite the hands that feed us.
Do you want to ruin the drama?
We won't ruin it then.
Isn't it matter of the writer's ability?
We have to give them some breathing room.
In a romantic comedy of 16-episode drama, where can the writer...
include the secret behind the character's birth?
It's possible.
Bang Mi Joo.
Is this how you've been handling your business?
Seong Joon. Don't be dramatic. Try to compromise.
We can only produce the drama with the fund from the investor.
It doesn't change the fact that...
putting in the storyline is absurd.
All we need is good ratings for us to make profits!
Director Bang!
Ms. Hong. What was that?
Did Director Han just yell?
I think he did.
Did he yell because we told Ms. Oh Dong Hui to come to work?
No way.
Why are they fighting?
This is getting scary.
Do you think there's a problem?
Dong Hui. Do you know anything about this?
No.
- A secret of the character's birth? - Yes.
Why? Why do I have to include it?
I don't know.
This might sound funny, but the investor wants it in the drama.
It can't be. I have never thought about that possibility.
That makes two of us.
Dong Hui. In times like this, you can't be flustered.
You must get a hold of yourself.
Once the writer starts getting affected by other people,
from that point on, you won't be able to manage.
But if the investor demands it,
how can a novice writer like me refuse?
You have me.
I told you I would look out for you.
I don't know why I feel so lonely today.
I feel like...
there are only two of us in this entire world.
I will make sure you write what you want to write by any means.
You can do this, right?
Okay, then. I won't be swayed by the investor.
All right. Please write good scripts.
By the way, will you be okay with handling both work and the scripts?
I will try my best. I will ask for leave of absence time to time.
You don't have much time. Start writing now.
Let's talk more after you write.
Gosh.
Why are you here?
I told you that you don't need to come as often as before.
President, but still...
You have nothing to report.
My father passed away 23 years ago.
My brother died, then.
I have...
nothing left.
I should wrap up this revenge quickly.
I plan on returning to the US and throw a party.
President.
I think you've been drinking a lot lately.
I have nothing to live for nowadays.
Still, you should listen to the report regarding Han Seong Sik.
Right.
Then what has Han Seong Sik...
been doing lately?
He's been locked inside his office for two days.
Only he would do such a thing.
Try to finish him as soon as possible.
From the start, he was too interested in money, power,
reputation, and women.
I lost my interest since he was an easy prey.
Things will be settled in a few days.
By the way, what will you do about Seong Joon?
You said you'd take care of him yourself.
I'm writing a drama these days.
- Sir? - I'm writing a drama with him.
It's the most fun thing.
I'll take care of that,
so you should take care of Seong Sik as soon as possible.
Okay. I will do that.
Also...
- What is it now? - Today,
Jeong Eun contacted me.
She wants to close her coffee shop.
Let her do whatever she wants.
It seems like...
she's leaving for some place.
I'm not interested.
President.
I'm going to sleep. You should leave now.
(1 message)
It's me. Please answer your phone.
He's unbelievable.
If you don't answer the phone again, I will go to your place.
What?
He's crazy.
Gosh.
Fine. Do whatever you want.
I will never come back to Korea.
Gosh.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving Korea tonight, Mom.
Where are you going again?
I don't know. I will go wherever I can go with the cheapest flight.
What are you talking about?
You don't need me, do you? You have Dad.
How did you know that?
Did you meet your dad?
Since he's back, you should try to work things out with him.
Hey!
Don't hate him so much. He came back just for you.
I'll go now, Mom.
Hey! Jeong Eun!
What is she thinking?
Fine! I hope you're happy, you jerk!
How can you dump a girl like that?
We dated for four months,
and I gave you my heart, my love, and my body...
Anyway, I gave you everything, and you changed so quickly.
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
How dare you play with me?
Fine. I hope you're happy with your life.
I will never see you again.
I hope you will be unlucky for the next 30 years, you jerk.
What? Did you say you played with me?
Do you think you are the only one? I did as well.
I played well! I played well!
Thank you! Goodbye, you jerk!
Gosh!
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Your call will be charged after the beep.
She's not picking up the call.
What if she actually leaves?
Goodness.
Where did she go?
Please open the windows
- I miss you my darling - What is this now?
I can't sing without an accompaniment.
I have dreamed thee too long
But known thee
With all of my heart
Half a prayer, half a song
Thou hast always been with me
Though we have been always apart
- Dulcinea - Is he out of his mind?
- Dulcinea - Wait there.
I see heaven when I see thee
Dulcinea
And thy name is like a prayer
An angel whispers
Dulcinea
If I reach out to thee
Do not tremble and shrink
From the touch of my hand on thy hair
- Is this a dream - We're taking you in.
Wait.
Ae Ri. Ae Ri.
I'll come back tomorrow. Good night.
Let's go.
Ji Hoon.
Don't study if you don't want to.
I didn't tell you to study, did I?
So let's move out.
It's not that easy to move.
You can just find your peace of mind.
The problem is that I can't find my peace of mind.
Why can't you find your peace of mind?
Your biological mother is right here.
And yet you can't defy your former mom.
Don't do it if you don't want to.
Saying once a son, forever a son,
she always pushes me to study.
Then why are you angry at me...
for not wanting to study?
I can't believe this.
Ah In,
you don't have to study if you don't want to.
Since when did you care about Chinese characters?
You don't have to do it if you don't want to.
But Aunt will scold me if I don't do it.
What? This is unbelievable.
Ah In, whose daughter are you? Are you Aunt's daughter?
Tell me where you belong.
- What's up with you now? - Where is my bean?
Goodness. I can't believe I'm doing this.
Chang Soo.
What is it?
This is tough.
What's so tough?
It's not cooked enough.
Hey,
do you think I'm your servant?
Do you? You tell me to buy you an Italian songbook,
fill up the humidifier with water,
draw you a bath, and boil the beans.
Do you think I'm your servant?
My mom did all those things for me.
That's what I'm saying. Ask her to do it when she comes back.
You can't do that.
Once a mom, always a mom. You're my mom, too.
What?
Look.
I have to memorize these lyrics.
Could you bring me a cup of water?
What?
Listen up, everyone!
Hee Sook isn't home right now.
If you don't want to study, don't study.
If you want water, get it yourself with your own hands.
Do you understand?
You'd better...
stay quiet today.
I will give you a good scolding if you upset me in any way!
Hello?
A piano?
The chest?
Sir!
I never said I wanted to sell this!
We've already closed the bargain, Ma'am.
That's not important right now!
We're taking this chest in exchange...
for a discount on the piano. I told you already. See?
I don't care. You can't take this!
- Let's go. - No. You can't do this.
- Let it go, Ma'am. - No! Put it down!
Put it down!
Put it down, Sir! Hey!
- Is it fun, Ah In? - Yes.
Do you play the piano now, Chang Soo?
Yes. I should learn how to play the piano...
to become a great opera singer.
Yes.
Put Hee Sook on the phone right now.
She's there, isn't she?
Really?
Did she really sell your chest without talking to you about it?
My goodness.
I took a day off...
and stayed home because the kids are on their spring vacation.
Hee Sook sent guys to take...
my chest, the article that my parents left me.
Put her on the phone now.
I'm going to kill her today.
She disguised herself as the cafe owner...
and went out to buy food.
Gosh, what?
I can't believe her.
You should come home, then.
I'm too upset that I'm going crazy here.
Hye Joo. I know how you feel,
but I can't just leave right now.
What does it have to do with you? You can just leave!
Well... Actually,
it's partly my fault that this happened to Seong Sik.
Why is it your fault?
Do you know Reporter Yim from Jinsung Daily News I worked with?
He came to see me a few days ago.
He asked me for documents on the corrupt relationship...
between Minjeong Party and Seonghan Group, so I gave them to him.
Seong Sik of all people got involved in it.
Really?
It's driving me crazy now.
Seong Hoon.
What did you just say, Seong Hoon?
When did you get back?
Did you say...
you handed over documents to Jinsung Daily News?
Let me explain, Seong Sik.
How... How could you do this to me, Seong Hoon?
How could you do this to your brother? How could you?
- How? - Wait, Seong Sik.
Seong Sik. What's wrong?
How could you do this to me?
Seong Hoon. Why is he doing this?
What's wrong, Seong Sik? Let go of him first.
Get off of me.
How could you...
help people ruin your brother?
What kind of a person does that?
Who does that?
- Who? - It's not that, Seong Sik.
Let me explain.
Seong Hoon!
- Seong Hoon! - I'm sorry.
How can this be?
Ms. Hwang.
Why don't you get up and eat some porridge?
No. I don't want to eat anything.
Come on now. Please get up.
- Gosh. - Here.
Everything tastes bitter.
My grandson is on the front page of the newspaper...
for doing something bad.
I'm his grandmother. How can I be eating now?
Don't say that. You should eat.
Well, it's not something so terrible.
He wasn't arrested or anything.
Arrested?
How can you say that?
What I'm trying to say is...
it may turn out to be something not so serious.
Sometimes you get into trouble,
and sometimes you have bad things happen to you.
Besides, your second grandson was on...
many TV shows.
He has been on everyone's lips.
That's what I'm saying.
He always has been so fond of the limelight.
I knew something like this would happen to him someday.
My goodness. Ms. Hwang.
Please calm down.
I'm going out.
Please eat the porridge when you feel better.
We're old women.
If we worry too much, we will soon die.
Please try to ease your mind, okay?
Are you Ms. Oh Dong Hui?
Yes, President Bang.
I see.
I heard you were signing the contract today.
I just called you here to meet you. Don't be scared.
I'm not, Sir.
Your grandmother is Ms. Oh Gui Boon, right?
How do you know my grandmother?
I grew up eating the food your grandmother made.
Did you?
I didn't know.
I guess she didn't tell you. That's disappointing.
You're her granddaughter,
so that'd make you my niece.
You can relax. Treat me like your uncle.
Pardon?
I heard both of your parents passed away.
Yes. They died when I was little.
That's why my grandmother raised me.
You look much better in person.
You don't resemble your grandmother at all.
By the way,
you somehow look familiar to me.
My grandmother...
always told me that I look just like my mother.
Is that so?
Did you...
know my parents well, by any chance?
I'm not sure about that.
I don't know if your parents are the ones I knew or not.
Anyhow, congratulations on becoming...
our company's scriptwriter.
I hope to see you often.
Yes, Sir.
Dong Hui. Can I talk to you for a second?
Why didn't Director Han come to work today? Is everything okay?
Sorry?
I'm not sure why he didn't.
Didn't you two come to work together?
You don't like us coming to work together.
Are you messing with me right now?
Did you have to push ahead...
to include a secret behind the character's birth?
What?
Director Han had a hard time because of it.
You know better than anyone that he hates those things.
What about you? What do you think?
I guess we can include it when it's absolutely necessary,
but I'm opposed to it if it's merely for the ratings.
There must be a reason why we have to have such a setting.
You've become so arrogant.
Do you think you're a sought-after writer or something? Listen.
If we fail to attract investors, Director Han will be fired.
If that's not what you want,
you'd better think about it again.
Mom,
I really didn't know...
you'd gladly say okay and come here.
House chores are...
much better than cleaning apartment buildings.
That's right.
Now that you're here,
I feel like we've gone back to the old days.
I'm glad to hear that.
Where are you going? Please take a seat.
You stayed until we finish our meals...
and served more side dishes as well.
Let's not talk about the past.
Why not?
Is it because it reminds you of Gwang Ho?
You know...
Gwang Ho is dead, right?
I do.
How did you know that?
It's been reported in newspapers. He had a boat accident.
That's right. You saw it in newspapers.
By the way,
you didn't come to his funeral, did you?
I told you my life was too hectic at that time.
That's nonsense.
You favoured Gwang Ho a lot more than me.
When did I favor Gwang Ho more?
Are you sure you didn't?
President and you...
loved him more than you loved me.
You didn't pay attention to me at all.
That's not true.
If you keep saying such nonsense,
- I won't come here anymore. - You won't come here?
I know you came here for a reason.
What do you mean by that?
I called you and visited you so often,
so you decided to have a close watch...
on me here, while avoiding unnecessary misunderstandings.
Isn't that why you're here?
What... What did you say?
Or...
are you here because you miss my mother...
who's gone missing?
What on earth are you talking about?
It doesn't matter. I live alone since my wife died.
I'm happy to be with you here.
Mom, please put some egg on it.
Please, Mom.
I want to eat it. Please.
Director Han, are you in?
Are you in?
Why does Seong Sik make me worried all the time?
Dong Hui.
What are you doing there?
Why are you knocking...
on the door of Seong Joon's room at this late hour?
I have something to tell him.
Seong Joon is still at work.
Okay. I am sorry.
Dong Hui,
enough is enough.
- Sorry? - Do you know what happened to us?
Everyone of my family is anxious and disturbed at this moment.
And do you want to fool around in Seong Joon's room that badly?
- I just... - Be quiet. I don't want excuses!
You're living off us now. Then, you should behave at least!
Why are you so slow-witted? Are you a kid?
I apologize. I'm so sorry.
Both the broadcasting station and my company liked the scenario...
because it isn't clichd at all...
and unique.
We cannot get rid of such charms.
Why do you not like it?
You also have a secret behind your birth.
What are you trying to tell me?
I thought we'd speak the same language...
as we both were raised in an orphanage.
A man encounters a wrongful death...
and leaves his two sons.
Since then, the two sons are separated...
from each other for more than 20 years,
unable to know whether their brother is still alive.
One of them is looking for his brother,
but it's not easy at all.
If the other one also had tried to find his brother,
they might have been able to meet earlier.
Isn't it dramatic?
Mr. Lee,
I'm sorry about your private matter.
Yet, bringing it to the plot is unacceptable.
I told you...
what investors expect. I invested my money,
then it should produce good results.
That's how I'm able to run a world-class investment company.
I thought you were polite and sincere,
but I was wrong.
You privately hired your in-law who lives in your rooftop as a writer.
I didn't hire her because she's my in-law.
You would know if you read her scenario.
There are countless writers who can write like her.
I think...
you failed to put your personal feelings aside.
That's not true.
Moreover,
you visit an investor without making an appointment...
and complain about his decision without presenting any base data.
You were raised by a father who only cares about his children...
and spent a comfortable childhood.
- I guess that's why you're rude. - If you felt that way, I apologize.
But you've crossed the line.
Why?
Did I offend you by mentioning your father?
Yes, you did.
But I know quite a lot about your father.
Everyone has their dark side.
- What are you talking about? - All fathers have...
their own ugly side they want to hide...
from their children.
And your father is no different.
We need to meet now.
Goodness.
Why didn't you call me earlier?
I stayed here all day long to decide the location of my store.
We could've had dinner together if you had called me earlier.
I called you because I have a few questions.
A question?
What's that?
Are you...
my birth mother?
What did you say?
Please answer me.
Hey, you're such a rude brat.
It took a long time for you to ask that question.
Just tell me the truth.
Gosh, how scary.
I'm too scared to tell you the truth.
Listen.
I assumed it when you just left without a word...
after giving me the money. You shouldn't be like this.
Your late father will resent you.
What do you mean?
I said your late father will resent you.
Do you know my birth father?
Of course.
When you were little, your father brought you to my store...
whenever he wanted to drink.
No. I only have one father.
That's what I've always believed.
That's why the father you have now is such a bad man.
He deceived you completely.
Do you know that?
Director Han.
What's wrong? Did something happen to you today?
I think I can include a secret behind the character's birth.
I've given it some thought.
Dong Hui.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Never mind.
What's the matter? What is it?
What's wrong?
I was...
adopted by this family when I was seven.
Up until now,
I thought I was a child my father had with another woman.
No.
To be exact, I chose...
to believe that.
How could that be?
There hasn't been any problem so far.
I've been happy.
But everything seems to be...
so confusing right now.
I don't know what the truth is,
or whether I should know the truth or not.
I don't know...
why this is happening to me.
I don't know any of that.
Director Han.
I don't know what I should do.
I'm so confused.
I don't know where things went wrong,
and...
what happens to the things I've believed until now.
I feel like dying.
Director Han.
Don't do this.
I know you're a strong person.
Please calm down.
Don't cry.
You're making me want to cry, too.
What are you doing?
Seon Mi is doing a good job.
They're going to eat and drink all night.
People just love free stuff.
- This is great. - Can I have some more beer?
What did you tell them the free food was for?
I told them today is the day my brother died.
I told them I was feeding chicken to people...
in my dead brother's age to honor him.
Gosh, Seong Hoon!
This is all your fault!
You handed over the documents!
Lower your voice, you brat.
What are you doing?
We've got to go home.
Be quiet and duck down.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Are we safe now, Seong Hoon?
Let's go home.
Gosh, Hee Sook.
Well done.
Let's go in.
Gosh, I'm so tired.
- It's Han Seong Sik. - That's Han Seong Sik!
- Oh my goodness. - Wait!
- Stop! - What are you doing?
Is it true that you illegally counselled...
Seonghan Group to be nominated to Minjeong Party?
No, it's not.
Did you really play a role as a broker...
for Minjeong Party and Seonghan Group?
No, he didn't. Don't do this.
- He doesn't know anything. - Come, Seong Sik.
- Stop it already. - Are you having an affair...
with Jang Yoo Ra, the news anchor?
Is it true that you bribed an official for Jang Yoo Ra?
How is she related to your illegal counselling?
What are they talking about?
Seong Hoon. I don't know anything about this.
I really don't know.
You are...
having an affair with her?
What are they talking about?
What's your relationship with Jang Yoo Ra?
Just die.
Die! Why don't you just die?
- My goodness, you brat. - Die!
- Rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'll be...
your dad from now on.
What?
From now on,
I'll be your dad.
What?
Let's go home with me.
Come on.
Should I give you a piggyback ride?
All right.
Hold on tight.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
What did you say to Seong Joon? What did you say?
Don't worry. I didn't tell him anything too important.
What is this whole thing about the accident and the revenge?
Your cousin Jeong Ah was injured very badly.
Hyun Jeong? Right, I remember her.
Why did you come here?
- We can't go to a hotel. - A hotel?
Who am I? Why did you take me from the orphanage?