- Rock-paper-scissors.
Hey.
Who are you?
I'll be...
your dad from now on.
What?
From now on,
I'll be your dad.
What?
Let's go home with me.
Come on.
Should I give you a piggyback ride?
All right.
Hold on tight.
- What's going on?
- I'm in front of...
Attorney Han Seong Sik's home.
He already went in a long time ago.
- Excuse me? Okay.
- Why don't you call him?
- Goodness.
- He already went in.
Lately, our neighborhood has become noisy.
President. Please get in.
Yes.
My gosh.
Isn't that Mr. Lee?
Goodness. So the rumor was true after all.
Mr. Lee has all the
power, not President Jo.
Why don't you just die?
- I'd rather have you dead.
- Mom.
That's not what really happened.
Please hear my side of the story.
Hear your side? We already read
it in the newspaper and on TV.
Why would we listen to it again when
we already know what happened, jerk?
If you are going to cause
trouble and break our hearts,
I'd rather have you dead.
Just go outside and die.
Mom.
Do you really wish that I die?
It's better to have a dead son than...
have an embarrassing son
who went to prison.
I won't go to prison.
I did many things,
but I can argue that I didn't
do anything illegal...
in the end.
Then, why are those reporters all
clustered in front of our house?
It's because they like to exaggerate
and make it into a big deal.
- Lower your voice.
- Seong Hoon, shut it.
It's all your fault.
I warned you before.
What do you mean this
is Seong Hoon's fault?
Father, well...
Seong Sik, don't drag Seong Hoon into this.
I lived too long.
- Mother, what's wrong?
- It's because I lived too long...
that I will end up watching my
grandson get sent to prison.
Grandmother, I said I won't go to prison.
Mother. What is all this?
I packed a few things like
toothbrush, toothpaste, and towels.
We don't have much time.
Hyung Seop. Send him overseas immediately.
Seong Sik. You can speak English, right?
Don't go to the questioning
by the prosecution and...
don't come to Korea. Understood?
Grandmother.
You only saw bad things on TV.
A crook like him is already
banned from leaving the country.
He's banned.
You're his brother. How
can you say such a thing?
Grandmother. Seong Sik went too far
and got involved in a bad deal.
By the way, what's going on with
Jang Yoo Ra, the news anchor?
Right. What is your relationship with...
Jang Yoo Ra?
- Grandmother.
- Answer me now!
Grandmother. It's... It's...
It's nothing.
Don't you dare lie to us.
If it's nothing, why would they
print it on the newspaper?
- You should just go inside.
- I am going to die.
I will be the one who dies.
Did you go to have dinner with this woman?
Goodness. Did you go to the gym together?
Mother.
It's not true.
- Hold on.
- Tell me.
You'd better tell me right now.
Tell you what?
This woman.
What is your relationship with this woman?
I asked you a question!
Nothing is going on between us.
We just had dinner once and
worked out at the gym once.
Is that all?
Yes. That is all. So what
are you going to do?
If so, how did your alleged
scandal end up in the newspaper?
I can't...
live...
because you have humiliated me.
- I can't live now.
- Wait.
You are pulling all of my hair out.
I am busy taking care of the children.
While I looked after the
children, you had an affair?
- I didn't have an affair.
- Goodness. He's pathetic.
By the way, what's up with your outfit?
I had no choice. There
was a gang of reporters.
I needed a plan to escape.
What is this? Is this Chang Soo's piano?
Are you all right?
I am not.
I won't let Hee Sook get away with this.
Wait. Honey.
Tell me right now.
- Goodness. I'm going to...
- Hey.
Hye Joo.
Just for today, you should
hold back your anger.
- All right.
- Honey. Find my chest, please.
Okay, I will.
- I will find it for you.
- I won't let it slide.
My goodness.
How can Mother pack a
suitcase for Seong Sik?
I told you to go inside and lie down.
What are you doing here?
When is he scheduled to present
himself to the prosecution?
It's the day after tomorrow.
I am going to give him a good scolding.
He has to pay for his actions
if there is any misconduct.
Honey.
What can we do? How can he
not face the consequences?
Appearing on that TV show was the problem.
That was the cause.
He should have diligently
pursued his path as a lawyer.
That's my point.
Seong Joon.
Father.
Where have you been?
The house was in chaos because
of your brother, Seong Sik.
You should've stayed at home...
and tried to be of help to your brothers.
Where have you been all this time?
Honey, why are you taking
it out on Seong Joon?
If he were here, would his
presence solve this problem?
I am sorry, Mother.
My goodness. I am incredibly upset.
Seong Joon.
Don't be disheartened by
what your mother said.
You know she's just upset
because of Seong Sik.
I'm okay.
She's been taking her anger
out on everyone lately.
Don't take it so hard, okay?
I'll go buy some relaxing
pills for your mom.
Dad.
- Yes?
- Can we talk outside?
What's the matter? Did
something happen to you?
My goodness.
Dad.
Yes?
- I've got something to tell you.
- What is it?
I mean...
To be honest,
I have some questions to ask you.
Ask me anything.
Tell me already.
Don't just look at me. Go ahead.
I...
went to the orphanage today.
The orphanage? What orphanage?
The orphanage...
you took me from when I was young.
- Seong Joon.
- I remembered my childhood.
You came...
and told me to come with you one day.
I also remember...
that you carried me on your back.
What on earth are you talking about?
And I remember...
Mom cried so sadly on the
first day I got home.
- That was...
- And you said this.
You said I was your son,
and you had me stay in the
orphanage for some reasons...
and brought back today.
I believed that...
for my entire life.
So I've never tried to find...
my biological father...
or wondered who my biological mother is.
All I needed was...
just you, Dad.
- What's wrong with you?
- I still have no father...
other than you.
Seong Joon...
But I just want to know...
who I really am.
I want to know...
where I am from and how you found me...
at the orphanage.
Please just answer these questions.
Then I'll stay by your side
for the rest of my life,
no matter what others say about you.
I'll live by your side
just like I have been...
up until now.
Dad,
I really admire you.
And I love you so much.
But I need you to answer me.
Who am I?
Why did you take me home
from the orphanage?
Please tell me.
Dad...
The career women are our
main target customers.
As they tend to enjoy
their hobby after work,
we plan to let them enjoy it
anytime and anywhere as they want.
What specifically is the concept then?
I'll elaborate further
on it at the next slide.
Please turn over the slide.
Hey, Dong Hui.
Yes.
As you can see, it's "Night Fitness".
It's a program to help the ladies...
who enjoy yoga at night...
to have more nicely fit
and colorful bodies.
Let me move on.
Director Han didn't even
attend the showcase.
And why does he have a long face?
This is frightening.
But Director Bang attended.
There's no need for both
of them to attend it.
Still, why is he so depressed?
- What do you think?
- Goodness.
These are the 1st and 2nd episodes
of Writer Choi's scenario. Read it.
- Are they already ready?
- I'm worried about Dong Hui.
I don't know if she's
working on her scenario.
Director.
Writer Choi already finished the scenario.
Sorry?
I see.
What do you think about the idea
to create a new brand line?
I think that sounds great.
I have high expectations for this
spring and summer collections.
This way, please.
How could you be distracted at that moment?
If you're that reluctant to
work, just quit your job.
- I am sorry.
- Dong Hui.
Do you think you've become a
great writer or something?
I don't care what you write. Just
don't forget what your job here is.
You even made me nervous!
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't you know...
how important the presentation was to me?
You're an assistant. You should
be able to assist us well.
- Seriously.
- Dong Hui.
Hello, Director Han.
Dong Hui, I need you to come with me.
Where are you taking her?
We have a meeting with the director
at the broadcasting station. Okay?
Fine.
Why is he holding her wrist like that?
What's gotten into him?
I think there's something going on...
between the two.
Shoot.
Where is Director Han?
Well, I saw him leaving.
Director,
he went to the broadcasting
station with Dong Hui.
Sorry?
Why are we here?
We can't go to a hotel, though.
A hotel?
Gosh.
Dong Hui, have some sleep.
You stayed up all night
writing the scenario, right?
- How did you know that?
- What do you think?
Of course, I went up to the rooftop.
Why were you awake at that time?
I had trouble sleeping.
Did you find out anything at the orphanage?
Well,
nothing special happened.
What do you mean? You went all
the way there for a reason.
I didn't want to ask anything to anybody.
What matters the most is how I feel inside.
That's why you couldn't
sleep last night at all.
Right.
What is this?
I feel sorry for you, Director.
I know how hard and painful it is.
I told you. I also grew
up without my parents,
so I had to create my
parents in my imagination.
But I had my grandmother with me,
and you had your parents.
I guess we are blessed enough.
So don't be too depressed.
It feels nice.
Sorry?
Your hand.
Don't say you thought of me as Moong Chi.
The lunch hour will end soon.
Have some sleep.
Okay.
Close your eyes.
You're not allowed to open your
eyes for the next one hour.
If you do, I'll be really mad at you.
By the way, would Moong
Chi be doing all right?
Why are you talking about
her out of the blue?
As I closed my eyes,
I see Moong Chi, who is as white as snow.
Did you really think about Moong
Chi when you patted my head?
Come on, Dong Hui.
Sleep tight.
It served drinks and meat until recently.
It's not bad.
Come out. Now.
Mr. Han.
Stop it.
Come out.
Mr. Han. Mr. Han!
What's wrong with you?
What did you tell Seong Joon? Tell me now.
I just told him the truth.
What?
Don't worry. I didn't tell
him the crucial part.
Why are you doing this to me?
Why did you show up all of a
sudden and interfere with my life?
I told you...
to help me since we used
to be close before.
You were on a roll...
as you were working for
a large firm back then.
Your house was the most
expensive in this neighborhood.
It's become quite shabby now, though.
I need more money.
They asked me to pay a premium
even for that small store.
I have to sign the contract today.
Although Seong Joon gave me
some money, it's not enough.
Did you ask him for money?
Why? Is there anything wrong with it?
You didn't give me money,
so your son did for you.
Do you really want to get nasty?
Stop it.
Director, Director Bang
was looking for you.
I know. We talked on the phone.
Dong Hui,
where have you been through the lunch time?
Dong Hui, I need you to revise
the scenario according to...
the director's opinions and
hand it in as soon as you can.
I will.
I guess they really had a meeting.
Director, you have a guest.
A guest?
Seong Joon.
I am sorry...
for waiting in an empty office.
Please excuse me.
What brings you here?
Let's sit down first.
So you decided to add the secret
behind the birth to the scenario.
Our writer went through some trouble.
There's no writer who
don't work hard like her.
The reason I came here...
is to discuss about the casting.
- Casting?
- Yes.
I selected some.
Aren't they members of idol groups?
They're very popular which
will secure the high ratings.
Now, you are...
meddling in casting matter as well?
They don't have any
acting experience at all.
I'm sure they can learn through this drama.
Gosh, why are they so serious?
Is he fighting with the investor?
I'll get going then.
President Lee.
You can't keep doing this.
As I told you earlier,
I'll exert my right as much
as I invested as an investor.
Don't feel too bad.
Please take my opinion into consideration.
Hyun Woo.
Tell me who you really are.
What...
did you just say?
I asked who you really are.
Seong Joon,
do you really not know who I am?
I do.
You're a investor of our project
and live across from my house.
I wasn't going to mention this,
but do you know...
what kind of situation Seong Sik is in?
Does it...
have anything to do with me?
There must be a misunderstanding.
Seong Sik begged me for help,
so I just introduced him to others.
That was my good will.
Do I have to be criticized for that?
I did it for him out of
good will, and that was it.
The one to be blamed is Seong Sik...
who crossed the line, isn't it?
Let's not bring the private
issues to the work.
You're not that naive.
Hello.
- He's here!
- He's here.
How did you get to know
President Lee of Seonghan?
You've become an official
candidate of Minjeong Party.
There's a rumor that you
were nominated in return...
for being engaged in the collusion
between Seonghan and Minjeong Party.
I... I will...
tell...
everything...
to the prosecution.
I need to get going.
Are you aware that Jang Yoo
Ra is getting married soon?
- Pardon?
- Jang Yoo Ra said...
she plans to file a libel suit against you.
Do you know about this?
Sorry? Is Yoo Ra...
I mean, is Anchor Jang...
really getting married?
Seoul Central Prosecutor's
Office charged President Lee...
of Seonghan without detention...
for providing a slush
fund to Minjeong Party.
The prosecution also summoned
Attorney Han Seong Sik...
to be questioned as a testifier.
Attorney Han told the reporters...
that he will tell everything
to the prosecution...
before he entered the building.
The Korean Bar Association stated,
it submitted Attorney Han's
scandals regarding...
the illegal advice and the
relationship with Anchor Jang...
- to the Ethic Committee.
- This is driving me crazy.
He loved to appear on television so much,
and his dream has come true today.
I can't handle this, Mother.
But he said he did nothing illicit.
Still...
Hee Sook, are you all right?
Grandmother, Mother.
I think...
I should...
leave now.
Sure.
Hee Sook, don't be too sad.
What if they get a divorce?
I am really worried about that, Mother.
So am I. Goodness.
Mom.
Yes.
Yes, Chang Soo.
- Did your piano teacher leave?
- She just left.
I see.
What's happening with Dad?
Everyone's talking about
him on the internet.
Chang Soo.
I told you not to go online while
playing the piano, didn't I?
My friend called me.
Mom, what will you do about Dad?
What do you mean what will I do about him?
First,
I should send you kids to college.
- What?
- Let's study now.
Go to your room and bring out your books.
Okay.
What are you doing, kids?
Aunt.
Pack up your books and come upstairs.
Hurry up. Sit down and open your books.
Don't mind what's going on in the family.
It's the adults' business, and
the adults will take care of it.
As high school students...
and as a preschool student,
you should carry out your duties.
Just mind your own business.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
Ji Hoon, why aren't you answering?
Ji Hoon. Ji Hoon.
Do you have to do this?
What do you mean?
Do we have to study like this?
We are not prisoners.
Until when do we have to
study under your watch?
You know the answer. It's until
you get into college, of course.
You won't study unless
you are being watched.
Can't we solve our own problems, too?
- What?
- Ji Hoon,
just be quiet and study.
You be quiet. Since when did you
become so keen on studying?
You're so annoying these days.
- What did you say?
- Ji Hoon,
you should study when I tell you nicely.
Why are you talking back to me every
time I tell you to do something?
So just tell your son to study...
- and play the piano.
- Han Ji Hoon!
How dare you talk to Mom like that?
- Chang Soo.
- Just raise your son well.
What? "Just raise your son well"?
What did you just say?
- Are you done?
- No, I am not.
I'm not done.
I am so sick of this.
Just raise your son Chang Soo well.
What?
Hey. What's going on?
Ji Hoon.
You guys go downstairs, too.
- Okay.
I need to talk to you.
I have nothing to say. You should go...
and talk to Ji Hoon.
I have too many things to say to you.
First of all,
the chest I inherited from my parents,
it used to sit where the piano is.
How could you sell it without
discussing it with me?
I discussed it with you, didn't I?
When did you discuss it with me?
You just informed me your
plan and carried it out.
Also, who do you think you are
to force my kids to study?
Your son is the boy who
puts oil on his hair,
uses his dad's toner,
and eats a piece of bean as a snack.
You are that boy's mother.
So I beg you.
You should differentiate
your child from mine,
and stop intruding on our privacy.
But we live in the same house,
and I see them all the time.
When I see Ji Hoon and Ah In play,
I can clearly see how they
will turn out in the future.
So how can I just watch them?
How do you know what will become
of them when they grow up?
There's only one thing they can
become of when they play like that.
A loser. A loser.
They will be a failure.
Goodness. What?
A loser? A failure?
I wasn't going to say this,
but I guess I have to.
Look what happened to your winner husband.
What are you trying to say?
Your husband was a great
student all along his life,
and he managed to enter a good
college and become a lawyer.
But what happened to your
successful husband? What?
What's the point of being smart?
He uses his smart brain...
to do everything illegal.
- Hye Joo.
- I'm sorry to offend you,
but you need to know the truth.
In my opinion, those who
used to be good students...
commit more bad things in life.
They harm more people, too!
Do you know that?
He got involved in this...
because he wasn't smart enough.
What? What did you say?
Had he studied harder and
graduated first in his class,
he would've gotten picked
up by a famous law firm.
If he was a part of a big law firm,
he wouldn't have gotten into
such trouble so helplessly.
Hee Sook, you are really sick, aren't you?
Never mind. Let's stop this. I
need to get the kids to study.
Hey, you can't go.
Let go of me.
You can't go!
- Hye Joo!
- What?
Gosh.
Please help us, Mr. Lee.
Please help my brother.
I'm in a difficult position.
- I shouldn't have introduced them.
- No.
I know that you meant well.
It's him who messed up.
He jumped into it without knowing
that it was going to kill him.
He's an idiot.
I don't know how I can help him.
I heard...
that you are no ordinary person.
- What?
- When you have those connections,
you can't just be a construction manager.
I am sorry.
I didn't mean to trick you.
I am running an investment
company in the US.
I was looking for other
investment opportunities,
and I developed interest in
Korean real estate market.
No wonder.
I thought acting like a rich person...
would just attrack scammers.
I apologize if I have offended you.
No, there's no need for you to apologize.
So...
please help my brother Seong Sik.
I did provide the cause after all.
So I will look into it.
Thank you so much. Thank you, Mr. Lee.
Even if he avoids the criminal punishment,
he will still have to pay the fine
and get his license suspended.
There's also the affair with Jang Yoo Ra.
Isn't that enough...
to make him lose his place in the society?
He won't be able to go on TV anymore,
and he will no longer be a lawyer.
That's true.
We still have to be...
good neighbors to them.
We're not after...
- Seong Sik anyway.
- Right.
I am tired. I'll see you tomorrow.
Wait.
Do you really want to get rid of...
Jeong Eun's coffee shop?
Didn't I tell you to do that?
Okay, Sir.
Did she leave Korea again?
It's as if three years of wandering
wasn't enough. Where did she go?
Open your heart to me
My dear Ae Ri
I can't sing without an accompaniment.
I have dreamed thee too long
But known thee
- With all of my heart - What is this now?
This jerk.
Is this a dream?
I just want to know
If this is a reality or not
Dulcinea
I see heaven when I see thee
Thy name is like a prayer
An angel whispers
Dulcinea
If I reach out to thee,
do not tremble and shrink
From the touch of my hand on thy hair
Is this a dream?
I just want to know
If this is a reality or not
- Dulcinea - Accompany us to the station.
I have lived for thee
Dulcinea
Lock him up well so that
he never comes back.
Even if they do, they can't
imprison my love for you.
Ae Ri. Wait for me. I
will be back tomorrow.
Good night.
What did you just say?
Let go of me. I will go myself.
Thank you.
Has he gone crazy?
It's so embarrassing. How
can he do this every night?
The more I think about it, I can't
leave like this. This is so unfair.
I've already said this so many times.
I have given him my everything.
He's going to treat me like this?
I can't let him do that.
I won't let him.
- Ma'am.
- You startled me.
I will call you right back, Ma'am.
What's up with you?
Didn't you say you were leaving?
Why are you still here?
I didn't leave.
Why?
I've thought about it for
two days at the airport.
I can't leave because
this is unfair for me.
What is so unfair for you?
There are a few things.
Anyway, don't sell my coffee shop.
I have to continue with it.
What are you talking about? An
interested tenant has surfaced.
What?
Look here.
Speak of the devil.
I'm sorry.
President. It's Jeong Eun.
I'm looking at her, too.
"One runs into one's worst enemy
at the worst place and time."
I'm glad I ran into you.
Get off right now. We need to talk.
President.
Let's go.
They are such jerks.
To be frank,
Jeong Eun called me this morning.
She demanded compensation
for recent happenings.
She said she won't let
you get away with this.
What did she ask for?
She demanded to give her the coffee shop.
Let her have it.
Okay, Sir.
Is that so?
Can I do that?
Okay. I understand.
Please do what I have asked you.
All right.
I took care of it.
President.
I'm glad...
that she is still brave.
Goodness. You are unbelievable.
Are you a thug? How can
you steal his property?
He gave it to me and I will
take it because I deserve it.
Jeong Eun.
You know President Jo
Moo Gyeom and Mr. Lee?
They seem strange.
How strange?
At some point, there was a weird rumor.
The rumor was it was Mr. Lee who
bought all the properties...
in this neighborhood, not President Jo.
Pardon?
It was Hyun Woo who bought
all the properties here?
That's what I'm saying.
That's why I said you are unbelievable.
Everyone lost their property to Mr. Lee,
but you managed to take one from Mr. Lee.
There's something fishy about Mr. Lee.
Don't you think so?
Why did he have to pretend
to be a manager...
on a construction site
in this neighborhood?
Why did he pretend to belong
to the working class?
Why did he hide his identity?
That's not all.
After he moved into the neighborhood,
a lot of weird things happened here.
That's why Mal Ja even
performed an exorcism.
She performed an exorcism?
Yes, she did.
She said the spirit of the driver
who got into a car accident...
came to our neighborhood.
She said one of his sons
came to take revenge on her.
Excuse me? What did you just say?
What accident and what revenge?
Don't you remember at all?
Your cousin, Jeong Hwa was badly hurt.
The driver...
ended up hanging himself with his tie.
The case was settled.
The driver had two sons.
I heard both of them were
sent to the orphanage.
No one knows what happened
to them afterward.
Mal Ja's claim is that his son
came to have his revenge.
A driver who committed suicide.
And two sons.
I must have been blinded by love.
I couldn't see what was
right in front of me...
because of a guy.
Leave immediately with this.
Don't ever show your face here.
I can't understand this.
Just tell Seong Joon that he is...
the son of the driver.
It's not like you killed him.
Why are you hiding it?
Shut it.
How dare you.
Seong Joon has reached a marriageable age.
All he has to do now is to get married,
have children, and live a happy life.
I don't want to...
hurt him by bringing up his past.
The same applies to my family.
But still. You shouldn't have told
him he was born out of wedlock.
Your wife must have given you a hard time.
Leave now.
Please go back where you came from.
Anyway,
that alcoholic man...
came to drink to my bar
and drank on credit.
I fed the children, but he
never paid for the food.
My mother and I were really annoyed.
Who knew that he was going
to help us after 20 years?
If I had known, I would've
fed them more food.
Do you still not know what happened
to Seong Joon's older brother?
Don't you remember? He
had an older brother.
Anyway, I'm going now.
I won't show up again, so don't worry.
It's even hard to eat now, Mother.
You still have to eat. Come on.
Scoop some rice.
Gosh.
It will arouse your appetite. Eat
up and get your strength back.
Where did Hyung Seop go
at a time like this?
I haven't seen him all day.
I know, right?
He's so busy these days. He
hasn't been of any help.
I feel...
so ashamed to face Ms. Oh.
Don't mind her.
How can I not mind her? She's
a very streetwise person.
She's seeing a man these days. She
always goes out to cook him meals.
Where does she go?
You should eat slowly.
Although you're an old man with gray hair,
you eat just like how you used
to eat when you were little.
Come on, Mom.
It's hard to change one's eating habits.
Also, I had gray hair...
since I was in high school.
Even so, try to eat slowly.
You're a middle-aged man with gray hair.
It makes you look crude.
Gosh. Now that I don't have a wife,
you're nagging me instead.
I always wanted to ask you this.
Why did your wife die so young?
After a few years of struggle
with pancreatic cancer, she died.
It was when Mi Joo was in high school.
It was hard on both Mi Joo and me.
My mother, that old grump,
used to be so mean...
to my wife.
How can you call your own
mother an old grump?
She is an old grump.
- You can't say that she's young.
- My goodness.
You're such an ungrateful person.
Mom. Can you fry two eggs for me?
Okay. Give me a minute.
Dad, I'm home.
Hi, Mi Joo.
- How have you been?
- You remember her, right?
Yes.
She's been coming to our house
to cook since a week ago.
You haven't seen her here
because you've been busy.
Is that so? It's good to see you again.
Yes.
Why don't you have a seat?
I'm happy to see you, too.
I suppose you haven't had dinner yet.
- Mom.
- Yes.
Make dinner for Mi Joo, too.
You should eat with us, too.
Okay.
Here you go, Mom. Eat up.
I am eating.
You two seem like real mother and son.
Really?
Thank you. I'll take it as a compliment.
By the way, how old are you now?
My gosh, Mom.
She's around the same age as Hyun Jeong.
Your face turned all pale again.
Hyun Jeong?
Who is Hyun Jeong?
Oh, you mean...
Excuse me.
Hello, Director.
Writer Choi finished the script, but
Dong Hui hasn't finished it yet.
I'm going to urge her
to finish it tomorrow.
If she can't finish it on time,
we'll go with Writer Choi's script.
How could Writer Choi
finish writing so fast?
That's not important. You should hurry up.
This is so unfair to me.
Didn't you know that from the beginning?
- This is so upsetting.
- You're talking too much.
I am still way cuter than Writer Choi.
Does that make you feel better?
You're a writer. You don't need to be cute.
Gosh. I'm just saying anything
because I'm too stressed out.
My goodness. Here. Eat this.
Jun Sung and Yeon Hee just met.
Try to develop the story fast.
Have them meet Woo Hyeon, too.
All right. By the way, it's about Mr.
Lee across the street.
He's unbelievable.
We've been acquainted, and we all
had a Christmas party together.
How can he pretend not to know us...
and push us to include a secret
behind the character's birth?
I actually don't like him very much.
I would punch him if he
wasn't our investor.
Anyway, he's a moron and a jerk.
Focus on the writing.
You're talking too much.
I feel like my heart
will burst with stress.
Now I understand why
writers smoke cigarettes.
- What did you just say?
- You startled me.
Why are you yelling?
If you start smoking and drinking...
thinking that's what writers do,
I won't just watch you do that.
Fine.
Here. Eat some more.
What?
What is it?
No. I can eat by myself.
You don't have to feed me.
- I wasn't aware.
- Gosh.
You've been just fine with
eating the food I feed you.
Whatever.
Hi, Dad.
Dad.
You're here. Have a seat.
- Have a drink.
- Okay.
- Can I have one more glass?
- Sure.
It's just that...
I don't think I gave you an answer...
to your question the other day.
More than anything,
I'm just so grateful to you.
I'm really grateful that you've
grown into a decent person.
I'm just an ordinary man.
I'm not successful or famous.
I didn't make a lot of money
like other people, either.
I worked at a company, and
raised you guys my whole life.
Seong Joon.
I'm sorry that I haven't
been a better father to you.
No, Dad.
- That's not what I meant. I just...
- I know.
I know what you want to know,
and what frustrates you.
But Seong Joon.
You said you love me very much, right?
- Yes.
- I do, too.
I love you very much, too.
That's why I'm asking you this.
Can't we just live the way we do now?
I've never thought you weren't my true son.
Dad.
You keep asking questions,
and it feels like you're not my son.
It makes me so lonely and sad.
Hello?
Seong Joon. It's me.
Yes.
It was so good to see you, so I'm
calling you for the last time...
before I leave.
There is something I want to tell you.
What is that?
You have an older brother.
- What?
- You have an older brother.
I know you already have a father,
but you should look for
your brother and be happy.
The bus is here. Goodbye, then.
Hello? Hello?
Look who it is.
- Hello. It's me, Jeong Eun.
- Yes.
You're Jeong Eun, the tomboy.
- Sir.
- Gosh, yes.
- I missed you a lot.
- All right.
You rascal.
How is Jeong Hwa? I heard she got
married and lives in the States now.
Stop asking me about Jeong Hwa.
Everyone in this school asks me about her.
She was such a pretty girl.
She was a brilliant student, too.
This filthy world only
remembers the first place.
You brat.
Luckily, it's spring vacation now.
There is no one in school.
By the way,
why do you want to see the yearbook?
There is a friend I want to find.
Let's see.
You want to see the yearbook of 1993.
Let's see. Where is it?
Here it is.
Here you go.
(Seoin Elementary School Yearbook)
Let's see.
"Lee Hyun Woo".
(Lee Hyun Woo)
Is he the one?
There is one more.
Gosh.
(Lee Hyun Woo)
(Seoin Elementary School)
What? What's wrong?
Sir.
Among the graduates of this school in 1993,
there're 10 people named Kim Hee Young,
and seven people named Kim Hye Jeong.
Also, three people have the same
name of the person I'm looking for.
Why can't people in this
country be more creative?
How can their names be all the same?
Let me see it.
Who is it that you're looking for?
His name is Lee Hyun Woo.
His father passed away.
His father?
Yes. Lee Hyun Woo.
Here he is.
What?
He's the one.
After he took pictures for the yearbook,
his father died.
That's why he couldn't come
to pick up the yearbook.
I heard that he was sent to an orphanage.
What?
Gosh. I felt so bad for him.
He was smart...
and kindhearted.
His younger brother...
waited for him on the playground...
every day.
I often took him to my office...
and fed him some food.
He was such a polite child.
He would make a deep bow to thank me.
Goodness. It was such a tragedy.
How could something like
that happen to them?
(Lee Hyun Woo)
Oh my gosh, you mother flower.
Shut it!
I curse that you were born.
I hope you die in a fire pit.
Yes. I'm Korean, you jerk. So what?
What are you going to do about it?
Mom.
Hey. Stay quiet.
I'm talking to your dad on the phone.
You want a divorce?
Fine. I'm divorcing you.
I don't want to live with a crybaby
like you anymore. You moron.
Hyun Woo! Hyun Woo!
I have to talk to you.
Look.
Did you...
Hey, Jeong Eun!
Jeong Hwa.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
You didn't ask Director
Han for it, did you?
Director Bang.
Listen. I heard that you got
the scar on your face...
from a car accident.
Dong Hui. She disappeared.
Have you found your brother, Sang Woo?
My brother is dead.
Do you regret what you said to me before?
Yes. I regret it so much.