He's the one.
After he took pictures for the yearbook,
his father died.
That's why he couldn't come to pick up the yearbook.
I heard that he was sent to an orphanage.
Gosh. I felt so bad for him.
He was smart and kindhearted.
His younger brother waited for him...
on the playground every day.
I often took him to my office and fed him some food.
He was such a polite child.
He would make a deep bow to thank me.
Goodness. It was such a tragedy.
How could something like that happen to them?
I think I ought to do something about this.
I can't let this be.
(Episode 30)
Hyun Woo! Hyun Woo!
I have to talk to you.
Look.
Did you...
Hey, Jeong Eun!
Jeong Hwa.
What are you doing over there? Come and help me with my luggage.
Hyun Woo. I will be back shortly. Wait here.
Okay?
I'm coming, Jeong Hwa.
Who is he, by the way?
He's no one. He's a neighbor who lives across the street.
Let's go in. Why are you back? Are you here on a trip?
This is great. Carry my luggage. Okay?
Let's go in, Ye Bin.
Please wait there. Did you get that?
- Goodness. Look who's here. - Jeong Hwa.
It's my daughter.
I've missed you so much, Dad.
How many years has it been?
Why didn't you tell us you were coming?
You've been well, right?
Of course, my dear.
Dad.
Uncle and Aunt. Jeong Hwa is here.
They've already met, rather dramatically.
Dad, you haven't changed a bit.
It doesn't seem you've aged.
Stop it. I have aged.
Do you know how old I've turned this year?
Han Jeong Hwa. Didn't you miss your grandma?
You've been well too. Right, Grandma?
You don't have to ask me that for my sake.
Who is here? Why are you so loud?
Hey, Jeong Hwa.
Mom. You have aged so much.
Did something happen to you?
Are you suffering from a disease?
How dare you talk to your mom that way, you brat?
You haven't seen your mom in years.
How can you be so rude and ask her such a question?
It's because her children are troubling her and making her suffer.
What's up with you? You didn't say you were coming.
How about your husband and your mother-in-law?
You're asking too many questions even before I could sit down.
Can you cook me a meal first?
The meals on the plane weren't to my liking at all.
Nowadays, even the meals in the first class are so horrible.
What are you doing?
I asked you to cook me a meal.
Hurry.
Gosh.
Did he go inside already?
How should I make him come out?
I shouldn't have missed that chance.
Is this Ye Bin?
I last saw you when you were very little. We meet again today.
Ye Bin, I'm your great grandmother.
Let's say hello. Hello.
What's the matter with her?
She hasn't seen you since she was two. She feels awkward.
That's not something you can say proudly.
No matter how great your life in the States is,
how could you never come back for the last five years?
- Am I doing nothing in the States? - What are you doing there then?
You quit your great job as an anchor...
and moved to the States right after you got married.
You visited us only once after Ye Bin was born.
Housewives in the States are really busy.
Are American housewives the only busy ones?
Korean housewives are much busier.
At least, you don't have to prepare sumptuous feasts in memorial days...
or make a large amount of kimchi.
You are still very mean and surly.
You haven't changed at all.
Mom, she's eating.
Are your parents-in-law doing well?
- Yes. - What about your husband?
Answer her.
Is James Jeong, your husband, doing all right?
We want to know if he's making a lot of money for you as a lawyer.
Yes, he's doing fine.
Mom, I want the meat well-done just like bacon.
Okay. Just wait.
It was so good to see you, so I'm calling you for the last time...
before I leave.
There is something I want to tell you.
You have an older brother.
You have a father, but you should find your brother and be happy.
(Ms. Kim Mi Young)
The number you dialed is no longer available.
Please check and dial again.
Ye Bin is so pretty.
She looks just like her dad.
She slightly looks like Jeong Hwa as well.
You're right. She looks different from Ah In.
I know.
You're so adorable.
- Seong Joon, you're back. - You're home now.
- Did you have dinner? - I did.
Ye Bin, this is your uncle. Say hello to him.
Hello.
Is Jeong Hwa here?
She is. She's taking a shower. Say hello when she comes out.
Okay.
Hello, Ye Bin.
It's been too long. I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
You're grown a lot.
Hello, Jeong Hwa.
It's been a while. Is James doing all right?
- Do you still live here? - Sorry?
How longer do you plan to live in this house?
Don't you have to be independent from our parents?
- What do you think you're saying? - Jeong Hwa!
What's wrong, Dad? He's lived off us for so many years.
Now he's grown up. He should stand on his own feet.
- How dare you? - Dad.
Do you still like your half-son better than me?
What?
Hey, can you stop such nonsense?
When you were gone for five years,
Seong Joon has been the nicest one to us.
That's not what I'm talking about.
I'm saying he's too brazen.
Jeong Hwa, follow me. We need to talk. Now.
- What's the matter? - Stop it and come with me.
- Mom, it is... - Quiet!
Has that wench gone out of mind?
Seong Joon.
- Are you crazy? What's wrong? - Was I wrong?
- Please stop it. - You were very upset...
when he first came here.
You're too kind to him.
Isn't he over 30 now?
How could you live with him for more than 20 years?
- Hey. - He's an adult now.
Tell him to move out.
I have no idea what's wrong with my family.
Let's put it aside. We need to talk about you.
- What about me? - Why hasn't James called once yet?
He has not just called us since you got here,
but for such a long time, I haven't heard from him.
Don't bother yourself about him.
Jeong Hwa.
Do you know Jeong Hwa came back to Korea?
I do. She arrived at Incheon Airport at 2pm today.
Now that Hyung Seop's arrogant daughter is back,
it has become much favorable for us.
The divorce suit between her and James Jeong, a lawyer...
in Washington D.C. is not over yet.
I was reported that she filed the suit...
as James was a mama's boy.
And she had intense trouble with her mother-in-law.
The odds are she'll win.
She's highly likely to get a large amount of alimony.
I'm sure Hyung Seop would feel terrible.
Of course. It's very painful for parents to see their daughter...
getting divorced.
It's nothing compared to the pain people feel when they die.
I want Hyung Seop to feel the agony of death...
by making his daughter hit rock bottom.
I need to figure the way out.
- What about your father? - He encountered a wrongful death.
That driver ended up hanging himself to death.
That's why I lost my brother.
He had two sons.
I was adopted. I am looking for my brother...
whom I lost 20 years ago.
So,
if that's how things went...
Mom.
Mom!
Mom, your daughter is back. Why are you ignoring me?
Ae Ri, I have a cold.
So I can't sing for you...
under the window of your room.
I need you to go to the place...
where we had our first kiss.
I still remember the scent from your lips...
when we had the first kiss.
He's a jerk.
He's such a mean jerk.
Why did he return so late?
We're too old to start something.
It's too late to start afresh.
He's a scum.
He's such a bad guy.
(This is the scent of your lips when we first kissed.)
Yes, Dad.
Your mom is crying right now.
You should comfort her.
Did you say Mom's crying? Why would she cry?
I made her cry.
That's all you need to know.
Anyway,
please take good care of my girl.
What?
What's happening to these two these days?
Why did he have to sing below her window?
Now everyone knows about it, and I am so embarrassed.
But anyway,
they are not the problem.
So,
there's a possibility that that's what happened.
Then...
who is the brother he found?
Hello.
See you around.
Wait.
What is it?
I have...
a question for you.
What is it?
Did you find your brother?
Did you find Sang Woo?
Did I...
tell you my brother's name?
You did.
You're just a neighbor,
and I shouldn't have told you something like that.
I found him.
What about him?
Right.
I see.
Do you want to know one more thing?
My brother is dead.
It turns out he died a long time ago.
- From what I heard... - You and Jeong Eun...
must talk about me all the time.
You should stop now.
It's a tragic story for me.
So stop it, unless it is your nasty hobby...
to talk about other people's misfortunes.
Mr. Lee.
I heard only your writer...
hasn't turned in the script.
Instead of prying into my personal life,
you should perhaps focus on your work.
Is it going well? Do you want to have a can of beer?
Dong Hui.
I've finished!
Gosh, you surprised me.
Goodness.
When did you come?
You surprised me. Why would you shout?
Director Han.
What is it?
I'm done. I'm done writing the first two episodes...
"Romance Learned through Books".
- Really? - Yes.
Hold on.
Dong Hui.
I'm done. I'm done!
Good job, Dong Hui. Good job.
Here. It's still hot.
Touch it.
Aren't you going to read it?
I think I shouldn't read it.
Why not?
I can't read it now.
It's a competition.
Everyone thinks I fix your script.
I don't want people to misunderstand you.
Why don't you just read it?
I wrote it to show you.
I didn't write it for other people. I wrote it to be praised...
and to be acknowledged by you.
I will praise you tomorrow.
Anyway,
you can beat Writer Choi tomorrow, right?
I'm not sure.
Everything will be all right.
What if it doesn't turn out well?
Don't worry. It will turn out well.
Even if it doesn't turn out well,
I will be there for you.
Good job.
Did you write the script with your whole body?
I wrote it with my fingers.
Why do you look so shabby then?
You do realize that only amateurs...
make it obvious how hard you've worked, don't you?
Because you delayed the submission by a week,
Writer Choi was able to finish planning for the next two episodes.
She still had time after that, so she went to a spa.
She doesn't look shabby like someone either.
But the result for the first two episodes haven't come out yet.
Why would she plan for episode 3 and 4?
That's what professionals do.
What would you have done if it was already being aired?
Are you going to be writing even when the shoot begins?
You know that the most important quality of a screenwriter...
is to submit the script on time, right?
Yes, I know.
I will never be late next time.
We will see about that. Will there be a next time?
At 4pm, we will announce which writer to work with.
Okay.
Let's see how well you wrote...
by dragging so much time.
You can leave now.
You didn't ask Director Han for a favor, did you?
What favor?
You didn't pester him to read the script, did you?
Director Bang.
We will know once we read the script...
whether he fixed it for you or not.
You can leave now.
You've all read Ms. Cha and Dong Hui's script, right?
Yes.
Please come inside.
Okay.
Are you done reading?
I am.
Let's start the meeting.
Hello.
I came to survey the preferences for new arrival products.
Why do you look so weak?
It's very unlike you. Are you all right?
I'm okay.
How are the customers reacting to the new products?
They love them, and we are running out of stock.
A lot of customers left their numbers...
and asked us to contact them when the new stock comes in.
I see.
By the way,
you look worried.
I am okay.
Stop, Chang Soo. One moment, please.
Chang Soo, I listened to the recording...
of your last lesson with your teacher.
- That part. - Which part?
This part. This part sounds slightly flat.
I see. You think so?
- We should focus on that part. - Yes.
Han Ji Hoon.
What?
I told you that you can't practice magic tricks.
But I intend to continue.
What did you say?
You. You! Do you think I will let you throw away your life?
If you are going to become a magician,
I will rather have you become an opera singer too. Did you get that?
Excuse me, Mother.
Goodness. Please excuse me, Teacher.
Chang Soo, start again. Teacher, could you continue?
Darn it.
Gosh.
Father.
Honey.
I am home. Your husband is here.
After being questioned...
by the prosecution for three days...
and having nine bowls of seolleongtang,
I have finally come home.
Honey.
My stomach feels sick.
Teacher, I think we should stop the lesson here today.
Please take care.
- All right. - Teacher.
Honey.
- Hee Sook. - Get out.
Get out. You'd better get out now.
How dare you come back here?
Honey.
- Hee Sook. - Mother.
- Get out. I told you to get out! - Mother.
Let go of me. Move aside.
You cheated on me. How dare you come back?
I don't need you now. I will live with only Chang Soo.
All I need is my son.
I don't need you at all. So get out now.
- Honey. - Leave.
Honey, this is all my fault.
I know what I did was wrong.
- It's all my fault. - I told you to get out.
Father.
Are you all right?
Of course, I am not.
Goodness. You're crying?
- You're crying. All right. - Honey.
- Hee Sook. - Stop, Mother.
Oaky. I will get out.
- You'd better not cry again. - Please don't do it.
It hurts. It really hurts.
So Seong Hoon runs a fried chicken restaurant,
and Seong Sik was questioned by the prosecution?
You don't have to summarize it so bluntly.
Don't you think you are being too burdensome?
- Mother, let me do it. - Leave it. I'll do it.
How can you live with your parents at your age?
- Look who's talking. How about you? - I am their daughter.
Daughters can live with her parents and sons can't?
Jeong Hwa.
We are going to move out as soon as we are back on our feet.
You're part of this too. Hye Joo.
How badly did you manage your household that you had to move...
back when he was laid off?
Pardon?
Goodness. That's exactly what Mother told me at first.
Anyway, your family and Seong Sik's family...
- are unbelievable. - Hey, you brat.
- Where did you go, Father? - Father.
Seong Hoon. Can you go down to the first floor?
- Why? - Seong Sik is back.
- What? - What?
- When did he come back? - What did you say?
Mother. Please stay. I'm afraid you might collapse again.
What did Seong Sik say? What did he say to you?
You should just stay here.
- Why don't you go down? - Okay.
What a chaos.
- Jeong Hwa. - What?
She still has a bad temper.
Oh, dear.
Hey. Seong Sik.
Why are you standing here?
Seong Hoon.
Hee Sook told me...
not to lay a foot inside.
Can you carry me inside?
What?
Seong Sik. What happened?
Right. Tell us how it went.
Seong Hoon.
Everything is over.
- What? - Now...
everything is over.
I won't be able to recover from this.
My life...
is doomed.
Seong Sik.
Goodness.
Here you go.
How is it?
You use quality coffee beans.
We do use somewhat of quality coffee beans.
By the way, why did you start a cafe?
I am surprised Aunt let you go ahead with this.
I guess Aunt isn't as scary as before.
Jeong Hwa.
That's right. She said...
the spirit of the driver who got...
into a car accident came to curse our neighborhood.
She said one of his sons came to take revenge on her.
Don't you remember at all?
Your cousin, Jeong Hwa was badly hurt.
Jeong Hwa.
- I have a question to ask you. - What?
Well...
You know the scar on your forehead?
I heard you got it from a car accident.
Hey. Why are you bringing up my painful past?
You are clueless picking up social cues just like when you were young.
I haven't been home for ages.
You don't have anything else to say, other than to ask that question?
I didn't mean it like that.
I am just so curious.
Do you remember the accident?
Why are you asking me that out of the blue?
Well, it happens that...
I went to see the janitor at our elementary school a few days before.
He mentioned about the accident.
Goodness. How is he? Is he well?
Yes. He's retiring the day after tomorrow.
He did ask how you were doing.
At that time, I guess a lot of kids were hurt.
Of course. It was a huge accident.
Among them, I was hurt the most.
Darn it. Did you know that because of this scar,
I couldn't put my hair up during my days as an anchor?
I see.
Do you remember anything else? For example...
Like anything about the driver? Or anything related to the accident?
For instance, the driver had two sons.
Do you hear yourself?
Why are you so interested in this accident all of a sudden?
It's like a drama.
Students from...
Seoin Elementary School got into. a car accident in 1993.
Sure, it's just like a drama.
Hey, when I think about that driver...
Goodness. He was such a pathetic man.
- And? - That's it.
As you know, I was badly hurt.
Father was in such a fury.
I am not certain,
but I think they drove the driver into a corner.
Really?
Anyway,
I heard something strange...
after I was discharged from the hospital.
People said...
that the driver killed himself.
There was a rumor.
What? He killed himself?
Hey, stop.
Why are you asking this?
I won't ask anymore. I'm sorry.
So what do you think about her scenario?
I'm afraid to tell you...
that I like Writer Choi's scenario better.
Really?
What about you?
I agree with Director Kim.
I myself isn't an expert,
but Dong Hui isn't a good writer yet.
I think the new secret about the birth ruined the scenario.
It must have been tough for a novice writer...
to change the plot in a few days.
But Writer Choi made it.
That's true.
This is the difference between novice and expert writers.
What about you, Director Han?
Which one do you like better? Is it Writer Choi's or Dong Hui's?
I like...
Writer Choi's better too.
In overall,
Writer Choi's scenario is better.
You've made an accurate judgment.
Then I guess Writer Choi's scenario is selected unanimously.
Well...
For the first two episodes, Writer Choi won by landslide.
Report them the result and tell them to prepare the next two episodes.
- Okay. - Okay.
Seong Joon, don't make any plans after work today.
Did you forget about it? We will have dinner with the winning writer.
We should cheer Writer Choi up.
We hurt her pride a lot by making her compete...
with a complete novice.
We must make her feel better.
Fine.
(Writer Hong from Contents Team)
Hello.
Dong Hui,
you're still a beginner.
So the plot flow and the setting weren't so good.
Tell her to visit one more store in Mapo.
- We got a call from there. - Please stop it, Mr. Park.
Dong Hui, by the way...
Hello? Dong Hui?
Dong Hui.
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
(Director Han Seong Joon)
Really? I understand.
Please have some rest. Goodbye.
She was going to make it,
but she doesn't feel well.
She wants to stay in today.
She said we can have dinner after she writes the next episodes.
Did she?
Let's have dinner together. It's been a while, hasn't it?
Is that okay?
Director Park also likes Writer Choi's script a lot.
He said she put the stories together naturally as a veteran writer.
I see.
She's a great writer.
An aspiring writer can never compete with her,
right?
By the way, I'm worried about President Lee.
What?
He meddled in the plot and even the casting.
I'm sure he'll poke his nose into the matter about writers.
What do you mean?
I'm not sure how long this competition will last.
Probably, it might end at this point.
Aren't the two episodes enough to judge the writers?
Why? Are you upset?
What are you talking about?
I'm asking if you're sad because Dong Hui lost.
That's enough. Let's not talk about it anymore.
Are you worried then?
Are you worried that poor Dong Hui might be crying alone somewhere?
Mi Joo.
You two are really ridiculous.
I lost my appetite because of the two you.
I'm leaving first.
President Lee, this is Mi Joo.
I came to your town because of work.
I guess I can give you the scenario now.
Welcome. This is unexpected.
You came all the way here.
I apologize for barging in at this hour.
But I have something to tell you urgently.
- Please have a seat. - Thank you.
Do you want some tea?
That'd be great. Thank you.
I'm quite surprised. You're cold-blooded than I thought.
Stumbling blocks must be removed.
What matters the most is the company's profit.
Wouldn't this put Seong Joon in trouble?
Pardon?
As I live across from his house,
I came to know about their relationship.
Let alone their personal feelings,
they're in-laws,
and she's the writer Director Han supports.
That's why we should make it clear.
We can't continue like this for the sake of Director Han.
I'll sleep on it.
Thank you.
Then I'll count on you and leave.
Okay.
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Please leave a message after the beep.
Come on, Dong Hui.
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Please leave a message after the beep.
After the beep, you will be...
Welcome.
Dong Hui, where have you gone?
Dong Hui.
I looked all over for you without knowing that you're here.
Please go back. I want to be alone.
I'm afraid I can't.
Please.
Everything is meaningless.
I'm a loser. I'm a fool.
I'm an idiot who can't even develop her own synopsis.
You should give up on me too.
Stop blaming yourself. Your script wasn't bad.
Writer Choi's script was a little better. That's all.
That's a possibility we've had in mind...
from the beginning.
I feel...
so bad.
I feel bad for my synopsis,
I feel bad for my script,
and I feel so bad for those who have been...
waiting for me.
Don't say that.
The one who hurt the most is you, Dong Hui.
I don't even deserve to be hurt.
I don't deserve to be consoled.
You're wrong. You did very well.
You were steady, brave, and confident.
You did a great job.
That's why I'm so proud of you.
You've only written a skit,
but your synopsis for a mini series drama was chosen among others.
You could've run away in fear,
but you stayed and fought with an experienced writer.
What's important is that you stayed and fought.
Really?
Of course.
So stop crying, okay?
I didn't even wash my face since yesterday.
That's dirty.
I'm a bad writer,
and now you say I'm dirty.
Why do I get more and more anxious as time goes by?
I've been writing all my life dreaming of becoming a writer.
I feel like my whole life was denied today.
I was dragged down to misery with each word I wrote down.
I felt like I was in a pit of fire.
I think I even saw the grim reaper.
I felt nervous, anxious,
and suffocated.
I really thought I was going to die.
After all that, this is the result I got.
So are you...
going to give up?
Are you going to give up your dream and fate...
because of what happened today?
Or...
are you going to reflect on it and improve yourself?
The latter, of course.
Then what are you waiting for?
I told you earlier.
I just feel bad.
I feel bad for my synopsis, my script,
and those who have been waiting for me.
My gosh.
That's a long list of things you feel bad for.
Also,
I feel bad for one more person.
I feel bad for you the most.
- Me? - Yes.
I'm fine.
I said I'd love you only in my writing,
but I couldn't love you in my writing...
or in the real life. That's why I feel bad.
Even after all that, I lost the fight.
I'm a fool.
An idiot.
Do you regret...
what you said back then?
Yes.
I regretted it...
a lot.
You should...
come up with a plan.
You can make a fresh start with your writing and your love.
Dong Hui.
- Well... - We're stuck again...
just like that day.
My goodness.
Grandma. What's wrong?
Dong Hui disappeared.
What? What are you talking about?
I came to see if she was writing, but she isn't here.
She won't pick up her phone either.
My gosh. Grandma.
- Goodness. Grandma. - Find Dong Hui.
Try to find Dong Hui!
Grandma. Please pull yourself together.
- Hold on. - Dong Hui.
My gosh. Okay. I got it.
It's me.
Dong Hui hasn't come home yet.
She's not answering her phone.
I think President Bang did something.
I doubt that. He hasn't shown any movements yet.
I can't just wait like this.
What if something happened to my dear Dong Hui? My goodness.
I can't wait anymore.
- I'm coming over to you. - No.
It will give them an excuse. You should stay where you are...
Mom. What are you doing here at this hour?
My gosh.
What's wrong?
I was just startled.
You showed up out of nowhere.
This is my house.
It's natural that I show up.
By the way,
what were you doing upstairs?
- I could feel the cold wind, - Okay.
so I was wondering if a window was open somewhere.
Here.
Come. Come and sit down for a minute.
But...
why are you here so early?
Well...
I couldn't sleep.
I boiled some soy beans...
and ground them last night.
You used to like ground soy beans.
Gosh. Is that why you came here with this...
at this early hour?
Goodness. I feel hungry already.
Let me eat it.
Sure.
What? You're getting divorced?
- Jeong Hwa. - Jeong Hwa.
It just happened.
We've filed for a divorce already. I'm just letting you know.
How could you?
- Jeong Ae. - Oh, my.
What should we do?
- Gosh. - Take her inside and lay her down.
I'm so worried about her.
She's already stressed because of Seong Sik. What should we do?
I can't believe this.
- My gosh. - This isn't done, Jeong Hwa. Honey.
My goodness.
- I knew Mom would be like that. - Enough!
No parent would be okay...
when their daughter says she's getting divorced.
Grandma. My husband and I have had a lot of problems.
You still can't divorce him.
Every couple has problems.
Anyway, I'm divorcing him.
Enough! Don't be absurd. You can't divorce him.
You can divorce him over my dead body.
Grandma!
Do I have to go through this again?
After what happened to Ae Ri 30 years ago,
do I have to watch another one in my family become a single mom?
- It's cold these days. - Shut it.
You should speak nicely.
You're a beautiful lady. You should speak like one.
Why did you call me here?
I just wanted to have a meal together with you.
Let's go in.
Listen to me.
I came here to say this.
No matter how many times you come to see me, we can't get back together.
Why not?
Have you forgotten what you did to me?
You abandoned me.
Ae Ri.
That's not what it was.
Why would I abandon you?
What was it, then?
You left me to study abroad...
and came back after 30 years. You don't think it's an abandonment?
I...
really didn't know you have been raising Jeong Eun by yourself.
What if you did?
What would you have done if you knew?
I would have...
come back to take you and Jeong Eun right away.
What if I hadn't had Jeong Eun? Would you have come back?
I was in the boarding house in Italy...
being jealous...
of the guy who would be receiving your love instead of me.
What...
What did you say?
What are you talking about?
I thought you would've been having a nice life...
married to some rich guy.
You know that...
I was a poor self-supporting student in Korea.
You weren't only poor.
You were pathetic too.
Yes.
That's why...
your mother was opposed to our marriage so strongly.
You couldn't even convince my mom. Do you think that's love?
Anyhow, I couldn't get over you for 30 years.
I was lonely living by myself in Italy and Germany.
I thought about you, and I felt jealous,
I was in agony, and I missed you.
It is love.
That's a load of rubbish.
What?
I said that's a load of rubbish. What?
- Do I have to teach you a lesson? - Gosh.
You shouldn't talk to me so rudely.
Do I really need to give you a good scolding?
Excuse me.
You're Mr. Ryu Myung Jin, the baritone singer, right?
Who are you?
Yes, I am. How can I help you?
- It's him. - It's really him.
What's wrong with these women?
Mr. Ryu. We are...
members of an opera club.
We all love your songs very much.
Is that so?
Can we have your autograph, please?
Sure. Give them to me.
Wait. Can't you see that we're eating here?
Stay quiet.
- What's your name? - It's Kim Ah Reum.
Ms. Kim...
I'm Park Mi Na.
- Ms. Park Mi Na. - Yes.
I'm Shin Seon Hee.
- Ms. Shin... - It's Seon Hee.
- Here. - Thank you.
Mr. Ryu.
Could you sing for us just a little?
We only listen to your voice on CDs.
I cannot sing when there is no instrumental accompaniment.
Please, Mr. Ryu.
Could you read this menu...
out loud for us, then?
"Grilled dried pollack, 15 dollars".
"Braised cutlassfish, 13 dollars".
"Leaf wraps and rice, Australian beef used, 10 dollars".
"Soybean paste stew with snails, seven dollars".
"Deluxe short rib soup, Australian beef used,"
"eight dollars".
- It's amazing! - Splendid!
So,
are you happy that you're popular among girls?
Don't eat your food like that.
You always ate so loudly, and you still do.
Ae Ri.
Give me your hands.
Why?
What are you doing?
What are these?
Give me your hands.
- Give me your left hand. - Stop.
- What are you doing? - The other hand.
What's wrong with you? Are you crazy? Stop it.
It looks pretty.
I'm going to tear them into pieces after you go.
Wear them on the day.
The day of what?
The day of my concert.
Jeong Eun gave you a ticket, right?
All right. I'll be going now.
Goodbye,
my dear Dulcinea.
He's still as obstinate as 30 years ago.
Let's go in.
Should we?
Are you okay?
Yes.
Dong Hui!
Grandma.
Where have you been last night?
I'm sorry.
Ms. Oh. Dong Hui had something at work...
Be quiet.
Get inside.
Ms. Oh.
Let go of me.
Get inside now!
Dong Hui had better come home soon.
I will teach her a lesson.
- Come inside! - Grandma.
Grandma.
Dong Hui! What were you thinking?
Grandma. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I actually...
Grandma, what's wrong?
Don't do this.
You are a bad girl.
If you're going to do this, go to your grandmother.
What? Grandma.
Go live with your grandmother!
What are you talking about? Where would she go?
Dong Hui doesn't have another grandmother.
What are you talking about?
Never mind. Never mind.
Goodness, what's gotten into her?
Hye Joo.
I must've done something terrible. What should I do?
Hey!
What did I tell you when you slept out last time?
Didn't I tell you I was going to beat you badly...
if you make Grandma get worried again?
How can you sleep out again?
And how can you sleep out with Seong Joon?
- Hye Joo, that's... - Assume the push-up position.
Okay.
What is it?
It's been so long since I came into this house.
What brings you here?
It looks like you are doing very well.
I guess you don't crave for cucumber sandwich anymore.
Or do you make it yourself?
It looks like you don't have anything particular to say.
Please leave now.
What are you doing?
I told you I had something to tell you.
I'll give you five minutes.
Because we were once special.
Your name is Lee Hyun Woo. You graduated Seoin Elementary School.
Your brother Lee Sang Woo always waited for you in the schoolyard...
until you got dismissed.
You were a good student who was kind and polite.
He adored his little brother very much.
After his father who used to drive a school bus wrongfully died,
he and his brother were sent to an orphanage.
Hyun Woo was adopted, and his little brother went missing.
What are you doing right now?
It's a story about a man I know.
By the way, that Lee Hyun Woo guy...
moved to our town six months ago.
And he happened to live...
right across from the man who was related to his father's death.
Why did you come here?
Did you come to take revenge?
Hello.
We've met once before.
Have we?
Aren't you Anchor Han Jeong Hwa?
- Do you know me? - Of course.
There was a time when every man in Korea knew you.
Is that right?
Hey! Wait! Let's talk more.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Golden Street?
Isn't that an investment banking firm on Wall Street?
Are you okay?
That driver was innocent.
What?
I'm here, Mom. It's me, Gwang Jin.
- Dong Hui. - Grandma.
I am sorry, but who is he?
He's my little brother. Are you happy now?