Your name is Lee Hyun Woo. You graduated Seoin Elementary School.
Your brother Lee Sang Woo always waited for you...
in the schoolyard until you got dismissed.
You were a good student who was kind and polite.
He adored his little brother very much.
After his father who used to drive a school bus wrongfully died,
he and his brother were sent to an orphanage.
Hyun Woo was adopted, and his little brother went missing.
What are you doing right now?
It's a story about a man I know.
By the way, that Lee Hyun Woo guy...
moved to our town six months ago.
And he happened to live...
right across from the man who was related to his father's death.
Why did you come here?
Did you come to take revenge?
This is really funny.
I guess you've finished reading that lousy romance novel.
Now you're writing a detective story.
Stop being sarcastic and just answer my questions.
So what's next?
So that Hyun Woo returned to the town he lived...
and dated Jeong Eun and walked away to take revenge for his father?
Are you saying you were dumped for nothing...
but revenge?
If that sounds to be an acceptable reason for our breakup,
you can think that way.
That's what I want to say to you.
You're right. I haven't accepted the fact...
we broke up.
But you should know that I'm not here to beg and plead for your love.
Why? That's not the real issue.
You're in a more terrible fix.
- What's the issue? - You should give up...
on the revenge.
I don't know what you've done, and what you're about to do.
But stop it.
I'm begging you.
Please don't, Hyun Woo.
You might put yourself in danger instead.
Jeong Eun,
the first impression I've got from you turned to be right.
Women who poke their nose into everything, make reckless guesses,
and speak what's on their mind without thinking just like you.
That's the type I hate the most.
- Hyun Woo... - Let me tell you why I left you.
This is the reason.
Your such thoughtless behaviors put me under a lot of stress.
But I tried to be nice to you until the last moment.
You need to stop here.
Do you think you're a detective or something?
Do you know anything about me?
I guess you've written a novel by yourself...
with what I've told you before.
I seriously need you to stop this.
You're making sick of you.
Hello.
We've met before.
- Have we? - Aren't you Anchor Han Jeong Hwa?
- Do you know me? - Of course.
There was a time when every man in Korea knew you.
- I see. - Wait. I'm not done talking yet!
Sir.
Would you spare me some time later?
I'd like to have dinner with you.
Well...
See you later.
- Jeong Hwa. - Do you know him?
By the way, why are you coming out of this house?
Well... It is because...
Well, I delivered coffee.
I see.
- Jeong Hwa. - Right!
I have to go meet my anchor friends.
I'm going to be a little late.
If it's okay with you, please watch Ye Bin.
Jeong Hwa! Jeong Hwa!
What is happening?
This can't be happening.
You met such an unusual girl.
Are you talking about Han Jeong Hwa?
I'm referring to Han Jeong Eun.
She managed to get very close to your secret.
I think we should finish our business here soon.
Right.
Let's get it done quickly.
It's very tough for me,
and I am exhausted.
Goodness, my one and only granddaughter is getting divorced.
Wait.
I should wear this on my head and stay in bed.
I should put on a show.
Only then, they will stop this nonsense.
Elizabeth.
What's wrong, Elizabeth? Goodness.
What is it?
Elizabeth.
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Oh, dear.
Don't worry too much about Jeong Hwa.
I will talk to her.
Did you talk to James?
He wasn't picking up his phone.
Honey.
What will we do?
We are about to have a divorcee in our family.
Why would you say that?
I will do everything to stop her.
She even packed up and moved to Korea. How can we stop her?
It's because you've been...
favoring Jeong Hwa since she was little.
She never listens to what we say.
It breaks my heart.
Both Seong Sik and Jeong Hwa...
are more like enemies than my own children.
Come on and eat some.
No.
I don't even have the strength to eat porridge.
Can I talk to you for a while?
What happened?
Huh?
Well...
Dong Hui's script didn't get selected.
Is that why you spent the night together?
Even if things didn't go well with her work,
you shouldn't have done this. This is just unbelievable.
I am sorry.
Dong Hui was really disheartened.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
So where on earth...
did you two go?
We were at a library.
What?
I am sorry.
Both Dong Hui and you...
are unbelievable.
Is everyone who makes dramas as strange as you two?
I know that you work together and that you are in-laws,
but before that, you are a man and a woman.
How can you stay the night together?
Even if Dong Hui was struggling,
you should've brought her home.
Do Mother and Father know about this too?
No, they don't know this.
What's wrong with you, Seong Joon?
This is very unlike you.
What is it? Is there something you want to tell me?
It's nothing.
We shouldn't have done it.
I am sorry.
Chang Soo, stop. Stop.
Chang Soo, what did your teacher say about this song...
during the last lesson?
"Though Not Deserving".
That's right. "Sebben, Crudele".
Even if you don't deserve her,
you will still love her.
That's what the song is about, isn't it?
- Yes. - How should you sing it then?
You should sing it more sorrowfully.
Okay?
Your lover doesn't love you.
Cruelly, she refused your love.
But you still love her.
You want to keep loving her.
How tragic is that?
How should you sing it then?
You have to...
You have to be more emotional. Right?
- Yes. - Right.
Now...
Where are you going?
I'm going to my home. Why?
Then listen to Chang Soo's song before you go.
No, thanks. You should take care of your son.
Aunt.
- Did you just call me Aunt? - If you keep doing that to me,
I'm not going to visit you when I win a cash prize at a competition.
Hey.
When you win that prize,
you should treat your mother.
Stop bothering your aunt. Okay?
Bye, Teacher.
She doesn't have affection for her kids.
That's why she's bad at bringing up her children.
Chang Soo, don't mind her. Just focus on your singing.
Should we restart from the next bar?
- Please play the piano. - Okay.
- I got it. - Okay.
Uncle.
Yes?
What is it, Ah In?
Aren't you going to call Yoo Ra?
Yoo Ra? Who is that?
My friend Yoo Ra.
You talked to her in the restroom the other time.
She's...
- She's no one... - Dad.
Stop now.
Stop what?
I've read everything on the internet.
Hey!
Who told you to read things on the internet?
Whatever. Just stop.
Anyway,
thank you.
You are the best, Ah In.
You're welcome.
What have you been thinking about?
I was thinking...
maybe I should marry off Dong Hui.
Dong Hui?
Honey.
Do you know any good man?
Do you want me to introduce her to a journalist?
Hello, no thanks.
I was thinking...
maybe I should start another business.
What?
We have to marry off Dong Hui.
And I am partially responsible for what happened to Seong Sik.
And even Jeong Hwa is causing trouble.
I feel so frustrated these days.
So what?
The idea I have...
is very innovative.
Listen, honey.
Excuse me, Mr. Han Seong Hoon!
Gosh, you surprised me. Why did you shout?
Stop the nonsense...
and just run your fried chicken restaurant diligently.
Do that. Okay?
Hye Joo, that business idea is...
I don't know. Stop it.
Go away.
- Hye Joo. - I said, go away!
We haven't seen each other in seven years.
We're here together now because we stayed in touch.
It's already very popular in Russia and China.
You can see how popular it is if you search it on the internet.
I already searched the website you told me about on the internet.
Like you said, it's very popular indeed.
That's right.
It has dolphins, seals, and walruses.
But the main reason...
for its popularity is because it's a theme park with many penguins.
You know how much people love cute animals in Korea.
Please take a look.
(The center of culture and leisure)
You haven't changed at all.
The one who hasn't changed is you, not us.
She's right. You haven't aged a bit.
I guess it's because you married a guy from an amazing family.
- They're not amazing. - Hey.
Your father-in-law is one of the richest people in Hong Kong,
and your husband is an international lawyer.
Yes. That's why there was a rumor that you married him for money.
It's fine.
Whether you marry a guy for money or love,
all you care about is money after seven years of marriage.
Why? It's because you have to raise your child.
That's right. She has a point.
This is a place where families can have a meal.
What are you looking at? Do you know him?
No. It's nothing.
Anyway, tell us about your husband.
Is he still a romantic?
- I'm not sure. - Look.
It's not so great to have a romantic husband.
He also does romantic things to other women too.
- What are you talking about? - I'm talking about Yoo Mi Na.
She also married a guy as successful as your husband.
Do you remember how much she bragged about her romantic husband?
Her husband is having an affair and living with his mistress now.
- Oh, my. Really? - Yes.
They had been separated for a year. Now they're filing for a divorce.
Let's meet again when you have...
details about the budget and investment costs.
Okay. I will call you in a few days.
He's an amazing swindler.
Well... I liked how he seemed professional.
Sometimes you can be...
quite mischievous.
Cheers.
Shall we split the check?
What are you talking about? You don't have to. It's on me.
Ma'am. Your bill has already been settled.
- Excuse me? - He already made the payment.
"President of Golden Street, David Lee".
Oh, my. Maybe it's the guy who was here earlier.
Golden Street? Isn't that an investment company on Wall Street?
Really? Jeong Hwa.
How do you know him?
You always get the nicest guys.
He's just a good neighbor.
Hello?
Can I see you for a second?
Come on in. Please have a seat.
I think it's better to have just one writer.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying we shouldn't have Dong Hui as the co-writer.
- President Lee. - A TV show is also a product.
If there is a broken part, we should replace it quickly.
Dong Hui and Writer Choi have a big difference in ability.
Besides, everyone chose Writer Choi's script...
for the 1st and 2nd episode.
I think it's unlikely that Dong Hui will turn things around later on.
She couldn't have written her script without Dong Hui's synopsis.
They both signed the contract as co-writers as well.
Pay Dong Hui compensation for breach of contract.
I believe it will be more efficient way to save...
both money and time.
- President Lee. - Why are you being so emotional?
I don't understand why.
I didn't say anything to upset you.
I'm making this decision...
solely based on the business perspective.
I just...
don't understand why you're doing this.
When you suddenly came to us to invest in our drama,
I thought you were being kind.
I was surprised to see you treat me kindly when I was hostile to you...
thinking that you were approaching my family for a wrong reason.
Were you?
Yes. I was.
But now I'm not sure anymore.
I don't know why you invested in our show and did me a favor.
Maybe you were just pretending.
I don't understand why you keep trying...
to make me suffer.
I don't understand why such a clever man like you...
became so emotional.
I don't really like the way your company works,
but there is one thing that President Bang and I agree on.
Do you know what it is?
Never run your business as a charity.
I'm a renowned investor.
I hope you haven't forgotten it.
So you should exclude your girlfriend...
from this project as soon as possible.
That's the wise thing for you to do.
- Are you okay? - Yes. I'm fine.
You must've gotten scolded a lot because of me.
Well... I just got a few slaps and scoldings.
Did you get slapped?
No.
I still don't regret it.
What?
I don't regret that we were together that night.
You're not going to change your mind again, are you?
Answer me.
No. I'm not going to change my mind again.
Okay then.
My sister and husband are only causing me trouble.
I'd better...
discipline them more strictly.
I'm going to work hard to write a good script.
I'm going to beat Writer Choi's script for the 3rd and 4th episode.
You should.
Why do you look unhappy?
It's nothing.
What's wrong?
I said it's nothing.
Gosh. You're making me worry. Are you going to keep doing this?
Are you?
- It hurts. - Lighten up, okay?
I've been scolded all day, but I'm still smiling.
You look so pretty.
So pretty.
Stop it.
- You're hurting me. - Okay.
This is driving me crazy.
Gosh. I was too busy with my work that I neglected them for too long.
What should I do?
Moong Chi. Come here.
I'm glad you came. Hey.
Moong Chi. What's the matter with you?
How can you let this happen?
Hey.
How involved are they?
They haven't gone too far, have they?
You should've stopped them by any means.
My goodness.
What should I do with you?
Gosh, Moong Chi.
I know it's not your fault.
They're young,
and we shouldn't have moved in.
What should I do?
Moong Chi, tell me what I should do.
Come here, Moong Chi.
I have no idea what to do with them.
Hey! Are you out of mind?
Do you think I'd let you take Ye Bin away from me?
Is she trying to take Ye Bin away?
What's going on?
I don't know.
You such a jerk!
You had lost your head over another wench...
and neglected Ye Bin so far!
Why do you want the custody now?
Oh boy. What is...
- Goodness. - What on earth is happening?
Do you think I'm a fool?
I know it's your mother who told you to bring Ye Bin back.
Stop talking about your mother. I'm fed up with her!
When you cheated on me,
your mother sided with you.
Jeong Hwa.
- Grandma. - Come here.
Stop it already. What time do you think it is? Give it to me.
Give it back to me.
I'll kill that jerk.
He's a piece of trash.
He's nothing but a scum, Dad.
James, this is me.
Don't you know how late it is here?
What?
I don't care what time it is there. This isn't right.
Ask him...
why we haven't been able to reach him.
Do you really not know why?
He couldn't contact us because he knew how shameful it is.
How could he answer your calls...
when he cheated on me and lived with another woman for three years?
Stay quiet.
James,
let's call it a day.
But I'll call you tomorrow. Make sure to answer it.
Still, Ye Bin is here with her.
You should've been more careful.
Fine!
Stop crying now.
What are you crying so loud for?
This is breaking my heart.
Ye Bin, you should sleep next to me. Come here.
Mom.
Ye Bin's dad is...
seeing another woman.
It's been more than three years.
And we've been estranged for about two years.
So how could I stay there any longer?
This is so humiliating.
I know. I understand.
Still...
Don't worry.
I'm sure I'll win the divorce suit.
It's him who caused us to get divorced.
Jeong Hwa,
is it your turn this time?
Your dad and I...
cannot feel at ease for a day because of our children.
I'm utterly exhausted now, Jeong Hwa.
So?
That's all.
That's what happened.
Is James insane?
He seemed to be willing...
to give her everything he had when he married her.
How could he do this to her?
That's what all guys are like, you know.
So what is Jeong Ae doing?
She got an IV at a clinic and fell asleep now.
I thought Seong Sik's problem is finally settled.
And it happened again.
Where is Jeong Hwa?
She shut herself in her room.
What on earth is this?
It's from smoke into smother.
You know how disturbed I am. Please just leave.
To where?
To the third floor.
I can't.
Why not?
There had been a big fuss because of Dong Hui the other day.
Elizabeth cried so loudly.
Because of Dong Hui? What happened to her?
She slept out.
- She slept out? - Yes.
So Elizabeth gave her a good beating,
even Hye Joo scolded her severely.
It must have been chaotic.
They kept it a secret from us.
I can't believe that Dong Hui slept out.
So that family is in a terrible mess too.
Dong Hui keeps apologizing,
but Elizabeth doesn't bat an eye.
Goodness.
Why don't you stay on the first floor then?
If you run into Jeong Hwa, you'll feel even more perturbed.
But Chang Soo is singing loudly there.
He sings all day long. It's too loud for me to stand.
I can even hear him singing on the third floor.
Dear me.
Grandma, I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
Please forgive me.
Then...
please don't tell me to leave you.
That makes me really sad.
I have no one else than you.
Please don't say that.
You are...
all I have.
I will work hard today as I did.
So please forgive me.
I will see you after work.
I'll come home early.
Have some.
I'm not ill.
I just lost my appetite.
I'm just saying you should eat some porridge.
Even if you don't eat, it won't solve anything.
How is your grandmother?
She doesn't even look at me.
Please cheer up. This, too, shall pass away.
I know. So I'll finish the next two episodes...
by the end of this week.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
You look beautiful.
You look better when you're energetic.
I know. That's what makes me charming.
Dig in.
But I don't feel like eating porridge.
How adorable.
Please stop. We're not far from our office.
I'll be fired if they see us.
Come on.
- How cute. - I said cut it out.
I'm going to be mad at you.
You don't scare me at all.
You have something on your face like a little kid.
Eat up.
It's tasty.
Stop, Chang Soo.
Teacher, I guess this is all for today.
See you later. Take care.
Mom,
are you angry?
I am not.
I am sorry.
This is...
not your issue.
Sorry?
We need a new instructor.
- You mean the instrumental teacher? - No,
we need a new vocal teacher.
Listen, Chang Soo.
Learning from a good instructor matters the most...
for vocal music students.
I think...
we should invite a new teacher.
Who?
I can't seem to put the pieces together.
Someone is definitely lying.
It's driving me crazy.
Dad.
Hi, my dear daughter. How have you been?
Have you been well?
Yes, I have been well. Aren't you busy though, Dad?
Of course, I am busy,
but I came here to give you a present.
A present?
Do you like it?
Dad!
Here you go. This is a shot of espresso you like.
Thank you.
I noticed that you didn't have a car given your age.
I used up all my money when I went to meet you.
I'm sorry about that and...
thank you for accepting me without giving me a hard time...
although I was away for 30 years.
Thank you.
Don't say such things. I told you I am not angry at you.
We can talk more later when we have time.
See that car over there?
- What? - You should...
take that car and bring your mother to my concert. Okay?
Dad. You're not giving it to me.
Is it to drive around Mom?
Look at you. Since you take after Ae Ri,
you are quite smart.
Dad.
I really love Ae Ri.
I haven't forgotten about her for the last 30 years,
but I...
might have loved you more than your mother.
That's why I really want to show her...
how much...
I loved her while I was away...
and how hard I worked.
I wonder if I do, perhaps, her anger might subside.
- All right. - You understand me, right?
Of course, I do.
All right. Thank you.
Dad. Don't worry. I will be at your concert for certain.
Okay. Bye.
Drive carefully.
I will.
(Seoul Detention Center)
- Ms. Yoon. - Jeong Eun.
What happened?
I heard what happened, but I'd have never guessed you'd end up here.
I didn't know either.
This is all part of my karma.
But no one lives in Korea without committing a single illegal act.
If you are unlucky, you get caught.
Ms. Yoon. To be frank,
I came to talk about the person who put you here.
Who do you mean?
I mean Mr. Lee.
His name is Lee Hyun Woo.
What about him?
I heard everything.
I heard the rumors and what you said.
I also checked on my own.
Mr. Lee is the son of the driver, right?
Yes. He is.
What on earth happened 23 years ago?
The truth is...
the driver was innocent.
What?
The accident happened because Guem Ja's bus brakes were old.
Then?
A lot of students were hurt.
Since no one died from it,
Guem Ja tried to settle,
but your uncle...
What did my uncle do?
He wanted to get to the bottom of the accident by all means...
and insisted that the driver be punished.
So then?
Jeong Eun.
Guem Ja, Mi Ja,
other parents, and I were going to...
settle the accident.
Guem Ja even came up with the settlement.
However, your uncle...
He was literarily jumping up and down out of anger.
We weren't able to stop him.
Guem Ja said...
if she become criminally liable for the accident,
her academy would be in ruins.
That's why...
she framed the driver and blamed it on his drunk driving.
I helped her to frame him.
He was known...
to be an alcoholic in the neighborhood.
Ms. Yoon. How could you do such a thing?
How can you frame an innocent man?
We didn't want to.
It was your uncle who hinted that...
he might have driven drunk.
He wanted him to take a sobriety test since he was an alcoholic.
He even said he'd sue Guem Ja for hiring such an unfit driver.
How was she supposed to handle your uncle when he went berserk.
Instead of both of them going down for the accident,
she thought one person would be enough.
This can't be true. Even if it was true...
It is true. Now your uncle has become soft.
Given his old character, this isn't out of his character.
Out of all people, how could a son of the driver return?
He even returned to his old neighborhood.
I felt awful and terrified.
I'd rather be here.
Does my uncle...
- know about this? - No, he doesn't.
It's been a lifetime secret between Guem Ja and me.
Ms. Yoon.
Why did you do that?
By the way,
how is your uncle's family?
I bet Mr. Lee won't leave your uncle's family alone.
(David Lee, President of Golden Street)
Hello. This is Han Jeong Hwa.
Thank you for yesterday.
I'd like to buy you a cup of tea. How about now?
You're already here.
Where would you like to go?
I will take you to a place I have in mind.
Sounds great.
(Mom)
- Yes, Mom. - What's up with you?
You said you wanted to have dinner together. Where have you gone?
I'm sorry, Mom. What time is it?
It's 6'o clock. What's going on?
I expected to have dinner together and yet, you're making me wait?
Goodness. This is so like you.
I will be there soon. Come out of the house.
- I will pick you up with my car. - With your car?
You have a car?
Goodness. Why do you have a car?
Ta-da! Starting today, I have a car.
Is someone getting married? What is this ribbon doing here?
What's wrong with it? It's pretty.
Did you buy this?
- A guy gave this to me. - Who?
This guy is new.
Right. Get in. We're late.
Please get in.
Where are we going to eat?
Wear the seatbelt.
Mom,
do we have to eat on a day like this?
What are you talking about?
You said you're taking me out.
I wanted to be treated by my daughter.
There's something much more important than food.
What do you mean?
Let's go.
(Bariton Ryu Myung Jin's Concert)
Why did you bring me here?
This is what's more important than food.
Mom, hurry up.
Goodness.
What are you doing?
After the concert,
we can eat with Dad. All three of us together.
- Jeong Eun. - Mom.
I am 31 years old, and I have never eaten...
a meal with my parents. I'm such a pitiful person.
They say you never know who will die first.
Please cut me a slack...
in case I might die before you. Okay?
I won't let this one pass.
- Mom. - Let go of me!
Mom.
Mom,
you know those people, right?
They are the people from the music industry.
They know both you and Dad.
You are famous, and Dad is even more famous.
So what?
Let's appear cool and fabulous.
You will get embarrassed if they see you like this.
Act like a Hollywood couple who are cool with each other...
after the divorce.
Let's go inside like one of them.
We are nothing like a Hollywood couple.
- Gosh. - You are the Hollywood star.
Let's go.
Come on, Mom.
Chang Soo,
this is the place.
Yes, Mom.
He is world-famous baritone...
Korea ever gave birth to.
- Yes. - Watching his performance will...
make you a world-renowned opera singer.
That's why I paid...
an unbelievably high price...
to buy these tickets for you.
Thank you, Mom.
Shall we go in, Chang Soo?
Yes.
Here are the tickets.
People are going in. Hurry up.
It's going to start.
Let's go.
Here are the tickets.
Mom.
You get it now, don't you?
Mom, why don't you take off your sunglasses?
I don't want to see your dad's face.
We came here to hear his singing, not to see his face.
You are unbelievable, Mom.
Thank you.
Thank you for coming...
to watch my humble concert.
I've dedicated my life to music,
and music is the only thing I know. I am a foolish man.
Even at this age,
there is nothing else I can do but sing, and...
it sometimes makes me embarrassed and sometimes makes me proud.
What a joke.
Tell him to sing one more song.
Mom.
What are you doing?
There is just one thing...
I regret.
I hurt the woman...
who waited for me.
My first love and my daughter...
are here.
Who are they? Who are they? Where are they?
Who are they, Mom?
They are right there.
They are seated over there. My love...
Professor Han Ae Ri...
and my daughter Han Jeong Eun,
I want to dedicate this song to you.
What? It's Ae Ri.
It's Great Aunt.
Please take a seat.
I am sorry.
Somewhere over the hill
Perhaps you live there
Before time and passing seasons
We are weak
Somewhere here where the wind reaches
Are there
- Any traces of us - Mom.
You and I have been lonely
For as long as time passed
Mom.
Just leave me alone.
Somewhere here where sorrow reaches
Are we still alive
Hello.
I am...
your fan.
I am sorry.
- I'm not feeling well today. - I know. I know.
I know. I know.
Have a seat.
Of course, I know. Have a seat.
I know how my aunt-in-law is.
She's not easy to deal with.
What?
I mean Professor Han Ae Ri.
I am her niece-in-law.
I think...
there's something I can help you with.
Dong Hui is determined.
Her computer might get set on fire.
Her pride must've been hurt. She failed on her first try.
Dong Hui, you can do well this time, right?
Yes, of course. I can do well.
Why is she so confident?
Dong Hui, have you done...
the survey for the yoga and Pilates line?
Most professionals liked them.
They like the design and the excellent elasticity.
The report is on your desk.
How is it received among the age groups?
Our target age groups, the 20s and 30s are most receptive.
The moving studio will open...
in Konkuk University Station where there will be a younger clientele.
The report regarding this matter is on your desk as well.
What's wrong with you, Dong Hui? Are you sick?
She's not sick. She's angry that she lost to Writer Choi.
She is sick with anger.
I really hope you win this time, Dong Hui.
Did you survey reactions towards the competing company's new products?
I did. I did everything.
Please just look at your desk.
Did you see the way she looked at me? I can't believe this.
- Hello. Director. - Hi. Director.
- What are you doing, Ms. Oh? - Pardon?
She's writing next episode's script.
She finished all her given assignments. I just checked.
You are writing next episode's script?
Yes, I am.
Didn't Director Han inform you?
What do you mean?
Hello, Director.
Director Bang. Can we have a word?
Didn't you get the message yet?
- What message? - She'll no longer write scripts.
How did you find out?
How? I heard it from President Lee.
I am going to try to persuade President Lee. Don't tell her yet.
Why? Han Seong Joon. Are you serious?
Why are you dragging this out? How much help can she be?
When she finishes the scripts, we'll end up using Writer Choi's scripts.
If we continue with this, we are sacrificing our resources...
to help her gain experience and earn money.
President Lee agreed on this. That's why he called you in.
Why are they fighting so much?
Is it about the scripts again?
Did you talk to President Lee about this?
No, he called me first and told me this himself.
Don't look at me like that. I don't play games.
Then it's fine.
What are you going to do?
Whatever it takes, I will convince President Lee.
You should do whatever you want to do.
What do you mean that I should do whatever I want to do?
Don't pick at my words. I am tired.
Seong Joon.
Can you please leave? I'm exhausted.
Go home and focus on your writing.
She's right.
You got too many assignments from the Marketing Department.
Don't say that.
I also hope that she would succeed as a writer.
That's how she will keep giving me soybean paste and red chili paste.
Don't worry about that. I will continue to provide with those.
Anyway, how can you be so easily bribed?
My point is you should write as if today is your last day alive.
I will.
- Hello, President. - Hello, President.
Hi. Are you going home now?
- Yes, Sir. - Yes, Sir.
Look who's here. Aren't you Dong Hui?
- Yes, President. - All right.
- Are you going home too? - Yes, I am.
I see.
Mom. I am home.
Gwang Jin is here.
Although it was so sudden, I did try to prepare something for the guest.
I wonder if this will be to the guest's liking or not.
Dong Hui.
Grandmother.
Who is it?
It's Han Seong Joon across the street.
You're visiting me often now.
- Would you like a drink? - Yes.
Come in.
Can you take out the ice?
All right.
Thank you.
It feels more friendly to see you in my kitchen.
Here you go.
If you were my brother, we could have...
eaten ramyeon together, Couldn't we have?
I am just joking.
If we become too friendly, it will interfere with our business.
Let's go to the living room.
All right. So what do you want to talk about?
I can't let go of Writer Oh Dong Hui.
This is so like you.
I am not running a business.
I am not making a product but a work of art and cultural art.
That's why the crew members including writers aren't...
pieces of tools. We are colleagues producing a work of art together.
They're not pieces that I can change because they are not adequate.
You are the worst as a businessman.
Whether it was kindness or hostility towards me that made you invest,
if you invested because you believed in my ability,
I hope you can continue to trust my decisions.
I hope you would give Writer Oh at least a chance to redeem herself.
What is the reason I have to trust your decisions?
I say this with respect.
I would like to appeal to your emotion.
Please consider me as your brother and give me another chance.
Don't you think what you just said is rude?
I certainly told you that my brother is dead.
I am too desperate that I am willing to be rude.
Do you like her that much?
Are you asking me about my personal feelings?
Can I ask? Just like an older brother asking his younger brother.
I love her very much.
How about you? Have you ever loved anyone?
I am not certain. I've never...
Well, I might have loved once or twice.
I didn't have time, for I've looked for my brother my whole life.
I've never rested, loved anyone,
or gone on trips.
I only worked...
to find my brother.
In a way, I've only loved him...
and looked for him my entire life.
Although the result...
is too miserable.
Seong Joon.
You should leave.
I am cold-hearted by nature.
I don't intend to get involved in someone's love life.
So you should leave now.
Sir.
Thank you.
If I may, may I ask who this is?
Why do you ask?
Just because.
I'm seeing a lot of new sides of you tonight.
That's my brother when he was young.
Does it answer your question?
What?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
How serious are you and Seong Joon?
How involved are you with him?
Are you okay?
You're a naughty man.
Last night, he told me...
that his brother is dead.
Didn't you hear me?
Hyung Seop drove your father...
to death.
One more thing. It's about Seong Joon.