It said Hyung Seop drove your father to his death.
That can't be true.
- It can't be. My dad is... - Come to your senses.
Your dad? Which one?
Do you mean your current dad who lived in an expensive house...
and acted superior because he worked at Seongsoo Trading Company?
Or do you mean your real dad who got beaten up...
and hung himself because he caused little injury...
to rich folk's children?
Which one are you talking about?
I can't believe it.
I just can't.
Right.
I guess it's natural that you find it hard to believe. Why?
It's because Hyung Seop has been such a wonderful father to you.
Do you know that?
Your father only cares about his children.
Your sister Jeong Hwa was badly hurt, so he was furious.
He was an arrogant person who would do anything for his children.
After all that,
Did he think raising that man's son as his own...
was going to make up for what he's done?
I might not be a wealthy and noble person,
but I know others' children are also as precious as mine at least.
Hey, you shouldn't talk on the phone when you're driving.
Sir,
I was talking with my wife...
because my kid got injured on his way to school this morning.
Hang up already.
You're in charge of kids' safety. You can't use your phone.
Sir, he cares a lot about the kids.
Please don't worry.
How can I not be worried?
How would I know if he usually talks on the phone...
while he's driving or not?
I don't do that. I told you my kid got hurt.
Honey, let me call you later.
Guys like you always cause car accidents...
and get kids injured. Do you know that?
Sir, can't you see that I hung up?
- That's enough. - How dare you!
Grandpa...
He explained that his kid got hurt. Please give him a break.
He even turned the engine off. Don't you think that's too much?
Min Seok, get in.
- Ah In, let's get in the car. - Forget it.
I won't send her to the kindergarten today. Just leave by yourselves.
I'll talk to the principal later.
If you want to use your phone while you're driving,
quit this job and find a new one. Okay?
What will you tell the principal about me?
Sir. Goodness.
Seriously.
Enough is enough.
You're not the only one with grandchildren.
What's wrong with that old woman?
Grandpa.
Ah In.
Ah In, let's have fun at home with me. Okay?
No. I hate you.
Ah In.
It was for your safety.
Would the driver be fired today?
I have no idea.
If he gets fired, hire him.
Sorry?
He hasn't changed at all.
He still cares about his children only.
You know people don't change easily.
Today, the executives of Golden Street will come...
to Korea to see you.
We could just have a video conference.
I guess they wanted to come...
and see how you're doing as your absence is prolonged.
Right. I heard that Seong Joon hasn't come to work...
since yesterday.
Why is that? Does he no longer want to work?
I don't think so. It seems like he has some private problems.
He didn't show up without notice.
That is why...
he didn't come to my place to beg me to let his girlfriend...
keep writing the scenario.
What do you plan to do with Jeong Hwa?
As you can easily expect,
I'll have dinners...
and watch movies with her.
Mom.
- Ah In, stop running. - Ah In.
Why are you back home?
Grandpa told me not to go to the kindergarten.
Why did you...
The driver kept talking on the phone while he was driving.
I'll talk to the principal first. Send her tomorrow.
Father, the driver is a really nice person.
It doesn't matter if he's nice or not.
He shouldn't be talking on the phone in the bus.
It might turn into a habit, and who knows what will happen?
Father.
I have to go to work today.
Don't worry. I will watch Ah In today.
Really?
I will watch her when I watch Ye Bin.
Where's your mother-in-law?
I don't think she can get up today.
That's understandable.
Mother.
I don't like you. You should get out.
I will talk Jeong Hwa out of it.
What will you tell her? What?
Do you think she will listen to you just because you talk to her?
- But still... - I don't know.
I have no idea.
I don't even want to look at you. Get out.
He still hasn't called me.
How inconsiderate.
Is it because of Jeong Hwa?
Ms. Oh. Are you there?
Come in.
Gosh.
It's before you head out for work, right?
Sorry to bother you in the morning.
You are not bothering me.
Seong Joon didn't come home last night.
I was wondering if something happened at work.
Well...
I heard he went to the countryside for an urgent matter.
To the countryside? Why?
I don't know. I only heard it through a phone call.
What a brat.
He should have called me to let me know.
How can he do this?
Anyway, I am relieved to hear...
he contacted you.
Sorry to barge in at this hour.
You should get ready for work.
I will.
The number you have dialed is unavailable.
- You'll be connected... - It's...
- to voicemail. - turned off.
What's going on?
What is wrong with you? What have I done wrong?
You really don't know what you've done?
What? What have I done?
How dare you throw a tantrum after you drank?
Is that the way to behave in front of our parents?
Honey, honey!
- Let go of me. - What have you done right?
- What? - I heard...
you made our parents worry the most.
You got laid off and was hurt at a construction site.
You opened that restaurant with our parents' pension, right?
- You little brat. - Jeong Hwa.
You moved in here, but I can't?
I can't stay at my parent's house comfortably?
I lived with my mother-in-law for seven years.
Why can't I make myself at home in this house?
Hey, this isn't your house. This is dad's and mom's house.
You are living off them too!
You aren't the only one. Seong Sik is also living off them.
So why are you picking on me?
What on earth are you doing?
Why are you yelling?
Do you want your mother to hear this too?
- Dad. - Father.
You brats.
I am sorry, Dad.
Hye Joo.
You should go to work.
- Seong Hoon. Let's talk. - Okay.
Jeong Hwa. You should get up now.
Jeong Hwa.
Enough is enough.
What's the matter with you?
Nowadays,
divorce isn't considered to be a flaw,
but it's not something to be proud of.
No matter how difficult it is,
I don't think taking it out on your family is right.
It's because I am stressed out.
Are you the only one who's stressed?
We are even more stressed out because of you.
Say that your stress level is 10, then our level is 100.
Besides, you know what?
The road you walked on before you got married was destroyed.
- What did you say? - That's why...
your nickname is radioactivity.
Hye Joo.
It's been 17 years since I've been married.
You can treat me like a sister.
Look who's talking. You brought your grandmother and cousin.
What?
"Look who's talking"?
Why did you start a fight with her?
She has enough on her plate. She's already stressed out.
She was so rude...
in front of you and Mom.
Leave her alone.
Ye Bin will treat her the same way when she gets old.
You must be upset.
As your mother said, I don't know what children mean to me.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have burdened you.
What do you mean?
I am not doing so well.
Running a fried chicken restaurant is good enough.
How about Seong Sik?
He always makes mistakes and is very clumsy.
That's how he is.
What other choice do you have? You are his brother.
You should take care of him.
Which brings me to my next point.
Why would you want to run another business?
Dad. This time, it will certainly make profits.
- Seong Hoon. - I can't...
live off you forever.
Jeong Hwa came back, and Seong Sik is struggling too.
I should lead our family since I am the oldest son.
Before I do that,
I should move out so that you won't be stressed out about me.
I can also save my face in front of my younger siblings. Dad.
The money that goes into my children...
isn't a small amount.
Even if it isn't, how could you think this way?
The item for this business will be successful for certain.
I've been thinking for a long time since my days as a journalist.
Oh, right.
Mr. Lee, the neighbor decided to help me as well.
- Mr. Lee? - Yes.
- Mr. Lee across the street? - Yes.
What kind of a person is he?
Lately, he is low in my favor.
Dad. He had his reasons.
Are you certain Mr. Lee will help you?
I'm certain.
So I ask you that you help me...
just this once.
Can you keep this a secret from Hye Joo for now?
- But still... - Dad.
Dad.
Yes. Mr. Lee.
Can you talk now?
Yes, I can.
Where are you now?
I'm at a company I invested in.
I invested my money. I ought to follow through to see how it is.
This is my life.
As is your right, of course.
Well...
By the way,
I'd like to meet you regarding the business we've discussed before.
Will you be available in the afternoon?
I am. Let's meet then.
I will contact you later.
All right. Thank you. I will see you later.
It's either go big or go home.
Life is hard.
It's cold. This is heavy.
Seong Hoon! How can you come to work so late?
So what if you are the owner?
Carry these now.
The headquarter sent us chickens.
You are so loud this morning.
It's because you don't do anything since you are the owner.
What do you mean I don't do anything?
You never do anything. Just now, you were on the phone, not helping me.
Who was it on the phone? Whom were you talking to?
Don't be so nosy.
There's no law that says I must work with someone like you all day long.
- Take this. - This isn't even heavy.
- You jerk. - Do you think I want...
to spend an entire day with you?
Don't kid yourself.
I'm so mad. I'm so annoyed.
President Lee.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
There's no need.
- Please take a seat. - Sure.
Director Bang is testing...
our new products. So here I am.
I have something to discuss with you.
You do?
What is it regarding?
I'm thinking of withdrawing my investment...
if the project continues to go on as it is now.
Why do you say that?
The way Director Han works is very different...
from my approach of handling business.
It seems he doesn't think about money at all.
Doing whatever he wants to do isn't exactly called running a business.
On top of that,
the rate the project is developing is quite slow.
I came to meet with Director Han and Bang regarding this matter,
but I couldn't even meet with them.
Director Bang is in charge of...
supervising FGC's overall business.
What about Director Han?
Well... Director Han is...
From my perspective, I've invested a large sum of money.
Don't you think I'll be in a pickle if this continues?
The company might think that producing a drama is an excuse...
and I went to Korea to have fun and waste my investment.
Which made me think that it's not a bad idea...
for me to stop here.
Do you not approve of...
- Director Han? - Well...
I decided to make an invest because of him in the beginning.
But as we proceeded with it, I couldn't trust him anymore.
If the project goes wrong, I'm the one who'd suffer a loss.
You wouldn't be the only one who'd suffer a loss...
if things go wrong.
There must be someone who'll be held accountable for this project.
That is...
Is that Director Han?
Of course. Our company can lay...
all the legal and financial responsibilities...
on Director Han.
That is why he is working really hard.
His life can be at stake.
- Is that so? - Sure.
I'm relieved to hear that.
The number you have dialed is unavailable...
How is writing the scenario going these days?
It's good. I'm doing my best.
Do you know that I made an investment in that drama?
I do.
I see.
Speaking of it,
could you please leave Director Han alone?
What do you mean by that?
I'll try my best with the scenario...
until you're satisfied with it.
Can you please stop meddling with the project...
so that he can make the best of his capabilities?
Do you backbite me in your room on the rooftop?
No, we don't.
He's not that kind of person.
He'd never do that.
- Why do you cover up for him? - Sorry?
I almost thought you're his girlfriend.
Anyway, I appreciate your opinion.
I'll take that into account. See you.
I promise to do my best.
We can do it. Thank you in advance.
Sir, what are you doing here?
It's very sunny today.
Spring is here.
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
I'm just enjoying the lovely weather.
Okay.
I have no idea what I am doing now.
You're taking revenge.
Did you have to put it that way?
I met Dong Hui who lives on the rooftop room.
I could see that she really likes Seong Joon.
Are you jealous?
No.
It was disgusting instead.
Well,
I was a little jealous too.
I was thinking what I did in her age.
All I did were studying and working all day long.
As you said,
I spent my young days planning the revenge...
and looking for my brother.
And he has a family who cares about him so much...
and a girlfriend who loves him.
Sir.
It's not too late to back out.
You know how wicked I am.
What's with you?
By the way,
is your uncle's family all right?
I'm sure...
Mr. Lee would never let his family live happily.
Hee Sook, what brings you here?
Is Aunt here?
- She's in her room. - I see.
How dare you come to my house?
Aunt.
Then, I'm leaving.
Are you trying to run away?
This is all your fault.
You met him when you were on a trip and made him return to Korea.
This time, Hee Sook dragged him into my mom's house.
What on earth do you think you're doing now?
What do you mean Hee Sook dragged him in?
Well, Jeong Eun,
I'll explain to you later.
Don't worry and leave. You should go.
You're always the worst troublemaker.
Jeong Eun, please leave. I'll see you later.
- Aunt. - Shut it.
What do you want me to do? Chang Soo has no instructor...
to help him to prepare for the coming competition.
What do you mean he has no instructor?
There are many instructors out there.
But he needs a world-class instructor.
So did you have to open up my old wound...
just to find a good teacher for Chang Soo?
Did you say it's a wound?
- Don't you think it's so romantic? - What?
Did you say it's romantic?
Think carefully.
You're such a happy woman.
There's hardly anyone who can still date a guy in your age.
Men don't even find women in my age attractive.
But your case is so special.
A charming man who still remembers you as his first love...
comes to you and calls you in a sweet voice like this,
"Ae Ri."
I especially like him that he hasn't come back for the last 30 years.
What's good about that?
I had to suffer for 30 years.
Living with one person for 30 years must've been more painful.
You know what Seong Sik is like.
I lived with him for 16 years already.
And I'm seriously sick of him.
You must be grateful that he showed up so late.
Be quiet.
I know you're trying to sugarcoat it because it's none of your business.
Aunt, please think positively.
Now that he made his comeback, Chang Soo might learn from him...
and make a good result at the competition.
Isn't it also a great opportunity for you...
to relieve your old grudges against him?
I no longer have anything to do with him.
And this isn't just about me. What about my mom?
If that jerk gets caught by Mom,
he'd be as good as dead. Do you know that?
- My goodness. - What is it this time?
He's in our place now.
I must haven't come here.
- He's alone with Chang Soo there. - What?
My heart is
Young and green
So I shall live
In a blue mountain
- During the long years - During the long years
- After years - After years
- The whole world - The whole world
- Has changed - Has changed
- Yet the blue mountain - Yet the blue mountain
- Remains unchanged - Remains unchanged
- So I shall - So I shall
- Live in the blue mountain - Live in the blue mountain
This spring
This is my favorite song composed by Kim Yeon Jun.
It's "I Shall Live In Green Mountain".
How can Chang Soo sing it so well?
Are you listening, Elizabeth?
Are you listening to Chang Soo's singing?
Yes.
I am listening.
If you're feeling okay, you should come out here.
Then you will hear it better.
Goodness, his voice is...
so loud and resonant.
You never know how children will turn out.
So you shouldn't look down on them because their grades are bad.
You have to be patient and watch them.
Who would've thought that Chang Soo could sing?
Right, Elizabeth?
Wait.
Is this Chang Soo's voice?
It feels strange.
Wait.
What is this unpleasant feeling?
This voice sounds very familiar.
Is it him?
Stop.
- Ae Ri. - Stop and hurry out.
You have to escape.
Grandma just called.
- What? - She asked if Chang Soo is singing.
- You have to run. - Okay.
Hurry up. Stop wasting time.
- Come on. Hurry up. Go! - Run!
Chang Soo, get your coat and follow me.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
Hurry up.
I am coming, girl.
- Run. - Okay.
Run.
Why is there nobody here?
Where are they?
This is strange.
I heard someone singing.
I heard the unpleasant voice...
that came from under our windows 30 years ago.
What is this?
Isn't this a man's handkerchief?
"Made in Italy".
Is there anyone in the house who's been to Italy?
I can't believe I'm doing this.
Welcome.
What are you doing here, Jeong Eun?
Are you here to eat fried chicken?
Where is Seong Hoon?
I don't know. He went out to meet someone.
He always makes me work and slacks off.
Have a seat.
Do you want anything?
Seong Sik, do me a favor.
Can you answer my question honestly?
What is it?
Hey.
Don't look at me with those scary eyes.
It reminds me of the nightmare at the Public Prosecutors' Office.
Seong Sik, why did you get fired from the TV show?
What?
Why are you suddenly hitting me on a sore spot?
Why did I get fired?
That was...
because I had no connection.
It feels so terrible when I think about that.
And then what happened? What happened after that?
What happened after that?
Mr. Lee introduced me...
to Senior Secretary Kim Young Tae, and I almost became successful,
although...
I ended up like this in the end.
- What? - Goodness.
Are you saying it was Hyun Woo who introduced you...
to that corrupt politician?
Gosh, you surprised me.
Hey,
I was traumatized by the interrogation.
They questioned me day and night.
But still, Mr. Lee saved me from going to jail.
Thank goodness.
Honestly, what did Mr. Lee do wrong?
It was my fault that I was blinded by the desire...
to win a position and did something illegal.
Anyway,
how can a person be so great?
The moment I saw him, I knew he wasn't just a construction manager.
But I never expected him to be the CEO of Golden Street.
Didn't you think it was strange?
What do you mean?
Didn't you find it strange that he went from a construction manager...
to a CEO of an investment company?
Jeong Eun, even Warren Buffett...
lives in the country town of Omaha, Nebraska,
disguised as an ordinary townsman.
He goes out to town in the morning to buy a newspaper.
That's the lifestyle of the true rich Americans.
You don't know anything. Goodness.
Our family is beyond help.
What does Seong Hoon think?
You know,
Seong Hoon is the biggest admirer of Mr. Lee.
Mr. Lee helped him so much, you know?
What are you talking about?
When he was laid off from work and was lost, Mr. Lee got him a job.
He got hurt after working only a short while,
but Mr. Lee paid him monthly pay, pension,
and even compensation.
Why did Seong Hoon get laid off from work?
Of course,
that's because he is incompetent.
He was so obsessed with that penguin business,
and he couldn't think about anything else.
How could he write good articles?
Mr. Lee helped him set up this restaurant too.
He rented out this place for a really cheap price.
Mr. Lee owns this building too.
He let me rent the office for a really cheap price too...
when I was opening my own business.
I miss...
that time.
I could go to your place.
I thought it would be uncomfortable for you.
I don't think your family would be happy...
if they find out about your business plan.
Did you tell the elders about it?
Yes, I did. They are not too happy about it.
I've failed before, you know?
Honestly, I don't want to recommend it to you.
When it comes to business, it's all or nothing.
I think your restaurant is doing quite well.
Why are you trying to do a new business?
I am a father and the eldest son of the family, you know?
My parents lost all their savings because of me.
Seong Sik caused so much trouble,
and now he's serving at my restaurant.
Goodness, and my younger sister is now...
Anyway, my future is dark.
My children are still very young too.
I feel very frustrated.
You have a big responsibility.
Yes. That's why I want to plan it thoroughly...
and raise my family.
By any chance,
did you check my proposal?
I am sorry,
but we are not experts in this area.
I'm afraid we can't invest in your business.
Is there...
absolutely no chance?
Mr. Lee.
We can't go on like this.
I've recently met someone...
who's planning a business similar to this.
What?
Would you like to meet him?
Really?
Now that Dong Hui comes to work every day,
Director Han doesn't come to work.
What's wrong with our team?
I know. It's very unlike him.
Dong Hui, do you have any clue?
I think...
I heard that he's going to a province.
To a province? Which province? Did he go on a business trip?
Ms. Hong, did he?
I wouldn't know.
By the way, it feels strange.
How does Dong Hui know what we don't know?
- What? - I know.
Stop being so ridiculous.
You can't help suspecting them when there are young people.
It's just that we're bored. We are bored.
Director Han is acting strange these days.
Where did he go...
at this important time?
Where's Mom and Dad?
They seemed very weak,
so I cooked chicken porridge for them.
You should've treated them better before.
What?
What's the use of cooking them chicken porridge?
You all failed and invaded their place.
Hye Joo even brought her family with her.
Jeong Hwa!
Jeong Hwa, you should eat.
Okay. Give me a glass of water.
Sure.
Wait. I'll get you a glass of water.
Here you go.
Stop it.
Ji Hoon. Ah In.
- Here are sausages. - Thank you.
- Aunt. What about me? - Ask your mother.
Here's a delicious salad for you, Chang Soo.
Mom. A salad won't be enough for me to sing.
You should still eat it. You didn't have vegetables today.
Okay. I will then if you say so.
What a nice boy. How can you listen to me so well?
Good boy. You are such a good son.
Mom. What a soft touch you have.
Hey, you. You are so over the top.
Stop it. Hye Joo.
It's because I didn't eat sausages.
How could you act like this?
Jeong Hwa. What is your point now?
Do you really want to live having your children switched?
What is this mess? It's confusing me since I was away.
- Jeong Hwa. What happened was... - Jeong Hwa.
This is a settled matter.
We had a difficult time coping with the switch.
You might be confused since you were away.
From our perspective, you are beating a dead horse.
So what?
So you should just have you meal. Make sure you chew well. Okay?
Mom, I don't want to eat.
Why? You have to eat a lot if you want to grow taller.
Hye Joo. Make a fried egg for Ye Bin.
A fried egg?
- Calm down. - Make one please.
Sure. I will make one right away.
Chang Soo. How did you end up learning vocal music?
My school teacher recommended it.
You know what?
Pavarotti isn't good at singing because he's fat.
It's because he's a good opera singer, we don't hold it against it.
You should lose some weight.
Nowadays, opera singers are slim and handsome.
They watch their figure like a soccer player.
- Okay. - And you, Ji Hoon.
- Are you going to be a magician? - Yes. I plan on it.
You think every magician succeeds like David Copperfield.
It's not true.
You know people make desperate effort in order to become magicians.
If you don't put all of your effort into it, you will end up...
taking out a rabbit or a pigeon out of a hat at a preschool recital.
- What? - And you, Ah In.
- Yes? - Can't you speak English well?
"Hi. How are you? I'm fine. Thank you." Is this all you can do?
I think for the time we stay here, you should learn from Ye Bin.
What?
Hye Joo. Calm down.
How can I calm down? She treats us like servants. She says things...
she shouldn't say in front of our children. How can I stay calm?
She's stressed out.
I told her this morning that she's not the only one who's stressed out.
What will you do? Will you fight in front of Father rand Mother?
Let me know if a daughter-in-law won after fighting her sister-in-law.
Then should I back off?
Then are you going to get a sword and lead a troop?
Please compose yourself.
It doesn't matter. We will forever be subordinates to her.
Hee Sook. Since when have you become obedient...
and accommodating?
You don't know me well.
Except for my children's education,
I was always obedient and accommodating.
My husband...
cheated on me with that Anchor Jang Yoo Ra.
Even though the whole country knows about the affair,
I didn't even bat an eye.
It only took me four days to recover.
In that sense, I hold you to the highest respect.
Some people are never meant to grow up. It's water under the bridge.
Jeong Hwa is one of them.
She will never come to her senses.
So let's not turn this into a big deal.
Why don't we just hold back? Okay, Hye Joo?
- But still... - Hye Joo.
All right. You're so close we might kiss.
- So what? - Have you gone mad?
- Calm down. - Stop it.
Jeong Hwa. Where are the children?
- They went down after we talked. - They did?
I see. Are you going somewhere at this late hour?
I'm going to buy coffee. We ran out. Why?
Are you going to get it for me? I need to help Ye Bin brush her teeth.
What a shame. I have to help Ah In brush her teeth too.
Why did you ask if you weren't going to get it for me?
Goodness. Are you all right, Jeong Hwa?
Jeong Hwa. Are you okay?
Are you hurt? You should've been more careful.
You should stop by a pharmacy too.
- Hye Joo. - What?
- What are you doing? - You're here.
What is that?
Is this yours?
No, it's not. Where did you get it?
- This is weird. - What is weird?
Never mind.
By the way, you don't look so good.
- It's because of Seong Joon. - What is it?
Did something happen to him?
He hasn't come home for days without calling us.
I thought he was on a business trip.
That's what Dong Hui said.
It doesn't matter how urgent it is.
He never forgets to call and inform us.
That's right.
I think...
- it's because of Jeong Hwa. - What?
You know how Jeong Hwa bullies him.
She even bullied him on the day he came here.
He thinks he's not welcomed even if we welcome him.
It must've been hard on him. He must have felt uncomfortable...
after finding out Jeong Hwa will stay with us for a while.
You know that Jeong Hwa isn't exactly the agreeable type.
Anyway, you need to reflect on your wrongdoings.
I told you not to spoil her.
Just because she was your only daughter,
you spoiled her by treating her like a princess.
Look how selfish she turned out to be.
I have no one to blame, but myself.
Gosh. Poor Seong Joon.
(A car accident in Bangbae-dong, 1993)
(Geumbit Academy's bus was turned over.)
(Geumbit Academy's bus)
Hyung Seop drove your father to death.
Think of Dong Hui as your cousin and get along with her.
If she were alive,
she'd be the biggest shareholder. Do you know that?
Then you will have no place in this company.
Is Ms. Oh that important to you, Dad?
20 years ago, she was a very special person...
for your grandmother.
This is Bang Mi Joo. Under Oh Dong Hui's family history,
Oh Gui Boon should be listed.
Can you do a background check on her?
And get me the files regarding Chairwoman Park's disappearance.
Are you feeling better?
Yes, I am.
Perhaps, you were exhausted.
No, I wasn't.
My house is quite big.
Well, people with resources...
always live in a big house.
By the way, I think my father relies on you a lot.
He doesn't rely on me.
It's just because I raised him since he was young.
It's just an attachment, nothing else.
From what I have gathered, I learned you were quite close...
with my grandmother who passed away.
She did take good care of me.
It was after I lost my husband.
I relied on her quite a lot.
She understood and looked out for me.
My gratitude towards her still hasn't changed.
Then you must be aware of...
my grandmother's disappearance.
Yes, I was informed after her disappearance.
Actually, I came to ask you something.
I don't think the reason why my dad is putting off reporting...
my grandmother's death is because he believes she is still alive.
If it is, he shouldn't have reported Hyun Jeong's death either.
If he admits that my grandmother is dead,
her will would automatically be revealed.
He must be afraid of what the will might state.
That's why I wanted to ask you...
if you know what my grandmother's will says.
How can I know what it says?
Do you have a copy of it then?
No. That's not possible.
Does it say anything about Bang Hyun Jeong,
my cousin?
No. I don't know that.
Really?
Of course.
How would I know anything about it?
Even your father doesn't know what it says.
There is no way a mere housekeeper like me knows what it's about.
I don't think my grandmother's alive.
It's been 20 years since her disappearance.
I believe...
we should follow her will whether it's advantageous...
to me and my dad or not. It's what she wanted.
I want you...
to convince my dad to report my grandmother's death...
as soon as possible.
I know my dad relies on you like you're his real mother.
You can at least do that, right?
I'm not sure.
I don't know if I can.
Besides,
wouldn't it be possible...
that your grandmother...
is still alive somewhere?
Pardon?
Your grandmother is such a strong person.
What are you talking about?
It's nothing.
I suddenly started to miss her.
I'm greatly indebted to her.
What are you doing here?
Why? Can't I be here?
You came to my place the other day,
so I came to yours this time.
Do you think I'm being childish?
No. I'm glad you came.
Please come back inside. I'll cook you some noodles.
Where is Director Han?
Has he come back yet?
No.
What do you think the reason is?
I'm not sure.
He has never behaved this way for the last five years.
Are you saying I'm responsible for this as well?
I'm just saying you're good at meddling in others' business.
If your scripts for episodes 3 and 4 don't get picked,
you should give up completely. You know that, right?
Yes. I do know that.
- Quit your job at the company too. - Excuse me?
I don't want to be involved with you anymore.
I'll pay off your brother's debt...
with my own money.
If your scripts don't get picked, please resign.
Also, stop coming to my house even if my dad asks you to.
We see each other at work and at home too.
Isn't that too tiring for both of us?
You're the one who came to my house today.
This isn't your house. It's Director Han's house.
Please tell him to call me when he comes back.
I'm going to become a famous writer,
and I'm never going to work with you.
You will see.
Stay still. I'm going to dry your hair for you.
Mother. I'm here.
Why did you come? You should be making dinner downstairs.
No. I didn't want you to take care of Ye Bin by yourself.
Where is Father?
He went to the supermarket to buy yogurt for Ye Bin.
Please give me that towel. I'll dry her hair.
All right.
Ye Bin. Let's sit on the sofa. I'll dry your hair.
Mother. I know you must be upset.
Of course, I am.
I'm sure there will be a solution.
No, there isn't. They've already filed a suit.
Nothing will solve it now.
Jeong Hwa and her husband didn't understand each other.
It'll be better for Jeong Hwa to just split up with him.
I'm not sure...
if she's doing the right thing.
You still shouldn't stay inside the house all day.
It'll stress you out more.
Don't you have aerobics classes anymore?
I don't have time to go to aerobics classes.
Jeong Hwa is causing trouble now right after Seong Sik's scandal.
I'm too embarrassed to even go out of the house now.
Besides, I have to babysit Ye Bin. I can't go anywhere.
Where is Jeong Hwa?
I don't know. She just went out.
Where did she go?
You're as beautiful as always, Ms. Han.
That's not true. I'm a woman who has a child now.
It's true. You don't look much different from before.
Thank you, sir.
All right. Are you back for good?
Yes. I guess so.
Did you want to meet me because you wanted to come back to work?
Yes. If you give me a good show to host, I won't say no.
But you'll have to compete with the young anchors.
Yes. I suppose.
It's very hard to host a good show...
even for young and popular anchors.
I see.
What are you doing this weekend?
- Sorry? - Do you want to play golf with me?
Sure.
Thank you.
Jeong Hwa.
Hyun Woo.
You look tired today.
Am I wrong?
You're right. I had a long day.
Do you have any beer?
I think beer suits this house...
better than coffee.
I got both.
You keep your place very neat.
It feels as if you're only staying here temporarily.
It's just my personality.
Beer tastes great when I feel frustrated.
Are you worried about something?
No one has given me a job yet.
I knew it would be hard to go back to work after seven years,
but I'm a little upset because it's not going so well.
Well...
Would you like me to help you?
I'm still confused whether you're just being kind...
or you're interested in me.
Is it ugly?
It's a deep scar.
I had a big accident.
An accident?
That accident left a scar on my life.
A scar that can't be forever removed.
Did it hurt?
I'm not sure.
It must have hurt a lot.
Why?
It's a scar that...
doesn't suit such a beauty like you.
Shall we go and get some fresh air?
Oh, my. You can see our house so well from here.
You can see the whole neighborhood here.
Our house looks so old now. It used to be the best building before.
It should be rebuilt.
What do you think about Channel T?
I think you'll be great on a show about current events.
You're a competent man.
Well... I thought you knew.
What do you want me to do in return?
I'm not sure. Why don't you...
give me some time to think about it?
Are you always like this?
Well... On some level.
It's a bit cold. Shall we go back in?
Okay. I think we got enough fresh air.
I just don't know...
what you're trying to get from doing this.
I actually felt very lonely today.
Thank you.
I also felt lonely today. Thank you for a lovely time.
Why are you still single?
Why are you getting divorced?
What?
If I had known such a great man was living across from my house,
I would've come back sooner.
I feel the same way.
I can go by myself from here.
- I guess that's better. - Good night.
Good night, Jeong Hwa.
Please don't do this.
I feel like dying.
I really feel like I'm going to die.
- Jeong Eun. - That's right.
I'm Han Jeong Eun, the woman you once liked.
I told you not to come here.
How can I not? I can't just let you ruin yourself.
I can't let my family get ruined.
I can't let myself get ruined.
Go and tell them then.
Go to your uncle and tell him who I am.
Hyun Woo. Please.
I'm tired of all this too.
Tell your whole family to settle things with me...
once and for all.
That's Mr. Lee.
I thought he was a decent guy.
What is he doing with a woman on the street?
This is hard for me too.
- Hyun Woo. - Please go back.
Hyun Woo. Hyun Woo!
Director Han.
I'm sorry I made you wait for so long.
I'm sorry I didn't answer my phone.
What's wrong?
You look terrible. What happened?
Director Han.
Give me a minute. I'm going to make some tea.
You must be cold. Please sit.
What are you doing?
What's wrong? Why are you doing this?
Why didn't you tell me you were going on a business trip?
What have you been doing? You look haggard.
Mom. I want my breakfast.
I set it up for you too. Where is Ye Bin?
She's still sleeping. She won't wake up.
- It's been a long time. - Yes.
By the way, you can't just go on a business trip without saying a word.
Mom and Dad were worried about you.
Mom. Are you the one who raised him so poorly like this?
You're in no place to say such a thing.
You're so immature. You need to grow up.
Still, he shouldn't have done that.
How can he treat his parents so rudely?
Are you having breakfast, Seong Joon?
What's wrong?
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
Is something wrong?
Gosh. Nothing is wrong.
Why is everyone picking on him? Seong Joon. Come on and eat.
You should be quiet too.
You always say mean things at breakfast.
You haven't changed at all.
Well... I'll have breakfast later.
Why?
Excuse me.
Oh, dear. What's wrong with him?
Did he just do that to make me feel uncomfortable? My gosh.
Seong Joon.
Come on out.
What's the matter with you?
Do you have something to say to me?
What's wrong with you?
You're making me upset.
I have...
something I want to ask you.
What?
What is it?
By any chance,
did you...
make my biological father die?
Is it true...
that you made my biological father die?
Seong Joon.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Checking her identity...
might make us lucky.
Until when...
do I have to live as if I don't exist?
Mom, Seong Joon has a woman.
It's Dong Hui.
My uncle really believed...
that your father had been drunk-driving.
Tell me.
Who am I? What are you keeping from me?