Don't you think it's too late to ask for forgiveness?
(Episode 39)
Did you think your wrongdoing would be justified if you raise Sang Woo?
I know I don't deserve to be forgiven.
I've ruined...
a guy's life.
And his young children have gone...
through a lot because of me.
How could I be forgiven?
If you know that well,
why did you come here?
I need you to leave now.
Leave already!
Before that,
please let me ask you a favor.
Please...
leave...
with Seong Joon as soon as possible.
My family thinks...
he's my own son.
But...
if they find out that he's not my son...
but the driver's son,
they will abandon...
Seong Joon coldly.
Then they will blame...
Seong Joon...
for everything.
So what does it have to do with us?
We no longer...
want to be entangled with you.
That'd be better for me as well.
Before it's too late,
before everyone finds out the truth,
please leave with Seong Joon.
That's for Seong Joon's sake.
Why?
Are you afraid that your family will know what you've done in the past?
You used to be a good father, a good husband, and a good neighbor.
Now you're afraid that others might find out your true colors?
Is that why you took Sang Woo away from me and raised him?
How dare you try to cover your sins like this?
You're such a coward and a scum.
Hyun Woo!
- Please stop. - See?
Now you know who this guy you believed to be your dad...
really is!
Please get up.
Let's go home.
Dad.
Seong Joon.
Sang Woo.
Sang Woo!
What are you doing?
Let me walk him home.
We can talk later.
Let's go, Dad.
- Seong Joon... - Hurry up.
Dad.
Go to your brother.
Let me take you home.
Hey.
You should be cursing me out and kicking me with him.
Why are you doing this?
You shouldn't be nice to me.
Go to him now.
Don't say anything.
Let's go.
Dad.
Seong Sik. Spread the blankets for him.
What? Okay. I'm going.
- Hey. Hyung Seop. - Honey. What's wrong?
Seong Joon. What's wrong with him?
He was fine a little while ago. What's going on?
- Goodness. - Oh my.
- Slowly. Be careful. - Hyung Seop.
- What's up with him? - Dad. Should we go to the hospital?
Dad. Should I take you there?
Hyung Seop. Pull yourself together.
What's gotten into you lately?
Han Seong Joon. Where did you go with Dad?
Hey. Why can't you answer me?
He was fine when he went out, but now he's not in good condition.
Where did you go?
I will tell you later.
Did you hear him?
How dare you act so rude?
You ought to answer when I ask you a question.
Where are you going now?
Leave him alone.
Don't bother him.
Dad.
What is he doing again?
What are you doing now?
Did you really have to do this?
What?
Anyway,
he is just a poor, weak old man.
What is your point?
You are right.
He's a bad person.
He shouldn't have done that,
no matter how precious his children were to him.
He shouldn't have mistreated and ignored...
poor people just because he had money.
I also hate and despise that kind of people.
If you know this,
how can you take him outside in front of me?
I hope you will calm down. If you don't,
you are no better than my father 20 years ago.
Who is your father?
Do you still call him your father?
Your father...
wasn't a selfish old man. He was a poor bus driver.
He had no connections or anyone to rely on.
There wasn't a single person who'd listen to his complaints.
A pitiful bus driver who was penniless...
- is your father. - I know.
I know how my defenseless father passed away...
and what mistake my current father made to him,
- but... - No.
You don't know.
Hyun Woo.
Do you know what this is?
It's the tie our father hanged himself with.
It's the tie Han Hyung Seop loosened...
in order to beat up our father.
Our father...
picked this up and hanged himself.
Hyun Woo.
Do you still feel...
sympathy for that vicious man after seeing this?
Do you still pity him?
Please...
Please give me some time.
How much more time do you need?
I've been waiting for 23 years.
I told you everything.
Even at this moment, I'm waiting for you.
I need time to hate him.
You had 23 years.
I had only a few weeks.
- Sang Woo. - During the last 23 years,
I trusted and followed my father.
During that time, my father wasn't a dead bus driver.
It was Han Hyung Seop.
It's a long period of time.
How could I...
throw away those years overnight?
Don't be weak.
You are not a kid.
So please. I beg of you to give me some time.
How could you...
Hyun Woo.
You...
Get a grip!
Mom. I'm going out.
How's Dad?
Can't you see?
He hasn't moved an inch since last night.
Don't bother Dad.
You should ask Seong Joon.
What do you mean?
I think the reason why he's acting like this has to do with Seong Joon.
Bring Seong Joon and ask him.
Jeong Hwa.
Stop talking nonsense and just go.
Are you all right? Can you sit up?
Dad.
I told you to go.
Anyway, I'm going.
Let's talk tonight.
- Are you going somewhere? - Yes.
You should say your greetings in the morning properly and go.
Goodness. She's so rude.
So please tell me.
What is going on with you these days?
Are you feeling better?
What was Jeong Hwa talking about?
Mother mentioned something about that too.
You told Mother that Seong Joon was not your son.
Why did you tell her that? What do you mean by that?
- Honey. - Hyung Seop.
I don't know what's going on with you.
Don't you think it's better to...
tell your mother and wife at least?
What you told me troubled me greatly.
That's why I told Jeong Ae what you told me.
I couldn't bear this by myself.
So tell us. What happened?
Why are you bringing up Seong Joon's past now?
You brought him home because you said he was your son.
You said he was born out of wedlock.
How can you tell us he's not your son now?
Don't press him for an answer. Speak softly.
Mother.
I lived with this man for 40 years and he seems to be sly.
20 years ago, he said he had an affair...
and brought a child home.
Now he's telling us that it wasn't true.
Then whose family does he belong to?
Did you turn someone else's son into yours and bring him home?
Whom have I been raising for 20 years?
Mother, if this is the case, this is more aggravating.
You don't have to feel aggravated by this.
Let's hear him out.
He's not explaining himself.
That's why I feel more insulted and uncomfortable.
Hey. Stop it. Ask Seong Joon when he comes back.
Ask him if he knows something.
By any chance,
does Seong Joon know about this?
Is that why you weren't getting alone well lately?
Is that it?
Honey.
It's not the time for you to feel glum.
It's not Ji Hoon's first time rebelling against you.
Besides, does it really matter in what place he is ranked?
What good is it if he's ranked first?
The house he's living in now has been put up as a collateral.
His father will be a manager of a fried chicken restaurant...
or a mediocre lawyer if things keep going as it is now.
Someone needs to come up with a plan to lead this family.
So what?
Who's going to lead this family?
It will be me, of course.
Please know your place.
Because of you,
the children are bullied at school.
Tell them to wait a bit.
Tell them their father will return as a new, reformed man.
Don't just think about your success.
Try to get Ji Hoon to study again.
Chang Soo is excelling at singing,
Ji Hoon's grades has dramatically gone down.
Hye Joo isn't the type to nag Ji Hoon to study.
It might help if I don't see him.
Living in the same house isn't helping.
- I'm about to lose my mind. - Shut it!
Be quiet!
Goodness.
Can't you really think about someone else than your children?
The grown-ups must be successful for the children to be successful.
He's only in his third year of middle school.
It will take forever for a teenager to restore his family.
- So what's your plan? - Why do you even ask?
Now that he wants to make money by getting a mortgage,
I will regain...
the tarnished reputation of our family using my old fame.
Reputation is money, right?
I will make some money with the reputation...
and get out of this house as soon as possible...
and no longer argue with my brother. Okay?
I'll move out of this house.
Honey, where are you going?
You should go talk to Ji Hoon. Honey!
Gosh.
Where are you going?
Hang on a second.
Gosh.
Oh my goodness.
Where on earth are we going?
Aren't you going to tell me?
Get off the car.
Where are we?
Are you going to bury me because I'm against your business?
Why would I bury you?
Why would I bury my wife who spent half her life with me?
I'm here to show you how you will live in comfort...
from now on.
- Live in comfort? - Hye Joo.
Watch carefully.
From here to there,
there will be the main building of the theme park.
There will be amenities for visitors over there.
And over there will be...
a huge aquarium.
- Where? - Right over there.
Do you see it?
- I don't see anything. - Hey.
You will see them once they are built.
World-famous architects will design the buildings.
The buildings will stand out.
Mr. Han, you are here.
I didn't know you were here.
Of course. We will start construction soon.
Well...
I came here with my wife.
Did you?
It's nice to meet you, ma'am.
When will you start construction?
We will start early next week.
Take a look at this.
As you can see, this is the main building.
This is the aquarium.
Are you sure you looked into it closely?
Hye Joo.
I feel relieved at heart just by looking at the land.
As a man,
I should've had...
a big dream just like this. Don't you think?
Are you sure everything is okay?
What do you think?
They will start construction next week.
So are you sure you checked the whole thing?
- You are... - Hye Joo.
There will be a light...
at the end of the tunnel.
(Inbox)
Why isn't the sales report ready yet?
It has never happened before.
Well, Dong Hui was in charge of the work.
So? Are you saying it's not ready because she's not here?
Are you using her as an excuse?
I'm sorry. I will have it ready as soon as possible.
Hello, Writer Choi. Did you get my message?
I was too busy to give you a call.
What do you mean you want to stay out of this?
Writer Choi, please don't be upset.
I understand it hurt your feelings.
As you know, Oh Dong Hui is a novice writer.
She won't be able to write well due to her lack of persistence.
I'm sure she will give up writing soon.
So please...
Writer Choi! Writer Choi!
I can't believe this.
Dong Hui is already fired.
Who would write the script now?
Did you run away just to be at a place like this?
Don't you know that Gui Boon ran away from my father?
Gui Boon has a connection...
with my grandmother who was the chairwoman.
My father is looking for Gui Boon...
to find my grandmother and her will.
All I'm saying...
is that you shouldn't trample...
on her time and trouble to hide in a remote town...
just because of your stupid love stuff.
Dong Hui.
Did you get caught by your grandmother again?
You didn't send me an email.
You didn't even read my email yet.
Is everything all right?
I'm worried.
It's just too long...
to wait until the weekend.
Right.
You nailed the scripts for episode 5 and 6 again.
I want to celebrate it with you.
(Your mail has been successfully sent.)
Senior Secretary Kim, how are you?
It's Han Seong Sik.
How have you been?
Senior Secretary Kim.
How dare you come here?
Well...
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm just here to pay my respects to you.
Your respects?
How dare you come here after doing such things?
Why...
are you upset? What did I do wrong?
I just went to the prosecutor's office...
and had seolleongtang. That's it.
I had six bowls of seolleongtang.
How could a small fry like you...
work as a mole?
What do you mean?
You and Lee Hyun Woo of Jinsung Daily News...
revealed the relations...
between Seonghan Group and Minjeong Party.
What? What did you say?
Gosh. He said he'd get me...
a smart and obedient guy as a scapegoat.
- It was a dirty trick. - What?
- A scapegoat? A dirty trick? - Shut your mouth.
Lee Hyun Woo of Jinsung Daily News...
got me a stupid and loud guy like you...
on purpose.
Then he made me a fool...
printing out the newspapers.
What?
What exactly do you mean?
Are you saying Lee Hyun Woo...
used me as a scapegoat?
To reveal the connection between you and Seonghan Group?
Seong Sik.
There's not much to say about it.
I won't let you set foot in this business again.
Don't even think about...
working in politics or broadcasting.
Get out of my office now.
Senior Secretary Kim.
Senior Secretary Kim!
Are you saying...
I should drop the case...
and settle my divorce?
Yes. They say you should do that...
if you want to take your child.
Why? Why do you think I stayed married to him for seven years?
Why should I step back without getting a penny?
This isn't fair.
I didn't cheat on him.
It's hard to prove your innocence about the photos.
They say Jinsung Daily News who spread the photos...
passed the information to James Jeong.
The photos were taken...
to catch you having an affair.
What did you say? Jinsung Daily News?
My older brother used to work there.
They don't have an entertainment department.
You're right. They were just a daily paper.
But they were recently taken over by Golden Street...
and has expanded the firm.
Then they created an entertainment department.
Wait.
Did you say Golden Street?
Yes. It is an investment company...
based on Wall Street.
They've made their way to Korea eating up many domestic companies.
The CEO is David Lee.
He's very famous in that industry.
David Lee?
Do you mean Lee Hyun Woo?
Yes, that's right.
That jerk.
Jeong Hwa! Jeong Hwa!
There you are!
- Sir! - Jeong Hwa!
Are you okay, sir?
Hyun Woo.
What is it?
Don't you know?
I heard you're the CEO of Jinsung Daily News.
Did you tell them to upload my pictures? Did you?
Who are you?
What's your real identity?
Why are you doing this to me? What did I do to you?
Tell me. Tell me, you jerk!
Is it your hobby to ruin a person's life?
Calm down, Jeong Hwa. Don't do this here.
Jeong Hwa, what are you doing?
Don't stop me.
Because of this jerk, all the struggles I put up with...
during my marriage became useless.
I lost my divorce trial!
He did that to you too?
Move.
Mr. Lee!
I need to talk to you too.
What did you do to me?
I just met Senior Secretary Kim.
Is it true that you wanted to use me as a scapegoat?
- What's going on with you? - Let go!
I have just as many things to say to him as Jeong Hwa.
Goodness.
At least tell me the reason.
Did I do something wrong to you?
What did I do so wrong...
to make you tear me into pieces?
I told you.
I am not a charity worker.
Aren't you fools for expecting...
my favor without any reason or anything in return?
What?
Am I your family?
Am I your relative?
Or are we even friends?
On what grounds did you ask for my favor?
I am just your next door neighbor.
Then you should've acted like a next door neighbor!
Why didn't you? Why?
If you want to know the other reason,
go ask your father.
He would know much better than me.
Mom. Dad... Where is Dad?
Mom, where is Dad?
Why are you looking for him?
Why are you making a fuss together?
Dad! Are you in there?
What...
What's going on? Why are they making such a fuss?
Dad, why is Mr. Lee, our neighbor...
doing these harms to us?
What are you talking about?
He told me to ask Dad.
I asked him why he's making our lives miserable,
and he told me to ask Dad.
What do you mean? How did he make your lives miserable?
Mom, Grandmother, everything bad that happened to our family...
was because of Mr. Lee.
What do you mean? Tell me in a way that I understand.
The whole story was revealed just today.
He's the one who made Jeong Hwa lose the divorce trial...
by making that scandalous photos go viral.
It was also him who persuaded me to get into politics...
after getting fired from the broadcasting job.
What do you mean?
Are you listening, Mom?
Wait.
Can it also be him...
who made me lose my broadcasting job?
Isn't it obvious?
He wouldn't even have broken a sweat firing you.
What on earth is happening?
Dad, what happened?
After all he's done,
he didn't even look guilty. He proudly told us...
to ask you what happened.
What happened? You know everything, right?
Tell me quickly. Will you?
So are you saying you all became like this...
- because of Mr. Lee, the neighbor? - Goodness.
- Goodness. - Grandmother! Grandmother!
Dad, please tell me.
Stop it, all of you!
Can't you see that Uncle is in pain?
Why are you torturing him when you don't know anything?
Stop making him miserable.
You know something, don't you?
Know what?
You told me to watch out for Hyun Woo.
Even before all these happened,
you told me to watch out for him because he's a dangerous man.
You knew something when you said that, right?
Right. Jeong Eun,
you asked me loads of questions when you came to our restaurant.
Why did you do that?
I...
Tell us everything now!
Why are you blaming me? It's not my fault!
Whose fault is it then?
It's all your fault!
Goodness. Honey!
Are you okay, Honey?
I will pour it for you.
- Never mind. - Come on.
What is it?
Are you really sure about this?
Of course, I'm sure about it. Why would I do it otherwise?
You're silly.
You know what that money means, don't you?
Don't spoil the fun.
Of course I know.
I don't particularly like my mother-in-law,
but still, I don't want anything to happen to their money.
They lived for 70 years,
and that house is all they've got.
If you use that house as a collateral,
then you really are a bad son to them.
I know. I know that.
Am I doing this for myself?
I am doing this so that I can provide better for them...
and to raise our children better.
But still, honey, you have to know this.
It's a sin for a child who's older than 40 years old...
to be depending on his parents like this.
You should really be ashamed of yourself.
That's why I am trying to make money and...
get out of their house.
I am really not sure if it's a right decision.
Watch me.
Later you will say that it was the right thing to do.
It's already happened,
so I can only hope that it will be a success.
Honey.
By the way,
our children saw everything we did.
What will we do if Ji Hoon grows up and asks us to fund his business?
- What? - I won't know what to say.
Tell us, Jeong Eun.
Tell us everything you know.
Actually...
Tell us, girl!
Hyun Woo is the son of the driver who got into an accident...
while driving a van for Geumbit Academy 23 years ago.
What?
What did you just say?
Are you talking about the van I was in?
Mom, what's that about? I don't remember it.
Goodness.
I remember it.
I got this scar on my forehead...
because of that accident.
But what about that?
The driver killed himself...
because of Uncle.
What?
That's absurd.
What do you mean?
How does his suicide have to do with Dad?
No way.
Mal Ja once said...
that the driver's son came back to take his revenge.
She's right, Aunt.
Is that Mr. Lee?
Goodness.
Did you say revenge?
Mom! Grandmother. Mom!
Mom!
Wake up, Mom! Mom!
What on earth is happening?
What on earth is going on?
Wake up, Mom. Mom.
- Bring water. - Bring water.
Hyun Woo.
Do you want some drink?
Why did you do that?
Do what?
Jeong Hwa, whom you call your sister...
tried to slap me in the face.
Are you asking why I didn't do anything to her?
Or...
are you asking why I didn't do anything to...
Seong Sik, whom you call your brother,
when he tried to have a go at me?
Those people...
don't know anything.
Since what happened yesterday,
did you worry about me at all?
I didn't get a wink of sleep.
You ran into my house...
and ask me why I did that to them...
instead of asking about the pain I've suffered from.
I knew...
things would turn out as Hyung Seop wanted.
I know his sins cannot be forgiven by any means.
But it's not their fault.
They just sat back...
and received everything from their parents.
As they're driven into a corner,
they tried to rip off a wealthy guy...
living across the street only to ruin themselves.
That's what they have done.
- Hyun Woo. - How could you yell...
and even swear at me as soon as you get here?
Isn't this ridiculous?
Am I to blame?
No,
this is just the way the world is.
They should blame their parents who spoiled them.
That's why they still live with their fully-grown children...
justifying themselves that that's what parents do.
I could become an independent person...
because I lost my father when I was little.
Don't make such sarcastic remarks.
Then you're no different from my dad.
Please stop, Hyun Woo.
This is enough.
- Sang Woo. - Let me...
take care of the rest.
I'll make sure...
no one gets hurt because of this.
Then I'll go to you.
No.
I'm sure you can't do that.
I've been watching you for quite a long time.
You can never...
put an end to all this on your own.
You're wrong. I can.
Are you sure?
Yes, I can.
Fine.
If you say so,
I need you to move out right away.
I'll stop everything as you said.
So disconnect all your ties with that family.
You know we have an appointment tomorrow, right?
The officials from the Golden Street headquarters are in Korea.
I want...
to show them my brother.
Come with me.
Make sure to dress up.
I think...
you're more good looking than me.
That makes me the happiest.
What are you doing?
Dong Hui?
You're back, Grandmother.
Why are you so absent-minded? How could you not notice me?
I was thinking about something.
What were you thinking about?
Did you have dinner?
Not yet. What about you?
Let me make dinner for you.
It's all right. I'm not hungry now.
Why didn't you have dinner?
You must not skip meals like that. You're still young.
I've had some snacks.
Aren't you cold?
I'm fine.
It doesn't really matter for old people like me.
Please don't say that.
What did you do today?
I did nothing special.
You stayed in all day long?
What else could I do?
You told me not to go outside.
Wasn't it hard to just stay in?
I'm all right.
I didn't go many places when I lived in Seoul either.
I just went to work and came home every day.
Okay. I'm relieved then.
I'm glad to hear that.
By the way,
I have something to ask you.
What is it?
Did you have to move this far?
I just wondered...
if there was some reason why we had to move to this remote town.
There's no reason.
I just wanted...
to lead a quiet life with you.
But...
there's something I am curious about.
Did you have any trouble with President Bang?
What... What on earth are you talking about?
What do you mean by trouble?
Why would I have any trouble with him?
Forget it.
I thought President Bang cared a lot about you,
but you didn't even call him before we moved here.
So I wondered if something happened.
I was just curious. That's it.
Gosh.
I also love living with you alone.
I really mean it.
Grandmother.
Yes?
Why are you still up?
Are you ill?
I'm okay.
Grandmother.
I just can't fall asleep easily.
Old people all have trouble falling asleep. You'll know later.
Were you crying?
Yes, a little.
Why?
Because I couldn't fall asleep.
I just couldn't help thinking about various things.
Grandmother...
I feel bad for you.
You're suffering a lot...
because I took you here with me.
That's why I cried.
Don't worry.
I told you I like it here.
It's quiet, so I can write the scripts better.
It's also comfortable to live with you alone.
You're not meant to suffer in this remote place.
Sorry?
You should have been...
raised in a wealthy family and received a lot of love.
You should have lived in a happy family.
You're going through a lot...
because of me.
Grandmother.
I am sorry.
I am really sorry.
I will pay a heavy price...
later.
Come here.
My Dong Hui.
My poor girl.
I'm sorry.
I am sorry.
Grandmother.
Why are you here so early today?
Chang Soo isn't here yet.
You know I left 10 minutes earlier last time.
So I came early today.
This is for you.
Are you here to play around?
Of course.
This is where my romance is played.
My goodness. That's lame.
I'll stay in my room. Leave when the lesson is over.
And I'll throw these flowers away when you leave.
I think it's too rude...
to throw them away in front of you.
Start the music.
Beautiful Dreamer,
Wake unto me
Starlight and dewdrops are
Waiting for thee
Sounds of the rude world
Past the sun
I feel empty inside
You are a cute pal in my dream
Listen to me
Listen to my beautiful song
Yes, Mom?
Nothing's going on at your house, right?
Nothing's going on.
What, Mom?
My ears are working fine. Why are you yelling at me?
What is this? Is someone singing?
I mean... Mom.
I turned up the volume today.
Goodness. That jerk.
By the way, what's up?
You know what?
I found out Mr. Lee across the street bullied our grandchildren.
What?
Mom. What do you mean?
Please wake up
I won't let her off easy this time.
Hey. Jeong Eun.
What?
What is this mess?
What mess?
The man you used to date.
Lee Hyun Woo across the street.
Is it true that he came back...
here to take revenge on your uncle?
It's not true. Mom.
If it's not, why did your grandmother call me to say this?
That's not what happened.
He had his reasons.
How can such a vicious guy have reasons?
Is that why he approached you on purpose?
No, Mom. He didn't do anything wrong to me.
Don't you see that he used you?
This is why he played you and then left you.
Because of him, you cried day and night and suffered.
That is not how it happened, Mom.
You are pathetic.
Today will be the last day for both of us.
What did I tell you?
Didn't I tell you to be careful of men?
You learned what I told you not to learn...
and didn't learn what you should've learned.
I am going to cut off all of your hair today.
- Hey. Ae Ri. - Come here.
- Come here. - This is beneath you.
Stop hurting my daughter.
What? Your daughter? Did you say "my daughter"?
You resurfaced after 30 years.
How dare you pretend to be her father? Stay out of it.
- Mom. - Today,
- Dad, are you okay? - I'm going to...
I am not okay.
What is this? You got zero?
How can you score zero?
Chang Soo. I am scared.
Ah In. Don't worry. I'm here.
Don't you think I know you did this on purpose?
There is not a day that goes by peacefully.
By the way, Mom is feeling under the weather. What should I do?
What's wrong with you? You had your fun.
It's time for you to pull yourself together and study.
Are you still rebelling?
So you should stop already!
I can study...
without you nagging me.
How can your rank drop like this...
if you can study by yourself?
The result speaks for itself!
My mom said it would be enough for her...
as long as I am ranked within the 10th place.
Why are you doing this to me, Aunt?
If you study just a bit,
you can be top of your class.
Why are you satisfied with just a 10th place?
Don't you realize anything from watching what happened to us?
Even if you pass the bar exam, become a reporter,
or graduate from the most prestigious university,
it's nothing unless you are the best.
Can't you realize it after seeing what happened to our family?
Aunt. That's all you see.
All of my parents studied hard.
Have you ever wondered...
if they are happy now?
Goodness. Listen to yourself.
Who said we are not happy?
We are happy. We are very happy.
If you want to be happy like us, you can start by studying.
If a smart boy like you doesn't study,
who would study?
Ji Hoon. Let's not give up. Please?
Chang Soo. Take your mother away.
Yes.
Ji Hoon. Please.
Goodness. What are you doing?
Didn't you go to your lesson?
Escort her upstairs.
Let's go, Mom. You're not feeling good. Why don't you rest?
Hold on.
Let me off. Put me down. Chang Soo.
Ji Hoon. You can be happy.
Ji Hoon.
I feel like she will suffocate me to death.
I can't breathe.
Ji Hoon.
It's really hard for me.
I can't live in this house.
Ji Hoon.
Your former mother...
raised you for a long time.
She thinks you are still her son.
She hasn't regained her senses yet.
So Ji Hoon,
while you live here,
don't argue with her.
Just let her have her ways sometimes. Okay?
Ji Hoon. Wait a bit more.
Mom and Dad are trying right now.
We are going to move out soon.
If she keeps at it,
there's no point for me to live in the basement giving up...
my room and comfortable life.
What?
I didn't come down because I wanted.
I came down here...
because living upstairs was a torture.
She even followed me here.
She's trying to kill me.
What do you mean?
What do you mean there's no point?
You...
came down because of your biological mother and father.
Whatever.
I didn't sleep a wink last night.
Don't you think he's sly no matter how you look at this?
That's my point. I am dumbfounded. This is so shocking.
I still don't feel at ease.
I knew it.
He made a small scratch on my car,
but he lent me an expensive car.
He let me rent an office at a low rate.
How could I have thought that he did those out of kindness?
I still have... Mom. Look.
I still have goosebumps.
How can he do this with such a gentle face?
Exactly.
I still remember the day he moved into the neighborhood.
The thought of it makes me shiver.
He treated us so well.
We treated him just as well as he did.
But how could he have...
such a vicious ulterior motive...
and befriend us?
The thought of it gives me goosebumps.
Crazy jerk.
He's a psychopath. He's out of his mind.
Jeong Hwa.
It's true.
To be honest, how can his father's suicide be your fault?
Why did he commit suicide leaving his children behind?
He should have raised them after paying for what he did.
If I were him, I wouldn't be able to get rid of my daughter's face...
until the moment I died.
Stop it.
This is all my fault.
Why is it your fault?
Did you kill that bus driver?
Did you help him hang himself?
Or did you hold him up to hang himself?
Honey.
I'm pointing out the facts. At that time, a lot of children were hurt.
Jeong Hwa almost died from the accident.
How could you have stayed on the sideline when she was about to die?
Besides, he drove under the influence.
You just called him an alcoholic because he was one.
You filed a report to the police. You didn't do anything wrong.
Is that why he committed suicide?
Goodness. It is a sad story indeed.
Grandmother. It has nothing to do with us.
Drinking and driving is a habit for people like him.
Even if he didn't get caught that time,
he would have definitely driven after drinking.
Then other children might have been hurt too.
Enough is enough.
You, stay out of it.
Is this why...
Mr. Lee grabbed you by the collar?
Jeong Eun should have kept her mouth shut.
I can't believe her too.
If she knew about this, she should've told us sooner.
How can she keep this a secret from us?
What if Mr. Lee did manage to ruin our family?
What would she have done then?
Gosh. She's ridiculous.
She'd better not show her face here.
Let's ban her from coming into our house.
Can all of you stay quiet?
I will take care of it.
How will you take care of this?
Honey. Why are you acting like this?
On whose side are you?
Goodness. What does he plan to do?
Oh, dear.
How does Seong Joon fit into this?
What about him?
I mean...
it seemed like he's visiting Mr. Lee quite often recently.
I was wondering if Seong Joon was affected by this in any way.
- What? - Even Seong Joon?
(Inbox)
Director.
Are you waiting for my emails?
I'm sorry I didn't send you an email.
I have a problem now.
I think it is about my grandmother,
but I know nothing about it.
And I can't ask her anything.
You said you were coming this weekend. I will wait for you.
I will tell you everything then.
I have three days left until the weekend.
I miss you.
Are you Oh Dong Hui?
Who are you?
What?
- We got it. - Let's go.
Why are you doing this to me? What are you doing?
Let go of me.
- You are here. - Yes, sir.
You look good today.
Today is an important day for you.
Above all things,
I don't want to cause any harm to you and your brother.
So I dressed up.
That's very thoughtful of you.
Where's Sang Woo?
I will meet him in front of my house at seven o'clock.
That's good to know.
I hope it will be...
a meaningful day for you two.
I hope so too.
People must be curious...
about David Lee's brother.
You bet.
You won't be afraid of anything...
even in New York...
as long as you have Sang Woo with you.
That's why you need a brother.
I guess that's why my father left him to me.
So that I won't be lonely...
and live alone in this rough world.
Congratulations on the party.
Thank you.
How did you know that?
When did you find it out?
I found out even before Seong Joon.
I heard it when I went to see Mal Ja.
Is that why you told me to go see Mal Ja?
I see.
You must've been through a lot of heartaches.
I'm sorry.
Seong Joon said he'd take care of it.
Please give him a chance.
I'm so sorry for him. He must be miserable.
Uncle.
Does your family have hard feelings toward Hyun Woo?
It's all my fault.
Uncle.
I know it wouldn't make any difference even if I tell you this.
But I have to tell you this.
I didn't want to tell you this though.
I know you've lived...
with guilt all your life.
If I can't help you, I don't want to give you a hard time at least.
But now that your family found it out,
you should know the truth.
Stop beating around the bush and just tell me.
The van incident.
In fact,
Guem Ja was going to give some money and reach an agreement.
But you kept insisting...
he was a drunkard and tried to call the police.
She were afraid of getting caught,
so she brought...
a false charge against Hyun Woo's father with Mal Ja...
to save her face.
What are you saying?
Hyun Woo's father...
was not drunk.
He already quit drinking.
He didn't even touch a drop of alcohol that day.
Uncle. You got the wrong person.
What?
I don't know what's taking her so long.
And what's wrong with you?
I will talk to Jeong Eun once she comes out of the room.
Uncle, what's wrong? Wake up.
- What's going on? - I don't know.
Aunt! Grandmother!
Aunt! Grandmother! Please come here.
What's wrong?
Dad, what's wrong?
What's going on? Honey!
What's wrong with him?
Seong Joon! Grandmother!
We should take him to the hospital.
- What's wrong with him? - Dad.
- Dad, wake up. - Hurry.
- Gosh. - Hurry.
- What's wrong with him? - What should we do?
What should I do?
Sang Woo must be running a little late, sir.
He'll come soon.
Seong Joon, where's your car?
It's down the street.
That's too far.
Hyun Woo.
What are you doing now?
Did you forget our plan?
Hyun Woo, Dad is sick.
Hyun Woo, I'm sorry. I will talk to you later.
It's me.
How's Han Seong Hoon's...
theme park business going?
Honey.
What's wrong, Seong Hoon?
Seong Joon, we have a problem.
What's wrong?
Where should I go? Which way?
Seong Hoon. Seong Hoon! What's wrong?
Seong Joon.
What should I do? We are in trouble.
My business...
- was a fraud. - What?
I should go.
I should go catch them.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Please save my children.
Do you think they'll think of you as family knowing you're my brother?
I don't want...
our family to know that...
you are Mr. Lee's brother.
Dong Hui, are you in there?
- They've moved out. - What?
Let go of me! Why are you doing this to me?