(Episode 4)
What was that?
Did you just hit me?
You shouldn't have touched me.
What do you mean I touched you?
I was sleeping here and...
you kicked, hugged, and touched me.
What are you saying?
It's because you were sleeping here.
That doesn't justify the fact that you touched me.
I'm not your girlfriend, am I?
I didn't know you were a woman.
Besides, what kind of a woman sleeps in a construction site?
This is what I've been doing for the last three years all over the world.
And I've encountered men like you.
They pretended to be nice and helpful...
but all they wanted to do was just touching my body and all.
What? Touch your body?
- Hey. - Don't come near me.
Don't come near me. I might kill you.
I've caught perverts like you in...
London, Paris, Rome, Amsterdam, Hague...
Rio de Janeiro, and Ushuaia.
I've caught so many perverts like you.
Did you just say Ushuaia?
It's a city, located in the southernmost of Argentina.
If you go further, you'll see Antarctica, too.
It's the place where Yang Jo Wi said...
we can throw out our sadness in a movie called "Happy Together."
Don't come near me. Don't.
My gosh.
Seriously...
Anyway,
I don't know what you do for a living.
But get out of here right now.
I'm speechless.
You are getting on my nerves with the way you're talking to me.
What do you mean?
Hey.
What do you think I do for a living?
How on earth would I know?
Besides, if you can sleep at a place like this,
you should know what I meant.
Don't you think so?
Then how about you? What do you do for a living?
I'm in charge of this construction site.
Is that enough?
I see.
Hello.
Do you understand now?
If you did,
please get out.
What are you doing?
I mean...
If you are in charge...
could you just let me sleep here? It's too cold outside.
This is the warmest place.
Just for a night.
I'll sleep here just tonight.
I'll make sure to clean up afterwards.
Come on. Please let me stay here for tonight.
Please...
Are you kidding me?
Excuse me.
It's not like the floor is going to worn out. You can let me stay.
It's just that I have nowhere to stay tonight.
You're out of control.
I have to call the police.
Okay. I will leave.
I am leaving!
Let's be honest. You might be the construction manager here,
but this building is not yours.
People are often mistaken.
They think they own the building when they build it...
even if there is an actual owner.
You might be on your high horse for being the construction manager,
but who knows?
You can be as miserable as me when the construction is over.
So what's wrong with helping each other at times of hardship?
I'm counting three.
One.
As you wish. Two.
- Three! - No!
Good luck with the rest of your life, you merciless man.
Nothing will work out in your life if you treat people like this.
You will get ill for no reason. Every friend will betray you.
Also, every woman you date will run away from you.
You will wander around these construction sites...
for the rest of your life and in the end, you'll die alone...
at a place like this. Then you will lie down...
and regret about today so badly.
Hey! Hey!
Stop there.
Hey! Hey! Stop there!
Goodness.
There's soup.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
No, I am up.
Hurry and get ready.
Yes. What's up at this early hour?
Is that right?
No. I can go now.
Yes. Where should I go?
Okay.
I will get ready right away and call you when I am there.
Yes. Okay.
Kids, get ready fast.
By the way, where did your mom go?
Where is the soy sauce?
Mother, where is the soy sauce?
Father.
What are you doing here at this early hour?
I came up to make you breakfast.
You don't have to bother yourself with that.
You can't do this. It's going to make things difficult for everyone.
Where's your mother?
- She is not here. - Did she go somewhere?
Anyway, it's good that you're here. Please take a seat.
Where is your grandmother now?
Seong Hoon said...
she's staying at a sauna. Is that true?
Yes.
My goodness. What do we do?
Father, you don't need to worry.
- I'll handle it today. - How will you do that?
You wouldn't have to move in here if you could handle that.
Seong Hoon shouldn't have quit his job at the newspaper company.
Why did he have to start a business...
and make your grandmother lose her house and her shop?
I am too ashamed to see your grandmother.
Is that what he told you?
He said he was going to start a business with your brother.
Yes, but Father,
my little brother must feel guiltier.
What kind of a business were they trying to do?
They said they were going to raise penguins and...
sell them to Africa.
What an idiot.
How can he sell penguins to Africa?
By the way, Father,
my little brother took the lead.
Seong Hoon just put his stamp on it.
- Mother shouldn't find this out. - I know.
No matter what he did, they decided to do it together.
That's why your grandmother lost everything, like her house and shop.
Yes. If you think like that, that's a way to put it.
There's only one solution.
Until you two get back on your feet...
and manage to afford her, she'll have to stay here with us.
Pardon me?
That's impossible, Father.
Where would she stay here?
It's a little shabby, but how about the rooftop room?
The rooftop room?
Eat up. Why are you picking at the food?
You have to eat good breakfast to be sharp at school.
I am eating.
Which private lessons do you have after school?
I have all three major lessons today.
Is that right?
Then I will pick you up tonight.
Meet me where I always wait for you, okay?
Okay.
Honey, try to eat everything.
You have to maintain your health for today's schedule.
- You frustrate me. - Aunt.
What is it?
Can we eat, too?
Where is your mother?
We don't know where she is.
We have to go to school,
and we need breakfast. That's why we came here.
Hey, eat slowly.
Okay. This is my normal speed.
Kids.
Mom!
Let's tie your hair and go to preschool.
Hye Joo, where did you go...
without preparing breakfast for your children?
- Are you all packed? - Yes.
Mom has to go to work.
- So Dad will drop you, okay? - Okay.
I am leaving.
What? You have to drop Ah In.
Where are you going? It's her first day.
Mr. Kim wants to see me. I'm leaving.
Honey, I have to go to work, too!
The soup is nice.
I can't believe this.
Why would they bother us at this early hour?
I can't believe it.
We're late. Hurry up.
Goodness!
- What do you want now? - Aunt.
Can you give me a ride, too?
We go to the same school, and we're in the same class, too.
- Chang Soo. - Yes?
- Please turn that game off. - I'm almost done.
Stop playing when I tell you to.
- Ji Hoon is studying. - Okay.
I told you to stop.
It's distracting me from my driving as well.
Okay, I'll turn it off soon.
Hey.
What's up?
You.
Didn't I tell you to stop or not?
I'm almost done. I'll turn it off soon.
What a brat. Get out of the car.
Get out.
I told you to stop playing, right?
You should have stopped when I told you to.
Don't you see Ji Hoon's studying next to you?
How could your mother buy you a smartphone?
And how could she let you play games like this?
Aunt.
I won't play it again. Can I have it back?
No.
I'm going to keep your phone for today.
Please, Aunt.
Please what? Just get into the car. Get in.
Aunt.
I beg you, Aunt.
Please don't do this, Aunt.
You better sit back and be quiet.
Please, Aunt.
My gosh.
Hee Sook, bring me my suit. I'm filming a show today.
My goodness. Gosh.
Hello.
Yes.
I'm done. Let's go, Ah In.
What are you doing in my house?
This isn't polite! What are you doing in my house at this hour?
What was that?
I mean...
It feels like it's my house, it seems like it's my house, but not
Is it something like this?
They must have seen me naked.
Father, Seong Hoon went somewhere.
Okay, I understand.
Consider what I said previously.
Okay.
Ah In.
Shall we play together?
- Have a good day. - Thank you.
What brings my eldest granddaughter-in-law here?
Did you sleep well last night?
Of course, I did. How about you?
I did, too.
Is Jeong Ae still angry?
She wasn't in her room.
Is that so?
Where did she go?
I should get to work now.
Okay. Have a good day at work. By the way,
Don't worry about Jeong Ae. Forget about her, okay?
Everyone's leaving in the morning just like the tide goes out.
That means it'll be empty during the afternoon.
And it's crowded at night. Jeong Ae should let it go.
Hold on.
Did she leave because she's angry?
The card is functioning.
Excuse me. I'm here to see Han Seong Joon.
Do you mean the director of Contents Marketing Department?
That's right.
Let's move the chair to that side. It's in the way.
Okay.
Please arrange the plants, too.
Producer Kim, is that the best you can do?
Should I put this flower on the desk?
Let's place it here for now.
Hello?
Someone is here to see Han Seong Joon.
Who is it?
A woman came to visit him.
Are you here to meet Director Han?
Yes, that's right.
I came to return his bag.
Would you like something to drink?
I brought you here because I need to go for a meeting soon.
Are you okay with it?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm a colleague and a friend of Director Han.
May I ask your name if you don't mind?
It's Oh Dong Hui.
I see. Ms. Oh Dong Hui.
How did you have his bag?
I mean...
The truth is...
we met coincidentally in Taiwan.
I dropped my passport and...
Director Han picked it up.
Then he lost his bag.
So I lost my passport again...
and he helped me register for my new passport.
I see.
I guess someone found the bag in Taiwan.
The tour agency contacted me.
So I came here to return it.
A lot of things happened in Taiwan.
Yes, a lot of things did happen.
Anyway, thank you for bringing it back personally.
I'll pass it on to him.
Director.
Please, take this.
This is to show our gratitude.
It's not necessary.
Please, accept it. You came all the way here to deliver the bag.
Okay.
Thank you.
Have your coffee.
Mrs. Moon.
The class will open next week. Why are you here so early?
Well.
I've got...
a situation.
Do you want to refund?
Yes.
Why do you want to get a refund? You really wanted to try it.
You told me it was one of your wishes.
One of my wishes?
I was just saying it.
It's too far to take the bus from home.
And I think the heels are too high.
It won't be...
good for my knees.
Moon Jeong Ae.
Why aren't you coming in?
Where are you going?
What will you do with the coat? Will you buy it or not?
You said you'll buy it. Why aren't you buying it?
Mrs. Moon.
Are you sure you want to cancel?
Yes, please.
Why? You were happy when it was rented out.
I was, but I have some personal problem.
Please tell them to understand us...
and I'm sorry.
Grandpa, are you ready?
- I am. - Then, start.
My back hurts.
Wait a second. You have dust all over your back.
- Do you want one more ride? - Yes.
Let's go home.
Now, I'll show you flowers.
If you see flowers, the time will fly. Hello, Mom.
- Are you babysitting today? - Yes.
- Grandma. - My dear cute girl.
Here's my little cute pumpkin.
Don't bother my son, okay?
Grandpa!
My kids are working hard to make a living, so I should help them.
Mom, I have something to discuss with you.
Yes?
What? Elizabeth is?
- Elizabeth? - No, it's nothing.
So Elizabeth is...
So is Hye Joo's grandmother staying in the sauna?
That's what I heard.
Seong Hoon was a good kid when he was young,
but why is he making such big troubles in series in his 40s?
That's what I'm saying.
I feel so bad for Hye Joo's grandmother.
By the way, I don't know if this place fits for living.
- Goodness! - This is driving me crazy.
Why is everyone interrupting my sleep?
Who is it?
You are...
Grandma! Uncle!
I missed you so much!
- Grandma, how have you been? - Why are you so frantic?
Please calm down.
Jeong Eun, what happened? When did you come back?
I arrived early this morning.
Grandma, Uncle, let me bow down before you.
Stop it and just follow me.
- Grandma. - Jeong Eun, did you have breakfast?
Mother, why don't you let her eat first?
Gosh, you eat like a pig.
Eat slowly. Here's water.
You should have some rice instead of ramyeon.
I was dying to eat ramyeon.
Look at you. Look at your disheveled hair.
Where on earth have you been?
- I've been to about 150 countries. - What did you say?
You bummed around 150 countries?
So are you all well?
I'm more than fine.
No matter where I was and what I ate,
I was always very healthy.
I'm sure you're so proud of yourself.
How can a grown up woman...
sleep anywhere and eat anything?
I can't believe you traveled so many countries.
What a naughty girl. What should I do with you?
Did you come back to see me pass out?
Grandma!
Goodness, how hopeless girl you are.
Hold on, I got something for you, Ah In.
Here. This is for you.
Thank you.
You were a little baby when I left, but look at you. You've grown up.
Does your mom know that you're back?
I don't know.
Did you call her?
Why do you move your fingers like worms?
You don't deserve to play Rachmaninoff's pieces.
Strike the notes harder and be accurate. Play it again.
If you play like this at the next lesson,
I'll make you stand in the hallway all day long, okay?
- Okay. - Now leave.
- Yes, Mom. - What are you doing?
I just finished a lesson. Did something happen?
Yes, it's something quite big.
What is it?
When your brother's sons moved in with their family,
you mocked them and rubbed it in, right?
Mom, I neither mocked them nor rubbed it in.
I called you to inform you that you're in the same situation.
What do you mean by that?
- What are you... - Jeong Eun is back.
Sorry?
Where is that wench?
What is that wench doing right now?
She's sleeping. She had three bowls of ramyeon...
and is sleeping on my couch.
I think she didn't take a shower for three years.
I opened all the windows because she stinks a lot.
My goodness, what should I do with her? This is nonsense.
She's not my daughter. Don't call me again, Mom.
Your mom says you're no longer her daughter. How pathetic.
(Yoon Surgery Clinic)
Look who's here.
You're here, my dear.
Hello.
My goodness.
What brings you here?
(Yoon Mal Ja)
- Are you a doctor? - What did you think I am, then?
You can scream if it hurts.
By the way, who did this to you?
What kind of woman was it?
It must have been a woman. I can easily tell that.
She must have been furious after she failed to win your heart,
so she hurt you with her sharp nails.
Tell me if I'm wrong.
I don't understand why you didn't love her.
It wasn't a woman.
You don't need to lie to me. I'm quite cool.
Didn't Jeong Ae tell you about me?
Well.
I got this scar while I was helping my neighbor moving furniture.
Right. She told me someone moved in.
So you helped them, right?
- Yes. - I see.
- So who moved in? - I think they're her sons.
- Her sons? - Yes.
- I see. - Is it done?
Stay still. Or I can't sew up your wound.
I said stay still.
Goodness.
- Goodbye, my dear. - Goodbye.
So it disappeared before 3am, right?
Where have you been?
- I was at the convenience store. - What happened?
You're back, Sir.
All the materials...
- disappeared from the storage. - Sorry?
- Where are the materials? - They're all gone.
We're sorry. We must have been more careful.
We reported to the police.
They'll come to check the security cameras.
Sir,
I found this on the floor.
I was sleeping here and...
you kicked, hugged, and touched me.
Get out now.
It's nice to see you again.
You visit us about this time every year.
- I can visit more often now. - I see.
- Please come in. - Okay.
(Lee Jae Cheol)
Did you sleep well?
Of course I did.
You didn't have to come.
I told you I was doing fine.
I was working outside and I just came by.
How are your in-laws?
They're happy to see Ah In and Chang Soo, right?
Yes.
Anyway,
they were living by themselves.
I hope you're not making things too uncomfortable for them.
Grandma.
You wouldn't...
want to come and live with us, would you?
What are you talking about?
Live with you?
In the morning, my father-in-law said...
you can live in the rooftop room in his building...
if you have nowhere else to go.
I can't believe what you're saying.
And why did you tell him about this?
I didn't. Seong Hoon did.
Don't be ridiculous. I can't live in his house.
I'd rather die on the street. That will never happen.
Stop saying things like that or I'll never see you again.
If that's what you want,
we'll just move out again.
Let's just stay in a motel like we used to.
I'd feel better that way.
It wasn't easy for you to move in. You can't move out again.
I told you to stay there until Seong Hoon gets back on his feet.
- What about you? - I said don't worry about me.
How can I not?
What if you get sick staying at places like this?
What about Dong Hui?
She's all grown up. She can't live like this forever.
If you could just come and live with us...
That's enough.
You should go.
Don't you ever come here again. Do you hear me?
No, it's fine.
I already have some experience. They probably didn't like that.
Anyway, thank you for everything.
Sure. I'll see you later.
Pour me a drink.
Mom.
Why are you so surprised to see me?
Pour me a drink, too.
Come on.
Mom. Don't drink too fast. You'll get drunk.
It's fine. If worse comes to worst, I'll just die.
We'll just stay with you for two months, so...
It doesn't matter if it's 2 months or 3.
You should live better so we don't worry about you.
It's not about how long you'll stay with us.
I'm sorry.
Don't be...
so upset that I'm treating you this way.
It's hard for me, too.
I know.
You'll see how hard it is...
when you get older.
- Let me. - It's fine.
Why did I have so many children?
I don't even remember how I raised...
all four of you.
I supported all of you when you were in high school.
Do you realize that?
If I add up all of your school years,
it's 64 years in total.
Besides, Seong Sik took his bar exam,
and you took your employment exam.
I packed your lunch millions of time.
I know.
If you do, you should live a happy life.
We raised you, educated you, and got you married.
What should I do if you just move in like this?
Do you know how it will change my life?
Do you?
I want to rest.
It's my life.
Let me do the things I want to do.
When I move out, I'll make Seong Sik move out, too.
Then you can rent the house and do the things you want to do.
All right. Since you brought it up, let's talk about that.
Honestly,
you only gave me some money when you got your first salary.
After you got married, you never gave me any money.
Up until now,
I've never...
had any money for myself.
I used all of your father's salary to raise you.
I've never had any money for myself in my entire life.
As I got older, I realized that I need more money than before.
If I get sick, I should go to the hospital.
I also need to get my teeth done.
Besides,
I need money to take care of my grandchildren.
Even taking care of my grandchildren costs money.
When your grandmother gave us the house,
I thought I'd be able to be...
a better parent, and to finally enjoy my life.
You ungrateful brats!
Look who it is.
It's Jeong Ae and her eldest son.
Hello. How are you?
I'm always great.
- What brings you here? - Nothing.
I was just on my way home from work.
Are you showing off that you're living with your son now?
You're having a drink with your son.
You look so great.
I heard your eldest son, a journalist...
and your second son, a lawyer moved in to take care of you.
That's...
How did you know that...
my sons moved in?
Everyone living in Bangbae-dong knows that.
Still, you should be enjoying your lives by yourselves.
Why did you move in to take care of them?
It's tiring if your children are too good.
That's right. I moved to Bangbae-dong.
It's a 150m house.
Don't ask me about the price.
I didn't buy it, of course. I can't afford it at this age.
It's my parents' house.
Inheritance?
Well...
They haven't told us about it yet.
It will be my inheritance someday.
Anyway, we live close by now. Let's have a drink sometime.
Okay.
Have you heard about what happened to Jin Sook?
Goodness. Her children failed in their business,
and got fired from their work.
They all came back as a failure.
She's having such a hard time.
She feeds them and babysits her grandchildren.
Someone saw her the other day, and she looked like a 70-year-old woman.
She's nothing like you.
You are so lucky.
That spiteful woman.
She's just trying to rub it in when she knows everything.
How can you be friends with a person like her all your life?
She hasn't changed a bit.
What can I do?
I lived here my whole life.
You should buy me a house somewhere else then.
She's such a spiteful woman.
- Let's walk faster. - Okay.
Mom! Seong Hoon!
Are you on the way home? Wait for me!
Or do you want to get some beer before heading home?
He's advertising to the entire town that he's moved into my house.
I know.
- Son. - Yes.
- Run. - Okay.
Seong Hoon! Mom!
Let's go get some beer! Wait for me!
Mom! Can't you hear me?
Wait for me! What's wrong?
Mom! Wait!
- Give me your luggage. - Thank you.
Moong Chi.
It's raining.
Go in, Moong Chi.
- Please go to Bangbae-dong. - Okay.
You pervert! Let's sleep together.
You will sleep all night like this with me.
You pervert!
That brat!
We can't pass because of the construction vehicle.
Is that right?
Then...
- I will get off here. - Okay.
Here you go.
- Here is your luggage. - Thank you. Take care.
Moong Chi, run!
Shush. You can't bark right now.
We're here. This is our home.
Let's go in, Moong Chi.
- Seong Joon! - Dad!
My goodness.
I'm home, Mom. Have you been well?
- Seong Joon. - Why did you arrive so late?
The flight got delayed.
Great.
Your youngest son Seong Joon came back...
safely after working in Shanghai.
Yes. Good job. I am so proud of you, my son.
Good job, dear.
Thanks, Mom.
By the way, you don't look too well.
No, nothing's wrong with your mom.
You're going to catch cold. Go wash up and rest.
We should turn on the heater. Did you call the company?
It's already fixed.
Seong Joon, you can take shower now.
Okay, Dad.
You should rest.
My youngest son is finally back.
Oh my gosh!
You darn dog!
You're back as well.
Granny, where do we eat breakfast?
Granny, whose dog is this?
Seong Joon is home.
Seong Joon is back? Really?
That's Seong Joon Junior.
Seong Joon!
My goodness.
Seong Joon, eat a lot.
How long has it been?
I think it's been around two years.
Gosh!
I am so proud of you.
You did something great while working in Shanghai for two years,
and you gloriously returned to Korea last night. Am I right?
You should learn from your uncle too, okay?
- Okay. - Okay.
Eat a lot, Seong Joon.
Mother cooked so many dishes because you came back.
This is what makes me disappointed in Mom.
When we moved in, she yelled at us to get out of here.
Then she cooked all these dishes for Seong Joon.
Mom! This isn't fair!
- Honey. - By the way,
what is she doing with Seong Hoon?
Seong Joon!
Jeong Eun.
It's been such a long time! Let me see your face.
- How have you been? - Good. When did you come back?
Last night.
Hey. Keep it down.
It's too early for that noise.
Mom, Dad! Come and have breakfast!
Eat up.
You must be out of your mind!
- My goodness. - Jeong Ae.
The kids will hear you. Keep it down.
What did you say you were going to raise?
Well...
I thought raising penguins and selling them to Africa would be...
Mom, let me tell you.
Penguins are endangered because of the global warming.
- If we raise a lot of them... - I can't take this.
I'll kill you, and kill myself.
I'm not kidding this time.
Gosh, you idiot.
- Dear. - Jeong Ae.
You can scold him some other time.
What are you going to do about Hye Joo's grandmother?
He lost her house and store.
She's now staying at a sauna.
As his parents, we should do something about it.
Gosh, I don't care! I really have no idea.
Come here, you brat.
- You've never been helpful. - My gosh.
What's wrong with you?
Mom, please calm down.
- Hello? - Elizabeth?
Who is this?
It's me, Grace.
Excuse me?
It's me, Hwang Mi Ok. You called me Grace Kelly.
Yes. How have you been?
Why are you talking to me so politely?
Let me get straight to the point.
Move in while our doors are still open.
Why aren't you answering?
I know you're as graceful as the Queen Elizabeth,
and I know you try not to owe anyone anything.
But Seong Hoon is...
about to get beaten up to death...
by his parents because he blew your store.
I heard you were worried about your children, too.
So let's make up later and...
for today, please be gentle and move in.
I'll send Seong Hoon to pick you up.
You're not answering again.
Do you have a problem with this?
One more thing.
Do you like dogs?
Did she just hang up?
She hasn't changed at all.
Grandma. What's wrong? Who were you talking to?
It's nothing. Go to work. I'll see you later.
Let's...
stay at a motel today.
Okay.
Grandma. Don't come outside.
- You should go. Have a good day. - Okay.
Get inside, Grandma.
Okay. Go.
All right.
Ma'am. Keep quiet.
That punk.
That little...
Do you want me to pay you in advance?
Look. You've been working here for a few days only.
I'm sorry. I wouldn't ask you if it wasn't urgent.
I'll work hard like a full-time employee.
Sir. Please help me out once.
- Listen. - I'm a reliable person.
- If you help me this time... - That's enough.
Just find somewhere else to work.
I don't want to hire a part-timer like you.
Excuse me?
Congratulations!
- What is this? - Congratulations on your return.
You must have gone through so much for the past two years.
Welcome back.
Go, Han Seong Joon!
- Let's go! - Let's go!
Thank you so much. I hope you've been well.
I'll look forward to working with you again.
(Meeting Room)
I can't believe them.
They should appreciate your hard work first.
Why would they start nitpicking right away?
To them, getting result is more important.
My dad is in Europe. He'll be back next month.
Just give him a call today.
Is that so? All right.
Get us some tea.
What is it?
I was going to give it to you.
Before you came, someone brought this bag here.
What was her name?
Oh Dong Hui?
- What? - I heard you lost her passport...
and helped her issue a new one.
Yes. That's right.
Why are you so surprised?
Nothing.
I thought I'd never find this bag.
I'm overwhelmed.
Overwhelmed?
My dad bought me this when I entered college.
I see.
I was surprised because I didn't know that.
Let's have dinner together. We should celebrate your return.
No.
I'm having dinner with my family today.
I got home so late last night. I didn't have time to talk to them.
I see.
Grandmother.
If you give me two months,
I'll find a place for us to live. So please...
Please help me out this once.
It's a rooftop room, so you wouldn't have to face my family.
Besides, you and my grandmother are similar in age,
so you can be her friend.
Seong Hoon.
Dong Hui. Hello.
How have you been?
I've been good.
How is your stay here? Isn't it uncomfortable?
- It's fine. - No, it's not.
You're a grown woman. It must be hard and uncomfortable.
Let's go. Pack your things.
Go where?
To my place.
To your place?
I'll give you two months.
Thank you, Grandmother.
Dong Hui. I'll get my car. Come out with Grandmother, okay?
Hello, Hye Joo? Yes. I'll bring them now.
Okay.
Grandma.
I'm home. I'll go and see Moong Chi.
Let's see where your eyes are.
Gosh, here they are. You're so pretty.
You're so cute. Don't go.
- Sit. Be a good dog. - Who are you?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
We meet again. Anyway, it's good to see you.
- Let's go to the police station. - Don't come after me.
You ran away? You're so done if I catch you.
I would have never thought that we could be in-laws.
Same here. Why are you glad to meet?
You should have stopped their plan with penguins.
Does that sound normal?
I wanted to make loads of money.
I heard you are the new in-law who moved in yesterday.
You're cute.
Please keep this a secret to my grandmother.
Then what will you do for me?