Lee Hyun Woo who lives across the street...
is my real brother.
What?
I am...
the son of the driver who committed suicide.
I'm Lee Sang Woo.
I am sorry.
(Episode 41)
Now everything makes sense.
Goodness.
I don't know what to say.
Hyung Seop,
don't you have a mother?
Don't you have a wife? Why did you do that?
You could've discussed it with us.
If Seong Joon didn't tell us,
were you going to carry the burden alone for the rest of your life?
Yes.
Even now,
I think I should've carried the burden alone.
What did you say?
Jeong Ae.
How can you lie to me like this?
How can you make me raise the son of...
that driver?
And you tore my heart by...
lying that you had an affair.
If I told you the truth,
would you have raised Seong Joon?
I certainly wouldn't have. Why would I raise him?
- Did I kill the bus driver? - Even if that's the case,
this is no way to treat your wife with whom you lived all your life.
Anyway,
it's Jeong Ae who raised Seong Joon.
It took years for her to accept him as her son.
At the end, she raised him well.
Then you should have at least...
told her...
who she is raising...
and from where you brought him.
That's what marriage is.
I'm sorry.
I was worried if I told her, Seong Joon wouldn't grow up well.
Mother.
Did you hear what he just said?
A poor man ended his life after all.
He left his children behind.
I couldn't turn my eyes away from them.
You should have brought both of them and raised them.
If you did, this disaster wouldn't have happened now.
I wanted to do that too.
When I went to get him, he was already adopted and left Korea.
What?
Goodness.
This is unbelievable.
What I have committed is quite grave, Mom.
Back then,
I only cared about my children.
Anyway,
you must have gone through a very difficult time all these years.
Mother.
What about preposterous feelings I have?
I just found out that I have been raising...
the son of the bus driver who committed suicide for 23 years.
I can't ever understand you.
I won't forgive you.
Goodness.
How will we resolve this problem now?
Why did you do it?
If I don't,
Dad and you will get hurt.
What about you?
I can't keep this a secret forever.
Things are already happening.
What will we do from now on?
All we have left is getting kicked out. Is that it?
You. Han Seong Joon!
How can you just sit here?
Jeong Hwa.
Go to that jerk, Lee Hyun Woo...
and tell him to find my brother, Seong Hoon.
Tell him to get our house back this instant!
Jeong Hwa. Stop it.
Jeong Hwa. Stop it. Stop!
Tell him to pay the monetary penalty Seong Sik paid.
How can you just sit here and do nothing?
How dare you stay in this house?
Jeong Hwa. You can't treat him like this.
This isn't Seong Joon's fault.
Why isn't it his fault?
He is Lee Hyun Woo's brother!
Jeong Hwa.
Hey, that's enough.
- Hey. - If you are his brother,
shouldn't you take full responsibility for this disaster?
Do you know...
for how long we fed, clothed, and raised you?
Is this how you repay our kindness?
Hey, Jeong Hwa. Come on.
- You. Come out now. Come out! - You...
- Let go of me. - Come out!
Go to your brother! You, jerk.
Look at him. He's doing nothing.
- Let me go. I'm not done with him. - Goodness.
Stop it! Be quiet!
How can a girl be so strong?
You are as loud as a train too!
Why did you bring her here?
What was I supposed to do?
If I leave her on the second floor,
she might end up beating up Seong Joon.
Do you think that's the only thing I'll do?
I won't let that sibling off easy.
Jeong Hwa! Can't you be quiet?
The midterm week will start the day after tomorrow for our children.
Are you going to keep this up?
Please keep it down!
This is the first...
midterm in their third year of middle school.
If you keep this up and they don't do well on their exams,
are you going to be held responsible?
Hey, Hee Sook.
How can you talk about their education when our house is ruined?
If I don't talk about their education,
what would I talk about?
Should I badmouth Father who has suffered all these years...
by bringing up what happened 23 years ago?
Or should I come up with a plan about Seong Joon...
who lost his family and grew up uncomfortably.
Or should I...
talk about our wretched feelings...
at Hye Joo...
whose husband, Seong Hoon...
ruined our family?
Should I do that instead?
Gosh. Sit down.
Hye Joo.
You haven't heard from Seong Hoon yet?
Not yet.
Should I go out and look for him?
What if he committed suicide somewhere?
Hye Joo.
How many times have I told you to take care of your husband?
Seong Hoon is a softie.
Don't you know that he lives well when he's being taken care of...
after spending all these years with him?
How bad were you taking care of him to cause this mess?
Exactly.
I think I should report to the police.
I agree.
We should report to the police. They will form a search party for him.
I mean...
if he moved into the house to take care of Father,
he should have done that. How could he...
lose Father's house overnight?
What does this house mean to him?
This house is the only inheritance...
Mother and Father will pass on to us. Am I wrong?
How could he single-handedly lose...
this house without talking to us first?
Let's send out a search party for him and catch him.
Hee Sook.
Was that how you were feeling, Hee Sook?
- Yes, it was. - What?
Seriously. Stop it.
We have to find Seong Hoon by all means.
Since he is weak-minded,
I don't know what will happen to him...
once he starts thinking of doing something stupid.
Why do these incompetent oldest sons hide...
after they ruin their businesses...
and the whole family?
Why do they hide?
They ought to go out and try to solve this mess.
Honey.
Don't be so cruel.
He's still my brother.
We are about to end up on the streets. How can you say that?
Hye Joo. Where are you going?
I'm going to go out.
- Hye Joo. Let me go with you. - All right.
Seriously!
Hye Joo. Hye Joo!
I can't believe them.
What?
This can't...
be happening.
Why?
Did you go for a run because you were feeling frustrated?
I mean you did completely destroy a happy family.
You must be if you are a human being.
You seem furious.
The problem at your family must have gotten quite serious then.
Is this what you wanted?
Do you know what condition Seong Joon is in?
Well, I suppose he's still pretending to be their family.
Hey, Hyun Woo.
Everything is over.
He covered up what you and my uncle did.
He covered for me who once foolishly loved you.
He took all the blame by himself. Did you know that?
Did you have to do this?
Does Seong Joon have to be hated and kicked out by his family?
Will that put an end to your revenge?
Who is the victim of this revenge?
Is my family the victim?
Don't you think you and Seong Joon are the victims?
What on earth happened?
Seong Joon...
kneeled down in front of my family...
and asked for forgiveness of what you did...
saying that it was all his fault.
After my family lost jobs and honor, they couldn't keep a cool head.
He let them give him a hard time.
Is that really what you wanted?
He's a pathetic jerk.
Hyun Woo.
You are such a bad person.
You only care about yourself.
You are a self-obsessed person who never cares about other people.
I told you the other day.
That I'm not a good person.
Did I ever tried to hide that I'm a bad person?
Okay. You are right.
I just forgot that.
I will never forget...
the lesson you taught me today.
I've tried to think...
that you are doing all this because you are hurt.
I wanted...
to help you heal your broken heart.
I've held out with that thought in mind.
I should probably thank you.
Thanks to you, I can finally let go of it and move on.
Take care, Hyun Woo.
I will leave...
all my feelings for you here.
Let's never see each other again.
What a jerk.
He doesn't even know how much I loved him.
This is the last time I'll ever come here!
The mortgage on the building of...
57-17, Bangbae-dong...
It is 1.5 million dollars.
What?
He borrowed as much money as he could.
The term of redemption is 30 years.
You should repay the principal and interest from the end of the month.
The interest rate will change every three months.
It's a large sum of money.
If the principal and interest are past due over two months,
the bank may foreclose on your house.
- What? - They may attach your property.
He just arrived at the office.
Why does he look so serious?
Maybe he can't reach Dong Hui.
If things go like this, our drama will be canceled.
I can't believe this.
Why is it so hard to air a drama?
What's wrong with Director Han by the way?
I know. Writer Choi and Dong Hui...
are so irresponsible.
We don't know it yet.
We still have some time left.
Whatever.
Gosh.
What? That's ridiculous.
Why would he close them?
This is Director Han from Contents Marketing Department.
I'd like to cash in retirement fund prematurely.
Is it possible?
All right.
Can I also apply for an employees loan?
I see.
I will visit as soon as the documents are ready.
Thank you.
Please let me out.
Let me out.
Grandmother.
Let me see my grandmother.
Hey.
Is anyone there?
Come on out.
You should eat.
Chairman Bang and Director Bang are out.
Gosh.
Yes. She's having breakfast.
It's a little late.
Okay. I'll be right there.
What is this?
This is a gift from Chairman Bang.
You can't use the internet with it though.
It's me.
What is Dong Hui doing now?
She just had breakfast and went back to her room.
She ate breakfast?
Yes. And she got...
a new laptop today.
All right.
Where on earth is Dong Hui?
I'm sorry, sir.
I told you to keep an eye on her.
It seems she just left last night.
Go find her.
Without Dong Hui,
I will never get the will from her.
Go find Dong Hui as soon as possible.
Right. What is Dong Hui doing?
She's at home.
And I gave her the laptop.
All right.
Did you call the sanatorium?
Yes. I told them we'll be there in two hours.
What about Gui Boon?
She hasn't called me yet.
Did you cancel the meeting?
It's pushed back to tomorrow.
All right. Let's go.
(Hearty Sanatorium)
What is this place?
Hearty Sanatorium?
(Hearty Sanatorium)
Do you know what this is?
It's the DNA test results...
of Hyun Jeong.
Why didn't I figure it out sooner?
Now that I think of it,
she looks just like her mother.
It's not just her face.
Even her character is the same as her mother's.
She's locked up in my house.
She keeps making a fuss screaming and yelling.
Do you really...
have to do all this?
Grandmother?
That's why...
you should've done my favor in the first place.
Then I wouldn't have wasted such a long time.
And you also wouldn't have had to spend...
a lonely life...
in this room like now.
You are the worst son the world has ever known.
It's really humiliating to hear you...
call me mother.
I feel exactly the same.
- What? - Am I not your son?
Why...
do you plan to give your fortune to the society...
instead of your son?
What has the society done for you?
None of those who inherited their parents' wealth...
led a decent life.
None at all.
But you were going to leave...
- your fortune to Gwang Ho. - Gwang Ho wasn't...
greedy like you.
He was competent,
clever,
and modest.
Your brother was...
a human.
Are you saying...
that I'm not a human?
You let your brother and his wife die...
and tried to take money away from your parents.
I won't give you anything, not even a penny.
Darn it.
Yes.
You haven't changed at all, Mom.
This is too harsh.
How can you give your money to someone else other than your son?
That's what parents must do, right?
You didn't bat an eye...
about this matter for the last 20 years.
You're so merciless.
Hyun Jeong.
Leave her alone.
She has nothing to do with this.
You already...
reported her death, didn't you?
You should...
give up on your plan to donate your money to the society...
and rewrite your will.
Or else,
Hyun Jung will...
suffer even more.
I'm leaving then.
- Keep an eye on her. - Yes, sir.
Let's go.
This is nonsense.
I don't believe this.
("Romance Learned through Books", Episode 7)
(Inbox)
Sang Woo.
We need to talk.
I have no idea what's on your mind.
Don't mind me. Just leave.
Why did you kneel down before them? You've done nothing wrong.
There's no point in hiding it.
They'll find it out in the end.
There's no need to make my dad and Jeong Eun suffer too.
Myself is enough.
So what did they say?
What did they tell you when they learned that you're my brother?
Didn't they tell you to beg for my mercy?
They're not such people.
Why do you have to do this?
Because you won't stop.
It's undeniable...
that they used to be my family.
At the same time, it's true that you're my brother.
So?
I'll straighten out the troubles you caused.
If you're done with what you came here for,
please go back to where you were.
Do you think they'd give you a chance to fix the problems?
It doesn't matter.
Even if they push me away or avoid me,
I'll do everything I can.
All you can do for them...
is give them a small amount of money.
Then do you think they'd appreciate it?
It's not out of goodwill.
I'm helping them because I'm their family.
Just like I begged them for forgiveness on behalf of you.
If you aren't going to help me take care of the problems,
just leave first.
I don't want...
you to get hurt anymore.
Fine. Do whatever you want to do!
And see what you can do for them.
You're such a fool.
What?
Never mind.
I'm so hungry.
You good-for-nothing panhandler.
I'm sorry.
- What do you think you're doing? - I'm sorry!
- Sir, I apologize! - Get lost!
Okay, sir.
Goodness.
Mark my words.
There are things going on around the family these days.
But you should never let them...
bother you.
Adults will deal with their own problems.
Teenagers will do their job.
And kids...
also have their own jobs to do.
Okay.
There's one more thing.
There's no need for you to worry about the person...
who has been away these days.
Aunt.
I miss my dad.
Ah In.
I told you to stop thinking about him.
Your dad must be doing fine.
Probably.
Then let's start studying.
You took a shower, had dinner and ate two slices of apple...
and a slice of orange after you came back from school.
So it's eight at night.
Ah In, study until 10 at night.
Okay.
Chang Soo needs to stay in shape...
as you have a lesson tomorrow.
So you'll study until midnight.
Okay.
Also,
the teen who has been slacking the whole time...
while doing magic...
will start afresh from now on.
Think of the midterm as an opportunity...
to start your new life...
and study until 3am.
Do you understand?
- Yes, I understand. - Yes, I understand.
Start.
"When I arrived, the payment..."
"Heaven is Cheon, a land is Ji."
"Black is Hyeon, yellow is Hwang."
- "Space is Woo, house is Joo." - "Father,"
- "Wide is Hong, rough is Hwang." - "I'll take care of you."
"Day is Il, a month is..."
Goodness.
Come. Come.
Let's go there.
No, it's not him.
Where did he go?
How many days has it been?
(Missing)
Why would you make something like this?
We never know, Hye Joo.
What if he lost his memory due to shock?
What will you do then?
I put so much effort into this.
You need to make it as eye-catching as it is...
to catch the attention of every passerby.
It's just that looking at the picture makes me cry.
Goodness. Wait, Hye Joo.
Wait, Hye Joo. That's a wrong place to lean.
Goodness. Goodness.
Hye Joo.
What's that? Follow me.
Excuse me. Hello.
By any chance,
have you seen a person like this?
I've never seen him.
Please look at him one more time.
Gosh, I said I've never seen him.
- You've never... - Gosh...
I said I've never seen him!
Run!
I can't believe it.
Goodness.
Where on earth did Seong Hoon go?
(Please wait!)
Honey!
Kids!
Dad!
Mom!
I am sorry.
(Are you struggling now? We will listen to your story.)
(Emergency hotline)
Hello?
What do I do?
Sir?
Hello?
What do I do?
Sir, have courage.
Talk to me now.
- I know how you feel. - I...
Hello? That's not it.
I accidentally pressed the button.
It's...
Goodness.
Sir, calm down.
Hold on for a second. I will help you.
Life is long.
Don't make a hasty decision. If you will wait there,
I will help you right away.
Slowly. Slowly.
Sir!
Kids, it's time for school.
Chang Soo.
Ah In. Wake up!
Ji Hoon, wake up. Wake up.
How can you fall asleep?
Today's the first day of the midterm.
You should've studied until the end.
Go take a shower to wake yourself up.
I will make lotus root juice for you.
Goodness! Is your nose bleeding again?
Wait. What do we do?
Ji Hoon.
Ji Hoon!
- Mom. - Let go.
Leave Ji Hoon alone.
What should I do with him?
(Missing)
Did you really wear that?
What else would I do?
We have to do anything to find Seong Hoon.
You are unbelievable. You are so embarrassing.
Hey, you should wear it and go outside too.
Then you become solemn and desperate.
It's just like looking for your separated family.
I think I should...
report to the police that he's missing.
I think...
he must've...
jumped into the Han River.
Hye Joo.
After living with him for so long, you still don't know Seong Hoon.
Seong Hoon would never be able to jump into the Han River.
Why? If he was such a determined person,
he wouldn't have made things get this bad.
Jeong Hwa.
Hey!
I don't know.
Tell Mom and Dad to come out.
We have to eat and gain energy...
to get back at Hyun Woo,
that jerk neighbor, together.
Get up now.
You have to eat.
You haven't eaten anything since yesterday.
I don't want to talk to you.
What are you doing?
Will lying down like this give you an answer?
I am not doing this to get an answer.
I'm doing this because I don't have anything to say.
It's not that I don't understand you.
But I thought about it all night.
Think about Seong Joon.
How shocked would he be?
Seong Joon must be the one having the toughest time.
Stuck in between...
his brother and our family, Seong Joon can't do anything.
A drop of tear...
dropped when he told us...
that Hyun Woo is his brother.
When I thought about it later, I felt so bad for him.
Right now,
we have to first think about what to do with Seong Joon.
I don't know what to do. I don't know.
Get up now.
What are you doing, Mother? Goodness.
- Goodness, Mother. - Get up.
Mother. Gosh...
You have to get up and eat...
to think about what to do.
Dad, I called you to eat. What are you doing?
Where's Mom?
She's coming.
Are you going to work?
Yes.
Okay. You should get going.
Okay.
Hey, Seong Joon.
Have a meal before you go.
What?
I just want him to have a meal before he goes.
How can you thinking about eating now?
All right. Here we are.
Mr. Han Seong Hoon.
You are home. You should get off.
- This isn't my house. - Please get off now.
We arrived. This is your home.
Goodness.
This is your house, right? Look.
Stop talking about eating right now. This isn't the right time for it.
Hey, he should still eat before he goes to work!
What did you say?
Can you two be quiet?
Even the elders of this house are being quiet.
How dare you kids raise your voice at this early hour?
Do you want me to scold you?
Who is it?
- Hi. - Gosh. Mom.
- Hello. Goodness. - Seong Hoon.
- Hello. - Seong Hoon!
- Seong Hoon. - Seong Hoon.
- Oh dear. - Goodness.
- Honey. - Excuse me.
Are you his family?
Yes, we are his family.
He's my son.
We stopped him from jumping off the bridge last night.
- What did you say? - What?
What?
Gosh. He stinks. He reeks.
So...
you borrowed 1.5 million dollars...
after putting up this house as a collateral?
Yes.
What is the monthly interest?
Seong Hoon. You must have been out of your mind!
1.5 million dollars isn't a small amount of money you can easily earn.
How could you?
Then what happens to us?
This house...
Do you know what this house means to us?
Do you know what this house...
- means to me? - Oh dear.
I'm sorry, Mom.
I mean...
we have to start paying...
the interest and the principal starting this month, right?
If the principal is 1.5 million dollars, the interest alone...
will be 7,000 or 8,000 dollars.
What are you going to do?
Even if we make money the best we can with the restaurant,
it won't be enough money for the interest.
How will we make a living then?
How are we going to educate our children?
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
You have lost your mind. You've gone mad!
I won't be able to live because of you!
Why are you so quiet? Say something.
How can you all be...
stupid and pathetic?
All of you are pathetic.
Mother.
Mother, I am sorry. This is all my fault.
Gosh. I can't survive this.
This is a complete tragedy!
I should go to a nursing home...
and live by myself.
If I live in the same building with them,
my life will end prematurely.
Goodness.
I mean...
1.5 million dollars are...
What do you want?
What are you going to do with my dad?
Your dad?
Remember? You met my dad the day before yesterday.
You told him to be where you two met the next day.
He's been there for two days, but he said you aren't coming out.
What?
Mom! Let me go with you.
Mom!
That's right. I told him to meet me there.
I've been so distracted.
Wait. I'll teach this jerk a lesson.
Follow me.
Our house is already in an uproar...
without your help.
So be quiet...
- and follow me inside. - Mother.
Mother? Hey, you.
You, jerk.
Today will be the last day for both of us.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Mother. - You're sorry?
You turned my daughter...
into a single mom for 30 years and you're sorry?
Hey, even if I tear you apart into pieces,
that won't be enough. You jerk!
Mom. Stop it. Don't do this.
Get off me.
While I was distracted,
all three of you were plotting against me.
Are you okay?
- You. - Mother.
You and I won't be able to see the light of this world from today.
Mom. Please stop. Mom!
I beg of you. Stop it, Mom.
You jerk!
Look at this.
Honey.
What is your plan?
What are you going to do?
We are about to lose this house.
The monthly interest is 10,000 dollars. That isn't a small sum.
How are you going to pay back all that money?
I think I ought to give Mr. Lee a visit.
Hey. Look.
That Mr. Lee...
is Seong Joon's biological brother.
Were you even aware of this?
What?
What do you mean?
He already took out the maximum amount of loans from the bank.
He took out private loans to make additional investments.
How could he take out...
mortgages and private loans to make investments?
Anyway, starting this month, he has to pay back...
the principal and the interest.
I believe the interest of the private loans...
will be quite a large sum of money.
Right now, Sang Woo...
has taken out a loan from his company...
and has gotten half of his severance pay.
He's also gathering all the money...
he has saved so far.
What?
It's Han Seong Hoon. How should I handle this?
Shouldn't you be going after the con artists instead of visiting me?
You don't look like you're in a hurry.
I guess you didn't lose a lot of money.
I heard everything.
What did you hear?
You came here because of my father's past mistake.
Because of that,
you ruined all of us.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Everything...
is our fault.
So please. Help us once.
I am...
sincerely sorry.
For what are you apologizing?
I'm apologizing for my father's past mistake,
what's happening now,
and what's going to happen.
I'm sorry about all of it.
It's all my fault, President Lee.
I didn't know you had a thing...
with my father.
I'm sorry about everything.
Please...
Please overlook it just this once...
and help us.
So...
are you saying you will admit your father's wrongdoing...
and regret it,
so you want your money back?
So you are selling your father for money.
All he cares about are his children...
and you are not like him.
Hyung Seop must be very disappointed to know that.
I'm begging you.
The house...
means a lot to...
my parents and grandmother.
I don't care what will happen to me.
But I just can't lose this house.
I was so foolish that I made this mess.
If you help me just once,
I will do...
anything you ask.
Why on earth did you borrow money from a loan shark?
President Lee.
Let go of me.
Please give a chance, President Lee.
Please. I'm begging you.
I want you to leave now. I don't want to see you anymore.
(Bonus, Severance pay, Loan, Installment savings, Extra pay)
(Inbox)
(To Dong Hui)
Dong Hui.
What's the matter?
I thought you'd call me once things are settled.
Why aren't you calling me?
I wonder if you are doing fine and everything is good.
I'm worried.
In fact,
I've been through a lot.
So...
I need you now.
Go have a meal.
Where were you yesterday afternoon?
I heard you didn't attend the directors' meeting.
Why didn't you attend the meeting?
Did you have something urgent?
Well...
I was busy.
Why?
Come sit down and eat.
I'm not happy with all this.
If you don't like to eat with me, I will come back later.
You don't need to. Have a seat.
So is everything going well with your writing?
Yes. Thanks to the laptop you gave me,
I'm devoting myself to it.
But I can't stay here like this.
Can you at least tell me how long I should be here?
I don't know.
It's about time your grandmother showed up.
She's coming a little later than I expected.
I'm done eating.
What?
What's wrong with you?
What makes you so upset?
Do you even care that I'm upset?
You just have your own way of doing everything.
Can't you see that...
everything I do is just for you?
Is that why you rub it in every time?
You are doing it for me?
You are doing things just to satisfy your selfish desires.
What did you say?
Do you think I'm a fool?
What do you mean?
Do you think I was born yesterday?
Do you think I don't know anything about your scheme?
What are you talking about?
How...
How could you lock up your mother as her son?
How could you do that to her for 20 years?
How could you force her into exile deep in the mountains...
as if she was dead?
Do you call yourself a son?
Do you think it is something a human can do?
Well...
How did you know that?
Why are you doing all that?
What will you get out of all this?
This company, this house,
and all the fame and fortune you've enjoyed...
are yours.
What else would you need?
You...
wouldn't understand a word I say.
Like you said, you just think...
everything is mine.
How foolish you are.
What do you mean?
This company, this house,
and all the fame and fortune I've enjoyed.
Even the car you are driving.
Everything will be gone once your grandmother dies.
Everything will be over. Do you understand?
What?
Your spiteful grandmother...
didn't leave anything...
for you and me.
But we've worked...
so hard for this company.
We devoted ourselves...
to make the company grow.
That's no good.
We are getting nothing for that.
Do you see it now?
I'm doing all this for you.
What about Ms. Oh Gui Boon?
Why are you looking for her?
Grandmother is alive.
You can persuade her.
She will recognize our hard work.
You have no idea...
what kind of person your grandmother is.
She will...
never redo her will.
That's why I need Gui Boon.
No. I need Hyun Jeong who's been taken care of by Gui Boon.
What? What does that mean?
Don't you understand?
Dong Hui in that room.
Dong Hui is...
Bang Hyun Jeong.
Darn it. I don't want to eat with her either.
What a brat.
It's almost over.
As soon as...
Gui Boon comes here with the key to the safe,
it will be over.
All you need to do is sit and watch.
Chairwoman Park.
What should I do now?
I'm sorry,
but I have no choice for my poor Dong Hui.
I never thought it'd end up like this.
Decades of work...
is going down the drain.
I'm sorry.
So you mean...
there's no way, right?
I'm sorry.
Let's sell it.
Sorry?
Let's sell this house.
Mother.
This house means a lot to you.
You built it with the money your parents left to you.
You gave birth to Hyung Seop,
raised him, and married him off in this house.
This is where...
your grandchildren and great-grandchildren were born.
I should save my kids first.
They're having such a hard time.
This house means nothing when my kids are suffering.
Grandmother.
I'm sorry.
My house...
doesn't have to be this building.
The place...
in which I can live with my children...
is my house.
So don't be so sad...
about selling this house.
It's all my fault.
I am sorry, Mom.
You know many things can happen in our life.
If we don't want to face rough rides,
we should die early.
If we don't like that option,
we must not have been born.
But we were born...
and we have to live.
We will have...
good times again later.
So let's just sell this house.
If all of us go out and work,
we might be able to buy a bigger place someday.
So...
stop hesitating and just sell this house.
Mother, we can't do that.
We can't sell this house.
We can never do that, Mother.
Guys, clean up. Someone wants to look at the house.
Who's coming?
What are you doing? We'll have visitors soon.
Welcome.
I'm happy that someone wants to buy it this quickly.
You know the location of this place is really good.
Please come in.
Hello.
Gosh.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Get out. Get out now!
I need you to move out in few days.
Sorry?
What's all this?
- What on earth is going on? - Gui Boon.
- He got a loan? - Hey.
Go get Han Seong Hoon!
We'd better not let Dong Hui...
know all this.
(DNA test results)
My name...
What?