You might hate it,
but I grew up...
with Dad's love.
You idiot.
That's a fact. So...
you should leave now.
I...
want to pay him back...
at least half of what he's done for me.
No. You're coming with me.
If you can't do that,
just consider me dead...
like you did until recently.
Sang Woo.
Sang Woo!
(Episode 43)
Where have you been?
Dad sold the house today.
I'm sorry.
I am so sorry, darling.
Gosh...
There's nothing you should be sorry about.
It's not just us.
Everyone lives like this.
Unlike the old times,
children drive their parents crazy.
So it's not your fault.
It's our shameless children who are at fault.
Thanks to them, we will be forced out to the streets...
at this old age.
At the age of 60, I thought we'd...
have a house, live off our pension,
travel from time to time,
and live happily while watching our cute grandchildren.
I never knew we'd end up like this.
Grandmother.
Grandmother,
please have a seat.
- Grandmother. - Shut your mouth.
Hey...
Jeong Hwa.
Do you have any problem with Chairman Bang, Grandmother?
Why would I have a problem with a person like him?
You're not meant to live like this.
What?
You should've been raised...
as a precious daughter in a big house.
Because of me,
you are going through too much.
Gui Boon had a special relationship with...
the former chairman, my grandmother.
My dad is desperately looking for her...
because of our missing grandmother and her will.
It's me, Bang Mi Joo.
What do you mean they're trying to scout Director Han?
Which production company is that?
Okay. Call me as soon as you find out.
What are you doing here?
Why are you looking at that? Give it to me.
What are you? Who are you to come in here and...
Is the lady in the picture...
your grandmother, the one you were talking about the other time?
- What? - Your missing grandmother.
You said you're trying to find her will.
That's why you are looking for my grandmother,
and that's why I'm locked up in here. Isn't that it?
That's right.
So what?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Why do you look at me like that?
It's nothing.
It looks like your family is full of stories.
What do you mean my family is full of stories?
What do you mean by that?
That's...
just the impression I got.
What are you doing?
Don't judge my family.
What does a girl like you know?
You know nothing, so just stay low until your grandmother comes.
That's better for you too.
Better for me?
Can things get worse than this?
- What? - Never mind.
Even so,
you were very hasty when you were reporting...
our largest shareholder, Bang Hyun Jeong's death.
Why do you keep delaying to report...
the former chairman's death?
Is it true...
that Bang Hyun Jeong is dead?
Bang Hyun Jeong.
Who...
is that?
We have to contact the board members as soon as possible.
I tried many times,
but Chairman Bang is watching not only you...
but also every board member.
He's watching their every movement.
So what should I do?
I'm worried about the chairman,
but I am the most worried that...
something bad might happen to Dong Hui.
I think...
it would be dangerous for us...
to contact them directly.
Like what the chairman said,
we need someone who can speak for us...
and persuade the board members.
If old people like us say it,
nobody will believe it.
Right.
Didn't you say Dong Hui used to work at FGC?
Hello?
Grandmother.
Mom. Is that Great-grandmother?
Mom. I want to talk to her.
Hold on.
Yes. It's me. Have you been well?
Grandmother. You are too cruel.
Weren't you worried about me at all?
You are not sick, right?
How is your health?
I am healthy.
Your family and your in-laws' family...
are all fine too, right?
I have a lot to tell you,
but I will get to them later.
Where on earth are you, Grandmother?
I am doing all right. Don't worry about me.
Hye Joo.
I called you because I need to ask you something.
What?
You mean Seong Joon?
What is it?
Take this.
What is this?
I put together the money I have.
I thought you'd need this when we move out.
Why would you give us this though?
Everyone in our family is struggling.
Grandmother even sold this house.
I don't know how else I can be of help.
I didn't take out any loan. Don't worry about that.
Please use it freely.
Seong Joon.
Don't you remember what I told you?
Take this back. I can't accept this.
Dad.
Take this now.
Why should he? What's wrong with accepting his money?
Goodness.
Do you mean to say we should use his money to rent a house?
You know that Seong Joon brought home his salary...
he earned every month without fail.
He wants to help because we are his family.
Honey.
Then did we raise him for nothing?
We deserve this money for raising him thus far, don't we?
I didn't know you were so calculative.
Seong Joon.
Can we talk?
Sure.
Sit down.
Do you...
resent us?
Mom.
I don't know how your fate and mine...
became so unfortunate.
When I heard from your dad...
that you were not his biological son,
I was furious at your dad.
You know that, right?
You know that I had a hard time accepting you as my son at first.
Yes, I am aware of that.
Regardless,
I did my best to raise you.
I tried hard so that no one said you were not my son.
I am also aware of that too, Mom.
But...
it turns out Mr. Lee across the street is your brother.
Your brother thoroughly destroyed our family.
At the end, he drove us to the corner. When I think about this,
I can forgive neither you nor him.
If I could, I want to ask him to compensate...
for the years I raised you.
I heard you asked for the half of your severance pay...
and took out a loan from your company.
How did you find that out?
Mi Joo came by the house.
Sorry?
She gave me money.
She said it looked like you had a problem.
She said she wanted to help.
Mom.
I accepted that money.
You're right. I thought what happened was unfair.
I accepted because I didn't want to give in.
What could I have done?
We lost...
this house.
Your oldest brother...
is about to be killed by loan sharks.
If I could, I want to kill myself too.
Mi Joo gave me the money,
so I took it.
Mom.
Seong Hoon said he will pay back the money diligently.
He said he won't just forget about that.
So you should know this too.
We have to find a house to live in.
With the money from you...
and Mi Joo,
we have to pay back the private loan first.
You and I will talk more later.
Let's settle the urgent matters first and we'll resume later.
Anyway,
we will spend your money wisely.
Tell her...
that we are grateful.
Get some rest.
Why did she ask for Seong Joon's number all of a sudden?
Is she trying to marry Dong Hui and Seong Joon in secret?
Or did they get caught again?
What is it, Mom?
"What is it, Mom?"
I can't let that go.
Let's go back to what we were talking about before.
Talk about what?
The pills. The pills I found.
Why are you taking those pills?
Since when did you start taking them?
Mom.
You are only 16 years old.
Why do you have to take sedatives on a regular basis?
On a regular basis?
That's not true. A long time ago...
When I lived with my former mom,
I took them because my uncle prescribed them.
Really?
Yes.
Aren't you going to tell me the truth?
I'm telling you the truth.
I don't take them anymore.
Hey, Ji Hoon.
I just got back from the workshop.
Have you been well?
Uncle.
I have a problem.
Why?
Mom found the pills.
Mom?
- Which mom? - The mom I have now.
Hye Joo, my mom.
Chang Soo.
Can you take them to the kitchen?
Yes, Mom.
But Uncle,
I am so worried.
Goodness. You don't have to worry.
I will explain it well to her.
Okay. Then...
I have faith in you.
What are you doing?
Why are you surprised?
What did you do...
in Chang Soo's room?
I did nothing.
Hey, where are you going? It's getting dark.
What's wrong with him?
I don't know.
Goodness.
Seriously.
Who knew that we would turn out like this at this age?
We are bleeding them dry.
Who knew that we would be sucking their blood out?
This is embarrassing.
Gosh.
I am afraid that Chang Soo, Ji Hoon, and Ah In...
will watch and learn from us.
If you are afraid,
how can you cost us the whole house?
Exactly.
I don't want to live anymore.
I can't face my parents,
I feel bad for my wife,
and feel embarrassed to my kids.
Goodness.
Seong Hoon.
Don't you think of running away from home...
or jumping off the bridge like you did before.
Leave me alone.
My life is so worthless,
- isn't it? - Seong Hoon.
Gosh.
I can do it on my own.
Don't be so depressed.
You've overcome worse things, right?
When I regain my lawyer license,
I'll work harder to make a living.
And if you manage the restaurant well,
we can stand on our feet again.
That's useless.
When will we be able...
reacquire our parents' house?
Seong Hoon.
Stop crying.
Now I feel like...
crying too because you're crying.
Gosh.
Seong Hoon, put your head up.
Look at me.
Why are they laughing so loud when we're crying?
They're such obnoxious wenches.
No way.
Seong Hoon.
Look at that.
What is it?
That jerk.
What's the matter?
Please calm down.
We haven't got our money back yet.
Forget about the money.
- Let go of me. - Seong Hoon.
Seong Hoon. Stop.
Hey.
- Mr. Lee. - Seong Hoon.
Why are you drinking here?
What bothers you this time?
Look at me, Mr. Lee.
Right. You're Seong Joon's brother, Mr. Lee Hyun Woo.
Gosh. I said stop it.
Get off.
Do you know...
how precious that house is...
to our grandmother and dad?
You are Seong Joon's brother.
How could you...
ruin...
our whole family...
and even our house?
Seong Joon...
Seong Joon is my dad's most precious son.
Do you know how much I cherished our Seong Joon?
Do you think we'd give up on Seong Joon that easily?
We'll never...
let you take him away from us.
Seong Joon is...
our brother.
Understood?
- How does it feel now? - Seong Joon.
What if he...
changes his mind? I told you.
He hasn't paid us yet.
Stay out of this.
Fine.
- Hey, - Let's get out.
- Stop it. - you can have our place.
But don't you dare go close to Seng Joon anymore.
- I said stop it already! - Just take that house...
- and leave Seong Joon to us. - Hurry up.
- Let's get out. - My gosh.
Our bill...
That guy over there will pay our bill.
- Let me go. - Please get a hold of yourself.
- Let go of me. - If we had known he'd come here,
- we could've ordered more. - Goodness.
This is so disturbing.
Where will they move then?
Wait.
I heard that you bought that place.
You must be happy that your dream has come true.
Fine. Good riddance.
Goodness.
Are you okay? What's wrong with you?
Are you drunk?
Wait. Be careful.
This way.
My goodness.
Dear me.
Why did you drink so much?
I see.
I guess you drank to celebrate the success of your plan.
I'm sure you were so happy...
as you can finally take revenge...
and demolish that house.
What's the matter now?
You must be happy. What's wrong with you?
Right.
You must've been drunk lonely all by yourself.
There's no one to celebrate with you.
But you know that nobody would be willing to do so.
That's exactly why you drank alone though.
Still, you shouldn't drink this much alone.
You must drink in moderation.
And I hope...
we don't run into each other anymore.
He told me to leave alone.
Sorry?
I'd been looking for him for my entire life.
And he doesn't want to see me anymore.
He just wants me to leave.
He even told me to think he's dead.
What have I done wrong?
My revenge is nothing compared to what I've gone through.
Did they lose their father?
Did he lose his children?
Are they suffering from being forcibly separated from each other?
I haven't forgotten about Sang Woo for an instance.
Now I finally found him,
but I have no memories with him at all.
Seong Hoon and Seong Sik have,
but I don't have any memories with Sang Woo.
Of course not.
I said 23 years are a very long time.
If that were so simple as you thought...
But it's them who took my brother away from me!
My childhood and youth were lost,
and I ended up with nothing.
I'm still alone.
Do you still think...
I should leave Sang Woo behind?
This isn't right.
I'm his brother.
Sang Woo's brother is me, not Seong Hoon or Seong Sik.
Hyun Woo,
you're drunk.
What have I got?
I haven't gained anything...
from living like this until now.
Gosh. Hyun Woo.
Hyun Woo.
Oh boy.
Why on earth did things go this way?
Goodness.
I think the style isn't bad.
Write a report of the meeting and upload it on the intranet.
Okay.
Then when should we hold a meeting...
to discuss the today's agenda?
- This time tomorrow would be good. - Okay.
Did you send the next two episodes to the director?
I did. By the way,
are those episodes written by Writer Choi?
What are you talking about?
Both I and the director found it...
quite...
Just tell me what you're talking about!
Well...
Well, she thinks...
it's weird that Writer Choi has changed her mind...
after she told us she would no longer take part in this.
You're so sensitive. It's not a big deal at all.
Are you saying the episodes are written by Dong Hui?
- Let me warn you. - Okay.
Make sure not to talk about Dong Hui ever again...
reading the scripts.
- Yes. - Until when do I have to hear...
about her who just ran away without a sense of responsibility?
- I'm sorry. - I'm sorry.
Is Director Han in there?
Gosh.
What was that? Why is she being so sensitive?
That's ridiculous.
I'm pretty sure the script has...
Dong Hui's style of writing.
Gosh, stop it.
Why?
You wanted to see me. I was in a meeting.
What? Why are you staring at me like that?
Did you come to my house?
Yes, I did.
I guess you heard it from your mother.
Thanks to you,
she took care of the urgent things.
That's a relief.
I told you I could help.
I'll pay it back as soon as possible.
Seong Joon. Why don't you let me help you?
Don't do this to me. I deserve to help you.
Your mother told me what is going on.
The money I gave her can't cover the whole thing.
Stop it.
Seong Joon, why aren't you trying to take the easy way out?
I'm here for you.
I've been looking at you and waiting for you for long.
Why are you trying to avoid me?
Mi Joo.
Just get some help from me and marry me.
You're the only person who can support your family now.
All your family is counting on you.
What's holding you back?
You said your family is the most precious thing.
There's nothing you can't do for your family.
Just marry me.
Then you and your family will be...
I'll give you your money back. So stop it.
How will you give me the money back?
What? Are you going to sell yourself to UN Production...
who's been offering you a job for the past two years?
Bang Mi Joo.
They are nasty.
You know that. That's why you've refused their offers.
I don't know how much money they offered you.
But if you move over to the company,
your career will come to a dead end.
That's none of your business.
You stupid jerk!
What's wrong?
What do you think you are doing? We are at work now.
What's so hard about that?
What's so special about you?
And I didn't have the guts...
to ask you this.
Let me ask you the question.
What does Dong Hui have that I don't?
Tell me! What does she have that I don't?
It's finally happening.
Gosh, what should we do?
Gosh, this is embarrassing.
What should we do?
What's the matter with you?
Do with it as you please.
- What are you talking about? - And...
please persuade Seong Joon.
I'll never give up on him.
I have to marry him.
What?
Why are you doing all this now?
Seong Joon's family is in trouble now.
They'd lose their house and end up on the streets.
I'm glad to hear that.
What an arrogant jerk.
Dad.
I'll follow your advice...
about Dong Hui and Grandmother.
But please let me have Seong Joon.
You're so stupid.
He already ditched you once.
Where's your pride?
Why can't you just give up on him?
Right. I have no pride.
So please,
let me have him.
Mi Joo, stop it.
There's no time to waste.
I'll stop at nothing to have him.
I'll never lose him to anyone.
Lose him? What does that mean?
I guess you understood me. I should get going.
Hey.
Gosh.
Hello? It's me.
What's going on with Han Seong Joon?
What's wrong with Mi Joo?
Watch his every movement...
and report back to me.
Can't you knock?
This is my house.
What?
I handed over the scripts with your name as you insisted.
Don't you like it?
Why are you talking down to me?
What?
What if...
I'm someone you can't treat like that?
Are you out of your mind?
I'm stuck in the room all day long.
So my head fills with various kinds of thoughts.
How dare you...
Don't talk down to me.
Then I won't talk down to you.
I think you are quite supercilious as you are an only child.
Chairman said...
you had a cousin named Hyun Jeong. If you grew up with her,
would you've been better?
What are you talking about?
It's just one of my miscellaneous thoughts.
Now that I'm stuck here,
I think about many things.
Or whatever.
Stop talking nonsense and write the scripts for episode 9 and 10.
Do you understand?
So what?
What do you mean so what?
Your brother and sister-in-law are going house hunting.
Gosh, I can't believe this.
I've seen...
a lot of things that are just unbelievable.
I thought I'd had enough,
but it happened again.
Gosh, they'd eventually become...
recipients of livelihood program.
What?
I told you before.
Don't devote yourself to your children.
You'll end up penniless...
and become a recipient of livelihood program.
What? Watch your mouth.
I'm just saying this as I'm upset.
I'll give you some money.
You don't have money.
I'll do it somehow.
It is my mother and brother I'm talking about.
I can't ignore it.
That'd be very helpful.
But you've lived alone all your life.
You should at least have some money in the late period of your life.
Don't say that.
By the way, he doesn't show up anymore, does he?
No.
Are you sure?
I'm sure, Mom. He doesn't.
If you ever see him again...
or live with him behind my back,
I won't be sitting still, okay?
Mom, why would I live with him?
- I should go. - Mom.
Why are you leaving so early? Have dinner with me.
We have a family meeting.
Mom, take care. Don't worry about it.
Gosh, you startled me.
What?
How did you get in?
Your mother left the door open.
Did you meet my mother?
I was hiding under the emergency stairs.
Are you out of your mind?
What are you doing here? I told you not to come.
I won't come again.
This is for you.
What is this?
I heard it from Jeong Eun.
Your mother is moving out.
Why would she tell you that?
Use it for her new house.
Why would you give me that money?
I'm not her son-in-law,
and I'm not your husband.
But I'm Jeong Eun's father.
I've saved some money...
from my opera pay.
And I sold my apartment in Seoul.
Use this money to get a new house.
And I'll never come back here again.
Ae Ri.
Take care.
I was very happy to see you again.
I should get going.
Hey, Myung Jin.
Myung Jin!
Gosh, what was that?
Why is he doing this?
Mom.
You're home.
Did you find a new house?
The rental fees are too high, so it's not easy.
We should keep looking.
House prices have gone up so high.
We haven't moved for a long time,
so I didn't know it was so bad.
We can't get a two bedroom house with what we have now.
- What? - What?
Grandmother.
Are Hyung Seop and Jeong Ae home yet?
- Yes. - We're here.
Did you find anything good?
Mother, it's not easy.
House prices have gone up a lot lately.
Goodness. Is that right?
Mom,
here.
This is the deposit we got back for our apartment.
We spent some...
on the fine...
and on some other things.
But we'll give you all the rest.
I told you not to mention about the fine.
Is paying a fine something to brag about?
No. All right.
I won't...
talk about it again.
I have this one.
It's the diamond ring James gave me.
Good thing I bore the embarrassment and kept it on.
It's going to worth good money.
I'll contribute it to the house.
- Jeong Hwa. - What?
What are you going to do with your clothes,
bag, and shoes you brought from the US?
- What? - We got no space for that anyway.
What are you trying to say?
I sold all your brother's clothes.
The nightclub waiters loved his clothes.
So I thought about your clothes.
We can sell your designer bags by auction,
and we can sell your clothes...
in secondhand stores in Itaewon.
They would buy them at a good price.
Hee Sook.
I am sorry.
We have nothing to give.
Hye Joo's salary is getting seized every month...
to pay back the debts I incurred from the last business.
You are...
You are unbelievable, Seong Hoon.
If I can, I want to sell my organs.
- Seong Hoon! - Seong Hoon!
You idiot.
Is it appropriate thing to say in front of your parents?
Will you watch your mouth?
I am sorry.
It's just that I am very sorry to all of you.
It's okay.
Your organs are useless anyway.
- Mother. - I am just really upset.
All right. Okay.
Anyway, thank you...
for your contribution.
Seong Joon gave me this.
Also,
Seong Joon paid back Seong Hoon's debts.
- What? - Did Seong Joon really do that?
Mom.
Did you...
end up accepting that money?
Yes, I did. You might blame me, but I couldn't help it.
It's an emergency situation.
We have to unite to get through this.
You are unbelievable.
Even if we scrape up every penny we have,
we can't even rent a three bedroom house.
We can't be picky right now.
Anyway,
from now on,
you have to tighten your belt.
Keep that in mind and come to your senses.
And you, Seong Hoon.
Yes, Mom.
Don't think about making money.
Just stay home.
That's helping the family. Do you understand?
Okay. I understand.
By the way, where did your wife go again?
I don't know.
Other hospitals give you medical certificates like this.
Why are you refusing to give me Ji Hoon's medical certificate?
You're Chang Soo's mom. No, I mean Ji Hoon's mom.
I am his mother.
I need to know why my son is taking this medication.
Show me Ji Hoon's medical record and...
the medical certificates from the past one year.
The medical record...
can only be viewed by the patient himself.
Why can't I see them?
My son got treated here because he wasn't well.
Why can't his parent see his record?
Then you should at least give me the medical certificate.
Dr. Kang told me to pay extra attention.
Pay extra attention to what?
He's my son, not his!
Wait. Is Dr. Kang back?
- What? - Is Dr. Kang back?
Doctor, it's an emergency.
Ji Hoon's mom, I mean Chang Soo's mom's here.
She keeps asking for Ji Hoon's medical record.
She must've seen his record the other time.
I think Ms. Park showed it to her because I wasn't here.
Even then, she kept asking why his blood type was different.
Goodness. What do we do?
What if she knows something?
Regretting it now won't change anything, will it?
Still,
I'm too scared, Doctor.
What if they find out that we swapped the kids?
Don't worry.
I will take full responsibility.
Oh, no.
What does she mean?
What does she mean you swapped the kids?
I heard it wrong, didn't I?
I just...
came here to see you...
because of this medication Ji Hoon's taking.
I came the other day,
but you weren't here.
By the way,
what does she mean...
that you swapped the kids?
Doctor.
Doctor, what on earth are you planning?
Huh?
What did you say?
Really? Are you serious?
Yes.
No way.
How can such thing happen?
I am so sorry.
But at the time,
Ji Hoon was in a very critical condition.
Ji Hoon, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Come down!
Ji Hoon!
Uncle.
I don't want to live.
I will...
stop your mom.
So please come down.
It's all useless.
Mom's going to kill me.
It's better to kill myself than to get caught by Mom...
and die while studying.
Is that why...
you told Ji Hoon that you will swap the moms?
Hye Joo.
I had no other choice.
I had to save Ji Hoon.
But you can't do this.
You can't do this.
Calm down.
And please let me finish.
How am I supposed to stay calm?
How can you plan such a thing?
Do you know...
how painful it was...
to endure that time?
It was the same for me.
I was sorry to Chang Soo,
and I was sorry to Chang Soo's parents.
But...
think about why I had to take this extreme measure.
You know.
You know my sister Hee Sook.
If Ji Hoon didn't get to escape her,
something bad would've happened.
So please, Hye Joo...
I don't want to hear it.
How could you...
How could you play with a family relationship?
Is it okay for a doctor to do that?
I will accept any punishment.
As his uncle...
As someone who's been watching him for years,
I thought...
it would be better for me to go to jail...
than to see something bad happening to him.
I wanted...
to protect Ji Hoon...
no matter what.
How about Chang Soo then?
Is it okay to disregard Chang Soo then?
Is Chang Soo someone...
who can be raised by any family?
Hey.
Chang Soo...
is a pitiful and sensitive boy too. Do you know that?
Hye Joo, that's... That is...
You are unbelievable.
I am sincerely sorry.
I have no excuses.
I will...
report you to the police.
Just know that.
I'm about to lose my mind.
Ji Hoon.
Ji Hoon. That little...
Aunt. Aunt.
You jerk.
How could you...
How could you deceive us completely?
You are smart.
Is that why you studied? To deceive us?
I am sorry.
I don't care if you are sorry or not.
How can you and your uncle plot something like this?
He didn't do anything wrong.
It happened because I asked him to.
Exactly.
How can a boy like you come up with a monstrous plan like this?
How dare you play with fate?
How dare you?
Do you know the calamity you will cause for our family with this?
The same applies for your uncle.
How can he go with the plan just because you asked?
I'm going...
to report your uncle to the police first. Do you know that?
I did it because Mom made me suffer so much.
I wanted to get out of her clutches.
Even if you wanted that badly,
this wasn't the right way.
This can't be.
You...
You tricked grown ups...
and your parents.
How? When your mom finds out,
this will ruin her completely.
Can you guess how great of a shock it will be for her?
Anyway, your mother...
did raise you thus far.
Whatever happens, your mother...
put a lot of efforts to raised you.
Ji Hoon.
Do you know how competent your mother was at work?
If she worked instead of raising you,
she would have been more successful than I am now.
However,
she gave up her career...
to raise you.
But how could a son of her...
How could you lie like this?
I still hate my mom.
When I am with her,
I can't breathe.
You won't accept her still.
Aunt.
Can you turn a blind eye to this just this once?
Please...
Please forgive me this once. Please?
Don't kid yourself.
We can no longer live like this.
This is absurd.
I am going to go and tell the family...
and your mother the truth.
Stop talking and follow me.
Aunt.
Aren't you coming?
Chang Soo.
Are you going...
to learn this song next?
Yes, Mom.
- Aunt. - Let go of me.
This is such a nice song.
It's from "La Traviata" by Verdi.
The heroine, Violetta.
An innocent farm boy, Alfredo.
This is the song they exchanged when they first met.
In this song, a spark of love...
starts to flicker.
I can't believe you will be singing...
this world renowned song of tenors.
I am very happy.
This is all thanks to you, Mom.
Can you move aside?
You are in our way. We're dancing.
What? We are in your way?
Ji Hoon. Can you move aside too?
I'm dancing with my Chang Soo.
What?
Chang Soo.
You are a great son.
I am...
very happy that you are my son.
I am happy and honored that I have you as my mom too.
I will remain as your son forever.
Chang Soo.
Don't let our family problems dishearten you.
Let's focus on your singing.
By all means, your mother...
will raise you as the world renowned opera singer.
Yes, Mom. Don't you worry about that.
Please don't, Aunt.
They seem very happy.
So...
can't we be happy too?
What?
What is this?
("In Love at Twilight")
Goodness.
Come in.
Oh, my.
Who is this?
Director Han. Long time no see.
How have you been?
I have been well of course.
By the way, it's so hard to see you nowadays.
You've been dodging my phone calls too.
You know that we waited for a long time.
We will give you a handsome amount of transfer fee.
Why did you stay at a ridiculous company like FGC?
They don't even support producing dramas.
I don't want to talk about that.
All right.
Goodness. You're hard to please.
Anyway, I would like to finish...
this drama perfectly and resign.
Of course.
It will help us too if you do.
By the way,
how many scriptwriters can you bring with you?
- Pardon? - We have...
some decent actors.
We need scriptwriters for us to produce dramas.
Don't you have some talented writers?
Or are they still under contract with other agencies?
I...
I just work hard by myself.
I am close to a lot of scriptwriters,
but I don't have anyone to bring with me.
All right. I got it.
That's how it all starts.
It starts from friendship. Anyway, I understand.
First, let's sign the contract first.
Hey!
Bring me the contract for Director Han.
Here you go.
We'll provide the best treatment and competitive salary in this industry.
We will send you the signing bonus within a week.
(Han Seong Joon)
Seong Joon.
Are you really not going to leave with Hyun Woo?
- No. - That's not right, Seong Joon.
- Jeong Eun. - I know.
I know how much you care about your family,
but Hyun Woo is your brother too.
He's your biological brother who has been looking for you for years.
If you abandon him like this...
I didn't abandon him.
The reason why I can't understand my brother...
is because I don't know if he had to go this far.
You know in what condition our family is because of what he did.
It's because all he had in his life were wounds.
You received a lot of love without getting hurt too much.
Now you should take care of him.
If you abandon him, he'll be all alone.
Then everything will be irreversible.
He had enough chances.
He could've stopped so many times.
But it's him who ignored all the chances.
That might've been his best.
No. He chose a wrong way.
It may have been...
better if we hadn't met in the first place.
For me,
I feel like he ruined everything in my life.
Seong Joon,
don't say that.
Please give Hyun Woo another chance.
I'm sorry. I'm leaving.
Seong Joon.
Thank you.
- It's not far from here. - Okay.
You have the address, right?
- Yes, I do. - Okay.
Who is waiting in the house?
Seong Hoon is.
Will we get there on foot?
Yes, Grandmother.
We can't take our car there.
The alley there is too narrow to park the car.
We will have to park...
our car in the public parking lots.
That will be so inconvenient!
That's what I'm saying. Shoot.
I didn't even want to pass by his house,
- but I'll have to. - This is awful.
Let's go, Ye Bin.
Let's get going, Mom.
What about Chang Soo and Ji Hoon?
Grandmother, we're here. Hurry up.
What are those you're holding?
These are the music scores for Chang Soo.
We'll carry these ourselves.
I didn't want them to be lost or ripped while moving.
Why are you so late?
I'm sorry. We forgot something.
There's no time to waste. Hurry.
- Ji Hoon. - Yes?
What is that?
It's a magic box.
Do you have to bring it with you?
- Darn it. - Ji Hoon!
- What's wrong with him? - Hee Sook.
- Mom. - Yes?
- Yes? - That cauldron embarrasses me.
- What? - Please keep a distance from us.
- What did you say? - Guys, let's just hurry up!
Okay. Let's get going.
- Gosh. - Grandmother.
- Thank you. - Let's go.
Let's get moving.
Hye Joo, be careful!
What are you doing? Hurry up.
Seong Sik, why are you not carrying anything?
It's because I have a heavy heart.
- Sir. - Bulldoze that house.
Pardon?
Demolish it as soon as possible.
Okay.
You're here.
How have you been, Ms. Oh?
I've been doing well.
I'm sorry to call you over all of a sudden.
It's all right. Don't mention it.
Ms. Oh,
what happened between me and Dong Hui is all my fault.
It was me who recklessly started liking her first.
I apologize.
Actually, I'd like to ask you...
a favor regarding Dong Hui.
Dong Hui is locked up...
in Chairman Bang's house now.
Pardon?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
Who in the world doesn't love her children?
If you really love me,
don't you have to try to understand what I really want?
I'm leaving. Cherish the memories here by yourself.
Mister.
Seong Joon, what brings you here?
Why? Can't I come here?
Who am I?
Dong Hui, please wait a little longer.
Director.