Director Han.
Find her.
Did they hurt you?
You've been well, right?
I'm sorry.
I found out too late.
I should have looked for you before.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what's happening.
I'm...
so confused.
Dong Hui.
Listen to me carefully.
Don't worry. Just wait for me.
Do what Chairman Bang wants you to do.
Don't go against them.
Trust me and wait for me.
You can do that for me, right?
What are you going to do?
What if that puts you in danger too?
I don't think that will happen.
I will resolve this problem by all means.
I will make sure to...
get you and your grandmother out of that house.
I missed you.
I missed you too.
(Episode 45)
What happened? What's the matter?
Dong Hui disappeared.
What?
What were you doing?
Are you kidding me? Go find her.
- Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Gosh.
Dong Hui.
Did you receive the script I sent you?
Yes.
You did a very good job.
Once you get home,
don't worry about anything and just work on your script.
Okay?
Yes. But...
Just listen to me.
And take good care of Ms. Oh.
Dong Hui.
I love you.
I love you too.
Gosh.
I think she left the building.
- What? - I can't find her anywhere.
Gosh.
There she is.
What?
Where have you been?
I went to the bathroom. Why?
You should have told me before going to the bathroom.
- Let's go. - Yes, sir.
- Who are you? - Well...
I'm from FGC.
- Can I talk to her for a minute? - Okay.
Chairwoman Park Chang Wook.
Hello.
I'm Han Seong Joon. Ms. Oh Gui Boon asked me to come and see you.
I'm here to help you.
Gosh.
Director Choi Jin Sung is...
all that remains.
He is the key figure.
If Director Choi helps us,
things would be a lot easier.
What did the chairwoman say?
If all the people on the list resigned from the company,
I should get the key from Ms. Oh, unlock the safe...
and hand everything in it to Bang Gwang Jin, she said.
She's trying to raise the stakes.
Then...
on the day Bang Gwang Jin announces the renewed will,
Chairwoman Park will return to the company.
This is...
the key to the safe.
She set you...
such a heavy burden.
There are Chairwoman Park's will...
and the truth about Bang Hyun Jeong who is supposedly dead.
It's a secret...
that they've tried to keep for their entire lives.
Please...
take good care of it.
Gosh.
How could you keep your old mother...
locked up like that?
That's so inhumane.
Get off me.
All the women in our family...
are so talkative.
Where have you been?
Did you...
I went to see your grandmother.
Dad.
You knew it, right?
You knew the whole thing.
I can't believe this.
You guys are so terrible.
How could a son and a granddaughter...
lock their mother and grandmother...
in a mountain for 20 years?
What on earth do you gain from this?
Shut your mouth.
How dare you say such a thing to us?
You should shut your mouth. You know I'm older than you!
It's so noisy. Just stop the quarrel.
So are you the one...
who killed my dad...
and mom?
That's not it. I told you I didn't do that.
I'm under a false accusation.
I can't believe this.
You can't do this.
It just doesn't make sense.
Excuse me, Chairman Bang.
Mi Joo.
As I said before,
I'm not interested...
in the money, power, and reputation.
They are no better than trash to me.
So let me and my grandmother...
get out of here immediately.
What have we done wrong?
I've known nothing all my life.
And my grandmother has lived in adversity until now...
just for Chairwoman Park.
We will live in obscurity...
as we have done so far.
So please let us out.
Don't worry about it.
I was going to let you out anyway.
Chairwoman Park will rewrite...
her will pretty soon.
Just wait quietly until then.
I don't want to keep you here anymore.
Send her up to her room.
You jerks.
All of you will pay for this.
You will be punished for this.
Bang Mi Joo, I'm not going to be sitting still.
Get off me!
- Gosh. - Dad.
Why did you take Dong Hui there?
It is the easiest way to change your grandmother's mind.
So what?
If she rewrites her will,
what will happen to Dong Hui?
It's simple.
She just said that.
She'll live as Oh Dong Hui.
Is it even possible?
You know she's Bang Hyun Jeong.
Oh Dong Hui is Bang Hyun Jeong. So what?
I'll be getting all the money and stocks...
for Bang Hyun Jeong.
Hyun Jeong will be just an empty shell.
She'll be useless.
Dad, please.
I don't want to see them anymore.
Just wait a little longer.
Everything will be over soon.
What are you doing?
Make some noise when you get in the house.
You said you weren't interested.
You were doing some research about UN Production.
That's just my job...
to analyze companies.
As a matter of fact,
I've done some research on UN Production.
As you know, it is a nasty company.
I believe you should let Sang Woo wash his hands of the matter.
I said I was just looking.
You should sell all the stocks of FGC Group.
There's no reason to keep them.
I think it's better to keep them for a little longer.
What do you mean?
According to our agent,
there's a rumor that Park Chang Wook is coming back.
What do you mean?
How can the former chairwoman of FGC group come back?
Recently, a rumor has been going around among shareholders...
that Chairwoman Park has been found.
Whoever it is, he's recklessly bold.
Pardon?
The return of the chairwoman...
must be a very bad news for Bang Gwang Jin.
The fact that this rumor is spreading means that...
someone's planning to take down Bang Gwang Jin.
Well, I guess that's possible.
Should I look into it and find out who's behind it?
No, there's no need.
Whether it's good news or bad news, it doesn't affect us at all.
Like what you said, we should just sell the stocks...
at the right time and go back.
Yes, I will report to you...
as soon as I get an update.
By the way, what will you do about Sang Woo?
I said I'm not interested.
Still,
you have to get him out of UN Production immediately.
He's an idiot.
It's...
It's the old lady who used to live across the street.
Your house is bigger than it looks.
Hello.
Can I take a seat?
Sure. Take a seat, please.
Do you want some tea?
I don't need anything.
Why don't you sit?
You should sit too, Mr. Gray Hair.
Sure.
These are...
gochujang and doenjang from our rooftop.
These days, men live well...
even when they live alone.
You shouldn't eat just anything because you're alone.
Store-bought ones are not good.
You should taste ours.
You didn't have to do this.
Do you think I want to give it to you?
I'm giving it to you because you took care of Ah In the other day!
You are an incarnation of vengeance.
Ma'am.
Let me finish.
When you become as old as me,
you learn to separate one thing from another.
Even if I am really mad at you and I want to kill you,
I still have to thank you for what you've done for Ah In.
Even if I'm really thankful to you,
I have to confront you about what you did to us.
It's not...
that I don't understand...
where you're coming from.
To experience such tragedy...
must've been so horrifying.
You were the eldest son to your father,
and you were the elder brother...
to your little brother.
But still,
you were just a sixth grader.
When you were supposed to be cared by your parents,
your father died,
and you lost your little brother.
- Ma'am. - Be quiet, boy!
I'm telling you...
that I am trying my best to understand you.
My children...
still can't understand you. They can't forgive you yet either.
But...
I sometimes...
can understand you.
I forgive you for a while too.
But...
you were too mean to us.
My son...
raised Seong Joon with so much love.
Regardless of what happened,
I think you should thank him.
Forget about everything that happened,
and just think about how well Seong Joon turned out.
Among the three brothers, he's the most successful one.
He's also the most handsome and the most mature one.
You should stop your vengeance now.
When I was packing these condiments,
I thought about that.
And it made me feel so sad.
I don't know if you will care about what I say,
but I've come here to tell you this...
as a grandmother.
I'll get going then.
I didn't get to move...
the pots in the rooftop yet.
I don't know if Jeong Eun told you this.
Let me leave them there until you tear down the house.
It's a shame to waste them.
Please do me a favor.
I'm really leaving now.
Ma'am.
You don't need to come out.
Mom,
now that we're eating ramyeon together in this small house,
I feel like we've become Heung Bu's family.
I feel like we're really poor.
But it's really cozy, so I don't hate it too much.
Did you say cozy?
You're unbelievable.
Gosh, it splattered on my clothes.
I'm over 60 years old, and I'm eating ramyeon...
in this small house with my grown up children.
How do you call this cozy?
Mom.
I'm just saying that's how it feels.
It would feel even better if it rains outside.
Mom, since this already happened,
we should live with a positive mind.
You can be positive all you want.
I can never be positive.
Goodness, it smells like ramyeon.
Where have you been, Mother?
I went to the roof top.
Why did you go there?
I got some doenjang and gochujang.
And I fed Moong Chi since I already went there.
You should've asked the kids to do it.
Why would you go there and drain your energy?
The real estate agent said they might tear it down soon.
We need to find...
a place to move her.
Grandmother,
eat some ramyeon.
Here you go.
We should be really thankful...
that we can eat this ramyeon.
Only if...
Seong Joon was smarter.
What are you talking about?
Think about it, Mom.
Seong Joon's brother,
Mr. Lee is very rich, you know?
If Seong Joon played smart,
we wouldn't be here doing this.
He's so tactless and loyal.
He could go straight to his brother, make up with him,
and talk him into giving us our house back.
No.
He could even get us a nicer house. How nice would that be?
- Hey! - Goodness.
I told you not to mention Mr. Lee in front of me, didn't I?
Well, it's just that I'm really sorry.
You idiot.
Is the one thing you managed to think about..
is exploiting his rich brother?
I'm not planning to exploit him.
That's a way of paying us back for everything we've done for him.
Mom!
Be quiet.
What did I do?
Don't you have self-respect?
I won't take it even if that guy will give us our house back.
I'll spit on his face right away.
You've gone too far.
Grandmother.
If you think about it, Mr. Lee is a poor thing too.
Mother.
Because of Hyung Seop's mistake, an innocent man died.
That's why Mr. Lee and Seong Joon...
became orphans overnight.
That's not all that happened.
Mr. Lee had to be parted with his only family...
Seong Joon for 23 long years.
Goodness. Think about you becoming orphans overnight.
Mother, are you...
taking sides with Mr. Lee?
I'm not taking any sides.
I'm just saying this because he's nothing like our children.
What do you mean he's nothing like us?
Look at our children.
None of you wished to...
leave your parents, and you all crawled back into the house...
and created this mess.
Mr. Lee made his own fortune and came here...
with determination to find his brother.
It shows how hard he's been living his life.
There's nobody like him these days.
So what are you saying, Grandmother?
Are you saying that guy's actions are justified?
That's wrong, Grandmother.
He shouldn't be doing this to us. We are innocent.
I'm just saying.
Just keep eating ramyeon. The noodles will get soft.
Okay.
I...
had to agree to play along.
I felt sorry to Chang Soo and you guys.
And I knew the family was going to become a mess.
But I had to save the boy first.
Goodness, it's shocking.
How can the eighth grader think of jumping off a building?
So I think from Dr. Kang's perspective,
he must have considered this to be quite a serious problem.
Dr. Kang...
knows how Hee Sook is.
He was well aware of Ji Hoon's condition.
Think about how serious it must have been for him...
to use this sort of plan to save Ji Hoon.
Besides, Dr. Kang's...
youngest daughter...
went through something similar to what Ji Hoon went through.
I heard she is paralyzed from the waist down.
Really?
Yes.
That's why...
he overreached...
so that the same thing doesn't happen to Ji Hoon.
He discussed that with me.
Goodness. Kids have to go through a lot these days.
If this continues, a disaster is bound to strike.
We ought to get rid of that college entrance exam.
But still. Father,
we know the truth now.
It's not something we can cover up by ourselves.
That's not an absolute solution.
Anyway, this is between Ji Hoon and Hee Sook.
We should tell Hee Sook the truth.
Let them find their own solution. Don't you think this is better?
Hye Joo.
Sure. Hee Sook will be thrilled to find the solution.
Don't you know that with Chang Soo's success,
she is more confident about her education method than ever?
But still.
When she finds out her son tried to kill himself...
What I saying is...
that people don't change. And that's the problem.
Besides, look how she's been living her life recently.
Yes, it was a lie,
but even though it was known that Ji Hoon wasn't her son,
she came downstairs to nag Ji Hoon.
On top of that,
she penetrated into the world of opera...
and made Chang Soo win the competition.
She even took Ah In.
As of now, Ah In learned 1,800 Chinese characters.
I think she knows the most about the Chinese characters.
She's capable of this.
She will definitely find a solution with Ji Hoon.
On the day Hee Sook finds out the truth,
she will drag Ji Hoon away and it will be Ji Hoon's last day.
Then what do you suggest that we do?
Are you suggesting that we live as it is now?
First of all,
we will solve the problem with Seong Joon.
Seong Joon and Jeong Hwa are still not speaking to each other.
Honey.
Goodness.
I heard it from Mr. Kim Han Gil.
You know where Chairwoman Park Chang Wook is?
Yes, I do. I visited her.
I can't believe this.
What world-shaking news.
How could this continue for 20 years?
Chairman Bang deserves to die.
I knew it. Something was suspicious.
However, there is a problem.
Even if the shareholders' did trust Chairwoman Park,
it'll be hard to win them over with just a rumor.
Besides, at every shareholder meeting,
you were mentioned to be replaced.
Everyone believes that you and Director Bang will get married.
I am fully aware that the shareholders...
who support Chairwoman Park don't trust me.
However,
it is not true that Director Bang and I will get married.
There are a lot of people waiting for Chairwoman Park.
You can't overlook the fact that it's been 20 years.
Chairwoman Park was worried...
that 20 years has passed.
During that time,
some of us could have changed side.
If so, you will be in danger, Director Han.
- Are you aware of this? - Yes, I am.
What is the reason of your involvement despite the fact?
I just...
think that an injustice must be corrected.
All right.
Do you have a definite plan?
I do.
Great. Then...
you must get Chairwoman Park out of his clutches.
(CEO Hwang of UN Production)
This is Han Seong Joon speaking.
Hey, Director Han.
I was wondering if things were going well.
I'm just calling to check.
- What is it? - It's nothing important.
Since you will be joining our production,
I told a few agencies that you are joining our company.
We had an agreement that...
you will keep my transfer a secret for a while.
I have to get things ready in advance too.
When I told them you are planning to join our production,
some agencies wanted to get involved in our projects.
That's why...
I thought that I should treat you better.
What do you mean?
A while ago,
I just transferred some money to your account.
Sorry?
It's for official expenses I planned on giving you once you start here.
Think of it as an advance.
Use it freely.
That's not necessary.
I will send the money back to you right away.
Well...
If you are thankful,
it'd be great if you can start earlier than the set date.
Mr. Hawng.
Then I will call you again later.
Chairman Bang.
Han Seong Joon.
What is he up to these days?
What do you mean?
Why is he meeting up with other directors?
Don't you know how Seong Joon is?
He likes to prepare to the fullest.
He told me that he wanted to help you properly.
He wanted to talk to other directors...
who turned their back on him.
He's meeting them to test the water.
If that's what he's doing...
He should have done this a long time ago.
Anyway I look at it, I don't like him.
Dad. He's going to be different.
Trust him, please?
Goodness.
Did you hear?
What is it? Over what are you making a fuss?
What is it? Are Director Han and Bang getting married...
or something?
What? What about Dong Hui?
Amazing. How did you know?
- What? - What?
He's marrying her?
Director Han and Bang are getting married?
Then the reason why Chairman Bang dropped by last time...
Was it really about their marriage?
Something is off. I really thought he liked Dong Hui.
What are you doing?
- Goodness. - Hello.
Stop chatting...
and work, please. Okay?
- Yes. - We will.
Why is...
Director Han trying to marry a woman like her?
- Seong Joon. - Hey.
You're here.
How are your meetings with the directors going?
Surprisingly, some of them were quite friendly.
- Why? - Dad already knew about this.
He knew that you were meeting up with directors.
Is that so?
That's probably why the news is getting around the company.
The news about our marriage.
I think...
the shareholder meeting will be held soon.
I don't think people need to talk about it.
The shareholders might think...
that you are going around to get their approvals of our marriage.
Which brings me to my question.
Do you think you can stop meeting the directors?
To be honest, I don't think Dad likes you meeting them.
Then I will stop.
Thank you.
Do you want to have dinner tonight?
Sorry?
Sure.
Let me just wrap things up.
What brings you here?
I'm here to feed Moong Chi.
- All right. - Okay.
Feed your dog then.
By the way,
I heard you signed a contract with a company that has a bad reputation.
There's not a thing you are not informed of.
I didn't like FGC,
but UN Production is worse than FGC.
You would have known that too.
I do. I well aware of that.
So?
Did you sell yourself to that nasty company...
in order to help the people...
whom you call your family rent a house?
Is this your method of cleaning things up?
If you are going to tell me the same thing, I don't want to hear it.
Get out of that contract immediately.
Do you think they will take responsibility for your life?
You should assume responsibility for your own life.
I'm well aware of that too.
So please stop meddling in my life...
and take responsibility for your own life.
Well then.
Here's your coffee.
- Thank you. Enjoy it. - Thank you.
Why do you look so surprised?
I'm just your neighbor.
When did you come? I didn't see you walking in.
I walked in while you're absorbed in making money.
Two coffees, please.
What was that?
Gosh.
What is it? What are you doing here?
Have a seat.
And have some coffee.
So this is the routine.
Would you do me a favor?
What favor?
Do I look like a pushover?
You know we broke up.
Don't you know what we call common courtesy between exes?
You're so ridiculous.
Please stop Sang Woo.
- What? - He won't...
listen to me no matter what I say.
Of course not. Did you only notice that now?
You didn't do what Seong Joon asked you either.
Why did you do something you'd regret in the first place?
Sang Woo sealed a move to UN Production...
to pay the deposit for his family's house.
Really?
The problem is the company is quite nasty.
He sealed a move knowing all that.
That idiot.
Then what is happening to Seong Joon?
He will be abandoned after being used up.
It means his career will come to a dead end.
Then you should stop him.
That's why I want you to stop him.
He won't listen...
to whatever I say.
You should have played your role well as his brother.
Then he would have listened to you. Don't you think so?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Seong Joon is very stubborn. There's no way I can stop him.
Anyway, please talk to him.
Hey.
Right.
Thank you for taking care of me that night.
What are you talking about?
What?
He knew the whole thing?
He should have said thank you before he started talking.
He's so rude.
By the way, what should I do with Seong Joon?
When winter is gone
And spring comes
Spring will be gone again
I know.
I know how you feel.
Beauty and hard life seldom go hand in hand.
You know...
a beautiful person like you...
is born under an unlucky star.
What can I say? You were just born beautiful.
You should blame your mother.
What am I supposed to do?
Now that he's dying,
I can't do anything.
It's only his fault...
that he was born...
with an ethereal voice.
Maybe it's time...
he should return...
his voice to the sky.
I can't believe this is happening.
I know great artists are...
born under an unlucky star,
but this is just too much.
I know.
There isn't a lot of time left now.
I'm so sad.
Is it true...
that he's given...
only three months to live?
Yes.
Only three months.
Unfortunately,
he will live on April, May, and June.
It's only May...
that has 31 days.
How devastating.
He's such a jerk.
Why did he come to me?
Does he want me to bury his body or what?
You should face your tragic fate.
How?
You should...
live with him...
for the next three months.
Just before he dies.
What?
It's...
only three months.
Aunt.
Do you hate studying that much?
Actually, I like studying. It is quite fun.
That's why I get good grades.
Then why did you try to kill yourself?
I was scared out of my wits to hear that.
When I get fully stressed out,
I feel like I want to die.
That's why.
I think...
if your mom finds out the whole thing...
It will kill me.
You!
Stop saying that.
It's not just about you.
In fact, I feel sorry for students these days.
Why aren't you eating it?
I have no appetite.
I bought it for you. Just eat it.
You are supposed to like it at your age.
Gosh, look at you.
I wish I could tell your mom...
that you're her son.
It will really kill me.
Hey! Stop talking about that.
Will you say that again? Will you?
Gosh.
I'm sorry.
Eat it.
Okay.
I have something to tell you.
It's about Seong Joon.
What about him?
I heard Seong Joon sealed a move to another company.
Isn't it a good thing?
Isn't it that he was offered a better job?
I know that's what usually happens, but this isn't the case.
The company who offered him a job...
has a bad reputation in the field.
People say it is a nasty company.
- What? - Then...
why would Seong Joon move to the company then?
It seems...
he got a huge money for his transfer.
But he shouldn't do that.
You said it's a nasty company.
Money is not an issue.
Wait. Did Seong Joon...
That's right.
He made such a decision to get you the house.
What?
Is he out of his mind? He can't do that.
What are you talking about?
He's moving...
to a nasty company just for the money?
Gosh.
Anyway,
you should stop Seong Joon no matter what.
If things go wrong,
his career will come to a dead end.
- I can't believe this. - Oh dear.
(Testament)
(Assigner Park Chang Wook, Assignee Bang Hyun Jeong)
Bang Hyun Jeong.
Who is that?
Why are...
Dong Hui's pictures here?
(Death certificate, Oh Dong Hui)
No way.
Why is Dong Hui...
(Death certificate, Oh Dong Hui)
It's just like what you saw. Dong Hui is...
Gui Boon's granddaughter.
But...
she died a long time ago.
- Then... - Yes.
The person who's living as Oh Dong Hui is...
Chairwoman Park's granddaughter.
She's Late Bang Gwang Ho's only daughter,
Bang Hyun Jeong.
How...
How can this happen?
I couldn't tell you until now...
because Ms. Oh asked me not to tell you.
I am sorry.
Then...
isn't Dong Hui in a great danger?
There's no way they'd leave her alone.
But to extricate the chairwoman according to our plan,
this is the only way.
So please send those files...
to Bang Gwang Jin as soon as possible.
What will happen...
to Dong Hui after I send them?
I can't give you a definite answer.
However, this is...
the only way for us.
No way.
Dong Hui.
Grandmother, how are you not well?
I'm okay.
I just don't have energy. That's all.
But your temperature is too high.
You can't stay like this.
We have to go to the clinic.
Ms. Oh Gui Boon asked me to deliver these documents.
Okay.
Are you Mr. Bang Gwang Jin?
That's right.
(Deed of Transfer of Stocks)
(Death Certificate)
Right. This is how it's supposed to be done.
Finally, everything is coming to an end.
Everything is over now.
Do you know what this is?
I don't know.
This is...
What is it?
I need to take Grandmother to a hospital.
What's going on?
Grandmother isn't well.
Please let me take her to the hospital.
I told you to wait, didn't I?
Until when? I beg you.
I won't run away.
Just let me take Grandmother to the hospital.
What if she passes away like this?
Aren't you...
worried that your grandmother might pass away?
You jerk.
Hey! How dare you talk to an elder that way?
You are terrible. You're terrible.
How can you do this to us?
How can you do this to my grandmother?
Let go of me. Let go!
Stop.
You want to save your grandmother, don't you?
You want to save both of your grandmothers.
You want to save them all, don't you?
Then you better listen to me carefully.
Dad, what are you trying to do?
Follow me.
Let go of me. My grandmother is sick!
Grandmother! Let go of me!
(Hearty Sanatorium)
Mother.
The old sayings are true.
There are no parents in this world...
who wouldn't do anything for their child.
It was going to turn out like this anyway.
So if you fixed it earlier,
Hyun Jeong didn't have to struggle.
She could've lived a happy life.
Now, it's about time.
This is the will the bank has been keeping for you.
And this is Hyun Jeong's stock certificate.
Gui Boon gave up as well.
Now, you just have...
to fix your will.
In my whole life,
I began as a street vendor...
and managed to save that much money.
I just wanted to feed, dress,
and educate my children well.
But that money became my enemy.
That money pulled siblings apart,
and that money...
also pulled apart the parent from her children.
Come closer.
Grandmother.
Goodness.
You grew up as a beautiful lady.
You became a beautiful lady.
I am sorry.
Don't say that.
There's nothing you should be sorry about.
I am the one...
who is sorry.
- Grandmother. - Yes?
Just...
fix the will for him.
But...
But you...
won't be taking anything then.
I don't need anything.
I've been living that way until now.
So Grandmother,
don't worry about me...
and just...
fix the will.
You've been stuck here...
for the past 20 years.
You spent too many years in here.
My darling.
Come closer.
My lovely darling.
Let me hug you.
Grandmother.
My darling.
My lovely darling.
(Testament)
(Park Chang Wook)
Okay!
I waited for 20 years. 20 years, I tell you.
It has turned my hair gray.
I have one condition.
I want you...
to release...
Dong Hui and Gui Boon.
- Mr. Kim. - Yes, sir.
- Take care of this. - Yes, sir.
I was going to release them anyway.
They don't have a penny to their names.
She will live...
as Oh Dong Hui for the rest of her life.
Don't you think so?
Gosh, my dear Ye Bin. You're studying English.
Mom. I don't want to study English.
You have to. You know Chang Soo came first place in his competition.
Children are supposed to study.
I want to go out and play.
You can't!
- Ji Hoon, stop right there. - No.
I told you to stop.
What are you doing, Hee Sook?
Why are you doing this to me?
Is this your report card?
Why are your grades so terrible?
Why are you closing your ears?
Stop closing your ears!
What's going on?
- What's the matter? - Hee Sook.
What's wrong?
Honey.
It's nothing.
It's no big deal.
I was talking to Ji Hoon.
Han Ji Hoon, follow me.
No.
I'm not talking to you.
Please excuse him.
Ji Hoon must have been stressed out with studying.
Follow me.
- I said no! - Gosh.
Hey!
What do you think you are doing to your Mom?
I mean,
she's your aunt.
He must be under a lot of stress.
You should stop it. Ji Hoon is not your son.
Why are you doing this to Hye Joo's son?
I just can't understand you.
Mother. You know that.
Seong Hoon and Hye Joo are...
not that interested in their child's education.
If Ji Hoon studies a little harder,
he will get first place in his school again.
He will even take the nation's first place.
- Ji Hoon, follow me. - No.
Hee Sook, stop it.
You can lead a horse to the water, but you can't make him drink.
There's no way you can force him to study when he doesn't want to.
I can't believe this. Honey.
Let's just focus on Chang Soo.
Ji Hoon is not our son anymore. Why are you doing this?
Just give him to Seong Hoon and forget about him.
Grandmother, Mother, and Father.
And members of this family.
I raised him for 15 years.
Even though...
I didn't give birth to him,
I raised him with all my heart for 15 years.
We are living under the same roof after all.
It doesn't matter whether he's my birth son or not.
Let's just make the most of our special abilities. You make money.
And I will be in charge of children's education.
What's wrong with that?
The problem is Ji Hoon doesn't want it.
Hye Joo, take Ji Hoon with you.
- Okay. - Bring him.
You can't go. Follow me.
Hee Sook, let go of him.
You should let go of him.
Ji Hoon needs to study.
What do you think you are doing with him?
Hee Sook.
Follow me!
Kang Hee Sook!
You wicked wench!
Do you want to see him die?
I said he needs to study.
- Hee Sook, stop it. - Hee Sook.
Are you out of your mind?
Stop it, everyone!
If you keep doing this, I'll run away from home.
Ji Hoon. Ji Hoon!
- Ji Hoon, you rascal! - Hee Sook!
I told you to stop!
Did you see that?
- Yes. - Yes.
I did.
It's that bad.
I don't think...
it is a good idea to tell her the truth now.
I know. That's exactly what I'm saying.
Hye Joo.
Still.
How long do we have to do this?
Let's say we will let it slide this time.
But after quite a while,
how will you tell them the truth?
You're right.
This is driving me crazy. What should we do?
It wasn't me.
Was it you, Dad?
Who would it be then?
Is that true?
Hey, since when were you there?
Well...
Chang Soo, what did you hear?
Is that true?
- What? - What?
Is it true that Ji Hoon and I weren't switched?
What should we do?
Was it really a lie?
Is that it?
Dad. Mom.
Grandfather.
Keep quiet.
Why are you doing this to him?
Stay quiet.
Is it really true?
Is it true that we were not switched?
I told you to be quiet.
Seong Hoon, stop covering his mouth with your hand.
- Keep quiet. - Stop it.
Grandmother, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
By the way, go give Seong Joon a call.
He's taking care of everything all alone.
I'm afraid if he'd be in danger.
Go give him a call now.
Okay.
Seong Joon, it's me.
Yes, we are out.
Grandmother and I got out of the house.
Moong Chi.
What are you doing here alone?
Moong Chi, I missed you so much.
My dear Moong Chi.
What?
Seong Joon really did that?
That's ridiculous.
He wouldn't do that. There must have been a mix-up.
Stay out of this, Mi Joo.
What did you say...
Seong Joon, that jerk did?
Moong Chi, good girl.
Good girl.
You've watched the house the whole time.
Thank you.
Dong Hui.
Seong Joon.
Are you all right?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I was worried about you.
I was so worried.
I'm okay now.
Don't worry about me.
I'm sorry.
And thank you.
You've been through a lot because of me.
I was worried about you.
I was afraid you'd get hurt...
or something would happen to you.
I've been worried sick about you.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
- Mom. - Seong Joon.
It's not about whether you do well or not.
Don't give up. Just kill him.
Seong Joon who you love so much...
Do you think you can protect him?
I can't stop here, can I?
- What's this? - If something happens to me,
you might need it.
Why are you looking for our director?
We are arresting you for manipulating the stock price.
Director Han.