What? Seong Hoon was conned?
Yes.
Again?
I can't believe it.
This can't be happening.
This is old news in my family.
How can this happen?
The truth is...
It's a long story.
Anyway,
we moved into a house on the next street.
It's a three bedroom house on a deposit basis.
That's why the whole house was empty.
You must have had a lot on your plate with your family problem.
I'm sorry that have I put you...
through my problem too.
What? You were locked up.
How could I have lived?
Director.
Thank you so much.
I will make sure to return your favor.
How will you return the favor?
Are you...
going to marry me or something?
Stop joking.
By the way,
did you figure it out?
Figure what out?
Figure out that you were to inherit the company?
Isn't that a bit funny?
A bit funny?
What on earth is this?
You're like the main character in your drama.
That's exactly my point.
I don't have any memories about my childhood.
They told me that I was an heiress.
Imagine my surprise.
It could have been nicer if I could have helped you out.
I'm sorry that I am a poor heiress.
I don't need money.
We are a big family.
If everyone works hard together, things will get better soon.
By the way, you must be disappointed though.
Exactly.
I should have been arrogant...
and yelled at Director Bang.
I lost my chance.
Dong Hui.
Hang in there a bit longer.
I think...
I might be able to help you get back what was yours.
No.
Don't.
I don't need...
what was mine before.
Have you forgotten when you first came to the company?
You had to sign that terrible contract because of your cousin.
I don't care.
Thanks to that, I became a scriptwriter...
and met you, Director.
So I don't want to be greedy.
I found out who I am...
and where I came from.
I'm okay with that.
But I just don't know how I can help...
my grandmother escape from the sanatorium.
I got out because of her will, but my grandmother...
I don't know if Bang Gwang Jin will keep his promise.
Don't worry about that.
By all means,
I am going to get her out.
I'm scared that might put you in danger.
I am...
not scared at all.
A scarier thing...
than that happened to me.
What happened?
I found out that you were an heiress...
and I thought I might lose you.
I was afraid.
No way.
Why would you be? Why would you lose me?
I came back here for you.
Don't worry.
Everything will be okay.
It will be.
Hye Joo. She's on the eighth floor.
Oh, no.
Grandmother.
Hye Joo, calm down. She's sleeping.
Please?
What on earth happened?
What is wrong with her?
It hasn't been long since she moved out.
First of all, we should meet the doctor.
Hey.
How did you know that I was here?
Grandma. Are you all right?
There's no reason why I shouldn't be all right.
Move aside. Hey, move aside.
Grandmother.
Goodness.
How...
How did you get here?
- Well... - Grandmother.
You are too mean.
You should have given me a call if you were sick.
How did you find out?
Seong Joon gave us a call.
He said he was with Dong Hui.
He said that you were in the hospital and to visit you.
What is wrong with your health?
Nothing is wrong.
I was just stressed out.
I must have been exhausted.
There's nothing to worry about.
Grandmother. You are too cruel.
You made us worried sick about you.
You are horrible, Grandmother.
What has gotten into you?
Okay. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
- Dong Hui. - Seong Joon.
Ms. Oh. It was quite an ordeal you went through.
Thank you so much.
I won't ever...
forget your kindness for us.
What is going on?
Why are Grandmother and Seong Joon getting along...
so well so suddenly?
Kindness? What kindness?
Well, Hye Joo.
- Seriously. - Ouch.
- You are the problem. It's you! - Hye Joo.
It's all because you started to date Seong Joon.
Because you started to date Seong Joon,
Grandmother got sick because she had to move out.
- You are the problem. - Hye Joo.
Hye Joo. Don't hit Dong Hui.
Look at you.
I heard you're moving to another company.
UN Production? Is that right?
How did you know that?
That's not the problem.
Go terminate the contract now.
- Seong Hoon. - I heard they are nasty.
Why would you go there?
You can't do that just for money.
Seong Hoon. It's not like that.
That's it. I heard everything from Jeong Eun.
If anything goes wrong with you,
our family won't be able to face you.
You must have gone through a lot.
I couldn't help you even after knowing all that.
I'm sorry I couldn't comfort you.
But we can't just receive help from you again.
I know we are family,
but we will be deeply ashamed.
Don't you think so?
I'm okay with it.
We are not okay with it.
Go terminate the contract anyway.
Would there be a cancellation charge or something?
Okay. I'll look for the money.
Seong Hoon.
Mom and Dad know the whole thing.
They are devastated too.
Why won't they be?
We are leaving all the burdens on their youngest son.
So make sure to terminate the contract tomorrow.
Okay?
What does that mean?
What's all that? Revenge? Mr. Lee?
Is President Lee Seong Joon's biological brother?
You didn't know that?
Didn't Seong Joon tell you that?
No. He just said he met his brother.
Seong Joon...
has been through a lot of heartaches lately.
I mean...
things are still hard for him.
So are you saying they are not talking...
to each other at all now?
Seong Joon is very upset.
President Lee made our family miserable after all.
How could this happen?
Dong Hui.
I have to say the same thing to you.
How could this happen to you?
What will you do with Seong Joon?
Why are you still with him?
Are you going to marry him or what?
- You still don't get it, do you? - Hye Joo, please.
Gosh.
Grandmother is watching.
- So what? - That hurt.
What? Han Seong Joon did that?
That's ridiculous.
It can't be true. There must have been a misunderstanding.
Stay out of it.
What did Seong Joon that jerk do?
Didn't you know?
Seong Joon is helping...
Chairwoman Park Chang Wook prepare for her return.
Gosh.
You didn't even know what your future son-in-law is doing.
Director Bang, are you sure you are marrying Director Han?
What did you just say?
What a jerk.
How did he find out about Chairwoman Park?
Dad.
It's Gui Boon.
- What? - Gui Boon...
and Seong Joon are in-laws.
Darn it!
You darn old lady.
I...
will make him regret it.
At the last moment,
I gave you the most important information.
On the day you officially take over as the chairman,
make sure to hand over...
the shares of the contents team to me according to the note.
I should get going.
You ungrateful jerk!
Why are you crying?
What are you so sad about?
Please get out of my room.
Shame on you.
I told you.
That jerk doesn't love you.
It just serves you right.
I thought he was a pushover.
How could he hatch a plot like that?
You're the only person who didn't see through him.
I don't know.
I don't know what to do now.
I should've fired him well before.
I couldn't do that because of you. Look at us.
It's like my own pit bull has turned on me.
I'm sorry, Dad.
You can do whatever you want now.
I don't know what to do anymore.
Now you have it all together.
I will never forgive that scumbag.
You should just stay out of this.
Dong Hui.
Good morning, Director Bang.
What...
What are you doing here?
- How dare you show up here? - Why?
Why shouldn't I be here?
You took all my money and position.
Do you even want to stop me make a living?
Don't kid yourself.
It wasn't yours to begin with.
Yes.
Yes, it was.
You and your father caused matters to come to this...
trying to take everything from me.
- What? - Even though...
I threw up everything and left,
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
but it doesn't change the fact that the Bang's blood...
flows in my veins.
And the fact remains that I'm your cousin.
Now that we are in the company,
I'll be polite to you.
So you'd better behave...
with the minimum amount of courtesy.
I heard that...
Writer Choi quit.
And you even handed my script...
saying it was Writer Choi's.
I'm the only one left now.
You can't complete the drama without me.
So I'll work hard.
Dong Hui, are you out of your mind?
Director Bang.
Be careful about what you say.
Even though I'm a person without a penny,
it won't do you any good...
if people in the company find out...
the relationship between you and me.
Dong Hui.
Do you think you can protect...
Seong Joon, who you love so much?
What can you do for Seong Joon?
It's not that you can only protect someone with wealth and fame.
Is that why you threw away Grandmother's will?
Is that why you let her rewrite it?
I didn't know...
you wouldn't like it.
Listen to me.
You won't be able to protect Seong Joon anymore.
- Really? - You can't do this now.
We have a problem with the drama.
- It looks good, right? - I don't know.
Gosh.
- Look who's here. - Dong Hui.
What a surprise!
Is that you, Dong Hui?
How have you been?
I'm really Dong Hui.
It's been a while.
Dong Hui, what happened?
- Dong Hui! My Dong Hui. - Stop it.
I missed you so much.
Wait. Please let go of me.
Stop it. I want to see Dong Hui's face.
- No, I won't. - Let go.
Gosh, he's funny.
Dong Hui.
Goodness.
What do you think you are doing?
Are you welcoming Dong Hui now?
She's been off the grid for two months.
Dong Hui, how ungrateful can you get?
How can you come back here like this?
Stop it. What's wrong with you?
Dong Hui, we were worried about you.
What happened?
I'm sorry to have worried you.
Nothing happened. It was just something personal.
Something personal?
How can you do this?
Is office your playground?
Is this a place you can come and go as you please?
Do you think you can just not come if things come up?
I am sorry. I am really sorry.
What's up with all the fuss?
Director Han. Look.
Dong Hui is here.
Dong Hui came to work.
Hello, Director Han.
Dong Hui.
Can I see you in my office?
Sure.
- I'm surprised. - What?
Why isn't Director Han surprised to see her?
Why do you think it is? He just can't believe it. Goodness.
Anyway, I'm so happy Dong Hui's back.
What's so happy about it?
We don't have to worry about not having the script now.
Why did you come to work?
You know that you can't put your guard down just yet.
I know.
But I thought hard about it.
I think this is better.
I am the person Gwang Jin wants to hide.
I need to be all over the place...
to draw his attention.
And that will make you freer.
Dong Hui, but this is still too dangerous.
No, I can really do this.
The heiress who doesn't have anything and has no hope...
can be good too.
The lowest rank employee can be good too.
So don't worry about me,
and you should be careful.
You know that, right?
What? Did you say Dong Hui came to work?
Yes.
Is she out of her mind?
That means it will be easier...
for us to watch her. So it's good for us.
Right.
Watch who she talks to. Watch her well.
Should I have locked her up...
with Mother?
There's no need.
Don't you just have to get a hold of Seong Joon?
What's the point of locking up the heiress without any share...
and make her get full of herself?
Just let her continue being the low-rank employee.
Only then, she will know her place.
Right. You are right.
Right.
Mi Joo, are you certain...
that you are over Seong Joon now?
Yes.
I can't bear it anymore.
I can't watch Dong Hui acting like the unfortunate heiress...
or Seong Joon...
planning all of this for her.
Right.
Now...
you are coming to your senses. This is how it's supposed to be.
Only then, this company will become yours.
Do you know...
UN Production?
What?
Here.
Sir.
Why are you so surprised?
I've come...
to talk to you.
I heard...
you hid Seong Joon away.
Goodness.
I didn't hide him away.
I went through the official procedure to...
What?
I am sorry, sir.
But it was a shame...
for us to give up on Seong Joon.
Don't give him up.
Kill him.
What?
Because of a strange rumor,
my company's stocks are...
hitting the daily permissible ceiling.
It makes me feel very bad.
You know...
that I acknowledge you...
as a good businessman, right?
Yes. Thank you, sir.
I will make you earn the money...
you were trying to earn through Seong Joon.
Sir?
You should...
buy our company's stocks.
The whole lot.
If you knew that, you should've stopped Seong Joon.
How can you not stop your little brother?
I heard you have a big company, and you are a good entrepreneur.
You should've stopped your brother.
What's good about having a family?
Isn't it good because you can help each other in times of trouble?
Seong Joon is very stubborn.
If he thinks something is right,
he wouldn't stop even if he's threatened to death.
And now...
his entire family is about to be forced out onto the streets.
He would gladly sell his body for us.
Do you think I didn't stop him?
I already tried stopping him.
You should've stopped him well.
Jeong Eun said it's very dangerous to be involved in this.
I heard that company is very bad.
Do you think there's anyone else in our family...
who can function as a person?
Because of his pathetic family,
he's living a pathetic life.
You are his brother. Do you want to let him work...
for that dangerous company?
Hyun Woo, say something.
Mr. Gray Hair's here again.
You must be a set.
Hello, ma'am.
Anyway,
I said everything I needed to say. So I will be going now.
Don't forget what I said...
and please persuade Seong Joon.
Do you understand?
I'll get going now.
That family is truly unbelievable.
One day, the grandmother came,
and today, the mother came.
Should I be thankful to them...
for being so worried about Sang Woo?
And why am I getting scolded by them?
Why did she come?
She came to ask me to stop Sang Woo from working for UN Production.
They won't let Sang Woo work for such a dangerous company.
Sir.
Something even more serious than that just happened.
Last time, I told you some people are trying to...
bring back Chairwoman Park Chang Wook to FGC.
I heard Sang Woo is involved in it.
What?
What did you say?
Sang Woo?
Why would he do that?
I don't know.
I don't know the reason.
Why would he do that?
Doesn't he know who Gwang Jin is?
He would do anything for his own interest.
How can he become Gwang Jin's enemy?
You should meet him...
and talk to him in person.
Sir.
Sang Woo doesn't even want to see me now.
We fought again last time because of this area.
You still have to meet him. You have to ask him the reason...
and help him to plan the escape.
Ta-da.
This is for you.
What is that? Why did you buy pyjamas?
Goodness. Wait.
This is for you.
Okay.
What are all these for?
What do you think?
It's a pyjama set for a newly wed couple.
What?
They are...
matching pyjamas...
for a newly wed couple.
Aunt, isn't it so romantic?
How is it romantic?
- Goodness. - I love it.
Hey.
Shouldn't you be wearing a hospital outfit?
You are going to die soon.
Aunt, don't say that.
Don't say such thing.
You promised to get along well...
for the next three months.
Goodness.
I told him he could stay here. I never said we'd get along well.
Come on, Aunt.
I think this is just wrong.
He didn't show his face for 30 years.
And he appeared again just before dying.
Do you think it makes sense?
Is he an elephant?
They go back to their forest on time for their death.
Aunt.
Your tragic fate.
Think of your tragic fate.
That fate isn't for everyone.
You have to be beautiful and graceful.
And you need the first love you can never forget.
You're the only one in Korea...
who meets all the three conditions.
You know you can't be this cynical.
I realized...
that everyone dies in the end.
Aunt, come on.
- Dad. - Jeong Eun, you were here.
Yes. I closed the cafe late last night.
Are these yours?
Yes. There aren't many, right?
Will you really live with us?
Did Mom say yes?
- Of course not. - Aunt.
Jeong Eun, what do you think?
Wouldn't they be like newlyweds if he moves in?
So I brought...
- pyjamas for you two. Look. - Goodness.
Hee Sook...
Hee Sook!
Jeong Eun,
why are you so slow-witted?
You must stay out of their business.
But I think it's too ridiculous.
How could you tell Mom that my dad has a fatal illness?
How will you live with the consequences?
Let's not worry about it for now.
If they fall in love with each other again,
your mom would be happy...
that he wouldn't die of an illness.
Also, they'd appreciate...
that they got back together.
Hee Sook, you really know nothing about my mom.
If Dad doesn't die in three months,
she might kill him herself. Okay?
I just need you to stay quiet.
Eunha Contest which is Chang Soo's second contest...
will be held at the end of May.
So let's leave it at that for now.
- What? - What?
Should I go back and live with you?
Can I just live with my current parents?
What did you say?
Say that again.
You know I wanted to just live with you back then.
I know you did.
But you had no choice since Ji Hoon wanted to live with us.
Yet, if it hadn't happened,
I wouldn't have been able to become who I am now.
- What? - What?
Although I lived with my parents,
Mr. Han and Ms. Seo,
I didn't know what I was good at...
and what I was talented in for 15 years.
It was your teacher who recognized your talent,
not Hee Sook.
Still, if it were you, do you think you would have been...
able to make me prove my capacity as a vocal singer?
It's not merely about money,
but about continuous parental care,
the amount of attention, and conviction.
Jeong Ae.
Mother, where have you been?
Of course, I went to church.
Did you pray today?
Would our family's financial condition be better soon?
I realized that we should focus on children's education.
It's not late yet.
Mother.
I stopped by Mr. Lee's house...
and went to the market.
Why did you visit Mr. Lee?
I went to get the glass containers for food from before.
I also needed to discuss with him about Seong Joon's matter.
What did you need to discuss about?
I told him that he should've stopped Seong Joon...
as his older brother if he had known that Seong Joon was...
engaged in such an illicit matter.
- You did? - Yes.
Don't visit him too often.
You might start liking him.
Mother.
Wait. Am I a housekeeper or what?
Why do I wash dishes every day?
Let me think.
Didn't Hye Joo come home?
Why doesn't she show up in the kitchen at all?
And this is the most important.
What is it?
I prefer Ms. Kang Hee Sook as my mother.
She's pretty, skinny, and fashionable.
She even smells great.
She's a good cook as well.
I'm sorry, honey.
She's very feminine too.
I love it especially when she...
calls me "Chang Soo" with her tone of voice.
You're such a jerk.
Don't you know how much love I gave you?
I even took you to my workplace.
I fed you and changed your diapers...
in the company bathroom, you bad son.
- Honey... - Hye Joo.
- Wait. Stop! - How...
It isn't just about me.
Think about Ji Hoon. He'd suffocate if he lives with his former mom.
That's true though.
- Father. - Dad.
But her education style...
fits me just right.
You'd better be quiet.
Chang Soo is right.
Father.
Dad, still...
What if Hee Sook finds out that Chang Soo and Ji Hoon...
weren't actually switched?
That'd be horrible.
Gosh. What are they talking about?
Mom. Grandmother.
What's going on outside?
- Isn't it Jeong Hwa? - This is unbelievable.
What's the matter?
Chang Soo and Ji Hoon...
What's going on this time?
Be quiet.
Nothing. Please don't mind us.
Mom, Chang Soo and Ji Hoon weren't switched.
- Stay out of this. - Get off.
Chang Soo and Ji Hoon weren't switched in the first place.
It was just a lie.
What?
Aunt,
you can't say that to them.
So they haven't been switched even once?
You're right, Mom.
I can't believe...
that he came up with such a dreadful scheme.
Ji Hoon's uncle is a really bad guy.
I can't stand this.
Just calm down.
We told you.
He didn't want Ji Hoon to suffer the same fate as his daughter.
Still, how could he tell us such ridiculous lie...
as a doctor?
It's your fault as well.
You're involved in every complicated issue...
about our family members' birth. It's unbelievable.
Why do you bring that up now?
Mother, look how sly he is.
That's why I warned you before you got married to him.
I told you to be careful as he's quiet...
but sly.
Mom.
So what should we do with this?
How can a problem occur after another?
What is this?
Did you decide to make my life so dynamic?
Even if that was the case,
you two, who were totally fooled, are idiots.
I said be quiet.
So what do we do?
Will you switch your kids back?
That's impossible, Grandmother.
Chang Soo wants to stay with Hee Sook.
I have no idea what we should do with Ji Hoon.
If we tell Ji Hoon to live...
with Hee Sook,
he'll get stressed out.
Mother, still...
This isn't right. It's ridiculous.
This is total nonsense.
Can't we just let them live the way they are now?
That's out of the question. I need you to be quiet!
I'm worried about Ji Hoon though.
What are you all doing here?
Is this a family meeting?
Why didn't you call me then?
Right.
We should put soybean paste and chilli paste in the fridge.
That's right. I almost forgot, Mother.
- Me too. - We must put them in the fridge.
Chang Soo, go make your bed.
Right. I will, Aunt.
Hold on...
Why are you all leaving?
Did Seong Sik open the restaurant?
Dad, I'll go to work now.
Okay.
Why are you all leaving all of a sudden?
- That's right. - Did something happen?
Let me tell you. What happened...
You must help us now.
- How can you be so lazy? - Mom!
All you do is idling, you lazy wench.
(Sang Woo)
Sir.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
We've received an official document from FGC.
I think Chairman Bang plans to disclose...
the former chairwoman's will...
in the upcoming general meeting for stockholders.
Gosh.
What on earth is Sang Woo up to?
If our guess is right,
the day of the general meeting would the D-Day.
Why did you stop here?
Why don't you ask for help?
The only person who can help you is...
Jeong Eun, isn't it?
Why are you here, Hyun Woo? I was expecting Mr. Jo.
He fooled me.
What?
Mr. Jo has set this up.
I can't believe him.
Why did he set this up though?
Did you ask him to?
I heard you have something to discuss about the shop.
Why did you tell his family what Sang Woo did?
Hyun Woo. You asked me to do so.
You wanted me to persuade Seong Joon.
He's not easily persuaded.
Grandmother has to collapse,
his mother has to yell at him,
and his brothers have to scold him...
if you want to persuade him.
So...
is he going to get out of the contract?
I am not sure about that yet.
I don't know what's going on with him,
but it's hard to see Seong Joon nowadays.
They are much better than I am.
His family is better.
Hey, do you want to hear a funny story?
When I was young, I had...
a big fight with Jeong Hwa. We were pulling each other's hair.
Out of all the times, when we were fighting,
our grandmother gave us some money...
and told us to buy ourselves a corn dog.
Do you know what we did?
We stopped fighting.
We took the money and held each other's hand.
We went to buy a corn dog.
Are all women like you?
No, that's how families are.
Seong Hoon and Seong Sik fought...
a lot when they were young too.
Seong Sik was crying because Seong Hoon beat him up,
but when Seong Hoon said he was going to buy some toys,
Seong Sik stopped crying and followed me.
They were childish.
No.
It was because they were family.
So...
I don't know what happened between you and Seong Joon.
Why don't you go and see Seong Joon?
He...
doesn't like me.
No, that's not true.
Hyun Woo.
Fights between siblings always happen.
Everyone fights with their siblings.
It's nothing special.
So...
just like we went to buy a corn dog...
and to buy some toys,
you should go and see Seong Joon. Okay?
I mean you are in charge of managing Golden Street, a conglomerate.
Yet, you don't know what to do with your brother.
Isn't showing your unconfident side of you...
to me embarrassing?
You are still...
not good at things other people do easily.
That made me...
pity you.
That was one of your charms.
Please go if everything is settled.
I have to go and clean up the coffee shop.
You know that I will be running the shop until the end of April, right?
Thanks to Mr. Jo,
I get to walk looking at these cherry blossoms.
Jeong Eun.
Yes?
Can't you just continue running the shop?
What?
I told you I don't want to. I told you we are done.
That's how I can keep visiting the shop.
Sorry?
Gosh.
Something is going on.
What?
What is it now?
Goodness!
I have to count them again.
Don't you think so?
About what?
I'm talking about our family.
They are definitely...
hiding something from me.
No way. Who is it? Why?
How can they deceive you? It's harder than deceiving a ghost.
You can even find all of my secret funds.
Who on earth can hide things from you?
Gosh.
No.
I have a hunch.
Gosh.
I think...
they are hiding something from me.
Hey.
I thought I was going to die today.
Your mom got so close to finding out everything.
What?
Goodness.
What are you going to do?
As of right now,
everyone in the house found out except for your mom and dad.
How did that happen?
Well...
It sort of happened that way.
What are you going to do about this?
I thought I was going to have a heart attack.
What is your plan?
Aunt.
I'm really scared. What do I do?
My goodness, you brat.
What am I going to do with you?
- Are you having fun? - Yes.
- How about you, Ye Bin? - I'm having fun too.
Are you?
This time, why don't you get on an airplane?
Seong Joon.
I was just playing with Ah In and Ye Bin.
Go to your great-grandma. Stop bothering your uncle.
- Yes, Grandma. - Yes, Grandma.
Have a seat here.
Okay.
The company you signed to join...
Dad.
Let me finish.
Don't join the company.
I heard it's a nasty company.
Dad. You don't have to worry about it.
How can we not worry about it?
We can't stop worrying about it since we have found out everything.
Why would you go to that horrible company with your competence?
Mom. I'm fine.
I will do a good job.
It isn't about whether you will do a good job or not.
The company is the problem.
Let's not drag this out.
Get out of that contract right away.
Dad.
Listen to him.
Nothing bad comes from listening to your parents, Seong Joon.
Yes?
This is Hyun Woo. I'm in front of your house.
Can you come out for a second?
Hey, is it your brother?
Go meet him.
Don't be so stubborn. Go meet your brother.
You were probably resting. I'm sorry to have disturbed you.
It's okay.
The thing is...
I didn't mean to check up on you.
It's just what I do.
I happened to know things about FGC.
I see.
Are you helping Chairwoman Park...
prepare for her return?
Yes, I am.
Do you even know how dangerous it is?
I do.
Why would you do this knowing all that?
Tell me, so I can help you.
Chairwoman Park...
is alive.
She's been in confinement for 20 years.
I'm just trying to make things right.
So why do you have to do that?
Bang Gwang Jin isn't a person you can deal with.
It seems okay as he hasn't noticed it,
but once he finds it out, you will be in danger.
Are you doing this...
knowing all that?
Sang Woo.
You'll be in danger. You can't do this.
Listen to me.
I'm sorry.
I'll wrap things up with UN Production...
when this is finished.
I didn't really think that through.
It turns out you were right about that.
All right.
You made the right decision.
- So about FGC... - But I have to...
do this no matter what.
- Sang Woo. - Hyun Woo.
Don't worry about it. It'll be all right.
It has to be all right.
No, you can't do that.
Anyway,
thank you for your concern.
Sang Woo.
I just met Sang Woo.
As I expected, he doesn't listen to me.
Have the analysis team study every move FGC makes...
and report it by tomorrow morning.
And I need to see you now.
Okay.
Hello.
Here.
It's been a while, Dong Hui.
Yes. I'm sorry for coming here at this late hour.
It's all right. I just met Sang Woo.
Sang Woo?
Is Seong Joon's real name Sang Woo?
Lee Sang Woo and Lee Hyun Woo.
In fact, I'm here to ask you a favor.
I don't even know where to start.
The thing is, Seong Joon is in danger.
Seong Joon is helping my grandmother,
I mean,
he's helping Chairwoman Park of FGC prepare for her return.
Is Chairwoman Park...
your grandmother?
Yes. She's my grandmother.
Now I understand.
I understand why he's doing it taking all the risks.
Did you know about that?
Yes.
That's why I met Sang Woo earlier.
I told him to stop,
but he wouldn't listen to me.
You're right. It's too dangerous.
I don't want him to be put in danger because of me.
All I want is to lead a quiet life...
with my two grandmothers.
But there's no other way to get my grandmother out of there.
That's why Seong Joon is doing all that.
I get it.
Now I understand...
what's happening.
I'm very sorry.
You don't have to be sorry.
I'm his brother.
It's my duty as his brother.
Instead, this is just between...
the two of us.
If Sang Woo finds everything out,
things will get more complicated.
It's late. I'll drive you home.
Where do you live now?
Well... It's...
Gosh.
I heard the house had been sold.
Are you sure we can stay here?
Don't worry. I got permission.
How did you get permission?
They've still got time until they tore down the house.
He said we can stay here until then.
You saw that too. We still have doenjang, gochujang,
and even Moong Chi's still here.
Grandmother.
Don't worry about it. Just have a seat.
Gosh.
I cleaned up the house yesterday.
Nothing has changed.
Grandmother, do you want to lie down?
I'll make the bed.
Moong Chi, Grandma is here.
Why is the door left open?
Gosh.
Oh my gosh.
Elizabeth.
- Mi Ok. - My goodness.
How long has it been?
How have you been?
Where have you been the whole time?
How could you be so insensitive?
How could you be so cold-hearted?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
My goodness.
How could you not call me even once...
after leaving like that?
I'm sorry about that.
I heard everything about you.
It's about my children,
so I don't know what to say.
They just...
tried to do something for the best. What could I say?
Now that things have happened,
nothing can be retrieved.
I just want us...
to take good care of each other while we're alive.
Then they will...
face the reality of life...
with all the warm memories.
You're right.
I agree.
After you left, I've given it a lot of thought.
It's just a young man...
and a young woman liking each other.
What choice do I have?
As the old folks tried to meddle in and stop them,
things have...
ended up this way.
So I was thinking...
maybe we should...
let Seong Joon and Dong Hui marry...
if they still love each other.
What?
Dong Hui, what do you think?
This is quite comfortable.
I should sleep in this pyjama tonight.
Gosh.
So newly wed couples wear same pyjamas like this?
All right.
What else wouldn't I do for love?
By the way, is he out or what?
He said there'd be a recording.
Is he out?
Gosh.
I said I'd let them get married, but why wouldn't they say anything?
That's ridiculous.
Are they rejecting my proposal?
Ae Ri, what are you doing?
Where are you? Are you in the kitchen?
Mom.
When did you come?
- Oh no. - Mother.
What do you think you are doing?
Mom.
Look at you. What are you doing?
Why are you wearing same pyjamas?
Did you two get married without telling me?
You jerk.
- Come here. - Mom, stop it.
Stay out of my way.
You jerk. I told you not to come ever again.
How dare you come here? I'll kill you.
Mother.
Stop it, Mom.
He can only live...
three more months.
What?
(Seong Joon)
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
Are you surprised?
No.
What brings you here?
The shareholders received the official document.
The general meeting will be held soon.
Yes, I know.
Is everything ready?
Yes, it's going accordingly.
By the way,
did you really prepare...
this big event by yourself?
What?
I am just proud of you. That's all.
I served Chairwoman Park for a long time,
but I never dared to do this.
Of course, I didn't even know that she was alive.
There's nobody helping her.
If there were people to help her,
she wouldn't have been locked up for all those years.
What?
Right.
You're right. Of course.
(Bang Hyun Jeong file)
(Copying 22 items)
What's this?
Seong Hoon,
I'm giving this to you just in case.
You will need this if something happens to me.
What do you mean? What would happen to you?
Is something wrong?
What's this?
It's a news material.
- News material? - Yes.
You have many journalist friends.
That's why I am giving it to you.
What's the point of giving it to me?
You should give it to your brother. He's the head of Jinsung Daily News.
Still.
Why you...
What are you up to these days?
Tell me honestly.
Seong Hoon.
What are you two doing?
What is it?
The breakfast is ready.
I'll go to work now.
- Okay. - Seong Joon.
Have a good day.
Wait.
What's that?
Seong Hoon.
Aren't you a little old to ask Seong Joon for this?
You are unbelievable.
You don't know anything.
Seong Joon!
Seong Hoon.
Why don't you...
share it with me?
Good morning. Good morning.
Good morning.
You're early, Dong Hui.
Goodness. Seeing Dong Hui writing...
in this early morning...
makes me feel so relieved.
- Right? - I know. Gosh.
Please write the episodes 9 and 10 well.
All right.
Resign after writing episodes 9 and 10.
- Stop it. - Stop it, sir.
You're checking the stocks again.
Will you turn off the computer?
Who are you here for?
Where is Mr. Han Seong Joon?
Okay.
Good job. Right.
Finally, Seong Joon is...
done for.
Why are you looking for our director?
What is it?
We are from the financial crime unit.
What?
We will search you for manipulating the stock price.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I think I need to find what's mine.
A girl who has nothing like you can't do anything.
What did you say?
I'll put an end to this.
Goodness. What's going on?
I'll kill you all. How dare you scam me?
Dong Hui, come here.
I am sorry. I'm really sorry.
Did you miss me a lot?