(Sauna)
It's me.
It's Oh Gui Boon.
How have you been?
May I ask what this is about?
I somehow drifted into a situation...
where I have no place to stay.
I have nowhere to go...
with my granddaughter.
I am terribly sorry to say this,
but can you help me a little?
Hello?
I'm not in a good situation, too.
I am held in suspicion.
You should hide somewhere first.
After some time passes, I will contact you.
I am sorry.
Hello? Hello?
Grandmother, I will stop at a gas station first.
Okay.
Welcome.
- Please charge 50 dollars' worth. - Sure.
- Where is the toilet? - Over there, sir.
Okay.
Grandma.
Are you okay?
I have to be okay.
But still,
you hated going in-law's.
When you live life, there are some things you can't control.
And you just have to endure it.
Then good days will come again.
All right.
Sorry for making you wait.
Let's go now.
Grandmother, I'll start driving now.
My goodness.
(King penguin)
(Emperor penguin)
Look at them!
Look at them sticking to their family members to survive.
Ji Hoon, turn up the volume.
Okay.
- Grandmother. - Wait.
My goodness. What will they do? What will the baby penguins do...
if their parents don't come back?
They die.
Really? Poor things!
I feel terribly sorry for them.
Goodness.
Mother, what are you doing right now?
Are you trying to make me upset?
Of course I am not. I am just trying to study penguins.
Ji Hoon saw this documentary during biology class.
You should watch it, too. Song Joong Ki is narrating it.
He even has a sweet voice.
By the way, if they sell those cuties,
I do want to try raising them.
Don't you agree with me, Ji Hoon?
I agree.
Mother!
What's the use of lying in your room?
He's still going to be your son.
Since you're already here, you should watch this.
Even those parent penguins are...
doing that to save their offspring.
Even animals take care of their offspring. So how can you not?
Now that it happened, you should just accept it.
Stop it, please! This is so hard for me!
That's that.
- What did you do? - Pardon me?
Why are you picking a fight with Hye Joo now?
When your husband came up with a ridiculous idea,
you should have stopped him at any cost.
What did you do the whole time?
I couldn't stop him.
Besides, you told me not to complain about whatever he does.
You told me to obey him.
What is it? Are you trying to laugh at me?
No, I am not laughing at you.
He looks like he's the easiest man to fool,
but he's unbelievably stubborn.
When he's into something, he never listens to other people.
Yes, Seong Hoon has been like that ever since he was young.
Even so, you should have stopped his plan with penguins.
How was he going to raise and sell those penguins?
Did that sound normal to you?
Penguins? My goodness.
Be quiet.
Why isn't one of you better than the other one?
How can you and your husband be so same?
Maybe that's why we live together.
What?
I am sorry.
You frustrate me. You really do.
I feel like my life is getting shorter...
when I see your family.
Do you know that?
Gosh. My goodness.
Mother! Mother!
Mother! Are you all right?
What's wrong, Jeong Ae?
The penguins are killing her.
Mother. Mother.
I am sorry.
Are you okay, Mother? Mother!
It's nice and clean now.
She's here.
Mother, what should I do?
Should I take you to the doctor? Or Should I call the ambulance?
Why would you call the ambulance? Stay quiet.
What are you doing? Grandmother-in-law is here.
Hye Joo and Hee Sook, let's go and greet her.
Yes, Father.
Honey, what are you doing?
Mom.
Honey.
- Just go. - Please come out.
Mother, are you okay?
- Hey Joo. - Hello.
- You're here, Grandma. - Hello, Grandmother.
I hope it wasn't a arduous journey for you.
It wasn't at all.
How have you been?
What are you going to do? She's already here.
Mother, what am I going to do?
How can I live with my kids and in-laws?
Who told you to have a son like him?
By the way, she is a victim. She was conned by your son.
Rush outside.
Take care of your in-law who lost her house due to your son.
Since we are on the subject, penguins are not like abalones.
How can one raise penguins?
If it was that easy to raise, there would have been...
a crowd of people stringing penguins on the street.
Mother.
I did come here bearing my shame.
I am so sorry and embarrassed.
That's nonsense.
Please don't think that way.
They are our children and we are all parents after all.
We need to stick together when times are hard.
In fact, it's the opposite.
I don't know what to say about my son.
I'm sincerely sorry.
Father, she is my youngest sister.
That makes you an in-law.
When did you grow up to be a woman?
Hello.
Welcome. Please feel free to say here.
- Where is Jeong Ae? - She's coming.
It's nice to see you, Mrs. Oh.
How have you been?
I've been well, of course.
Welcome, Mrs. Oh.
- It's been a while. - Yes.
How have you been?
Let's stop here.
Let's take her upstairs.
- What are you doing? Lead her. - This way, please.
- Dong Hui. - Please go inside.
This is a bit small.
No, this is fine.
Thank you for taking care of us.
No need to thank me. This isn't the first time living together.
Unpack your things and let's have a meal.
You should say hello to other family members. too.
- Yes. - Come down soon.
Okay.
Gosh.
You are so cute. Hello. What's your name?
You are so pretty, but I can't see your eyes.
Where are they? Let's see where your eyes are.
I'm home. Let me say hi to Moong Chi quickly.
Let's see where your eyes are.
Gosh, here they are. You're so pretty.
You're so cute. Don't go.
- Sit. Be a good dog. - Who are you?
- Why are you here? - Why are you here?
This is my house.
- What? - Dong Hui, come down to eat.
Dong Hui, what are you doing? I told you to come down.
You're home.
You should have your meal.
- Yes, Hye Joo. - You haven't met Dong Hui yet.
Dong Hui, say hi. He is the youngest brother-in-law.
Seong Joon, she is my youngest sister.
What? What is it?
Nothing.
Hello.
You two sounded silly.
Who talks like that to an in-law these days?
Dong Hui, everyone's waiting. Hurry down.
Okay. I see.
- You too, Seong Joon. - Okay.
(Seocho Police Station)
This is the night when the robbery took place.
I think she might be an accomplice.
Shouldn't we identify her first?
But where can we find her?
I've never seen her around here.
Korea has the best sauna.
Let's go.
My necklace.
Excuse me, have you seen my necklace?
(Geum Soo Bathhouse)
My goodness.
Where's my necklace then?
- Who are you? - You were a woman?
Yes, I am a woman. So what?
What are you doing in my construction site?
What am I going to do? I'm going to die.
I don't want to go back there.
I don't want to see that mean guy.
Is the construction finished?
Mr. Lee, what should we do? It costs about 30,000 dollars.
This is breaking my heart.
We have to catch the thief.
They'll check another security camera tomorrow. Let's wait.
Thank you for your work. You can go now.
- Yes, sir. I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
Where did I sleep that night?
I slept right here.
Where is my necklace?
Did someone take it?
(Prohibit Approach)
Who is it?
Is anyone here?
Who is there?
What is it?
What is this?
Is this how I put them on?
How to put them on?
I bought them from Italy myself.
I'm sorry, Grandma. I shouldn't have brought your toiletries.
What is this for?
Stop going through it, you pervert. It's just a woman's toiletries.
Gosh, I don't know whose it is.
That was close.
We meet again.
Why do you keep coming here?
What's the reason?
Anyway, it's good to see you. I was looking for you.
Let's go to the police office.
Wait. Gosh. Hey!
Wait. Why are you running away?
Stop.
My gosh.
I said stop.
Don't follow me.
Hey!
I'm sure I've seen him somewhere.
I can't remember where.
Is he gone?
Why is he taking that with him?
He can't do that.
You can't just go.
Pay your tab from three years ago.
You took 2 boxes of soju, and 1 box of beer. Pay for them.
Ma'am. I'll pay you later.
- When? - I'll call you.
What are you talking about? Hey! Jeong Eun!
Does he live across the street?
Oh, my gosh.
You ran away?
You're so done if I catch you.
Why on earth would he take it home?
And I didn't do anything wrong.
Why do I keep running away from him?
If Grandma finds out, I'll be dead.
How can I take the toiletries back?
Hold on.
Is he a pervert or what?
How are you, Jason?
Not too bad. How about you?
I'm just monitoring today's trade performance.
Yes. The Dow Jones Industrial Average Index rose by 0.61 percent.
And, like you said, the energy sector rose by four percent.
You also need to pay attention to the Federal Reserve...
officials' speech next week.
They will probably...
enact a reduction in the national budget.
Will do.
When are you coming back?
There's not much to worry about since the market is on the rise.
But please don't leave Golden Street vacant for too long.
I won't.
Please handle everything until I get back.
No worries. I won't let you down.
What are you doing, Mom? Let's eat.
Hold on.
You are in-laws. You should greet each other.
Gosh. They can do it after the meal.
They're in-laws. It's not polite.
They should greet each other before eat.
My goodness.
Now...
You're two grown man and woman. I know it's uncomfortable...
and inconvenient for you to live in the same house.
But think of this as a special bond you share,
and try to be nice and considerate to each other...
and get along.
There isn't anything you can do about this.
You must live together. Do you understand?
If you do, stand up straight,
and bow to each other to show your respect.
I said bow, Seong Joon.
Make a deep bow to Dong Hui politely.
Okay.
How about you, Dong Hui?
They look so great. They have both grown to fine man and woman.
Mrs. Oh. This is my youngest grandson.
Isn't he handsome?
Yes. He is.
Gosh. You've raised Dong Hui to a very graceful...
and cute woman.
She's nothing like you.
You have a round and flattish face and broad shoulders.
You look like a man. You said you were frustrated...
because you can't easily find clothes that fit you.
That's what you said to me. But your granddaughter is...
so pretty. Gosh.
- Oh, my. - Grandmother.
- Yes? - You should eat now. Please come.
Shall we?
What is today's dinner?
- Since my grandma is here, - Yes.
I made bulgogi and spicy marinated crab.
Really? I love spicy marinated crab.
Gosh, this is upsetting.
Aunt. Give me food. Isn't it time for dinner?
Give me food, Aunt.
What?
Why are so many people here?
- You're back. - Jeong Eun.
Let me see. One, two, three, four, five,
- six, seven, eight... - Don't mind her. I'll handle it.
Hey. Follow me.
Mom. You should just introduce her to everyone.
There's no need. She's just a pedlar. Come here.
Grandma. Did you call me a pedlar? Grandma.
Gosh, it hurts!
If your in-laws moved in, you should introduce me to them.
How can you be so harsh?
Forget about it and go back to your house.
Jeong Ae is on edge right now because so many people moved in.
You shouldn't walk around in front of her.
Just pack your things and go home.
No. Mom doesn't like me.
What about us? We don't like you, either.
Grandma!
Look. This house is full.
My grandsons' family and even Seong Hoon's...
in-laws moved in.
We have no more place for you to stay.
You won't fit, okay?
What did you say?
I can't believe what you just said.
Why do you keep interrupting me while I'm performing something?
I don't care what you do. Just take your daughter!
She has nothing to do with me. She's not my daughter.
I can't believe they left me out.
Even Hye Joo's grandmother is here, and it's an utter chaos now.
- Hye Joo... - Anyway, she's not my daughter.
Please tell that wench who returned after three years...
that there's no room for her here, so she has to stay there.
What?
Hey, Ae Ri!
What? Is that really true?
It is.
When I heard about that, I thought it was a lie.
Honey.
I know he's so square and naive,
but how could he believe that they could raise penguins here?
My goodness.
This really drives me crazy. What's gotten into his head?
- That's what. - So, is Hye Joo's grandmother...
staying in this building?
Yes, she is.
My brother must have gone out of mind.
- The water is hot, right? - Yes.
Are you happy?
I am.
Good for you. That's enough.
Come and sleep.
Okay.
Moong Chi.
Good night.
Hello.
Is it a Taiwanese version or a Korean version?
Let's go for the Taiwanese one first.
Did you return home safely that day?
Yes.
Did anything happen on your way?
Not at all, thanks to you.
What happened to your brother?
- I don't know. - I knew you wouldn't.
It's nice to see you, anyway.
Why are you glad to meet?
It's a Korean version.
I never knew you'd be Seong Hoon's brother.
Me either. I never thought we'd be related in this way.
If we had knew, we would have bowed to each other in Taiwan.
Anyway, welcome to our house.
I hope you'll feel comfortable here. Goodnight, then.
Right. Thank you for returning my backpack.
Well...
Please wait a minute. I have something to tell you...
I don't want to brush my teeth
I don't want to wash my face
I don't even want to take the sleep out of my eyes
I won't take a shower
Let me secretly
tell you my secret
I didn't take a shower yesterday either
I will sing
I rather spend the time singing
I can sing all day long
And it's still not enough
I don't want to brush my teeth
- I don't want to wash my face - Hello.
Hello. I heard you are the new in-law who moved in yesterday.
- I hope we can get along well. - It's nice to meet you.
There's no room for me to stay here because of you,
but please don't get scared when I dart in and out of places.
Also, do not tell my grandma on me.
Let's get along and help each other out, okay?
I'm Han Jeong Eun. I'm 30 years old.
My grandma calls me a spinster,
but I'm still young at heart. What about you?
I'm Oh Dong Hui. I'm a 26-year-old girl.
Girl? That's really a cute way of introducing oneself.
- How cute. - Thank you.
Anyway, where are you going at this early hour?
I have a part time job.
I also need money. Should follow you there?
Well. It's my first day, too.
Then, please tell me...
if they pay you a lot and assign an easy task, okay?
Okay, I will.
Goodbye, Dong Hui.
See you.
Gosh.
I don't want to brush my teeth
I don't want to wash my face
I don't even want to take the sleep out of my eyes
Grandma, I'm here. I guess Dong Hui went out.
That's right. She left early in the morning.
Why are you here?
To ask you if you slept well last night. Wasn't it cold in here?
- Go downstairs now. - Why?
Your parents-in-law won't like this.
We can take care of ourselves,
- so don't come up here. - Still...
I said go downstairs.
- Father. - What is it?
How is Mother now?
Just leave. Go now.
What's wrong, Father?
Just go out.
All your energies are...
focused on inside your body and mind.
Now you have...
delta brainwaves.
You'll now hand over the control over your life...
to yourself.
I admit...
that there's nothing wrong in my life.
I love myself.
Therefore, I sincerely love my life.
He gives me a headache.
The morning hours are the most important.
If you feel sleepy, eat the medicine I gave you and drink some coffee.
- I will. - You have a gym class today, right?
- Yes. - Do not run.
Or you'll get too tired to concentrate in the afternoon.
Tell the teacher that you sprained your leg and read books, okay?
Okay.
You can go now.
How can you not even say bye to your mom?
I will pick you up at night. Meet me where I always wait for you.
Okay?
Hey. Hey.
- Aunt. - Aren't you going to school?
Are we already at the school?
"Are we already at the school?"
We got here a long time ago!
I see.
I will go in now. Bye, Aunt.
Why do you say bye to me?
Am I your mom?
What on earth does your mom do every morning?
She doesn't fix breakfast and she doesn't give you a ride, too.
I am not sure.
My mom is always busy.
She's rarely cooked us breakfast.
I will see you at home later in the evening.
Thank you for breakfast this morning!
I can't believe it.
Both the mother and the child are so thick-faced.
Excuse me.
Are you Chang Soo's mother?
- Pardon me? - You are, aren't you?
No, I am not Chang Soo's mother.
You are Chang Soo's mother. Why are you hiding it?
What's wrong with you? I am not Chang Soo's mother!
Stop lying! I saw him saying bye to you! How dare you lie?
I am going to settle things regarding Chang Soo.
Look! By yesterday, Chang Soo had...
356.75-dollar worth of bread.
Settle this amount, Mrs. Han.
Hurry up and pay me!
Okay.
Daddy will take you to the preschool today.
- Okay. - You're a good girl.
I am so happy that you're home, Dad.
- Really? - Yes.
- Should I stay home all the time? - Yes.
Uncle.
Hello.
Ah In, go down and get your backpack.
- Please bring daddy a shirt, too. - Okay.
Are you going to work now?
Yes.
Well. Have a nice day.
By the way.
- What? - Seong Hoon.
Why do you dress like that?
Why?
What's wrong with it? I'm at home.
Seong Hoon.
Is that something to be proud of?
- What did you say? - I've been wanting to...
say this since last night, but I've been stopping myself.
You should not have left your job.
Why did you start a business and get your in-laws bankrupt?
Why did you have to make your grandmother-in-law come here?
- Seong Sik. - Don't you...
feel bad for mom?
Mom is making a huge fuss and getting all stressed out...
because we all moved in.
How can you bring your grandmother-in-law here?
We literally live below each other.
Your grandmother-in-law is at the very top. Then there's granny.
Below her is me, and below us is you and your family!
Mom is not a layered cake.
How torturing would it be for her?
And now we have mentioned it. So let me tell you this.
Not everybody can run a business.
You're not meant to be a business man.
You should have been thankful for your payment and stick to your job.
You can't possibly run a business.
What? What did you just say?
Be thankful for your payment and stick to your job?
Honey.
Go hiking with me.
I will go and buy you what you like. So come with me, please?
Staying home will just stress you out even more.
Your first son got into a car accident on the way to work.
We need money to operate on him.
My son...
is out of work.
Anyway, we need money to operate on him.
My son...
is home right now.
Yes, you idiot.
I got tired of my tiny wage,
so I wanted to run a business. After that,
I wanted to earn a lot of money and make my family happy.
Also, I wanted to be a good son. What's wrong with this?
That is the problem.
The men in their 40s get so excited by the idea of running a business.
But they end up destroying everything including their family.
Do you think nobody is asking me to start a business?
They said that my status as a lawyer and...
a political commentator are good enough for a business.
Someone even asked me to start an entertainment agency.
And another person said he would start a management firm just for me.
Do you know how many offers I got?
But I refused everything on the spot. Why?
I refused because a silkworm needs to eat only mulberry leaves.
Seong Hoon, this is just unbelievable.
How can you bring your in-law here?
- How can you be so shameless? - What? Shameless?
Are you done?
- How dare you say that to me? - Daddy.
Never mind. Let's stop.
Let's talk later.
Let's go, Ah In.
Bye. Don't be so emotional.
Try to be rational. Seong Hoon!
And what are you doing in the middle of our place?
Do something about your chest!
Gosh!
Oh my goodness.
That's it. Smile a little brighter. One, two!
That's it. One, two.
Stand together.
That's it. Here we go. One, two.
That's it. Can you go behind her and hug her?
- That expression is good. One, two. - Wait!
- Let's take some break! - Let's take a break.
What's wrong? It was going well.
It was going well?
You're shooting a film!
I told you to come up with a storyboard for a commercial,
and you came up with an art.
- It's useless! - What are you doing right now?
I came here to help because you asked for cooperation.
You should be help then.
What is this? You all read it, right?
Yes.
"A man and a woman run into each other during night hiking."
"What will happen to them? Will they fall in love?"
I told you to sell the product, not to write a TV drama!
Is it a horror story?
It's scary to run into people when you're up the mountain.
They'd never fall in love!
What? A horror story?
You said even a commercial needs a story and...
asked the marketing team and the contents team for cooperation.
That's why we've been working all night until now even it's not ours.
I even brought our writer. You should be thankful to us.
We're busy working on the next drama series.
This is why every drama you make fails.
- What did you say? - Mr. Park!
What's going on?
You're here.
He's making a huge fuss because he doesn't like our storyboard.
Mr. Park, I heard you prepared this for three months.
The final confirmation was done a month ago.
It's not something you can quit simply because you don't like it.
He should think about how to sell the products.
He keeps approaching it as if it was a drama series.
Then don't order me around.
Is the Contents Team the secretary of the Marketing Team?
You always make us work for you!
Then you shouldn't waste all the money we make!
When we earn money, you waste them on dramas.
You're like a parasite feeding upon human.
What? A parasite?
The nuclear reactor is exploding today!
Mr. Park.
What's going on?
You're here, ma'am.
Why are you arguing?
We're shooting a commercial, and the drama team isn't helping.
So I was scolding them.
I don't think it's up to the Marketing Team leader...
to discuss whether or not if they help our company.
I wasn't discussing it.
We work so hard to earn money,
and they always spend money saying they are doing some arts.
It happens to the latest drama series, too.
They got tricked by a coordinator in Shanghai...
and lost 200,000 dollars, didn't they?
So I was trying to talk around and...
address it symbolically.
From the start, that business was considered as an investment.
Please be more patient for the Contents Team, Mr. Park.
Of course. I will.
I will wait.
Can't you be friendly to each other now?
Mr. Park, the team leader of Marketing Team...
must stop being so annoying like his name.
He might hear us.
Conflict exists in any organization.
You should solve the conflict wisely.
How can you fight every time you meet?
He always talks about money whenever he sees us.
People must think he's the director of Contents Marking Team.
He's using his age and experience...
to look down on our team.
He's right. He's so annoying.
Let's stop.
Like what Ms. Bang said, conflict exists in any organization.
But it should arise for the growth of the organization.
Let's not get your emotions involved.
That's why he should fix his personality.
Or he should change his name.
Right, Director Han, you said you didn't get to meet...
the sister of Seo Cheol Min again, right?
Yes.
Seo Cheol Min's younger sibling was a sister?
Yes. Didn't you know?
Then you have his grandmother's phone number, right?
Let me have it, please. I'll call her and catch her.
That's how no one can pick on you for spending company's money.
Please give it to me.
I don't have it.
I lost all of my contacts in my phone.
Director Han.
How? How did that happen?
I don't know what to do now. I think I'm going crazy.
Isn't he home? Why isn't he answering?
I have to find my toiletries today.
Jeong Eun
Detective.
I missed you.
Did you?
When did you come back?
I came back a few days ago. Isn't that good?
Yes, It is.
It's been so long.
I know. Since I haven't seen you for so long,
do you want to have lunch with me?
Jeong Eun, isn't it nice to ride the car without being drunk?
Yes, it is.
Detective, where are we going?
Here you go.
What is this?
Eat it and cooperate with us.
You really caught her, sir.
How can you not recognize Jeong Eun?
- Detective. - Okay.
The soup's getting cold.
Hello.
What is this?
So...
you reported me, right?
Is this how you treat me because I slept in your construction site?
Besides, I didn't even sleep there. You kicked me out.
You just didn't sleep there.
Did you forget already?
My forehead.
The wound won't be healed for four weeks.
Do you want to cooperate or settle this?
What do you mean? I have no money.
Besides, why do you keep coming back to my site?
And why do you run away?
Do you feel guilty?
I don't feel guilty. I went to look for my necklace.
By the way, why did you take my toiletries?
Don't lie to me. What did you do to my toiletries last night?
Did you touch my things? Did you use my towel or not?
Are you a pervert?
Jeong Eun, do you want Tangsuyuk?
Add in fried dumplings.
Tangsuyuk and fried dumplings, please.
Here you go.
So...
you want to know if I remember this guy's face?
This is the guy you faced before you went inside there.
Can you remember his face?
I'm not sure.
- Yes? - Where are you?
I'm in the subway.
- Are you going home? - Yes. Why?
You didn't even say you were going home.
Do you know we didn't even have a meal together since you came back?
I'm sorry. Let's have it this week.
I'm a bit tired. I came to work early in the morning.
Are you sure it's not because of Mr. Park?
I'm sure.
Why aren't you driving the company's car?
I will use from next week.
For now, public transportation will be better.
Okay, then. I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
This is 24-hour gym.
Exercise.
We have classes for pilates and yoga.
This is 24-hour gym.
Excuse me.
Well...
can we talk for a moment?
I'll buy you coffee.
(24-Hour Gym)
Why are you squirming?
You look just like a cabbage worm.
A cabbage worm?
Stop squirming like a worm and get to the point.
What do you want to talk about?
Well,
it's about my brother's debt.
Seo Cheol Min stole 200,000 dollars, right?
Please keep it down. What if someone hears you.
You must feel uncomfortable meeting me as one of your in-laws.
Yes, I am.
Of course.
Why? Were you going to run away?
What? I told you I will pay you back.
But...
Still...
Put yourself in my shoes. Imagine you see...
the person you need to pay 200,000 dollars back every day.
Wherever I look, all I see is the debt I have to pay back.
When I eat, I see the debt. When I say hi, I see the debt.
Hello. Good morning and then I see the debt again.
Think how uncomfortable this must be for me.
Then what do you want me to do?
Should I just stay in my room?
That's not what I meant.
Gosh.
Pleas keep this a secret to my grandmother.
That's what I wanted to ask.
My grandmother swore she would...
never move into her in-law's house, but she moved in because of me.
She couldn't let me sleep in saunas.
But imagine if she finds out that he owes you 200,000 dollars.
That will kill her.
So...
please keep it a secret to my grandmother.
I'm begging you.
Please.
Is begging your specialty?
Don't you have a dream?
A dream?
You looked like you knew what you wanted and had your own aspiration.
Don't you have any goal?
I do, but I'm in a predicament now.
Anyway, are you going to keep it a secret or not?
- You are my in-law. - Then what will you do for me?
- Yes? - Yes, we are in-laws,
but money's a different matter.
What can you do for me in return?
What do you want from me?
What do I need to do?
- What will you make me to do? - I don't know.
I'll think it over tonight.
Will it be hard?
Will it be something embarrassing?
- Something embarrassing? Like what? - I mean...
Things like ringing the door bell and running. Or singing out loud.
That's how you must have played with your brother.
What will you ask me to do?
I can't sleep when I'm curious. Excuse me.
Excuse me?
What will I have to do? I'm not going to make a fool of myself.
What will it be?
Please, are you even listening?
You can't ever be a free rider.
People should feel a sense of honor.
Yes, I know.
- Start sweeping from that side. - Okay.
Let's see.
It's perfect.
I guess you really went to an art school.
I haven't been drawing for a while now,
so this took me some time.
Here.
Gosh. Jeong Eun, you heavy drinker.
She'd be perfect if she doesn't drink that much.
She'd be drunk as a skunk...
and sleep on the bench over there.
I'm saying I'd set you up with a good man if you didn't.
Gosh. This is so detailed.
Are you sure this is how that man looked like?
Don't you know me?
I have a memory of Einstein.
I never forget the things I saw.
Can I go now?
Okay.
Jeong Eun. Let's have a drink sometime.
Take care.
By the way,
can't you just catch him using his license plate number?
Do you remember his license plate number?
Of course. He didn't cover the front license plate.
It's 84 N 785... Something.
What can it be?
Hey. You should have told us about the plate number sooner.
You should have asked me about it first.
You little... She is driving me crazy.
You should have told me that you needed me as a witness sooner.
You impaired my image.
What are you going to do? People in this neighborhood talk a lot.
Didn't you...
build your image by drinking alcohol...
here and there?
You're sharp. You don't miss anything.
It must've hurt very badly.
What are you doing?
By the way,
I've been thinking while looking at your face.
Why do you...
look so familiar?
We've met three times including today. Am I right?
No. I don't mean that.
I saw you somewhere before.
What are you doing?
Have you lived in Iceland?
Maybe in a place where you can see auroras.
I've never even been there.
I suppose. You're a construction manager.
Or maybe you were on a trip to the Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia...
to see the sunset.
There was a guy who approached to a tall lama,
got spat at by it,
and shouted out, "Oh, my gosh!" Aren't you him?
Lamas are animals that look like you, right?
What? I can't believe this guy.
My gosh. I know.
You're the guy who was selling water and mangos...
at the supermarket in Kenya's Tsavo National Park. Am I right?
Please stop.
Were you the guy who smacked my head...
to see the Mona Lisa in the Louvre in Paris?
Why did you hit me? I wanted to kill you.
Where did I see him? Where was it?
Wait for me.
Did you...
repair...
the eaves of palaces in the Forbidden City of China?
You're a construction manager now. It makes sense. It was you.
Wait here. I'll get your toiletries.
Are you the president of Golden Street...
on Wall Street of New York?
Aren't you David Lee who always ate the cucumber sandwich?
Right? It's you.
You always came in around 3am and bought a cucumber sandwich.
You're David Lee, the president of Golden Street,
aren't you?
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
You're rich enough to buy a country. Why are you working here?
Did your business fail?
- What did you say? - You can't do this to us.
Hey. You'd better be more polite to me.
If you get married, it'd be so tiring to your wife.
I'm sure it was Cheol Min's sister.
What is it? Is everything okay?
It's true that she worked at Carnival Sandwich.
Her name, Han Jeong Eun, is also correct.
Do you write drama series?
Why did you go through my stuff without asking?