Wait here. I'll get your toiletries.
Are you...
the president of Golden Street at Wall Street in New York?
Aren't you David Lee who always ate the cucumber sandwich?
You always came in around 3am and bought a cucumber sandwich.
You're David Lee, the president of Golden Street, aren't you?
I remember now.
With my memory, I should be working for NASA.
Don't you...
remember me?
I used to work as a cashier...
at a sandwich shop in front of Golden Street.
I used to serve you all the time.
It was three years ago.
So it was the winter of 2013.
Don't you remember?
(3 years ago in New York)
Welcome to Carnival Sandwich.
I would just get a sandwich and coffee, please.
How would you like your sandwich?
Just cucumbers and mayonnaise.
You always came at 3am and ordered that weird sandwich.
The reason I remember you is...
out of all the vegetables, you only wanted...
cucumbers and mayonnaise.
I thought your taste in food was cheap.
That's why I remember you.
So I told you that the sandwich wasn't nutritious,
and you told me to mind my own business.
You told me to focus on my job. You were so mean. Don't you remember?
Anyway, what a small world.
Come on.
Nice to see you again.
Is that you, Jeong Eun?
Uncle.
Why are you crouching down?
I was just saying hi.
Why would you say hi like that?
Don't you live across my house?
Yes, I do. Hello.
Do you know him, too?
Of course, I do. He moved in across the street.
Is that so?
I met him coincidentally, but it turns out...
Well. I should get going, then.
Take care.
Hey, what about my toiletries and my necklace?
Excuse me.
Hey, give me back mine. You told me that you would.
Hey, you.
What's wrong?
I need to get something from him.
Hey, return my things quickly. What are you doing?
I followed you because you said you would give back. Hey!
- Excuse me. - Jeong Eun.
You'll wake up the whole neighborhood. Maybe he's busy.
You can get your things tomorrow morning.
He's not busy.
I only came here because he said he would give them.
What a jerk. You know that?
Come inside.
Okay.
I need you to check something.
Check if there was a Korean woman named Han Jeong Eun who worked...
at a sandwich shop called Carnival Sandwich in front of Golden Street.
- Her nickname was Golden Cat. - Okay.
Why aren't you sleeping?
It is him.
I asked you why you aren't sleeping.
Please go to sleep. Don't interrupt me when I'm thinking.
You are mumbling. It's scary.
Who in the right mind will marry her?
Okay. Good for you.
I came to visit you and you make me work at your shop at this hour.
What are you going to do if I get robbed?
Don't you think I'm clueless?
I know you gave me this shift so you can spend time with your boyfriend.
Fine. I'll deal with it.
It's only until I save enough money to go to South America.
I'm hanging up now.
Welcome to Carnival Sandwich.
I will just get a sandwich and coffee please.
How would you like your sandwich?
Just cucumbers and mayonnaise.
Okay, but that won't be very healthy.
We offer a variety of other vegetables.
Would you like some?
That's none of your business, is it?
Sorry?
Just sell what the customers ask for.
Just do your job.
By any chance,
are you Korean?
- Excuse me? - Are you from Korea?
No, I'm Chinese.
Happy Halloween.
Freeze. Hands in the air.
Turn around and face the wall.
Okay.
You. Take out everything from the register.
I won't even make it to South America.
What are you mumbling about?
Speak in English.
Okay.
I'm never going to make it to South America.
Hurry up.
- Hurry up. - Okay.
You are here.
What are you doing? Call the police.
Okay.
Excuse me.
You are Korean, aren't you?
- Then why did you lie? - Are you an international student?
No, I am.
Because it's a hassle.
- What? - Bring the sandwich and coffee.
Excuse me.
I'm grateful you caught the robber,
but you are mean. Are you always like this?
Good for you. How can you make me work even if I'm leaving today?
Even though I did get to save up for Brazil, but you are mean.
Anyway, after I'm done delivering this...
I have to go to the airport right away.
So come on time to the shop.
I'm never going to work at your shop ever again.
Did you get that? See you later.
Over here.
- 20 sandwiches? - Yes, that's right.
Do you know who ordered this one?
Can you bring it to the executive's office over there?
Okay. Thank you.
Was he the President of this company?
I would never see him again.
Hey, David.
Why don't you give me my necklace and toiletries back?
You said you would give them back.
Why aren't you keeping your word?
Hey, David. Are you listening to me?
Give them back now!
Give them back!
Gosh, it's so cold. Why would people jog so early in the morning?
I get it. You have a nice body.
Ma'am. You should be preparing breakfast.
I love you.
Gosh, it's freezing.
She should be here by now.
Look who it is.
You're Jang Yoo Ra, the news anchor.
Gosh, I didn't expect to see you here. What a small world!
- Do you live around here? - Yes.
I live in Bangbae-dong. How about you?
I live in Banpo-dong.
My gosh. I can't believe we're neighbors.
I live in a house in Bangbae-dong. It's 150m².
I guess you jog here every morning.
Yes. Do you jog in the morning, too?
Of course. I work out every morning.
Only then I can start my mornings happily.
If I don't,
I won't feel so good.
By the way, what are you doing tonight?
I have a show to host.
That's right. We'll be on the same show tonight.
Why don't we have dinner together afterwards?
I think we were meant to meet here like this.
I'm not sure.
Just have dinner with me.
I know a great restaurant.
How does that sound?
Wait.
Let's have dinner together.
How about watching a movie after that?
Hey, wait.
Slow down.
Why are you running so fast?
I wonder the kids are having a good breakfast.
What?
Why do you care if they're having a good breakfast or not?
I just said it because this soup is delicious.
I just wondered if they made any soup.
I told you not to care about them...
and the food they eat.
How can I not care? We live in the same building.
Even so, we should keep our private life separates from them.
I told you already. If you don't, I won't be able to stand it.
Also,
I have things to say to you, too.
Your brothers moved in with their children.
Is that why you decided to bring your dog in, too?
How could you bring your dog from China? How?
Mom. Moong Chi is a low-maintenance dog.
There're no low-maintenance animals.
It takes a lot of efforts to keep a dog.
When your brothers were young,
they brought a dog, a cat,
and even a pigeon into the house.
I fed the dog, cleaned up the cat's droppings,
and checked if the pigeon's wing had healed or not.
It died eventually, so I buried it in the mountain.
When I was climbing down, it started to rain. It was so hard.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
Take care of your own dog. Okay?
Okay. I will.
You should stop.
That's enough.
You're such a bad-tempered woman.
Go on and eat.
Ah In.
Ah In. It's time to go to preschool.
Why did you make a mess here?
Daddy. Do I look better in this dress, or in this dress?
We don't have time. Just wear what you're wearing.
Now, let's go.
Goodbye, Dad.
Aunt. Please give me another bowl of rice.
Why didn't you eat any of that delicious food?
Do you like my mom's food?
Of course. It's so good.
Your mom's food is the most delicious one in the world.
Then eat it by yourself.
Wait for me.
Why isn't she giving us a ride today?
Do you want her to give us a ride?
Of course. Her car is the most comfortable one.
You should be her son instead. My mom's car makes me sick.
Wait for me, Ji Hoon!
- Gosh. I'm late. - Hye Joo.
- Can I talk to you for a minute? - What?
About what?
By the way,
I didn't realize this before, but your mom is so pretty.
I want to marry someone like her.
She's pretty, good at cooking and driving,
and she makes a beautiful home. Right?
Why does he hate her so much? I like her.
Please prepare breakfast for your children.
Don't you know that Chang Soo eats breakfast here every day?
Did Chang Soo eat breakfast here every day?
Yes. He thinks it's his house. He comes to eat every day.
I know you're living downstairs,
but he should have a sense of shame.
- Hey. - That's not all. He's slow-witted.
I make gestures to stop him from coming, but he doesn't stop eating.
That's why he's gotten so fat.
Look. I'm sorry,
but you should watch your language.
It's not like he got fat because you fed him.
I've been feeding him all along.
Hye Joo. Were you even listening to me?
Also,
here.
What's this?
It's Chang Soo's tab at the school cafeteria.
The clerk thought I was Chang Soo's mother, so I had to pay it instead.
If you had been feeding him well, he wouldn't have eaten...
356.75-dollar worth of bread.
- My gosh. That brat. - Another thing.
Chang Soo listens to music at night.
Doesn't it bother you that he falls asleep...
with the music on? We can hear it from upstairs.
All right.
I hear you. Let's talk about this later.
I'm late for work.
You're not the only busy person. I'm busy, too.
Did you just yell at me?
You think working women are the only busy ones.
Housewives are very busy, too.
Do you know that I couldn't give Ji Hoon a ride...
because I wanted to talk to you?
I said let's talk about this later in the evening.
I'm saying...
you shouldn't act big just because you work.
Please take care of your own children.
What? Act big?
These aren't food. You shouldn't eat them, okay?
You shouldn't bite them or tear them, either.
Just until I get back. Okay?
You're the best dog.
Where did you come from? Where's your mom?
What about your dad?
Where are they?
Hello.
All right. It's time for breakfast. There you go.
I'm going to work. Be a good girl until I get back. Okay?
Is it a girl?
Yes. She's a girl.
I see.
Aren't you going to work today?
I am leaving now.
See you around, then.
(Great Gatsby)
Director Han.
What brings you here at this hour?
Director Bang told me to deliver the car to you...
because you won't drive the company car.
Ta-da!
You drive very well.
You're the best driver.
When I commute using public transportation, I have time to...
read and think. I love that.
You are so old-fashioned.
If you are a man, you need to own a car.
Only then the girls will go "Honey!" and love you.
- Is that right? - Of course.
Right. Director Bang was asking me about signing the webtoon artist.
Was she?
Wait. Please stop the car, Director Han.
She looks like the sister of Seo Cheol Min.
Wait, please stop the car. There is...
Please stop. There's Seo Cheol Min's sister.
Gosh!
Darn it! Did you not see her?
See what?
I'm sure she was Seo Cheol Min's sister.
That's impossible. You said we have a meeting. Let's hurry.
We want to combine the strengths of viral marketing to...
storytelling marketing and come up with our marketing concept.
With a humane story contained in the product,
you will capture the consumers' hearts.
We will build trust so that those consumers will recommend...
the product to the other consumers.
- It's good, Director Han. - Isn't it?
As soon as I heard it, I thought it was a great idea.
The Contents Team will develop the story that will...
touch the hearts of the consumers. Based on that story,
we will plan the marketing events for upcoming fall and winter season.
I love the idea,
but we have to plan and execute events frequently.
We are already short of hands.
You should hire an intern.
If you're short of hands, ask for a new recruit.
Yes, Director Bang.
She's always clear and delightful.
What do you think, Producer Kim?
Producer Kim?
Producer Kim!
Why are you so distracted during the meeting?
I'm sorry.
I am sorry. I am so sorry.
I don't like everyone from the Contents Team.
Wait for me!
I'm sure it was her.
I saw her around Director Han's house.
She was the sister of Seo Cheol Min, who we met in Taiwan.
Perhaps you are mistaken.
No! Gosh.
Anyway, when are you leaving the office today?
Why do you want to know that?
I'm going to go around the area near your house.
That's not necessary, is it?
Never mind that. Producer Kim,
can I speak to you in private?
What? Why would you pay for that?
I was the head of production of that drama.
Also, I had the final say in hiring Cheol Min as the coordinator.
So I will make up for the company's loss with my own money.
I shouldn't let it hassle many people.
That's nonsense.
I feel bad enough that we're getting disciplinary actions and pay cuts.
Why would you take all the blame at the last moment?
I can catch her. I'm sure she was his little sister.
Anyway, I hope you will accept that and stop expanding this problem.
I will tell the legal team, too.
Director Han. Director Han!
Yes, Seong Hoon.
Are you doing well?
Yes, of course.
I called to ask you something.
By any chance, do you know Choi Jin Sung from...
the Company Newsletter Team of LK Group?
Of course I know him. What about him?
Someone introduced me to him. I am going for an interview.
I see. I will find out more about him then.
That would be nice.
By the way, Seong Joon.
What do you think about my grandmother-in-law and...
sister-in-law staying at our place?
Seong Sik is making such a big fuss,
so I wondered if you were okay.
I don't mind it.
Don't worry about me.
Thank you for saying that.
My sister-in-law is...
around your age, so please treat her well.
She's such a nice girl.
Okay. I will do that.
Go back to work then.
- I'll see you later. - Okay.
Seong Joon!
What are you doing? Shall we go on a date?
The chef changed around six months after you left.
The ingredients of japchae and doenjang jjigae changed,
but namool became even better.
Try it.
It's nice.
You're quite difficult, you know?
You like food that requires a lot of work.
When you're married, your wife will be very tired. Right?
I love that you're back.
I wondered when I'd get to eat this with you again, and here we are.
By the way, what did you talk about with Producer Kim?
What?
What did you tell him when you talked to him in private?
It was nothing. It was something personal.
What was that personal thing?
- Mi Joo. - I am his boss.
It will take me three seconds to find out if I call him.
But I want to hear it from you.
What's wrong with you these days? Why did you become so secretive?
I am not secretive. It's just that it's a very personal matter.
So can't I know that personal thing?
I suddenly feel cheap.
Fine. I won't ask more.
But I am getting angry at you.
What's this? You came back a long time ago,
and it took us a long time to dine together.
Don't you think you're too mean?
Am I? I apologize.
But you know that I've been busy.
I know. That's why I'm cutting you slack.
I am just warning you that I can't do that any more.
You know that, right? By the way, what will you do about that girl?
I think the company will take the necessary measures.
Isn't it okay if she pays back?
I don't know about that. She still committed a crime.
You seemed to be bothered with it,
so I ordered the legal team myself.
The legal team will take care of it now.
Just pass the ball to them. Only then people like Mr. Park...
will stop picking on you and slandering you for no reason.
It's bad for your promotion, too.
Never mind. Don't get involved. It's my problem. I'll take care of it.
Seong Joon.
It's a 24-hour gym. Thank you.
It's a 24-hour gym.
Goodness.
What are you doing, Elizabeth?
Let's go eat sujebi. I will treat you to celebrate your moving in.
I'm fishing out pickled cucumbers.
- Goodness! - They should've been fished out.
Now they are all mushy and moldy. How will you eat this now?
Still, it's a shame to waste it. So I'm fishing out good ones.
When did you make these pickled plums?
I did last summer.
My cousin in Gwangyang sent me the plums.
Then you should've take them out in about three months.
Now it's inedible since the toxin soaked out from the seeds.
I took them out for now, so let's boil them tonight.
Please leave them.
If that has gone bad, let's just throw them away.
Let's go out and eat sujebi with me.
You can't just throw them away.
You put money and efforts to make these.
You just need to be a little diligent.
I can't believe that nobody in such a big family takes care of this,
and look how bad it's gone.
My goodness. I am already well aware...
that you served the feast when the Queen of England paid a visit.
There you go again.
- I'm just... - You still have...
the habit of stepping in every business.
When did I do that?
Don't you remember it?
For Seong Hoon and Hye Joo's wedding,
we had to use every means to reserve the famous hotel.
Then, you stepped in all of a sudden...
and cancelled the reservation.
And you earned the sponsorship from Andong Hanok Village.
I still can't believe that you came up with such idea back then.
Anyway, because you decided to hold a traditional wedding,
we had to run here and there to rent buses...
and cancel the new suits to reorder hanbok.
Moreover, Andong is really far from here.
We stopped by three rest stops and got there.
You prepared everything in the same way you did for the Queen...
and gave us a lecture on traditional courtesy.
But we were really exhausted and starving.
You know you went too far, don't you?
I wasn't the only one who went too far.
Your mother-in-law wore a dress like hanbok...
and bobbed around the hall...
only to overturn the table. So we had to delay the wedding...
for two hours to make all the food again.
I imitated Grace Kelly...
only because you imitated Queen Elizabeth.
No one cares what old ladies like us wear.
Pardon me?
Please stop and let's just go have some sujebi.
I'm in the middle of working. I have to finish it.
This is unbelievable.
What a waste. My goodness.
Goodness.
She's full of inferiority complex.
How stubborn.
Ma'am, didn't you say you'll go out for lunch?
I will. Jeong Eun, let's go out to have lunch.
Where's that little girl?
She just said she's going out.
Where did she go?
I saw a gap there. I need you to measure it before you resume.
- Please check the other side, too. - Okay.
And the marble wall must be flawless.
I need you to check...
- if it has any cracks on it. - Okay.
Why haven't you begun the third floor's reinforcement work?
Didn't the subcontractor call you yet?
- I'll contact them right away. - Okay.
Tell them if they don't come here by this afternoon,
- I'll nullify the contract. - I will.
Excuse me.
How could you just walk away like that?
- Is that why you're here? - Yes, that's why I'm here.
It might be nothing to you, but it's really important to me.
You said you'll give it back. Why did you just go home that way?
Come to my place by 7pm, then I'll give you back.
By when?
- By 7pm. - Fine.
You must return it, okay?
Please leave. I'm busy now.
Do you think I'm not busy?
By the way,
what happened to your company?
Just out of curiosity,
did your business fail?
You're rich enough to buy a country. Why are you working here?
I guess it really went bust.
I heard that investment firms undergo ups and downs every day.
Still...
I can't believe you ended up here.
I don't know who you are talking about from last night.
David Lee of Golden Street in New York.
That's not me. You've got the wrong person.
No, it's you. You know I have a great memory.
Didn't the police contact you? They caught the thief, right?
Anyway, we'll talk about it later.
You must give my things back to me tonight, okay?
Yes?
I checked.
It's true that she worked at Carnival Sandwich.
She worked from November of 2013 to February of 2014.
It's her friend's store, and her name is Han Jeong Eun.
I will sing
I rather spend the time singing
Why haven't you been around these days?
No, I haven't. I just skipped few days.
Did you fall ill?
I didn't.
But you don't look well.
What's the matter? What's biting you?
What's wrong with all of you? I'm just fine. I have no worries.
I just skipped few days because I was tired.
Goodness, fine.
I'll buy you lunch for Jeong Ae with such a long face.
- Seriously? - Really?
Yes!
Let's eat pork ribs.
- That sounds great. - What a good idea.
I said I'm totally fine. I don't need pork ribs.
If you feel that bad, you can buy us some coffee, then.
Shall we go to Jeong Ae's house to have some coffee, then?
- Okay. - To my house?
Yes. It's been a while since my last visit.
You can't. My mother-in-law is at home.
Isn't she living on the third floor?
What? Well...
I have to make lunch for my husband.
I saw him go mountaineering earlier today.
Not today, okay?
Let's have lunch later. I'm leaving.
What's with her?
She's so weird.
She is so strange.
Why does she want to buy me lunch out of the blue?
Goodness.
Hey, Jeong Ae!
I know Jeong Eun is back. I need you to pay her tab.
What tab?
She took liquors several times.
Why are you asking me to pay it back?
She's almost like your daughter.
She's not my daughter.
Do you think my house is a shelter for people in need?
Why am I always the one who should take care of everyone?
I have no money. Ask her mom to pay back!
Why on earth is she so mad?
Why does everyone around me annoy me?
Jeong Ae!
Gosh, why...
- Why are you here? - What do you mean?
- We can't have lunch without you. - She's right.
So we brought jokbal to eat together.
You like jokbal, right?
Of course, she does. Let's eat jokbal and drink coffee.
That sounds good. We haven't had lunch for a while.
- Then, let's go in. - Wait. Wait.
Why do you want to come into my house?
That's where we always hang out.
Hold on. Don't you have to go work today?
It's Thursday, my day off.
- There's a part time doctor. - Let's go in.
Wait a second. Gosh.
Let's go inside.
My husband will come home shortly.
We'll leave right after we finish jokbal.
Do not underestimate mountaineering.
You know it takes longer to climb down a mountain.
- Let's go in. - Let's go inside.
- I want coffee first. - Wait here.
I'll boil the water and bring some plates.
Stay there.
Why... Why are you here?
Well...
I ran out of ramyeon and coffee.
Gosh, Reporter Han Seong Hoon.
Hello.
Goodness, you're not working?
I do not usually shop in places like this.
But...
I came to see if you have...
balsamic vinegar and anchovies.
Professor,
we do have neither balsamic vinegar nor anchovies,
but I need you to pay your daughter's tab!
- Excuse me? - You need to pay her tab.
Jeong Eun put a box of soju and beer...
on her tab.
Aren't you Jeong Eun's mother?
- Yes. - I heard she is back.
Did you see my daughter?
I saw her just the other day at the police station.
Again? Was she at the station?
Ring these up please. How much?
Chang Soo.
Aunt.
What are you doing?
Why did you open my refrigerator?
Nothing.
Food poisoning bacteria was found in snacks produced from a conglomerate.
What are your thoughts on this, Mr. Han?
- Long time ago, there were... - What are you eating?
- a lot of junk foods... - I'm eating cheese sticks.
You had dinner already.
I was feeling slightly hungry.
Darn it.
- Mr. Han, please calm down. - Yes, please.
This snack was known to be organic.
The company emphasized it was organic which customers prefer.
Yes, it's true. This is also a problem
Because everyone is making a fuss about organic food lately,
there are people who are trying to take advantage of this.
The best way to approach this problem is...
to farm one's own food on the rooftop just like my grandmother.
We all should farm the food that we'll consume.
This is by far the best way to go.
Anyway, anyone who's playing with food...
will have to face severe punishment. That's my thought.
Thank you for your opinion.
So your grandmother has a farm on her rooftop?
You're welcome to visit.
I don't think so.
In "Today's Current Event", we discussed about...
the reality of junk food.
We'll be back tomorrow with a different topic to discuss.
- This was Jang Yoo Ra. - And Park Bong Seok.
("Today's Current Event")
- Thank you. - Good job, everyone.
- Well done. - Good job.
Hold on, Ms. Jang.
Why don't we have a meal?
I have plans.
Don't be like that.
Why is it so hard to have a meal with you?
Ms. Jang.
Ms. Jang. I'll treat you with something expensive.
Grandpa, when is Mom coming home?
She'll be here soon.
Play with your brother.
Chang Soo, stop eating.
You're going to sleep soon. Why are you still eating?
- This will be the last piece. - Goodness.
What's wrong with you now?
Did something happen today?
Chang Soo. Ah In. I'm home.
Did you eat? I'll cook your dinner.
Today,
they ate dinner at Father's.
So...
I cooked bulgogi for them.
- Why did you do that? - Father...
wanted to feed them dinner. How could I ignore his wish?
I had to drive Ji Hoon to his academy,
but I told him to get a cab.
I cooked bulgogi and japchae, and sent the food upstairs with them.
Hee Sook, did I eat the food?
- Why are you blaming it on me? - Hye Joo.
Can't you come home early?
Because you always come home after dinner,
I have to cook dinner for everyone in this building.
Are you picking a fight with me because I come home late?
Then don't cook dinner for everyone in this building.
How could I when Father is trying to feed them dinner?
How can I pretend not to see what's happening?
If you can't pretend, then remind yourself of your first intention.
My first intention?
You moved in to take care of Father.
Then...
when Father's trying to cook dinner,
how can you not help him and take care of him?
What did you say?
Did you just grab me?
- Are you trying to hurt me? - I said...
I was going to take care of Father.
When did I say I was going to take care of your family?
So what?
Do you want to have a fight then? Fine. Let's go.
Why is it hard to have dinner with her?
What are you doing now?
Why are you screaming in my house?
Honey, what's going on?
Hey, is this your house?
Is it yours?
This house belongs to Father.
You're sly like a fox.
You only moved in a month ago.
How can you say this is your house?
Why don't you go ahead and hit me?
- You started this, not me. - My goodness.
Hye Joo. How could you act this way?
Even though she used to work for you,
you can't treat her the same way as you did before.
- Hey. - My goodness.
How dare you talk down to me?
Hye Joo, don't do this.
Even though he was in junior class at your college,
you can't boss us around.
He is your brother-in-law.
- What are you talking about? - Everyone, be quiet.
What's wrong?
- What happened, honey? - Seong Hoon.
I told you not to wear this.
Be quiet. I'm not on TV.
You can wear your fancy clothes at home all you want.
By the way, why are you here?
I'm stressed out from my show.
Your show is all you talk about.
If you can appear on TV, everyone in Korea can.
Not you.
- You are not on TV. - What did you say?
Look at you. You call yourself as a political commentator,
but all you do is going after the higher authorities.
Gosh.
Goodness.
I'm still on TV.
But you got laid off from your company...
- and I still have a house. - What?
- What did you say? - Honey.
- What did you just say? - What?
I didn't say anything wrong.
Hye Joo, you need to cook for your children.
It's not like I am not cooking for them purposely.
I just had a bad timing.
What's going on?
What?
You should be ashamed of living in your parents' house.
Look who's talking.
You moved in, too.
Please, let's not get into each other's business.
I want to do the same, too.
Do you think this is comfortable for us to live with you?
What did you say?
I'm going to kill them.
Honey.
You shouldn't have belittled me first.
Stop it. Let's stop it here.
Don't you ever talk to me again.
- Right back at you. - What did you say?
What are you doing?
- Mother. - Mother.
- Mom. - Mother.
All of you. Come upstairs.
How old are you all?
Are you the same age as Chang Soo or Ji Hoon?
You are all in your 40s.
If you moved into your parents' house, you should know your place.
How can you fight and make a fuss?
I'm so embarrassed by you all. I can't lift my head up around...
- in this neighborhood. - Mom.
Hye Joo hit me.
Why did you hit my son?
Well,
I didn't hit him.
What?
Hye Joo.
- You hit me like this a while ago. - Be quiet.
I'm sorry, Mom.
We had a little disagreement of opinions,
but we will resolve it within today.
Please don't worry.
Don't...
say a word.
My heart broke today...
because of you.
Seong Hoon. Did something happen?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me, Mother.
Actually, since we're living in the same house,
it's hard to separate our private life.
- Your private life? - Yes.
That's right. It's good that you brought that up.
I actually wanted to talk to you about it.
You've already moved in.
There's nothing we can do about it.
But from now on, we should...
keep our private life separate.
- Pardon? - You should...
pay rent.
What?
- Mom. - Mother.
It's not just rent. Pay for the electric bill, too.
- Mom. - The water bill, gas bill,
and even the sewer bill, too.
How could you move in to leech off of your old parents,
and live without paying us any money?
Who took two onions from my fridge earlier?
Mother. That's...
I wanted to make Father bulgogi.
Put two onions back in my fridge.
Mother. I used them to cook Father...
He's your father-in-law, not mine.
Also, you moved in on the 30th.
I'll be collecting rent.
Mom... Mom.
No. Mom, no.
You can't do that. Please don't do that.
Mom. You can't do this to us!
Mom! I can never do that! Never!
This is absurd!
- What are you doing? Mom! - Mother.
- Mother. That may be too much. - Mom.
I can't do that!
Do whatever you want to do. I just can't!
Mom!
He told me to come. Why isn't he answering?
I found it.
- Are you sure? - I'm sure this time.
How long is he going to keep me waiting?
Isn't he home?
Let's calm down.
Calm down.
Hey! Where are you going?
Give me my necklace and toiletries! Where are you going?
We're here.
You look tired. Go inside and get some rest.
What is it, Mi Joo?
Don't you know what's wrong?
How could you do this?
I thought you'd be different once you come back to Korea.
How long should I wait?
You came back from Shanghai, but you haven't changed at all.
- Mi Joo. - We've been dating for five years.
It was 3 years before you went to Shanghai, and 2 years after.
We didn't exactly say that we were in a relationship,
but we spent time together while working.
That made us share a special relationship.
Above all,
you must've known about my feelings during all those times.
It's been frustrating and upsetting,
but the reason why I could bear it was...
because you never pushed me aside.
We had meals, drank tea,
watched movies, and went skiing.
When I went to Shanghai, you always escorted me.
- Mi Joo. - Why did you push me aside today?
When we were talking about Cheol Min's sister,
you said things like, "Never mind", "It's my problem", and all.
What did you mean by that?
I'm sorry,
but that's not what I meant.
Let's get married.
I can't stand this any more.
I gave out all the flyers.
Then why would they be inside the trash can near the subway station?
Because of people like you,
I can't trust anyone with the flyers. Do you know that?
No, Sir. I really gave out all of them.
Please believe me.
Some people take it and just put it in the trash,
but you can't blame me for that.
How should I know...
if you really gave them out, or just killed time...
and shoved them in the trash?
No. I didn't do that.
Please believe me.
I stood for six straight hours to give out those flyers.
Please give me 30 dollars for my daily wage. Please.
Hey. My goodness. If you think this is so unfair...
Here. Take this and go. Okay?
Don't ever show your face around here. Do you understand?
My gosh.
How was your day, Moong Chi?
I missed you, too.
(The Test of Love)
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. I just came to see Moong Chi, and I saw the books.
Weren't you drying them in the sun?
I thought they would get soaked from the night dew.
Forget it. I'll take care of them. Please go down.
You're late.
Yes.
Did you cry?
No.
Goodnight, then.
Do you write...
drama series?
Why did you go through my stuff without asking?
Thank you for cleaning up the books,
but you shouldn't look into others' belongings.
Maybe you think you can walk all over me...
because I have to pay you back what my brother owes you.
But I still try not to ask anyone for favors.
I work hard to live my life the best way I can.
What is it? Is everything okay?
Everything is fine.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to pry.
I was just cleaning up.
Forget it.
Take this.
What is this?
I got paid from the gas station.
I could've given you more, but this is all I can give you today.
Take it.
It's 300 dollars.
So deduct 300 dollars from 200,000 dollars.
Then I have to pay you 199,700 dollars more.
Goodnight then.
It's a Korean lunch buffet.
You can have a Korean lunch buffet for only 6.90 dollars.
If you come after 2pm, you get a cup of delicious coffee, too.
It's a different menu every day, and there are over 20 dishes.
It's a cheap and delicious Korean buffet.
It's a Korean lunch buffet.
It's a different menu every day, and there are...
- over 20 dishes. - Is it only 6.90 dollars?
Yes, that's right.
We know each other, don't we?
Hello.
Hurry inside.
Wait. I am going inside.
Why do you keep pushing me?
When did I push you?
It's because you were walking too slowly.
(Lunch Korean buffet for only 6.90 dollars)
Director Han, I caught Seo Cheol Min's sister. Ta-da!
Aren't I talented?
Seo Cheol Min's sister?
Let's start the meeting.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I don't know how to pay back that money.
What kind of a brother tortures his family like this?
Don't touch it! I went on a trip to meet Dad.
That's why I wondered around the world!
She's the senior I like and admire the most.
That's how Seong Hoon and Hye Joo ended up getting married.
Can you ride a motorcycle?
We've been friends since three years ago in New York.
Why are you here? What are you doing here?