Sir, these are the final 10 pieces for the new writer prize.
Are there any good ones?
Well. Why don't you read them yourself?
Where is Producer Kim?
I'm not sure where he is.
(The Portrait of Family)
Hurry inside.
Wait. I am going inside.
- Hurry. - Why do you keep pushing me?
When did I push you?
It's because you are walking too slowly.
Director Han, I caught Seo Cheol Min's sister!
Aren't I talented?
Seo Cheol Min's sister?
Let's start the meeting.
- What's happening? - Director Bang.
Director Bang, I caught Seo Cheol Min's sister at last.
Look. She's right here.
So you mean she is the sister of Seo Cheol Min who...
ran away with our money?
That's exactly right.
Producer Kim, you did something amazing this time.
Don't mention it. I did it out of love for my company.
What happened?
- It's a long story. - How long?
Mi Joo.
Didn't she bring your backpack from Taiwan...
before you came back to Korea?
- That's right. - Then let me get this straight.
Out of the blue, a woman came to return your bag.
She said you two met in Taiwan.
She lost her passport and you helped her to issue a new one.
Let's just say it's possible because you are nice...
to everyone.
But did you know...
she was Seo Cheol Min's sister or not?
What is your name, Miss?
My name is Oh Dong Hui.
Is it? Okay. Ms. Oh.
You are in a serious predicament.
Because your brother ran away with our money,
our company faced a great loss.
That brings me to my next question.
Where is your brother?
I don't know.
- She doesn't know. - I mean...
you must keep in touch with your brother.
I haven't heard from him.
Excuse me.
Your brother disappeared with 200,000 dollars.
How can you be so irresponsible?
You haven't heard from him? Is that all you're going to say?
Do you want to go to jail?
But why is your last name Oh?
Hey, do you think that's important at this moment?
She doesn't know where her brother is.
If they are siblings, she should be Seo Dong Hui. Don't you think so?
But why is her last name Oh?
Why is that so?
Why can't you say anything?
- I'll tell you later. - Why can't you tell me now?
It's complicated.
Are you going to stay silent?
Look. It's right. Her name is Oh Dong Hui.
You got the wrong person. Come on.
No, it can't be. I'm sure it's her.
In Taiwan, you were Seo Cheol Min's sister.
How is this possible?
He is my brother.
He is my second cousin,
but we grew up together.
So he's like my real brother.
Then you should have told me from the beginning.
Isn't it hard to ask her to take legal responsibility?
She's not the thief and she's his second cousin.
Your name was Dong Hui, right?
Do you have other immediate family members?
I don't think you have to be here for this.
Ms. Hong, how can you say such thing?
Producer Kim, you're hopeless, too.
We aren't loan sharks.
How can we ask her to be responsible when she had nothing to do with it?
That's exactly my point.
We shouldn't expect too much from him.
How can you say that?
Producer Kim, send her home.
- Excuse me? - Get her information. Let her go.
What's wrong with you, Director Bang?
I told you that we won't be handling this matter.
I told you let the legal department to take care of it.
You must not try to solve the problem personally.
I won't accept it.
I'm not trying to solve it personally. I just...
It is neither my nor Director Han's problem.
It's the legal department's problem.
As a matter of fact, it turns out that she's not his real sister.
She's his second cousin.
What Producer Kim did was pointless.
Don't make a fuss and let her go.
Watch it. Goodness.
Perhaps, my job has something to do with it. How can I let her go...
due to a misunderstanding? It's like a drama.
A second cousin? She can't take responsibility legally?
If you live under the same roof, that makes you family.
Excuse me.
Don't think I'll back down and give up.
They might let you go because they are soft, but I assure you I'm not.
I'll chase you to the end of the world.
I'll make sure I get...
the money your cousin robbed.
Wait.
Doesn't he have a grandmother?
Give her number.
- Excuse me? - Give me his grandmother's number.
Have this.
When it's all melted, my class will be over.
Okay.
Sang Woo.
Don't go anywhere. Stay here.
- Did you get that? - Yes.
Welcome.
How can I help you?
I'm looking for someone.
Who is it?
I'm from Seoul.
Okay. Please come this way.
Is it him?
No, he's my youngest son.
I see.
Until when did you raise him?
I raised him for about a year.
I had a flower shop in Bangbae-dong 33 years ago.
On a rainy day, a boy was...
crying in front of my shop.
I asked him why he was crying.
He said he was lost and he was sobbing.
So I took him to my house and raised him.
But someone must have filed a report.
Back then,
I wasn't well off to legally adopt him.
So the police took him away.
Where did he go?
He was sent to an orphanage located in Gwangju, Gyeonggi Province.
I had affection for him since I raised him,
so I visited him every month.
When did you last visit him?
It's been a long time.
He turned 20 when I last saw him.
Right. He worked here for a while.
Do you have a photo of him?
Of course, it must be inside the house. Please wait here.
- Mr. Kim. - Yes?
I told you not to stack materials up in the passage. Clear the area.
No, leave the electrical cords.
- Electrical team will handle them. - Okay.
Mr. Park,
there's no handrail up there. Be careful when you install elevators.
- Yes, Sir. - Good.
Gosh, why do they never put handrails there?
Hello, Sir.
You know me, don't you?
Goodness.
I'm the good neighbor who helped you catch the thief.
So what does he have to give you back?
My toiletries and my precious necklace...
are in Mr. Lee's house.
- A necklace? - Yes.
It's the most valuable thing to me, so I need to get it back right away.
But he doesn't seem to have any intention to give back.
I'm sure he's a pervert.
Still, I'm not sure if he'll be okay with this.
Sorry?
We've been friends since three years ago in New York.
- Friends? - Yes.
- Please go in. - Okay.
Mr. Lee really hates to let people in his place.
I came here just to get the specifications,
but if he finds out about you, he might get really angry.
I'm the one who must be really angry.
He said he'd give them back.
Anyway, hurry up. We should leave soon.
I have this one. Let me see.
The window...
Goodness.
Where on earth did he keep them?
Wait. Did he install the locks on both sides?
He is really weird.
What is this?
It's Bangbae-dong's model village.
Sure, he manages construction sites.
Well, let me see.
This is Mina supermarket,
and this is the sauna.
This where Mr. Jung's lives,
and this is Yoon Jae's house.
I found Ms. Yoon's hospital here.
Our house is right at the center of the town.
It's such a lovely neighborhood.
If found it.
Why did he keep these in such place?
Do you mean this door knob?
We can't fix this.
A skilled technician must be here.
Listen up. The security system doesn't operate because of this.
It's a wealthy town, so it must be fixed right away!
Gosh, hold on.
Miss! Did you find yours?
Yes, I found one.
Where did he put my necklace?
Where is he now?
Well,
he died from a car accident when he was 21.
He went to Seoul to find a new job...
and got into a car accident.
What's wrong? Are you all right?
What is this?
It is really old. Isn't this someone else's as well?
(Seongsu Corporation)
Isn't Seongsu Coporation the company...
where my uncle used to work at?
Did he also work there?
- Goodness. - Is he okay?
- Please wake up. - Please let us take the patient.
- Will he be all right? - Mr. Park.
- Gosh. - What happened to him?
What? Mr. Park fell from the building?
I told him to be careful!
Did you call 911?
Miss, close the door when you leave,
okay?
Sorry?
Wait for me, Sir!
What's this?
Is it locked?
Sir, please let me out.
Sir!
Gosh, am I locked in?
What should I do?
I'm sorry tell you the bad news.
Please don't be. It's okay.
Thank you for letting me know...
what happened to him.
Are you his older brother?
I think I am.
Why isn't your sister with you here?
He talked about his sister...
very often.
He said his sister raised him as their mother left them.
I think I'm in the wrong place.
Pardon?
There were only two of us.
We had no one else except ourselves.
We only had each other...
in the world.
Okay.
I see.
Please take it.
Although he's not my brother,
let me repay your kindness...
to take care of the poor boy for over 10 years.
Please stay healthy.
Please wait. Wait a minute!
Goodness.
How did it go?
We were 100 percent confident when we found him.
He also lived in Bangbae-dong.
You're fired.
My brother isn't dead.
I fired him. He's a conman.
He found someone who's dead.
Don't let him work in that field again.
Mother, I am back!
Why are you here?
What do you mean?
I thought you'd feel lonesome, so I came to see you.
And to bring you some onions.
Then, put them in the kitchen and leave.
Okay.
Mother,
I'd also like to make you lunch.
I bought your favorite small octopus.
I was too busy moving in and taking care of Ji Hoon.
I think I haven't been a good daughter-in-law for a while.
It won't take long. I will cook a delicious octopus stir-fry.
Let's eat lunch together.
What's gotten into her?
Mother, your lunch is ready.
It's amazing.
Please take your seat. I cooked the stir-fry and bean sprouts soup.
Come on. Sit.
You should eat the stir-fry when it's still hot.
I never expected this.
I'll eat it since you cooked it.
How is it?
It's good.
By the way, the octopus must've been expensive. How much was it?
Goodness, Mother. It didn't break my bank.
Don't worry about it.
I will cook it more often.
Come on. Eat before it gets cold.
Goodness.
The octopus is very soft and delicious.
Right, Mother? Eat a lot.
Do you not like bean sprouts soup?
- No, I am going to eat it later. - Right!
You hate bean sprouts soup.
I forgot.
- No, I don't hate it. - Don't say that.
Because Father drank every day,
you cooked bean sprouts so many times.
You said you even hate the smell of bean sprouts.
It must have been so tough for you.
I'm sorry. It was so tactless of me to say it.
Right!
I heard Seong Sik always came home drunk...
when he was in college.
Don't even bring that up. Your father-in-law couldn't even...
compare to him. Whenever I think about how much he used to drink...
I know! He troubled you by getting involved...
in student movements, other activities, and all.
It must have been so tough for you.
But still,
thanks to that, Seong Hoon and Hye Joo got married.
If you think about that, it wasn't that bad after all.
Right, Mother?
Come in.
Come in. Come in.
Mom.
This is my friend Yeong Cheol.
- Say hello. She's my mom. - Hello.
And she is...
the woman I like and admire the most.
She's Hye Joo.
Hello, Mother.
My name is Seo Hye Joo.
Seong Sik drank too much,
so we thought we'd take him home.
Mom, we still have the wine you made, right?
Please let us drink just one bottle of it.
Come in, guys. Come this way.
Come on. Please follow me.
Come on, Hye Joo.
I will pay for everything today! Just keep drinking!
Goodness.
Mom.
Why do you always cook bean sprouts soup?
- Seong Sik drank a lot yesterday. - That's got nothing to do with me.
Then you should have cooked another soup for me.
You know I hate bean sprouts soup with green onions.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I forgot to skip the green onions.
Next time, I will cook another soup for you.
And...
how many times did I tell you that bracken is bad for men?
No, it's not.
I heard it's got nothing bad for men.
Mom!
I entered Jin Seong Ilbo at the top of my batch.
How can you not trust what your journalist son is saying?
Okay. Fine.
I won't cook the bracken again.
- Cook me a fried egg. - Okay.
Hey. Hye Joo?
Hello?
You should wake up now.
Excuse me?
Girl. You should go home.
You have to get married.
You can't sleep here like this.
Wake up now.
You will have to marry a man one day.
You know?
Hello.
Come.
Take a seat. You should eat before you leave.
Okay. I'm sorry.
Here you go.
It's hot. Here.
Thank you.
Goodness! I'm sorry, Mother.
I must have reminded you of the bad memories.
No, you didn't. Let's eat.
Get that!
This is why you need to have a good past.
Watch me.
I am going to make sure...
to kick you out of this house.
Your qualifications are more than enough,
but unfortunately, we can't hire you this time.
Can you ride a motorcycle?
Yes, of course I can.
- Are you all right? - I'm okay.
Is my motorcycle okay? Darn it.
Goodness.
Mother, I'm home.
What are you up to, Mother?
What do you care?
What is it?
I just came to say hi.
We live together. Why would you say hi?
But still, I came home from work.
And also...
I got the sugar donuts you like. Do you want to have some?
No, thanks. I don't want any.
Don't refuse it.
Just try one.
This is from a stall in front of my office,
and it's really good. I said I don't want it!
Did something happen to you today?
Nothing happened.
Then what's wrong?
Do you hate me that much?
Yes, I do.
I hate you. How did an alcoholic protestor...
become my first daughter-in-law?
I hated you since the first time you came to my house.
Why would you bring up the past out of the blue?
I don't get it.
What's gotten into her?
Mother.
I'll put this in the kitchen. Eat this when your hatred...
towards me goes away a little.
Okay?
It's bean sprouts soup.
What's this smell?
I recognize this perfume scent.
Kang Hee Sook you wicked witch!
Goodness.
I know.
I always advise him to focus on being a lawyer...
rather than being on TV.
But my husband never listens to me.
Men are always like that.
He always yearns for something new...
rather than earning profit.
It's not easy to assist him.
Goodness, is Atty. Park like that, too?
Even so, you should stop him from going on TV.
It's tough to be a public figure.
Your privacy is never guaranteed.
By the way, the coffee you sent me is delicious.
Thank you.
Ms. Kang, give me a cup of coffee, too.
Yes, boss!
It's nothing.
I made a mistake.
Can I call you back later?
Yes. Okay.
Okay.
Hye Joo.
What's up, Hee Sook?
What did you just say?
Did I say something?
What did you say when I was talking to Mrs. Park?
I asked you for a cup of coffee. What's wrong?
What did you say before that?
What did you call me?
What did I call you? Well, what did I call you?
- I don't remember. - Hye Joo!
Why would you yell?
Will you keep doing this while living in the same house?
Hey, Ms. Kang,
If you do like this one more time, I won't let it slide.
Do what?
Don't come between Mother and I!
I know so many of your secrets...
from your three years of working.
Do you want me to go on top of this house...
and reveal all your secrets?
I don't...
I don't have any secrets. Okay?
Think carefully.
For your information, I won't reveal your dating history.
Dating history? Do you think I had such a thing?
No way.
I can't believe this.
She's the one who's done wrong things!
How do I kick her out?
Chang Soo!
Are you here to get a medical check-up?
- Don't you weigh 100kg? - Stop it!
Hey.
Let's go.
We don't have time. I have to get done fast and go.
Okay.
You weigh 47kg.
Goodness! What are you doing?
My mother said she'll give me extra pocket money if I weigh 99kg.
Put on your clothes. I will deduct 1kg from your weight.
You're big enough.
You weigh 121kg.
When I subtract 1kg, it becomes 120kg.
Say good bye to your allowance.
No!
Stop making a fuss. You look like you could even cook a cow.
But it really hurts.
What do you think your blood type is?
- B. - How about you?
Me?
I don't know.
Is it C?
There's only "hepatitis C".
I remembered it. It's O.
- You're not joking, right? - No.
Am I wrong?
I think it's right. Is it right?
Ji Hoon
Are you not going to eat your corn dog?
We must eat because we had a blood test.
By the way, don't you have tutoring?
Attend the tutoring. Otherwise, your mom will be very upset.
You're not going to eat it, right? Then I'll have yours.
Chang Soo.
I...
don't want to live.
What?
Because of my mom,
I might die.
Hey!
Let go of me. Let's talk later.
Let's talk today. I will tell you everything.
Can you drink soju?
What does that mean? That was a sharp question.
I was just asking if you could drink soju.
I think I've never drunk soju with you.
Of course. I love wine.
Of course.
Actually,
I knew she was Seo Cheol Min's little sister from the start.
I don't know if it's okay for me to say this or not,
but I just let her go.
Why?
I told you before. It seems like she can't afford it.
But if you let her go, you'd have to let everyone else go, too.
I know.
But when you live life,
there are people who really doesn't have anything.
But they should at least take the legal responsibility
for what they have done.
Isn't that better for their lives as well?
You can't just do something bad and refuse to be arrested.
Stop drinking.
You never drink this fast.
What's wrong with you?
You know,
I have a rule for cutting people some slack.
When you work, you meet all kinds of con-artist-like people.
I first try not to let them get to me. Then if I get tricked...
like how I get tricked by Cheol Min, I won't cut him slack.
I'd follow him to the end...
and make him pay for it. If he can't pay,
I might send him to jail.
Then why did you do that to Seo Cheol Min's sister?
- I think she knows her place. - What do you mean?
It looks like she knows...
that what her brother did was embarrassing.
She honestly accepted that her brother has made mistakes.
I thought it was amazing to see her trying to pay for it.
Did you think that was amazing?
Yes.
I did.
But how much will she be able to pay back?
I don't think there's any way for her to pay back everything.
Isn't it enough for her to know that it was wrong?
That's why I let her go.
Even if Producer Kim was throwing a fit?
- I feel bad for Producer Kim. - How about me?
Don't you feel bad for me?
For you...
I feel sorry about everything.
You're a bad guy.
Then, marry me.
I can't do that.
Why?
Because I know where I stand.
What do you mean?
Let me ask you a question, too.
Can you eat fishcake?
How about sundae?
Forget it.
- Seong Joon. - Excuse me.
Can you give me some fishcake?
- And bring some sundae, too. - Okay.
You're home.
How did Producer Kim catch you?
You saw the picket I had, right?
How can I not be spotted with something like that?
Anyway.
I'm sorry, I must have put you in a bad spot today.
Is that why you're sad? Because you feel embarrassed?
No, I was thinking what I did to deserve such brother.
It takes a lot to hurt my ego since I went through a lot.
But...
I've been thinking for the whole day,
but I have no idea how to pay the money back.
Exactly.
I think I felt better when I was trying to get money out of you.
Look who's talking.
You asked me what I was going to do for you in return.
I was only joking.
Put yourself in my shoes. Would you have seen it as a joke?
It's Producer Kim. He called me 20 times today.
Yes, Producer Kim. I'm home.
I just got here.
What are you saying? How can I put my grandmother on the phone?
I'll visit you tomorrow.
Please. I beg you.
Okay.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Is he blackmailing you?
Yes. I think a loan shark might be more suitable...
for him than a producer.
We can't fix what's already been done.
Let's go to Taiwan again.
What?
Let's go to Taiwan to catch your brother.
- That doesn't make any sense. - Why doesn't it?
What kind of a brother tortures his family like this?
If we catch him, everything will be solved.
He must take responsibility of his actions, not you.
- Do you think I want to? - Then what?
I wish that either he gets caught...
or returns quickly.
But until then,
I need to protect my grandmother.
As this is what happened,
she must have caught on a bit about Cheol Min's situation.
Still,
I can't let her know that the in-laws are involved.
She's not happy to live at her in-law's house.
Imagine if she finds out about Cheol Min and your company.
Then she won't live here.
It's not only a matter of place she lives.
- It'll crush her pride. - Is it you, Dong Hui?
- Grandmother. - What are you doing out here?
I thought who might be mumbling out here.
Hello.
I was looking at Moong Chi.
- Did you have dinner? - Not yet.
Come inside and have your dinner.
Would you want some dinner, too?
That's okay. I'll have it downstairs.
Come inside.
But...
Producer Kim keeps trying to tell my grandmother.
What should I do?
Gosh, what is she doing outside?
Hello?
You should talk if you called.
You refused my offer to have lunch with me.
How can she not want to know about me for two days?
You have inferiority complex, victim mentally, and a huge ego.
It's a good thing that I learned how to restrict the caller ID.
But what is Jeong Eun up to? I haven't seen her the whole day.
- What is it now? - Hey.
- Have you seen your daughter? - Who are you referring to?
Is Jeong Eun there? I haven't seen her the whole day.
I'm going insane.
How long will I be locked up here?
Maybe she went on a trip again.
Did you forget?
She left three years ago without saying anything to us.
She came home drunk the previous night.
Then, she wasn't there the next day when we went into her room.
How can you be so cold-hearted toward your own daughter?
I'm different from Jeong Ae.
I don't want my child to walk all over me.
Mom, do you know what I'm doing now?
I'm dinning alone.
- I'm drinking alone. - What do you mean?
That means I'm fine living on my own.
Mom. So...
should I go abroad...
to study?
Study abroad? See if you can get remarried or not.
What did you say?
Get remarried? Mom!
Goodness.
What should I do?
I think he's here. What do I say if he asks why I'm here?
What are you doing here?
Well, I mean...
Let me explain this.
Why are you here?
What are you doing here?
Excuse me.
Let me explain. I just...
How did you get in here? Who let you in?
That's...
Do you want to die?
Is this the police?
Let me go.
Let's talk at the police station.
Look, David. Do you really have to do this?
We're neighbors, and we went through some stuff in New York.
How can you do this to me?
David.
You'll pay for this, okay?
Let's talk at the police station.
- You brat! - Gosh.
My gosh. I can't put my head up in the neighborhood because of you.
How could you be taken to the police station right after coming back?
You just came back!
This is unfair. I'm innocent.
Are you kidding me right now?
Gosh. All you ever do is causing troubles.
Mom.
Gosh. I can't believe you.
I've always been ashamed that you're my daughter.
This is so embarrassing. Let's go.
My goodness.
What's this?
Can't you tell what it is?
Read the electric, gas,
and water meter at the kids' house every month.
Write down the number there,
and collect the charges from them.
Honey.
I told them to transfer the rent to my bank account.
So you should take care of that.
Do you really have to do this to the kids?
Of course.
Are you going to pay for that instead?
You know we don't have any money to spare.
But we're their parents.
How can I ask them for these charges?
It's not like they're paying us voluntarily.
If you don't want to do it, give it to me. I'll do it.
Fine.
Fine. I'll do it.
I can't believe you.
You're such a dreadful person.
I called you because you didn't come out to jog this morning.
I had an early shooting.
That's why.
I didn't know. I waited for two hours.
Yoo Ra. Why don't we have dinner together?
Why are you calling my first name in all of a sudden?
It's not a sudden.
I just wanted to be friends with you.
Yoo Ra. I'll come and pick you up at the broadcasting station.
How does that sound?
Gosh, it's just one dinner. Why are you so...
I'll call you back.
Ah In.
When did you get in here?
A while ago. I had to use the toilet.
My gosh.
By the way, who is Yoo Ra?
I have a friend named Yoo Ra, too.
You must not tell anyone about this, okay?
No. I'll go and tell my dad.
Ah In. Wait. Please don't say anything.
Wait.
Gosh, it hurts.
Don't be such a baby.
Tell me how you hurt your back.
It just happened.
Everything you do upsets me.
What are you doing? Get ready to go to preschool.
Okay.
Dad.
Yes, Ah In. What is it?
I saw Uncle...
talking to my friend Yoo Ra on the phone.
What are you talking about?
It's a secret.
What is this? Why can't you answer me?
What's going on this time?
Are you out of your mind?
How could you...
do this badly on the test?
Besides,
you tried to hide it.
How dare you lie to me?
How could you? You little brat!
You're the third place. How can you be the third place?
How could you drop to the third place in a month?
I can't believe you did this!
Aunt. Please don't hit Ji Hoon.
Don't hit him.
What are you doing? Let go of me.
Aunt.
Hit me instead. I'm fat, so it won't hurt that much.
Get off of me!
Go upstairs. I think Hee Sook is tormenting Ji Hoon again.
Gosh, I can't believe that woman.
Why do you think I'm living like this?
I moved in here...
and I'm taking care of your grandparents.
Why do you think I'm doing this?
How could you do this badly on the test?
Besides,
you lied to me about it. How could?
Hey!
It's none of your business.
You.
I'll report you to the police for abusing your child.
- What did you say? - I'll report you to the police.
Look. Getting good grades doesn't make him happy.
Getting into a good college won't make him successful.
I said this is none of your business.
- Mom. - Let go of me.
Frankly, you graduated from a local college.
Even though you did,
you're now living in a 150m house,
and having a nice life.
Ji Hoon got the third place and it means he did really good.
Why can't you just leave him alone?
I just don't understand you.
Ji Hoon.
What did you...
just say?
What?
I said leave Ji Hoon alone.
Getting good grades doesn't make him happy.
How could you?
The kids were here.
How could you...
dredge up my past like that?
How...
How could you...
tell them that I graduated from a local college?
How could you?
Calm down, Ji Hoon.
Let go of me! My mom is a witch.
Wait for me, Ji Hoon.
It's good.
I like the material.
The material is okay.
It fits nicely as well.
The jacket looks much nicer...
since you're the one who's wearing it.
You look great.
Okay.
All you need to do is set a reasonable price. Push it through.
Okay, Ms. Bang.
Please go ahead. I want to jog for a while longer.
Okay, Ms. Bang. Have a good jog.
Gosh, I'm exhausted.
Good morning. I missed your call.
Yes. Where are you? You weren't in your office.
Did you want to see me?
Yes. I need your authorization on something.
Do you have to speak that way?
Instead of that, you can say you need to consult or discuss...
something with me.
It means the same thing.
Is that why you told me that...
you know your place?
I've been thinking about what you said to me since last night.
I'm a bit disappointed, but I don't feel bad about it.
I'm disappointed because there is still a wall...
between you and me.
I don't feel bad because it means...
you're still attracted to me on some level.
- Mi Joo. - I'll try harder.
I have new hopes.
- I still need your authorization. - Let's have lunch together.
How about sundae soup? I'll see you later.
Mi Joo.
- Hello, Director Han. - Hello.
There's something I should tell you.
Please come.
Hello.
Everyone. Let me introduce you our new employee.
Her name is Oh Dong Hui.
Hello. I'm Oh Dong Hui.
I look forward to working with you.
Aren't you going to take a bath?
If you want to stay in this house, get rid of that shabby clothes,
and get washed up.
Are you hearing me or not?
Take off these shabby clothes!
What's wrong with your hair? Also, what about your clothes?
- And why are you wearing this? - Don't touch it.
Dad gave this to me.
What... What did you say?
What did you just say?
Dad gave this to me.
I met him in 30 years and he gave this to me.
I met Dad in Spain.
I went on a trip to meet Dad.
That's why I wondered around the world!
But that jerk wouldn't...
return this necklace.
I had to have this, so I can come to see you. But he wouldn't return it.
That's why I went to his place. You don't know anything.
Hey. You shouldn't do that. We'll get in trouble.
- Really? - You brats. What are you doing?
- Let's go. - Stop, you punks!
Look. Dad made us cucumber sandwiches.
It looks delicious.
I'll go inside and eat it with milk.
- Hyun Woo. - Don't look, Sang Woo.
Hyun Woo. What's wrong with Dad?
- Let me see. - No.
You can't see it.
Don't look, Sang Woo.
It's 3, 5,
and six...
My goodness.
How can she ask her children...
to pay something like this? She's a terrible person.
So, it's 6, 3, and...
Gosh. You're from the house across the street.
Hello.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I hope we get along, Director Han.
You're unstoppable, Dong Hui.
You already caused us trouble.
You'd better work quietly and behave yourself.
I have a younger brother.
Nice to meet you. I'm Lee Hyun Woo.
There's something strange about their youngest son.
I can't do this any more.
He doesn't listen to me since that day.
Where do you go every night? To see someone? Is it a guy?
What are you doing?