(Episode 8)
What should we eat for dinner?
The housekeeper is off today.
We have some octopus stir-fry left. Let's make a fried rice with it.
We have octopus stir-fry?
Yes, Hee Sook made it yesterday for lunch.
Really?
She's quite friendly, isn't she?
- I don't know if she really is. - Please come inside.
Goodness.
What an unexpected pleasure.
Hello.
My goodness.
You don't have to take a bow to me.
I should have visited you earlier, but I'm sorry I was too busy.
I thought it'd be appropriate to visit you properly,
and that's why I am here.
Ma'am, I hope we can get along well.
You're such a polite person.
Dear me.
You're not just handsome, but very special as well.
Jeong Ae,
there was no point in expecting Song Joong Ki to move to our town...
as we have such a handsome, cool,
and polite gentleman here right now.
Mother.
It's really nice to have you.
We also planned...
to properly introduce ourselves to you...
in the near future.
Thank you for welcoming me.
I must be really lucky to have such nice neighbors.
It's pretty hard to have good neighbors.
Indeed, that's so true.
Anyway, I think I've made a mistake to you.
A mistake?
Gosh, Jeong Eun did?
Is that really true?
What happened?
I was very bewildered and startled,
so I just reported her to the police right away...
without asking her what happened.
I realized that she's your nephew...
after I called the police.
Why on earth did she break in his house?
Gosh, that's why she hasn't been home that day.
She ended up in the police station again.
Why did she enter the house where a man lives alone?
She must have gone out of mind.
It's so shameful.
So is Jeong Eun still in the station now?
I called the police right away to release her.
They said her mother came and took her.
Then, she'll be fine.
Ae Ri must feel really terrible because of Jeong Eun.
I apologize.
I should have handled it myself.
Please don't worry about it.
She thinks of the police station as her another home.
So don't mind it.
I'm sure you were startled a lot...
because of Jeong Eun. Why don't you have dinner with us?
It's okay, Ma'am.
Come on. Let's have dinner together.
I can't let a guest leave without serving dinner.
Gosh, Mother.
Don't you remember we were going to eat the leftover octopus?
We can't serve leftovers to him.
Take out all the meat we have in the fridge.
Goodness, why do you make things so complicated?
The interior is very simple but it's cozy.
I'm sure you took a lot of care.
Do you really think so?
We have lived in this house for over 30 years...
since our kids were this small.
So many things had been broken...
and worn as well.
So we had repaired the broken parts and remodeled the house.
- Sir, - Yes?
please speak to me casually.
I find this way more comfortable.
I'm not really used to talking without using the honorifics.
I couldn't talk down to privates when I was on active service.
Where are you parents?
Both of my parents passed away.
I'm so sorry.
Do you have any siblings?
I have a younger brother.
I see.
You two must be really close to each other, then.
Well,
please come have dinner.
- Okay. - Let's go.
I guess I bothered you too much.
I'm sorry.
Please don't be. We just made...
bulgogi and japchae.
Of course, we must treat you to a nice meal.
We might have to see each other for decades.
Please have a seat.
You're right, Mom.
Please sit here.
Thank you so much.
- You're welcome. - Please enjoy.
- Let's take seats. - Okay.
You really eat well.
What type of girl do you like?
- Sorry? - Mother,
he's in the middle of eating.
May I tell you after I finish dinner?
Okay. Just don't forget to answer it, okay?
- I won't. - My goodness.
- Gosh. - Mom.
Mom.
Why... Why are you here?
I didn't know you had a visitor.
He lives in the house across the street. Say hello.
You have met him before.
I have. It's good to see you.
It's nice to meet you.
Please sit down.
Okay.
Join us for dinner if you haven't had yet.
It's okay, Dad. I'll eat with Ah In.
Will Hye Joo come home late tonight?
- I think so. - Why?
- Why? - Speaking of dinner,
please let me take two eggs.
What?
I'm sorry.
Please enjoy your dinner.
Thank you.
Gosh, I never though they would be with a visitor.
I need to talk to you.
What happened?
- What do you mean? - Do you have to ask?
Producer Kim told me to work for the company at least to pay the debt.
But still, how can you make such decision without me?
It doesn't matter. It's between me and the company, not you.
I calculated and since my salary is 1,000 dollars,
it will take me 16 years and 8 months.
Of course, it can be quicker if I get a raise.
You think you have that much time on your hand?
What did you say?
Are you saying that what I'm doing is...
- a waste of my time? - I...
didn't say it that harshly.
I mean you shouldn't have signed a contract like that.
Don't you know consequences of such contracts?
What choice did I have? He was about to visit my grandmother.
Besides, it doesn't matter how long it takes. I have to pay it back.
Also, I have a job which is hard to find nowadays...
although my salary will be distrained.
It's good that I can pay my brother's debt back.
Don't worry. I have a plan.
- What plan? - I have one.
In fact, I can't tell you right now.
And don't worry. I'm going to...
make sure they don't find out we are in-laws.
If they find out,
I think the company might...
shift the blame on you. They might think...
you protected and helped me on purpose.
I didn't really want to work at the same company, though.
But this was the only way. I'm sorry.
So I'm going to do everything in my power...
to keep our relationship a secret.
You're unstoppable, Dong Hui.
To be honest, I'm happy to have a job.
Why are you happy?
How can you be happy when you have to pay the debt for 16 years?
My part time jobs don't pay well, too.
Besides, I'm glad I can earn my living...
doing things I want to do.
Things you want to do?
By any chance,
did you want to work at our company?
Yes.
Why?
I can't tell you now.
- Come on, Ms. Oh. - Anyway, please do support me.
Okay?
I knew it since you got into a cab with me in Taiwan.
How can a woman get into a taxi with a stranger?
And you were chased by gangsters.
- You even followed them. - Please stop talking.
I give up now. Let's go home and eat.
Are you hungry?
Of course I am. It's dinner time. How can I not be?
I didn't even have my lunch because I was so shocked.
Don't blame it on me.
Look at you, talking back to your boss.
I knew you were going to be bossy.
- Excuse me. - What is it now?
You can go first.
Why? Are you not going home?
I need to stop by somewhere.
Where?
I can't tell you.
Director Han, please get home safe.
I'll see you tomorrow at work.
Goodbye.
Hold on, Ms. Oh.
I think I need to change the pipe.
Goodness, really?
How can you let your guest work after dinner?
Mother, he said we should change the pipe.
I told him so many times to change it,
but he never listened. Now look what happened.
I know how to fit it. It was just not that bad to be changed.
It wasn't a crucial problem back then.
How can you say it wasn't a crucial problem?
Try to live in a house where there's a flood in it.
Men in our family are useless.
I agree with her.
- Mom, how can you be on her side? - Why can't I?
I taped it so that it wouldn't leak.
I'll come back tomorrow and put in a new pipe.
I told you. He's better than Song Joong Ki.
I really appreciate it.
If I called a plumber, this would have cost a fortune.
You served me a good dinner.
Thank you.
Don't mention it. I had a great time.
My wife made this kimchi. Try it at home.
- Thank you. - I'm not sure about other food,
but she makes the best kimchi.
It must go really well with ramyeon.
Is that you, Seong Joon?
Yes.
You haven't met him, right? He moved in across our house.
- Hello. - Hello. I'm Lee Hyun Woo.
- I'm Han Seong Joon. - I see.
Don't be strangers to each other.
I'll get going then.
- Okay. Goodbye and see you again. - Yes.
- Did you have dinner? - No, not yet.
Let's go in. I'll prepare your dinner.
You don't have to. I'll prepare it myself.
Your mom's angry.
Because I didn't fix the leak.
- Really? - She said we are useless.
That was harsh. Let's go inside.
Let's get inside.
Be careful.
How are you, Moong Chi?
You want your treats more than me, don't you?
Dong Hui...
isn't here.
I don't know where she went.
(I made a promise and I intend to keep it.)
Yes, president.
Moong Chi, aren't you going to eat your dinner? We must go for a walk.
Let's try to look for your eyes.
There's something strange about their youngest son.
I don't remember them having the youngest son. Look into it.
Yes, Sir.
It's a square of s.
Let's see. It's ax plus two squares.
And it's multiplied by two and take a half of it later. Then k equals...
three.
How can he not correct such an easy question?
I can't believe this.
Cheers.
This is delicious.
- Where are you? - What do you want?
- Where are you? - I'm having dinner.
Are you still eating dinner? It's 11pm.
Why are you so grumpy?
You should come home early.
- How can I raise our son by myself? - What are you talking about?
You raised him all on your own so far.
Then, do you expect me to take care of your parents by myself?
It's all on you. You were the one who said...
you would take good care of my parents.
- Are you kidding me? - Is it...
Is it because Ji Hoon's grade went down?
Forget it. When are you coming home?
Okay, fine. I'll be home soon.
When?
My gosh.
Hello? Honey? Honey?
My husband is no better than my son.
I get a lot of phone calls. I apologize.
It's from your wife, isn't it?
Sorry?
No way, it is not.
That was a funny joke, Ms. Jang.
What do you mean? Didn't your wife nag at you to come home early?
I said that's not true. She never nags me.
Are you married?
Gosh, I never knew you are.
I thought you got divorced.
Divorced?
Did you think I was single?
Thank you.
Then, let's make...
a toast.
Cheers.
Thank you. I enjoyed it a lot.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
I'd like to pay by three-month installment.
- Sorry? - Three-month installment.
I said three months.
Okay.
Yoo Ra, how will you go home?
Someone will pick me up.
- See you, then. - Take care.
- Goodbye. - Bye.
Ms. Jang. Ms. Jang! Wait a minute!
Gosh, Yoo Ra!
Hey! Where are you going?
Ji Hoon!
What is it this time?
What did you just say?
Do you really don't know?
I can't believe you got the wrong answer to this question.
You solved this so many times!
Look at this.
In this A coordination, X2 is...
2A, 4A square.
If you draw a line from this point,
you can get the height and the width.
Then, what's X?
It's the cube of 6A.
Then, what's K?
It's three!
Why did you miss this easy question?
You missed this question and fell to the third rank!
Are you out of mind? Are you?
Those who solve math questions like a calculator...
hardly make it to the gifted high school.
How could you get this wrong? You've solved it so many times.
They just changed few numbers. How on earth could you get it wrong?
What's gotten in your head?
I can't do this any more.
Say that again.
I said I can't do this any more.
I ran into a wall I can't cross. I'm really at the end of my rope!
I no longer want to study!
I've done everything as you said.
But I cannot do this any more!
What... What?
Have you lost your mind?
How dare you yell at me?
Did you just fly in the teeth of me?
We need to talk more at home. Get in the car.
Ji Hoon, where are you going? Stop right there.
Ji Hoon!
The number you have dialed is not available at this moment.
There will be charges after the beep.
So you had me...
treat you and your friends to dinner and now you ignore my calls.
What a foxy wench.
- Uncle! - Gosh.
Is Yoo Ra not answering your calls again?
You scared me again.
Gosh.
Since when have you been here?
Am I invisible to you?
Yes, you're invisible.
It's because you're too small, okay?
- You little... - Are you going to knuckle me?
No, I won't.
Please flush the toilet.
Okay.
I'm asking what you will do.
I said okay.
Please don't say just okay.
We must pay the rent to Mother. It's the 30th of this month already.
How will you pay her?
I said I'll take care of it.
Now, it's not my business any more.
Make sure to take care of it yourself, okay?
Okay. Please leave now.
Gosh.
Chang Soo, what are you doing?
Uncle, I'm making ramyeon.
Where's Hee Sook?
I think she's ill.
What?
This is unbelievable.
Ah In, come take a seat. I'll make you breakfast.
Ji Hoon, come out and have breakfast!
What's wrong with you? You must make Ji Hoon breakfast.
Chang Soo is making ramyeon for him.
Honey!
I don't care what he has for breakfast.
You're such an unbelievable woman.
You were obsessed with organic and nutritious food before...
and made him a sumptuous feast every morning.
How can you neglect him just because his grades went down?
This is really horrible.
Ji Hoon, have breakfast before you leave. Hey.
Seriously.
I'm sick of both of you.
- Is Aunt okay? - I don't know.
- She went on a strike. - A strike?
Then, come have some ramyeon.
This is awful.
Chang Soo, you must eat now.
You have to go to school.
Right. I will.
Goodness.
Chang Soo, it's very tasty.
Thank you.
What's going on here?
Did you have my son cook ramyeon for you?
I didn't! He just made it for himself.
You just made a wrong guess.
He's right. I made it because I wanted to eat this.
Where's Hee Sook?
She's on a strike today.
A strike?
Hey, Hee Sook.
I really don't understand you.
How can you make your son leave with an empty stomach...
just because his grades dropped a little?
It's none of your business.
He ranked the third in the entire Seoul,
and that's really amazing.
Maybe,
it's amazing only to you.
Wouldn't you even find it amazing...
if Chang Soo's grades rank higher than the 30th?
- What? - And...
why did you tell him that I graduated from a local college?
He doesn't listen to me since that day.
Hey, I'm sure that's not the reason.
And Chang Soo is responsible for all this.
Why do you blame him out of the blue?
It's because Ji Hoon lives in the same house with Chang Soo.
All Chang Soo does is playing and eating all day long!
That made Ji Hoon become lazy,
and look what happened now!
Hye Joo,
do you really have to live with us?
What did you just say?
Are you going out today?
You had a haircut yesterday and you're dressed up nicely.
Grandma, I got a job.
You got a job?
Yes.
Where do you work, then?
I'll tell you later.
I'll make a lot of money...
and let you live in the lap of luxury.
Please wait a little longer, okay?
Thank you.
Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello, Director Han. - Hello.
Hello, Director Han!
The door's closing.
Yes, hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
Stop coming in. Take the next one.
Goodness.
Gosh.
What are you talking about? We brought her here.
That's not important. We requested for an intern.
She's not an intern. We hired her as the assistant writer.
Assistant writer? You always drain our funds.
Are you going to increase payroll cost again?
We're the money-generating team. We should hire an assistant.
What's going on?
- It's nothing, sir. - It's nothing, sir.
We were having a debate.
I will report it to you later.
Producer Kim!
Don't you think...
you're being unreasonable this time, Mr. Park?
We're struggling here because we're short-staffed.
And you're asking for a darn assistant. That's why we are upset!
What? A darn assistant?
- Hey, do you hear yourself? - Wait.
I don't know exactly what is happening here,
but I will do everything. So please don't fight.
- Really? - Really?
Everything?
Okay.
What's happened to my room?
Mom!
Mom, did you rent out my room?
Yes, I did.
A room was being wasted.
- Still, how can you do that? - How can you just...
leave home without saying anything to your mom and...
go out of reach for three years? Instead of waiting for...
that ungrateful child, I chose to give the room to my student...
who visits me all the time and takes care of me when I'm sick.
So I decided to consider her as my daughter.
Na Eun went to the U.S. for training. She'll be back soon.
Then where will I stay?
I hope you wouldn't stay at my place,
but we're still family.
So just stay wherever you want.
- What? - Except for Na Eun's room.
Dong Hui, these are supplex and polyester fabrics.
Please match them with the fabric list and number them accordingly.
Okay. I will.
Dong Hui.
Please summarize these drama proposals as soon as possible.
Write down each one's subject and concept clearly.
Okay.
Also, please convert these scripts into pdf files, okay?
Also, please classify these, too.
Divide them into mini-series, weekend drama and daily drama.
Okay.
Please take it to the Research and Development Team.
Okay. I'll be back.
Where is the Research and Development Team's office?
Please move the Research and Development Team's...
Friday presentation to Wednesday.
Our competition might release their product at the same time.
Okay. I'll move it.
And please schedule a meeting with Chinese distributor.
Okay, Director Bang.
- Ms. Oh. - Yes?
Can I talk to you?
Producer Kim informed me yesterday.
I see.
How's work so far?
I still don't know a lot of things, but the work is fun.
The work shouldn't be fun.
The police is already searching for Seo Cheol Min.
When he gets caught, he will receive a criminal punishment.
He won't receive indulgence...
just because you work here.
I know that. He committed a crime, so he should get punished.
I just know that...
he can't pay the money back even if he gets caught.
I shouldn't be a nuisance to other people.
You've already become a nuisance.
You incurred damage to our company...
and you scarred our record.
So you should stay low...
as if you don't exist when you work here.
Okay. I understand.
Director Bang.
Come in, Seong Joon.
- You can leave now. - Okay.
I was going to go see you anyway.
Let's eat lunch together.
I am sorry.
Going up.
What should we eat for lunch?
Should we really go try that sundae soup?
It's not as bad as I thought. It looks quite okay, too.
What are you thinking, Seong Joon?
What?
- Why? - I made an effort to come here.
Shouldn't you give me some credit for it?
Try it. It's quite tasty, too.
- Is something bothering you? - No.
It's nothing.
You're not supposed to talk and think too much here.
Hurry up and eat your soup.
I'll cut you slack since you're handsome.
You better stay handsome.
Otherwise, I'll get upset.
Yes, this is Oh Dong Hui from Contents Marketing Team of FGC.
Yes.
Mr. Park went out for lunch.
So he's not available right now.
Okay.
- What? - How could you do that?
How can you feed warm food to our family's enemy...
in a friendly vibe?
Family's enemy? That's nonsense.
Our family's enemy is you. Do you know that?
Why am I?
Why would a grown-up woman break into a man's house?
We are so embarrassed because of you.
Did he even tell you that?
Are you interested in him?
Even if you were interested in him,
you should just ask him to have a cup of tea.
How can you shamelessly barge into a man's house like that?
You're dead, David!
So,
have you decided to live in your mother's house?
Don't you see that I'm taking my stuff?
My goodness.
We have to finish everything today. So get here by 3pm.
Hey!
How can you eat beef bulgogi...
after putting me in jail?
That's not all you ate.
I heard you also ate marinated crab, kimchi, and...
freshly cooked japchae. How could you enjoy them?
Did you just laugh?
Hey, David!
Because of you, I had to...
reunite with my mom in jail after not seeing her for three years.
It's not like we don't know each other.
We even met in New York.
They say even brushing past a person is one's karma.
How can you lock me up in jail just because I entered your house?
Then you came to my house and had a nice meal.
How can a person be like that?
You weren't like this in New York.
What happened to you?
Stop.
Stop bringing that up.
What did I say?
Stop talking about New York.
I told you many times that I am not your acquaintance.
That's why I put you in jail. Got it?
If you got it, leave now. If you keep doing this,
I'm going to report you for interrupting my work.
What did you just say?
- Is everything going well? - Yes, it is.
I'm not done yet.
What now?
Listen carefully.
If I see you again,
I am not a human.
Hello.
Yes.
I greeted you yesterday.
Yes. Yes, you did.
By the way, what brings you here?
It's nothing. I was just passing by and I thought I'd take a look.
I'll see you around, then.
Bye.
What?
Really?
Did that helper quit?
I see.
It's two dollars.
I don't know. it's hard to find a good person these days.
How much will you pay her in a month?
I think you can find a good person with that money.
Okay. I will ask my customers.
Excuse me.
Is someone looking to hire helper?
Why do you ask?
If it's okay, I want to have an interview.
I live right across the street.
I recently moved here.
I see.
I think you can't do it at your age.
Women these days are very picky.
Nobody would hire someone old.
Still, I beg you.
I used to run a side dish store.
I once ran a traditional wedding food store, too.
When I was younger,
I worked at a big mansion...
as a resident helper.
I see.
Then please leave your number with me.
Okay.
Goodness. What brings you here?
I came to cook you lunch.
- What? - Lunch.
You said you were craving for sujebi the other day.
Where is the kitchen?
- It's... - Is it there?
Come and eat sujebi.
Goodness.
I only used flour and zucchini.
I hope you'll still enjoy it.
What are you doing? Take your seat.
Well...
I'll give it a try.
Goodness! It's so good!
Is it? That's good.
Did you do magic?
How can this lump of flour be so tasty?
Thanks to Elizabeth,
Grace Kelly's eating well.
Stop calling me Elizabeth.
Elizabeth,
please visit me more often.
We live in the same house anyway. Let's stay close. Okay?
Go ahead and eat more.
Stay still.
You got too many shots that your veins hid.
There you go.
Are you exhausted?
Always.
Don't you sleep?
I don't have much time to sleep.
Why not?
You must know.
Hello. How are you?
Include the new five-piece beauty set...
in the tax-free items.
And tell them to come up with a marketing proposal.
Okay.
I am sorry. I'm working.
I was actually going to call you.
What?
Do you want me to come to the school now?
What do you mean?
Did you just say Ji Hoon's grades fell...
because of Chang Soo?
Actually, Chang Soo...
always stays by Ji Hoon even in school.
And I found out about this today.
I heard they live in the same house.
According to Ji Hoon's mom,
Chang Soo always plays games and listens to music at night,
and visits Ji Hoon's room.
So Ji Hoon couldn't concentrate in his studies.
She wanted me to warn you.
Hey, why are you crying, Hee Sook?
It's nothing.
Who made you cry, Hee Sook?
I...
I think I can't get promoted because I'm from a local college.
Hey.
It's not because you graduated from a local college.
That's okay.
I know.
Other people graduated from a prestigious college.
I'm the only one...
from a local college.
Don't cry. Next time,
I'll make sure you get promoted.
- Do you mean it? - Of course.
Trust me.
Coffee wakes me up.
I drank too much last night.
Ms. Kang,
you make the best coffee.
Is that so, Manager?
Thank you.
By the way, how do I look today?
Will my future mother-in-law like me?
Yes, she will.
You think so?
But she knows about my past.
Your teeth are clean. I checked.
Really?
By the way, are you seeing anyone? Do you want me to set you up?
Set me up?
Hye Joo.
- How can you marry my brother? - We already decided.
- Move aside. - Hold on.
How can you hide it for five years?
How can you do this to me, Hye Joo?
Excuse me, Manager.
- Here's your present. - Thank you, Ms. Kang.
Say hello to each other.
Hee Sook.
Come out.
Come out!
Hye Joo. Let go of me.
It hurts.
You.
How dare you slander my son?
Did you disrespect my dear son?
You should have raised your dear son better.
- What did you say? - Am I wrong?
Even though we are living in the same building,
my son and your son won't be the same when they grow up.
Chang Soo will never walk the same path as Ji Hoon.
But look at him now. He's trying to be close friends with him.
He comes to our house all the time without being invited.
He's bothering my son, Ji Hoon.
Hey, Hee Sook.
- Are you done? - No, I am not.
I don't care how you raise your son.
But shouldn't you at least take care of your son so that he doesn't...
- cause troubles for other people? - Hey.
You're the one to talk.
Try to live without causing any harms in this country.
Me? Causing harms?
You are one of those selfish moms.
You don't care about anyone, but about your own son.
What? What did you call me?
Because all you do is eat and stay at home, you don't know...
what to do with your energy. You nag your son for your own happiness.
And look what has happened!
You're hurting your child.
You say, "Raise the price for apartments and private education."
You should try to live without causing troubles for other people.
Hey, if you want your son to live a good life,
you, as a parent should help him.
What did you say?
Did you say all I do is eat and stay at home?
Is that all?
Yes, that's all. So what? What are you going to do?
Look who's talking.
You abandoned your children to make money.
What?
I abandoned my children to make money?
Why? Am I wrong?
You don't make any sacrifice for your children like a selfish mom.
You're a working mom.
Isn't that true?
I'm going insane. Seriously, I'm going crazy.
Okay. Let's calm down.
Hey, you...
You ought to learn a lesson by...
one of 100 thousand working moms.
What? I abandoned my children for money? A selfish mom?
What was that?
- Hey. - What is this? You're ignorant.
My son scored the lowest grade. How can I not be ignorant?
My gosh.
Apples don't fall too far from the tree.
We're both going to die tonight.
- Do you think I won't do anything? - Let go of me.
- Let go. - You let go of me first.
What? What did you just say?
- Gosh. - You.
- Hey. - Let go.
- It hurts. - Hey.
Let go.
Come on.
Goodness.
What has she done?
I don't want to wash
I don't want to my face
I don't want to clean my eyes I won't wash
I will only let you know
- Only you will know - My gosh.
To be honest I didn't shower yesterday, too
I will sing
I rather sing than wash
For lovely Dulcinea and my beloved daughter
I don't have enough time to sing
I will sing
I don't want to shower
What are you doing?
I had sujebi for lunch with my in-law.
We had bibimbap for dinner.
Now, we are watching the news together.
Hey, I'm not lonely since she moved in.
We're going to play cards later.
I wanted to tell you these things.
That's why I called you.
But why do you sound so down?
Mom, just hang up.
I'm having a hard time.
What's wrong with her?
Did she fight with Jeong Eun again?
Who were you talking to?
My daughter. She will turn 60 soon.
I think we're living a long life.
Exactly, they work as a good indicator to measure our age.
It's so weird to get old as she gets old with me.
Who would have known that we would dye our hair together?
Next news is about a murder case...
of two Koreans who were shot in Philippines.
The victims were involved in a fraud case...
who fled the country to Philippines.
- The police... - It's scary to travel abroad now.
Why are there so many people like them?
But still, how can they kill people for that?
Please take care of my grandson in overseas.
It's okay even if he goes to jail.
Just make sure he comes back safe and sound.
I beg of you. I beg of you.
Hey.
If I didn't have to...
go home and take care of Ah In,
you would have been dead by now.
Hye Joo. If...
If I I didn't have to pick Ji Hoon up,
you would have been dead.
- We'll finish this later. - Okay.
I'm sorry I'm late.
No. You're right on time.
Is that the house?
Yes.
I will...
destroy them step by step.
- You're here. - Now,
let's see.
How many of you have worked at a construction site?
- You're here again. Please get in. - Hello.
You can get in. You, too.
Would you like to get in?
Sure.
Are you sure you can handle the work?
- Get in. - Excuse me?
Get in now.
Are you sure this is okay?
It was your first day at work and you looked tired. That's all.
Still.
Do you think there can be an absolute secret?
People will find out about...
our relationship someday.
We should hide it as long as we can.
- Director Bang said... - What?
Did she say something to you?
She just told me that...
I caused severe damage to your career,
so I should be more careful.
Listen.
Where are you going?
Just some place.
Do you still work part-time?
I don't.
Then...
where do you go every night?
To see someone?
Who would I see?
Is it a guy?
I still have a huge debt to pay. I don't have time for guys.
That's why I'm asking where you go every night.
(Seocho Library)
Are you happy now?
Please get home safely. I'll see you tomorrow.
You were serious.
Are you studying for the civil service exam?
Not just that.
Call me if you're scared.
I should walk Moong Chi, so I'll come and pick you up.
I'm fine.
You took out a student loan from us for four years.
You should be working and paying us back by now.
I'm sorry. I haven't gotten a job yet.
You're sorry?
I can't believe this punk.
Is it our fault that you haven't gotten a job?
- Is it our fault? - Please don't hurt me.
Wait. The girl just went inside.
Search that side.
What do you think you're doing?
- How did it go? - I don't think she's here.
Let's check that side.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
We caught them. I don't think we need to take them back to Korea.
We'll take care of them here.
Stay still.
Mister.
Can you turn around?
I said turn around.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I heard he already got a job at another company.
I'm thinking about entering the broadcasting industry.
He's sick because he mind is weak.
You don't even feed us well.
I wish Aunt was my mom.
The guy always kisses the girl.
No one can predict the relationship between a man and a woman.
I spent most of my time alone.
That's why I used my imagination to make up the things I didn't have.