BioskopKeren
What are you doing?
What's going on?
We caught them. I don't think we need to take them back to Korea.
We'll take care of them here.
Stay still.
Mister. Can you turn around?
I said turn around.
Excuse me. What's going on?
Are you here to use the library?
We don't read books.
Then will you stop making noise and leave?
Gosh, lady.
You have offended me.
Should I call the police?
Let's go.
What do I do? It's them, isn't it?
It's them.
(Seocho Library)
(Episode 9)
The library is closing.
Please wrap things up.
The library is closing. Please leave.
What's going on? Is everyone out?
Darn it.
I'm sorry. I always cause you trouble.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
No, you're just on time.
Is that the house?
Yes.
I will destroy them...
step by step.
Please help me, Uncle.
Thank you for giving me a chance...
to pay you back, Sir.
You should call me by my name now.
Should I?
Hyun Woo.
I'm really happy...
to see you again.
I missed you a lot, too, Uncle.
Aren't you cold?
I left my jacket and bag in the computer room.
Do you want to put this on?
No, I'll just bear it. I'm too embarrassed.
Don't refuse it.
All sorts of things happen in life.
Don't be too harsh on yourself.
By the way,
- did you come here to write? - Yes.
Did you read it by any chance?
- I did. - What?
Why do you keep looking at my work?
This is why you wanted to work at our company.
Yes.
Actually,
there are a lot of people...
who wants to work at your company...
as an assistant writer.
So?
Is that why you signed that unfair contract?
The contract that ties you for 16 years and 8 months.
Actually, I can pay back before the contract gets over.
If I win the TV drama script contest,
I will get a cash prize of 10,000 dollars.
- If I get that... - I don't think you'll get it.
When did I say I'll get it? I said there's a chance.
And what's wrong with having a dream and hope?
How can you ruin my dream like this?
Are you trying to make me disheartened? Is that your hobby?
Well,
I know it well, too.
Do you learn writing from anyone?
No. Who would teach me?
I want to take some writing class,
but I have to make a living first. So I can't attend any class.
- So do you write yourself? - Yes.
- With the library's computer? - Yes.
My brother took the laptop I got from Hye Joo as a gift.
Actually, I went to Taiwan to get my laptop.
Your brother is truly unbelievable.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
What's up? Did you forget that there are gangsters out there?
Well,
in dramas,
a man always kisses a woman in a scene like this.
I just remembered that.
Why...
What's wrong with you?
I'm... I'm so sorry.
I must be mad. I'm mad.
I didn't have any other intention.
I mean...
Wait. Please hold on.
Hold on.
Yes, Grandma.
Do you know what time it is? Why aren't you still home?
I am sorry.
I have to work all night. I don't think I can go home.
How can they ask you to work all night?
You just joined.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I will try to finish work as soon as possible and go home.
What are they doing to a young lady?
If they keep doing that, just quit.
I'm sorry, Grandma. I'll rush home as soon as possible.
- Is it your grandmother? - Yes.
She wants me to quit work.
You should quit.
Maybe I should.
I think I won. My goodness.
No, you didn't.
Let me see.
You need five more cards to win.
You're impatient.
Really?
Then what about all the other cards I got?
You need to get the cards from the same group.
Otherwise, they're pointless.
I thought more cards meant winning.
How can you ask me to play cards at 2am when you're so bad like that?
I just remembered that I didn't give you soft persimmons.
You don't have to lie.
I couldn't sleep, too.
I wonder why old people can't fall asleep easily.
Because our lives are reaching an end.
We can do whatever we didn't get to do before.
How can your granddaughter spend the night at work?
Are you sure she's not with a man?
She's not that kind of a girl.
You never know.
You know nothing about young adults these days.
No one can predict the relationship between a man and a woman.
I just meant that she should get married soon.
She has a goal.
A goal? What is her goal?
You don't have to know.
Women shouldn't have goals. They should just get married well.
- I won. - What?
I won the game.
When did that happen?
It just did.
- Give me the money. - Goodness.
My goodness. Come on.
Let's go.
It's all good.
I dreamed of sleeping in a pile of books.
Why do you want to be a writer?
Well...
Is it because you want to be famous?
Yes.
And you want to make a lot of money, right?
Of course.
And you want to date a good-looking actor, too.
Just like my grandma, you want to date...
Park Bo Gum, Song Joong Ki, and Gong Yoo, right?
It's a lifelong wish.
I'm seeing new sides of you, today.
("Anne of Green Gables")
How disappointing. These are the reasons you want to become a writer.
In fact, I have one more reason.
It's because I don't have my parents.
On TV, I see a lot of parents.
I wondered why I didn't have mine and was living with my grandmother.
My grandmother worked.
Hye Joo and I had a big age gap,
and Cheol Min always went out.
So I spent most of my time alone.
And I was poor extremely.
That's why I used my imagination to make up the things I didn't have.
Your parents weren't around?
No.
I have no memory of them.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be. Why are you sorry?
It means...
I'm going to be a famous writer and make a lot of money.
I'm going to pay you back the debt and quit my job, too.
Watch me. I'm going to be...
the most famous TV drama script writer in Korea.
Anyway, thank you for today.
Don't forget about me when you become a famous writer.
Of course not.
"She was a 11-year-old girl who was wearing a tight and short dress."
"The dress had yellow stains with white..."
"which made her look very unappealing."
"She was wearing a faded straw hat."
"Under the hat, her red hair was thick and..."
"braided into two that was placed behind her back."
- "Her face was small and..." - You read it wrong. It's slim.
You pronounced it wrong. So it's my turn.
"Her face was small and slim with a lot of freckles."
"Her mouth and eyes were big."
"Then color of her eyes became green or gray..."
"depending on her mood and the sunlight."
Don't fall asleep. You'll freeze to death.
- "In short..." - It's wrong.
"In short, any good observers could..."
"think that this homeless girl..."
"might have a rare spirit with her."
Hey, I told you to throw out the trash.
- Move it somewhere else. - Okay.
Always be careful. Just like any other day.
- Okay. - Yes.
Here you go.
Thank you.
I'm sure the floor manager will go over it,
but let me tell you a bit about the job since it's your first time.
Okay.
Your job is to take care of the trash on the construction site.
I see. I understand.
- You're a fast learner. - Yes.
I was a good student.
You have to collect the trash from each floor and put them in a bag.
After that, place it in a designated area on the first floor.
It won't be hard although it might be physically tiring.
That's no excuse.
I need a job.
Let me know if you need help.
Okay.
Well,
how much would...
I get paid if I work here?
We give 130 dollars per day.
I see.
130 dollars per day...
Anyway, thank you so much.
I'll do my best.
Are you talking about that side?
Hey, you. Be careful.
Why are you so careless?
Concentrate on your work.
You'll be seriously injured if you fall from there.
Okay, I'll be careful. I'm sorry.
He is even younger than me.
- I'll instruct them, then. - Okay.
For this side, I think we can follow the blueprint.
We can decide later after we see how it goes.
Okay.
Mother, if you have this,
you can check the balance...
in your account and transfer money, too.
If you download this application, you'll get a text message...
right after someone sends you money.
Look.
You can check the rental fee I sent you yesterday, right?
Goodness. I can check it.
This is amazing.
What a convenient world we live in.
- Of course, it is. - The rent is really in my account.
- You can check it, right? - Yes.
I'm going to be late. I need to work outside this morning.
I'll be in after lunch.
Put every invoice file on my desk. Okay.
Hee Sook is such a pest.
I have a meeting with my clients.
What am I going to do?
She ruined my face.
Who is texting me this early in the morning?
Who is it?
What? Moon Jeong Ae? Who is Moon Jeong Ae?
"Good morning."
Who's sending me a text early in the morning?
Hee Sook.
She's not answering.
Oh, my.
The number one is gone.
What do you mean the number one is gone?
Let me explain. If the person reads your message,
- the number disappears. - That means...
Hye Joo read my message, doesn't it?
Oh, gosh.
I guess Hye Joo read your message, but decided to ignore it.
What? Ignore my message?
A new message.
My goodness.
Who is it this now? Let me do my makeup.
Are you ignoring my message?
(Are you ignoring my message?)
Who is this woman?
Why does she keep talking to me so rudely?
Who are you? Why do you keep sending me messages?
I can't do my makeup because of you.
Don't you have a job?
Look at how she speaks to me.
Oh, my. She must have gone crazy. How could she talk to you like this?
Hold on. I shall teach her a lesson.
- Hold on. - Why aren't you answering me?
If you're going to reply so slowly, don't send me messages.
- You slow fool. - What?
"If you're going to reply so slowly, don't send me messages?"
Mother. Give me your phone. I'll write the messages for you.
Go on, Mother.
Don't you recognize your mother-in-law?
How dare you talk to me that way?
"Don't you recognize your mother-in-law?"
"How dare you talk to me that way?"
I sent it, Mother. I'll add a few more words.
"This is why I hate you so much."
"You always do the things I hate."
"How do you expect me to like you?"
"Also, as the eldest daughter-in-law,"
"you did nothing to help this family."
"You say you have to work, and hardly stay home."
"Isn't that why you look down on me?"
How does that sound, Mother? Was that good?
(Isn't that why you look down on me?)
I didn't know it was her.
Oh, dear. This is crazy.
I forgot that it was Mother. What should I do?
Come upstairs at once!
(Moon Jeong Ae)
How could you save my number with my name?
How could it be "Moon Jeong Ae"? Am I your friend?
Well... It's not that, Mother.
As I started working,
I formed a habit of saving...
people's numbers with their full name.
Don't be ridiculous. That's not an excuse.
No one saves their mother-in-law's number with full name.
Hee Sook. Give me your phone.
Yes, Mother. Please wait.
Here you go.
My dear Mother.
Look at Hee Sook's phone.
It says, "My dear Mother".
Mother. You can change it within three seconds.
You shouldn't believe that.
She also may not mean it.
Whether she meant it or not, I can see it right here.
Do you think people always hide the things they really mean?
Change my name right now.
Yes. I'll change it. I'm sorry.
How does "My respected Mom" sound?
Don't call me Mom.
Then...
"My respected Mother"?
Isn't it too obvious that you don't mean that yourself?
It's fine. Let her.
She should respect me at least for the moment I call her.
Or she will keep looking down on me. "Oh, my. Jeong Ae is calling me."
"Why does Jeong Ae call me so often?"
"Isn't Jeong Ae crazy?"
Mother. Why are you doing this to me?
Isn't that why you ignored my messages?
Mother. This is so unfair to me.
Hurry up and change it.
Okay. I will.
I'm changing it. I'm sorry.
My respected Mother.
Also,
why aren't you paying me rent?
Okay.I'll pay you today.
What happened to your face?
Hee Sook says she bumped her face when she was pushing Ji Hoon's desk.
What happened to you?
I was pushing Chang Soo's desk as well.
Chang Soo doesn't have a desk. He doesn't study.
Stop talking nonsense.
Are you disrespecting me again?
Hey.
- Are you going to keep doing this? - What do you mean?
You're obviously trying to come between me and Mother.
So be a better daughter-in-law to Mother.
What did you say?
Come here.
- No. - Come here.
Use your energy on something else.
If I catch you, I'm going to kill you.
Catch me if you can.
You're dead. Come here.
Hye Joo. Don't you slam the doors.
Are you grumbling because I scolded you?
It wasn't me, Mother.
Why do you hate me so much?
She's no match for me.
Oh, my. It's the director of the boarding school.
Hello, Director?
Now?
Yes. I can go there right away.
Okay. I'll see you later.
Hello, Min Seok?
- What are you doing? - I sent Ji Hoon school,
and I was going to go out as well.
Ji Hoon came to my hospital yesterday.
I sent him there because he doesn't study saying he's sick.
Did you give him a good IV infusion?
What's your plan for today?
I said I was going out. Why?
If it's not something important, come and see me.
- What is it? - We'll talk when you get here.
- Come straight away. - I can't.
I have to see the director of the boarding school for Ji Hoon.
Anyway, I'll call you later, Min Seok.
Hee Sook. Hee Sook!
(Seocho Library)
We're late. Hurry up.
- What is it? - My car is over there.
Look. I'll go first.
Count to 100 and come out. Okay?
Let's just go in together.
We can't go in together.
Just count to 100 before you come. Okay?
Dong Hui!
Count to 100.
Hurry up.
What is this? What time is it?
You're a rookie, but you're the last one to come.
You should come before we do, and work harder than any of us.
I'm the busiest person. Why should I pick up the coffee?
Why were you late?
Have you lost your mind? Does your mind come and go?
How long do I have to keep doing the things a rookie should be doing?
Stop it already. It's not a big deal.
- Be quiet, Ms. Hong. - Be quiet, Ms. Hong.
Please be quiet.
You're all scaring her because she was late once.
Are you going to be late again?
I'm sorry. It won't...
happen again. Never.
- Answer the phone. - Yes, Sir.
Thank you for calling.
This is Oh Dong Hui of FGC Contents Marketing Team.
Yes.
- Good morning, Director Han. - Good morning, Director Han.
The meeting will start in 10 minutes.
Yes. I'm listening. Please go on.
Counting 98, 99,
and 100.
Okay.
I'll bring it to you right now.
Good morning, everyone.
- Is Director Han here? - Yes. He just came in.
Is that so?
He was a bit late today.
- Seong Joon. - Hi.
Why do you look so haggard?
- Do I? - Yes.
Did you stay up all night?
You didn't shave, either.
What are you doing?
You look like a mischievous boy today.
You didn't even change your clothes. I know you're a neat person.
Did you drink last night?
I didn't. Gosh.
What brings you here?
I've made a list of scriptwriters for the TV series next year.
Really? What kind of writers did you pick?
I just included budding writers.
This is unbelievable. Didn't you say you don't like budding writers?
As you know, money matters the most.
Full fledged writers require a great sum of money,
and none of them are available now.
So I selected new writers who has written...
scripts for few short dramas.
What's wrong with her?
Does she always work like that?
She's already lost in dream from the morning.
She's not.
I'll go to the Planning Department.
That's why I told you not to late.
Don't ever be late.
Or you'll become the first intern, assistant writer...
and a dumb who's fired in the first week of working, okay?
Hurry up.
What's wrong? Why are you making a grimace?
Why are you sitting there with a sour face?
Mom, I'm okay.
Don't even try to fool me. Your face tells me...
that you're so depressed and has lost a will to live.
Is it because of Jeong Eun?
I understand. She's such a trouble maker.
She made a fuss all day long even when she was little.
I've never seen anyone so peculiar like her.
I've heard about boys...
who tease and make fun of girls,
but she was the only one I know...
who bullied other girls and even lifted their skirts.
There's more. She won other boys' marbles and game cards.
Then, she shouldn't have hit them at least.
She hit the boys who acted up,
and made us deal with the angry mothers of the boys...
who lined up at our front door.
Mom.
What? Are you mad because I spoke ill of your daughter?
Mom...
Mom,
you were embarrassed when I gave birth to Jeong Eun, right?
Why do you bring that up out of the blue?
Of course, I was embarrassed.
It was long ago, about 30 years.
The world is still harsh to unmarried mothers even now.
And your father was a high-ranking official. Do you remember?
I do.
Why are you crying? Did something happen?
Did you have a big fight with Jeong Eun?
Wait, I must call Jeong Eun over and teach her a lesson.
That's not necessary, Mom.
It's not Jeong Eun's fault.
I just...
kind of feel lonely...
as the weather got cold these days.
That's why I told you...
that kids are useless when they grow up.
I told you so many times to find someone...
and start again.
Hyung Seop and Hye Joo...
willingly registered Jeong Eun as their child...
so that you could live your life. It's you who rejected it.
You didn't even bother to have an interest in any guys.
Do you know how mean you were to the guys?
I know.
What's the matter with you?
Mom, I'll get going.
Thank you for the tea.
Ae Ri.
What on earth happened to you?
What's all this mess?
How could she put her wet laundry on the piano?
What a senseless wench.
Hey!
Jeong Eun!
What's all this?
- What is it this time? - What did you say?
How can you mess the house like this?
I told you to remove that tent.
And the couch isn't something to hang your clothes on.
Why do you put your clothes on it?
I can't believe...
that you placed your wet laundry on my piano.
Don't you know how valuable the piano is to me?
You said I can stay anywhere I want in this house.
But I never said you can do whatever you want here!
Fine. I'll clean up later.
- When? - I'll do it soon.
So I'm asking when you will do it.
I have had...
the house keepr clean this big house only once a week,
and that was just enough.
How can you mess up the whole place right after you moved in?
This isn't even your house.
It's my house.
Do you think you can live like this?
How can you be so rude and conscienceless?
This is why I shouldn't have moved in.
That's what I'm supposed to say.
I shouldn't have let you move in.
I'm the one who had gone out of mind.
We never suit each other well.
I think the same, too.
Fine. I'll move out as soon as possible.
How dare she...
Hey!
Jeong Eun!
When will you clean up?
Jeong Eun! Jeong Eun!
I hate her when she nags me. I must move out.
How should I make money anyway?
Okay.
Thank you.
Gosh, I forgot my bag.
I do have my bag.
I have my bag.
Now, I shall begin the 420th briefing session...
on opening a cafe.
Let me explain the three factors you must check...
before opening a cafe with an initial capital.
You should check the location,
how much capital you have,
and how sustainable your business would be.
How many menus do you have?
Will I be able to make all of them?
We have 12 different coffee drinks...
and about 40 kinds of desserts.
I think I'm not talented in this.
How long will the training take?
I finally found an amazing business.
I saved enough money to secure the startup costs...
thanks to my thrifty and frugal living.
Where should I open it?
The issue is rent.
- Excuse me! - I'll call you later.
- Please be careful. - I'm sorry.
I apologize.
Then, I'll see you later.
Ma'am, who is he? I haven't seen him before.
Haven't you heard of him? He's the one who bought...
all the properties in Bangbae-dong during the last three months.
- He did? - Yes.
- Hello. - Hello.
You'd better be careful.
Sorry?
- I said you need to be careful. - Gosh.
Ms. Jang is...
pretty famous for that.
Pardon? Ms. Jang Yoo Ra?
What do you mean she's famous? She's famous for what?
She takes advantage of men and dates no one.
Even if you give her everything you have, it only lasts three months.
Three months?
That's too short.
She doesn't care about martial status,
but she cares about social status.
Social status?
You don't have a lot of money.
Under diligent and kind parents,
you studied hard and made it all the way here, right?
Right. I did.
Yes, that's true.
Then she won't be interested in...
people like you and me.
- What? - Anyway.
Be careful.
Three months?
No way.
I can last more than three months.
("Today's Current Event")
Did you get home safely that night?
When?
The night when you had the reunion dinner.
Yes, I did.
I got out as soon as I paid,
but you were gone.
I had other engagements.
I see. That's why.
You had other engagements.
I didn't know that. I was disappointed.
I wasn't too disappointed.
I was disappointed just a little.
- Gosh, it's hot. - It's hot.
- This is so hot. - Are you okay?
- It's really hot. - Gosh, look what happened.
What are you doing?
I'm just trying...
Goodness.
I was just trying wipe it.
I just wanted to clean it.
Are you okay?
Hold on.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Let's get ready and leave, everyone.
Okay.
- That was fast. - What?
- You have a meeting today, right? - Yes.
Let's go together. I'm heading that way.
I'm not trying to hit on you.
Ms. Oh. Aren't you going home?
I need to finish what I started first.
That's a great attitude.
If you come late, then you should go home late.
Okay.Goodbye.
Director Kang will be at the vice president's birthday party.
I think this is a great chance for you to meet him.
Goodbye.
We're late.
(Go to college. You can go with your GED.)
(Remember. To love is to share.)
- Add this in, too. - Okay.
It'll be 14 dollars all together.
Excuse me?
- Why is it so expensive? - You don't know?
Snacks nowadays are...
more expensive than food.
Is that so?
Then, I won't take this.
Okay.
- It's 7 dollars and 50 cents. - Okay.
What are you doing again?
I'm sorry.
Hey.
Yes?
- Were you calling me? - Is there someone else here?
Do you want this?
Isn't this sushi?
Thank you.
Don't thank me.
It was buy 1 and get 1 for free when the store was closing.
But still, thank you, Aunt.
It's been so long that I had sushi.
What hasn't been so long for you?
But,
this is for Ji Hoon. So don't touch this.
He's going to eat it when he comes back from his academy.
Ji Hoon is in his room.
What?
Move.
What are you doing? Why are you home?
Han Ji Hoon.
- Because I don't feel well. - What's wrong with you?
I just don't feel well.
What are you mumbling about? Speak up.
- Ah In, is it tasty? - Yes, it is.
Since you can't eat raw fish,
have fried tofu sushi.
Isn't it good?
This is your dinner.
Chang Soo, give me another one.
Okay, here you go.
What do you mean you don't feel well?
You're sick because your mind is weak.
I cook you a good meal. I drive you around so you don't catch a cold.
I get you herbal tonics whenever I can.
I even let you get IV fluids at your uncle's hospital.
How can you feel sick?
So it doesn't matter that your ranking went down, does it?
This is all because you're not concentrating on your study.
Good for you. I just went to look for a boarding academy.
You'll go there this winter vacation.
No, I won't.
- What? - Why should I go there?
Why? You'll go there to study, of course.
- Why should I study, then? - To attend a prestigious college.
We'll decide later if you'll major in law or medicine.
If your grades are not good enough, you can be a professor, too.
What will I do when I become a judge or prosecutor?
How dare you talk like that?
Chang Soo, what's wrong?
What kind of prosecutor will I be?
The kind that collects bribes, chases after power,
and puts innocent people behind bars?
The kind of doctor that only does expensive surgeries to make money?
The kind of professor that only takes care of wealthy students?
Do I have to study day and night to be one of them?
How could you...
What an ungrateful child.
How dare you to talk back to your mom like that?
She didn't give birth to you after having you for 10 months...
just to be treated like this.
She's trying her best...
to give you everything you need.
Who gave birth to you? Did you come from the sky?
I wish you have a son just like you.
That line sounds very similar.
Let's go now.
Mom.
I told you not to get involved with that family.
Why would you come up here?
Mother.
- I didn't want to go up. - Then why did you?
You didn't cook us dinner, but she gave us sushi.
You don't even cook for your children.
You always come home late.
I went grocery shopping.
So I can cook you dinner.
I'm not just talking about today.
The refrigerator is always empty. You don't give us breakfast.
I have lunch at school...
and eat ramyeon for dinner or goes to Grandpa's house.
That's too much, Mom.
I don't ask you for much like other kids.
I only want daily meals. Is it too much to ask?
You brat.
Chang Soo.
Be quiet, Ah In.
I should say the things I have to say.
Go on, then.
Get rid of the rice on your face.
Aunt is a good homemaker. She makes a beautiful home,
and she feeds her son well.
What about you? What do you do for us?
I'm a working mother.
Still, Aunt gets up earlier than you.
She also dresses up when she comes to our school.
When you came to our school, I was so embarrassed.
That's how...
the mother with a son who gets such poor grades dresses.
If I dress up when I go to your school,
people will backbite me and say I only care about my looks, not you.
- Do you understand? - It hurts.
How dare you?
If you like your aunt that much, go and live with her.
Call her Mom instead, you punk.
I would like to if I could.
I wish Aunt was my mom.
What?
Chang Soo.
Hong Gil Dong couldn't call his own mother "Mother".
I understand how he must have felt.
My goodness.
Live upstairs and never come back.
My gosh. It'd be great if he lives upstairs.
That's what I mean.
Go easy.
How did you hurt yourself again?
- Do you work at construction sites? - Nonsense.
What's this?
Pay rent and use the rest as living expenses.
Where did you get this money?
That's not important as long as I didn't steal it.
Put the pain relief patch.
Gosh. I can't take this any more.
My son and wife are driving me crazy.
They always yell at each other, fight, and stop talking.
This is why I don't want to come home.
I can't rely on anyone here.
Also, no matter how upset they may be,
a son should greet his father when he comes home,
and a wife should look at her husband when he comes home.
My gosh.
Plus,
she doesn't even do any of the household chores.
She goes on a strike so often.
Hee Sook. If I have an affair, you have only yourself to blame.
Do you hear me?
It's my underwear.
I should buy a few more pairs.
I'll be going, then. Keep up the good work.
- Goodbye, Sir. - See you tomorrow, Sir.
Mr. Lee.
- Gosh. - Hello.
Are you going somewhere?
Yes. I have some errands to run.
How is working here? Is it okay?
Of course. I'm fine.
Well.
Thank you so much for paying me in advance.
I know it was too much to ask after working here for one day.
Thank you so much for readily granting my request.
We're neighbors. It was no problem at all.
Even if you run away without paying me back, you live across from me.
I can go and catch you right away.
Gosh, Mr. Lee. I wouldn't run away without paying you.
Please just do the jobs I assigned you.
Of course. I will work harder.
Okay. I'll be going now.
Have a good day.
- Okay. You, too. - All right.
(Jinsung Daily News)
It looks like the stockholders are quite happy.
Why wouldn't they be?
After you took over our company,
the annual sales made a surplus.
We're now the third biggest newspaper agency.
Isn't it normal for a enterpriser to make a surplus?
That's why you take over companies.
That's right. There were people waiting to be placed in, right?
Yes. Here are the documents.
They're 10 employees and 22 reporters.
Please give all of them their jobs back.
They're all heads of the household.
You can't fire people so easily.
The company has recovered.
Keep your promise and reinstate them.
Okay, Sir.
But what about Reporter Han?
Reporter Han Seong Hoon got a job at another company.
I see.
I'll get going, then.
Now that this company is making a profit,
we should expand our investment.
I'm thinking about entering the broadcasting industry.
What do you think, Uncle?
I don't know who it is, but it'd be great...
to have such a rich person as one's father, uncle, or brother.
I'm so unlucky. My dad is in faraway land,
and my mom always nags me.
Why are you here instead of being in your own house?
My grandma is mean to me, too.
Why don't I have a rich relative like that?
Jeong Eun. What are you doing?
Can't you tell?
I'm cutting my hair here because I don't have money.
Dear me.
What is it?
It's boiled napa cabbage. Please give this to Ms. Hwang.
Okay.
Tell her to put some of it in the freezer and eat later.
Don't you sleep out again.
I'm sorry.
Don't smile.
I'll be right back.
Dad. Do you want to eat ramyeon?
How can the used amount be 22?
The water meter read 982 last month, and 1,004 this month.
That means 7 of them only used 22.
That doesn't make sense.
Why doesn't it make sense? They must have conserved water.
Are you kidding me?
It'd be more than this even if they used water for cooking only.
Are you really going to do this?
I told you to read the meters, and you fabricated the numbers.
- I didn't fabricate them. - Yes, you did!
My eyes became dim.
Did I read 6 as 0?
- You just keep lying to me. - Stop hitting me.
What? 1,004?
From 982 to 1,004?
Fine. I'll give you wings like a real angel.
This is the spot for the wings, right?
- Here are the wings! - Gosh.
Well... My grandma told me to give you this.
Okay. Thank you.
She said that if you have leftover,
you can put it in the freezer and eat it later.
Okay.
Goodbye, then.
Seong Joon.
Cook ramyeon for me. Let's eat ramyeon.
Your mom wouldn't cook for us. She wants us to eat on our own.
- You're here, Dong Hui. - Hello.
That's good. Please stay and eat ramyeon with us.
I'm fine.
Seong Joon. Cook three packs of ramyeon.
Okay.
- That's... - Please come in.
I just...
- Cook some for me, too. - Me, too.
Hi, Dong Hui.
Me, too.
Cook some for me.
Why would you want to join us? Go in and count the money.
Look at her.
Gosh. Eating with all of you makes it so delicious.
Doesn't it, Grandma?
Hey. Stop eating.
We should eat, too. You're eating it all.
Grandma. I didn't eat that much.
Gosh. Your hair looks ridiculous.
Who is it? Today is a holiday.
Oh, my.
- Gosh. Please come in. - Come this way.
Please come this way. How have you been?
Why did you make him come over in the weekend?
It's all right.
- You're having ramyeon. - Do you want some, too?
- It's okay. - Come on. Have some.
Take a seat here.
Grandma, it's not even enough for us.
Thank you so much. You really came to fix it.
I keep my word.
Please have some fruits with us when it's done.
Okay.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Goodness.
He's such a wonderful guy.
That's nonsense.
He's so sincere and reliable.
And that sincere and reliable guy let his company go under.
What do you mean he let his company go under?
Do you know him well?
I do. I've met him in New York.
- Really? - Really?
Then, tell me what happened.
When did you first meet him?
Forget it, Grandma. Just have some fruits.
- I've fixed it. - Already?
- Then, come have some fruits. - Please come sit.
I'm okay. I'll be leaving, then.
- Why don't you... - Goodbye.
Please have some fruits...
What's the matter? Is he angry?
Why do I have to do this community service in the weekend?
They never let me have my day off.
I can't believe people dump trash in this national cemetery.
It's so shameful.
Did they wipe tears with this?
Ji Hoon, do you have plans today?
I have a private lesson.
- Again? - If I don't take it,
the whole family will be depressed.
Ji Hoon!
Ji Hoon, what's wrong?
Ji Hoon, wake up.
Ji Hoon, are you okay?
Please help me!
Is there anyone? Please help us!
Please help!
He fainted all of a sudden.
- He collapsed. - That way.
Please help.
It's Ji Hoon. Come this way.
Doctor.
Take him to the emergency room.
Did you bring Ji Hoon here? Are you his friend?
I'm Chang Soo and we're cousins.
What? Chang Soo?
(Han Chang Soo)
Han Chang Soo?
Yes.
So you're Chang Soo.
Aunt.
What happened?
Ji Hoon. It's me, your mom.
- Ji Hoon. - We need to talk.
Ji Hoon has the early stage of septicemia.
The early stage of septicemia?
Viruses are found in his blood.
The blood pressure and blood sugar plunged, and that's why he fainted.
Why? Why did he fall ill?
You must know better.
Fatigue and excessive stress caused malfunction of the immune system.
He's been weird recently.
So please don't force him to study.
Min Seok,
you're trying to scare me, aren't you?
If he got septicemia because he studied, every student must have it.
Ji Hoon is in a critical condition.
He must avoid any stressful situation and have enough rest.
That's why I needed you to talk with me.
He has no time to rest now. He'll take the high school exam in a year.
Hee Sook!
When did you come home?
I came home a little late.
Why?
Nothing.
It seems like you worked until late.
Did you have fun at the party?
- Pardon? - You said you'd go to a party.
Right. I just had dinner and came home early.
Ask Moong Chi. I went up to say hello to her.
Please let me do it.
I'm full and even had fruits.
Let's go see if there's any ways to make money.
What are you doing?
Why are you doing this to me?
What's going on?
Tell me what you want.
(Father, I'll Take Care of You)
I want to read it. Please let me be...
the first one to read your script.
You have an important exam tomorrow.
I wish I can switch my mom with his mom.
If you can't defeat your enemy, be its friend.
I'm the one you saw in New York.
I'm David Lee.
Please come down first.
My mom's going to kill me. I don't want to live any more.
I was smaller than him.
What do you mean our boys are switched?