Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 12]
Let's get married.
I really wanted to say this.
I haven't gotten the ring back yet.
But let's get married.
I'm sorry.
I don't want to get married.
Why?
We are as happy as we can be now.
Why do we need to get married?
That's not it.
It's not like we are the only ones
needed for the wedding.
My sisters and brothers
don't even know that I'm sick.
Can you tell your grandmother
that I'm sick?
See? It's giving you a headache already.
Let's just stay like this.
I'm happy as I can possibly be.
It's that hump that we have to
get over anyway.
We still have to try,
even if it is tough.
I want to be Lee So Hye's
legal guardian.
If we submit a marriage certificate,
reporters will find out.
And If I leave, you...
Don't make me a shameless person.
I can never do that.
Why can't you do that?
Marriage is the "event"
that all the couples wait for.
- Why would you avoid that happy event?
- I don't want to do it.
I'm sorry.
I'm tired. I want to be alone.
Okay.
Okay then.
Ryu Hae Sung.
- Oh my.
- Why are you so surprised?
You told me to leave, and
you came here all of a sudden...
Are you upset?
What do you mean upset?
A man should never get upset.
You are upset.
I said no.
I know you are upset.
Yes, I'm upset.
How many times do I have
to get dumped by my Lee So Hye?
I'm getting dumped even when
we are living together.
I'm the Universal Top Star.
My pride is hurt.
Instead, I will grant your wish.
A wish?
I said I will grant your wish
if you quit smoking.
- Are you really going to grant my wish?
- Yes.
What is your wish?
- Can it really be anything?
- Yes. That was my promise.
Gosh.
So I mean...
We were supposed to get married
and go on a honeymoon and...
in a suite that has a great ocean view...
A panoramic view...
I wanted to spend
our first night together.
But since you are so against it...
The suite and the view
don't really matter.
We can just imagine
that we are in a suite.
As long as we feel comfortable...
Gosh.
Lee So Hye, you can't do this.
Are you embarrassed? Is that why
you're pretending like you're asleep?
So Hye.
Lee So Hye. Lee So Hye.
- How could you put foil in there?
- You told me to put it in there.
I told you to put it in the oven.
That's a microwave.
- You should have told me clearly.
- Gosh.
- Fire!
- Get that frying pan.
What are you doing?
Oh.
- Are you awake?
- Good morning, Writer Lee.
I was going to make you
clay-roasted duck.
- But Chang Seok burned it all.
- I did?
- Oh my.
- Who would put that in the microwave?
Throw that away.
- You.
- Leave.
You can't even cook this?
Geez.
I fell asleep all of a sudden
yesterday, right?
Yes. That's not fair.
For that, grant one more wish.
Gosh, that's nonsense.
What do you mean that's nonsense?
I was talking about something very
important. How could you fall asleep?
- Writer Lee, your friend is here.
- Seol.
- You are awake. Hello.
- Welcome. Your hair...
I guess you are making breakfast.
I was going to make you breakfast.
You have perfect timing.
How is your mother?
She got a lot better. Thank you so much.
You found a good nursing home,
and paid everything one year in advance.
My grandmother is there.
I thought it would be nice for them
to spend time together.
But I owe you too much.
I'm not giving it to you for free.
You should pay me back.
Find a job first.
Some will be taken out automatically
from your paycheck every month.
- Stop it.
- Why?
You should be accurate and clear
when it comes to money.
Of course. I will make sure
I pay you back.
So I found a good job for you.
It will also give you a place to stay.
And you will get a chef's paycheck.
How could you find such a job?
I don't even have a cooking license.
Here.
What about our house?
We are desperately looking for a cook.
- What?
- Yes.
Hae Sung and Chang Seok
renovated the guest room.
If you can stay here and
cook for us once in a while
that would be great.
Our So Hye is good at writing.
Cooking isn't...
Okay. I will do my best.
- Chang Seok, we should go.
- Where?
- Have a good time.
- Bye.
Go. Hurry. We don't have time.
Why did you buy so much?
I'm going to cook something delicious.
Why, why, why?
Come here. What are you doing?
Come to your senses.
She is still married.
She will be single soon.
You are going to support me, right?
Okay, I will support you. Go, go.
Stop it. Go.
Hey, this is not right.
What do you want to eat?
What should I make? Just tell me.
I'm Chef Baek.
Hm... Then...
That tteokbokki we used to eat
after school.
Tteokbokki? That's all?
I'm good at making Korean Court Cuisine.
- Oh, then... Japchae.
- You are a japchae killer.
Okay. Just wait.
- Please make something delicious.
- Okay.
What about your husband?
What did your mother-in-law say?
They are scared about that ledger.
They are begging me.
Don't worry about the ledger.
We put in in Hae Sung's safe.
I'm going to prepare the divorce papers
for when I see him.
I have to fight against
the owner of a law firm.
That's right.
Let's find a good lawyer.
Jin Tae knows everyone.
I'm not sure if that will be possible.
Hae Sung left his script here.
- I'll go and give it too him.
- Okay. Be back soon.
Hello.
We have many different designs.
Would you come inside and take a look?
- You look so pretty.
- You look very pretty.
- This is the one for you.
- You look nice.
- Have you decided?
- Should we try other ones?
- There are a lot of pretty dresses.
- They have a lot.
This looks good on you too.
You look so pretty.
- Seol.
- So Hye, where are you?
It has been a long time.
It's so nice to talk to you again.
How have you been?
What? What is wrong with you?
Don't you remember me?
Hey, it's me. Lee So Hye.
Of course I remember you.
What's wrong? Are you joking?
What do you mean joking?
We haven't seen each other for too long.
I missed you so much.
I even dreamed about riding
a motorcycle with you.
So Hye, where are you?
Here? Don't be surprised.
I'm getting married.
Yes, this is Hong Joon Ki.
Oh, yes. Ms. Baek Seol.
Dr. Hong. So Hye is acting strangely.
What do you mean strange?
Let's eat lunch.
Director Yoon, what should we
eat for lunch?
Let's order box lunch.
Director Yoon, we are getting
sick of box lunch.
We could take you to a Chinese
restaurant. How about that?
That's fine by me. What should I eat?
- Stir-fried seafood and vegetables?
- Stir-fried sea cucumber?
- Sweet and sour pork?
- Fried pork belly in soy sauce?
You lost.
Stir-fried meatballs and vegetables.
Yes, Seol. What's up?
Cheongdam-dong? Okay.
Let's have lunch together later.
- Director Yoon.
- What?
Let's order box lunch.
- Black bean noodles.
- Set A.
- Follow me.
- Let's go.
Be careful. The bride is here.
- Wow, you look beautiful.
- You look great.
- You have a very nice figure.
- Really?
It look great on you.
It's very nice.
Seol.
What do you think?
- You look so pretty.
- Right?
Should I try other ones?
Pick one for me.
What kind of dress did you wear?
I didn't even get to
see you wearing a wedding dress.
You didn't invite us to your wedding.
How could you do that?
You didn't keep in touch with us
after getting married.
Do you know how disappointed I was?
I'm sorry.
Why do I even need a friend?
Mi Sun and you.
You guys are all the same.
I couldn't call you
after getting married.
Mi Sun didn't answer my call.
She's always busy taking care of her kid.
Do you know how tough it was for me?
I got betrayed by Hae Sung,
and my miniseries failed.
I had no money, so I had to live
in that tiny room.
Do you know how lonely I was?
I'm sorry, So Hye.
There was nothing I could do.
It must have been very tough for you.
I'm sorry, So Hye.
I should have called you earlier.
Can't you call Mi Sun?
I called her just now.
She said she will be here soon.
Really?
Oh my.
Mr. Ryu Hae Sung, what brings you here?
- So Hye.
- Don't come here.
You should be doing the script reading.
Why did you come here?
If you have time to come here,
go memorize your lines.
Do you want people to keep calling you
"Acting Impotent?"
Do you not have pride?
Please leave. I have nothing more to say.
Gosh. That Universal fool.
I suffered so much because of him.
How could he come here
as if nothing happened?
What? "So Hye?"
Seol, that's pretty too, right?
This is pretty too.
It looks prettier up close.
Don't worry too much.
It's not like she has dementia or
something wrong with her brain.
She is having delirium because
of that medication.
Delirium?
It's a momentary confusion.
It's the side effect of that medication.
- It's common.
- What did she take?
Pain killers contains drug components.
So those components together
caused a problem.
You should talk to her
and take her home.
Don't be too worried.
Relax. Okay?
You are here. How do I look?
How about these?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
It's not the end of world.
She's not that serious.
Please cheer up.
It's just like when my mom was
first diagnosed with dementia.
It's not that, right?
This is different from dementia.
Delirium is a momentary symptom.
Once she calms down...
It won't last long.
So she doesn't have to
go to the hospital?
She will recover faster if she stays
at a familiar place with
her close friends.
Once she comes back to senses and
remembers what she has been doing...
It will confuse her.
It is more serious with the people
who have strong pride
in themselves. Like Writer Lee.
When that happens,
please be calm and console her.
And don't let her skip meals.
She has to eat well to fight off
the side effects.
I will make the foods she likes.
You should go back. I know you are busy.
We will take care of So Hye.
I will stay here until the meeting.
Don't worry. You can go.
Okay.
Welcome.
I came to say goodbye.
I'm leaving Adonis Entertainment today.
I have a goodbye gift for you.
I told you this already. Once the main
character dies, the drama ends.
If you leak this to the media
and make Hitman fail
you will lose a lot too.
Will you be okay?
Our Hae Sung knows so much now.
Yes, I don't want to take a loss.
But Hitman is making me lose
more as we move along.
So I'm just going to end it.
We had a press preview session on
that drama we filmed with newbies.
They were very positive about it.
I'm going to end Hitman
and air that drama instead.
What do you think? I can kill the main
character, but I will still survive.
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Why are you going this far?
I spent all that money and time
to raise an “acting impotent" actor.
But now he is trying to betray me.
On top of that,
do you want me to take losses?
Do you think you could just let this go
if you were me?
Okay. Let's do this then.
I will be responsible for Hitman.
How much will it cost to bombard me?
You will be responsible for Hitman?
You mean you want to let
Lee So Hye keep her last drama?
Wow, this is an amazing love.
It's a tearjerker.
I didn't know
you could be this romantic.
Please do me a favor.
Let me be in charge of Hitman.
Let's settle this.
Will it be okay
even if you have to give me
everything you have?
Yes.
Please make a contract.
I will make one too.
Hey, Ryu Hae Sung.
Consider this carefully.
If this goes wrong,
you will lose everything.
- What are you going to do then?
- What do you mean?
- I will spend less.
- Nothing will be left.
Do you think CEO Choi is going to
let you have Hitman that easily?
She will literally take
everything you have.
So we should do our best to
make Hitman a well-made drama.
I'm going to invest everything,
and make it the best drama ever.
Caring for a patient
is not as easy as it sounds.
On top of that,
you are trying to produce Hitman.
- Can you handle everything?
- I have to do this.
If Hitman fails...
So Hye will be having a very tough time.
That's true.
Have you found an attorney? I think
I should see him before I go filming.
I did. But everyone is related to
CEO Choi's brother's law firm.
This is not good.
There's no attorney?
Didn't Writer Sang Hwa say
she used to go to law school?
That's right. She did say that.
Hey.
- Get up.
- Oh my.
- I said get up. Your client is here.
- Why?
Universal Top Star, Ryu Hae Sung.
Gosh. Why would Ryu Hae Sung come here?
You can come in.
Get up.
Your favorite Ryu Hae Sung is here.
What?
Ryu Hae Sung is really here.
Yes, hello.
Are you really an attorney?
He looks way too young.
He passed the bar exam
with the highest score
and won first place
in the training group.
He is like a walking law encyclopedia.
But he is jobless at the moment,
so he has a lot of free time.
Wow.
- I admire you a lot.
- Me?
I volunteer in the same group you do.
Oh.
With the money that you donate
every year
a lot of people are getting
the help that they need.
I'm Kim Sang Wook.
Sang Wook? Your name sounds familiar.
- Sang Wook. Kim Sang Wook.
- That's great.
It would have been better if
he was Joo Sang Wook.
Anyway. It's great.
By the way. How can I help you?
It is a secret.
Can I trust you?
Of course. I protect my client's
secrets as if they were my own.
When I was adopted and stayed
in the U.S...
At the age of 17, I made a huge mistake.
I'm still getting threatened
because of that incident.
Are they threatening that they will
leak this to the media?
Yes.
If that happens...
I want to know if there's anything
I can do about that.
And I want to know if there's a way
I can stop them beforehand.
We should find a way.
Well.
Can you tell me
what kind of mistake you made?
When did you make that?
I made it just now.
Let's eat. I made your favorites,
tteokbokki and japchae.
Try it. It's amazing.
It looks good.
What about Hae Sung?
What time is it now?
Hae Sung is filming now.
It's three o'clock.
Three o'clock in the afternoon?
It's afternoon?
Seol.
You came here this morning, right?
Yes, that's right.
Then...
I wandered around like a crazy person.
So that was real?
It was not a dream, right?
No.
It's a side effect. It's delirium.
You will get better.
Did I really go to that wedding shop?
And Hae Sung saw that.
This is awful.
This is so embarrassing.
It's okay. You looked just fine.
No.
I really want to die.
I feel sorry to see you guys.
I'm embarrassed.
Hey, do you want to see
who should be more embarrassed?
I worked like a slave for 10 years.
And I cried in front of you guys.
I told you guys I can't do this anymore.
I should be embarrassed.
I'm number one.
Gosh, what are you talking about?
I got into trouble
as a senior in high school.
I've been number one since then.
I'm the champion in that department.
Let's fight.
What if I really lose my mind
and cause you guys trouble?
Don't worry. We are not going
to let you lose your mind.
You know I'm your bodyguard.
That's right. Don't worry about
losing your mind or acting strangely.
We are here for you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Don't cry. It's tiring.
You have to eat well
if you want get get better.
Cheer up. Eat it.
That's right. Let's eat together.
Eat some japchae.
Seol is very good at cooking.
Hae Sung.
So Hye just woke up. She's okay.
Okay.
Hae Sung is almost here.
What?
Gosh. Tell him I'm sleeping.
Thanks for everything.
Where is So Hye? You said she woke up.
She must have been very tired.
She went back to bed.
She fell asleep again?
Why don't you just let her sleep?
I just want to see her face.
I bought a delicious cake.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
Enjoy.
Princess So Hye, are you sleeping?
Are you okay now?
You looked so pretty
in that wedding dress.
Don't worry about it.
It was because of that medication.
I'm thankful that you came back
without getting hurt.
Stop it. I'm overwhelmingly embarrassed.
Don't be like that. Let me see your face.
I'm embarrassed too.
I didn't know you are having such a hard
time. And I asked you to marry me.
I deeply regret saying that.
Once you get all better
I will do a fancy proposal again.
If you reject me then,
I will really be upset.
Then forget everything
you saw this morning.
Why would I forget that?
You looked beautiful.
I should have taken a picture.
Oh my.
Let me see your face.
Don't cover your face.
Gosh, you are mean.
Honey.
It's my fault.
I was drunk,
and I think I lost my mind that day.
How could a son-in-law sing
a celebratory song when
my mother-in-law is in critical
condition? I was out of my mind.
Honey, please call me back.
What about your mother-in-law?
Did you find out where she is?
She had a surgery and got discharged.
She had a surgery?
- With what money?
- How would I know that?
I can't find where she went
after the surgery.
Then where is she?
She doesn't even have relatives.
Did you find her?
You can't get a hold of her yet?
I told you to lie down.
Why did you come here?
How can I stay in bed now?
At an important time like this...
That bitch.
She took our secret file.
We still took her in
even though she couldn't have a child.
How can she repay
our generosity like this?
She wouldn't have submitted it to
the prosecutor's office, right?
Do you think she has the guts
to do that?
She only cares about her mom.
She would need money for the surgery.
She took it to get some money from us.
I told you to just give her the money
for the surgery.
Why are we going through this trouble
because of that 30 million won.
This is making me anxious.
Whether it's a drawing or pottery,
let's sell what we can sell.
And find a place to keep the rest.
I'm too anxious.
I can't even sit straight.
It's her.
Honey.
You heard all of my
voice messages, right?
Now you know I'm deeply regretful
about the things I have done.
You sign it and take care of it.
[A DIVORCE BY CONSENT FORM]
- Honey.
- Stop acting funny.
- I'm not going to be fooled by you.
- I'm sorry. I will never do that again.
I will be nice to my mother-in-law.
Let's move out.
Then you will be free.
I don't trust you at all.
Not even one percent.
Give me one more chance.
We spent all that time together.
We still have feelings for each other.
I'm trying to go up higher. Fly higher.
Are you trying to break my wings?
You know this is a very
important time for me.
That's your business.
Until now, I have been living
according to your plan and time.
From now on, I'm going to live
according to my plan and time.
This is a great time to start fresh.
So did you purposely leave our house?
Is that why you took that file?
What are you going to do with it?
That's my lifeline.
I can't give that back to you until we
get divorced and settle everything.
You didn't even pay taxes
on those illegal assets.
Why don't you donate them all?
Who's supporting you?
Who are you staying with?
I'm at my friend's house. My friends who
are 100 times better than you
gathered everything they have
to pay for my mom's surgery.
Submit this form and call me back
once you have the alimony ready.
Did you come alone?
What about her?
- What about the ledger?
- She wants to get divorced.
- What?
- Once she receives the alimony
she said she will give back that ledger.
She must be out of her mind.
It's strange.
- She has changed.
- So...
How did she get the money to do
the surgery and pay for the nursing home?
She said her friends lent it to her.
Friends? She doesn't have any friends.
Secretary Yang, come to my house.
Now! Right now!
She has been working all day.
She fell asleep.
Seol said she will settle some things
and go see her mom.
She will be back tomorrow.
I will get going.
Thank you, Mi Sun.
Say hello to Pil Ho for me.
So Hye.
So Hye, where are you going?
Stop it, Mr. Ryu Hae Sung.
I have no feelings left for you.
I have a boyfriend. Okay?
So Hye.
Gosh, Universal Fool.
He never gives me a break.
Writer Lee.
What did you just say?
I said "Universal Fool," why?
Why am I a Universal Fool?
You know that better than anyone.
Why do you keep following me?
Do you have nothing to do now?
I told you.
I'm going "all in" on you.
- You can go first.
- Let me give you a ride.
We are going in the same direction.
Same direction? Where are you going?
There. That place you are going.
The one behind that.
Let's go.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Huh?
What is wrong with this?
This is the right password.
Why don't I have the key card?
Did I get my password wrong?
Did I do it again?
I came all the way...
Did I lose my mind again?
You got better faster than before.
Writer Lee, let's go together.
Stop it. I don't want to joke around.
Hold on a second.
We came all the way here.
Let's go on a date.
I want to go home.
What if I do something strange again?
I'm right beside you. Why do you worry?
You don't know how I feel.
It's very scary and awful.
I know what that's like.
I'm trying to be brave to tell you this.
I should have told you this earlier.
I can't delay it anymore.
What do you want to tell me?
It's more like a confession.
I have something to confess.
The reason I had to leave you hurt
for a long time.
The reason I had to
choose CEO Choi back then.
You know that I came
from America, right?
Yes.
I was adopted by a family in America
when I was young.
My mom was Korean.
Even though my father was strict,
they were nice people.
But in less than two years,
they had a baby.
It's obvious what happened after that.
I couldn't get their attention.
And so I caused some trouble
when I was a teenager.
Older kids in the neighborhood
said they would give me some money
so I got in the driver's seat.
There were drugs in that car.
Because of that, I was abandoned
and sent back to Korea.
And thanks to them,
I met Writer Lee So Hye.
And CEO Choi found out about that.
So she used that to her advantage
and dragged you around until now.
There's more to it than that.
CEO Choi found my grandmother.
She used to be my helper.
So I couldn't appear in your drama.
I had no choice.
She stills says she'll reveal everything
if I decline to re-sign with her.
And it will ruin your drama
that you worked so hard on.
You have been saying there's something
you wanted to tell me.
But I didn't even try to listen to you.
I'm mean.
No way. I would have done
the same thing if I was you.
I'm sorry.
How hard was it?
It must have been very tough for you.
My contract with CEO Choi expired today.
I'm going to work alone now.
That's nice. You will do great.
I will tell you once I come up
with a detailed plan.
It's scary for me too.
But I will do great.
So you have to fight too.
- Okay?
- Okay.
We have to cheer up.
Let's do this.
What are all these?
Come here and eat this.
I'm going to eat meat and cheer up.
I have to eat well to get better.
Wow, really?
- Are you feeling okay today?
- Yes.
I'm going to eat all of these.
I'm going to get better and
become Ryu Hae Sung's legal guardian.
- Huh?
- You will need a guardian too.
Am I wrong?
Well.
Let's get married.
Let's turn in
the marriage certificate later.
Let's just have a feast with friends
and have a small wedding.
Gosh.
Hold on.
Are you proposing to me
while you're eating meat?
Yes.
- Ah.
- I don't want it.
This is a lame proposal.
Oh, really?
Then.
What do you think? Is this good enough?
Let's get married.
I don't want it.
I'm going to dump you too.
Okay. Let's get married.
I will marry you.
- It's delicious.
- Isn't it delicious?
When Hae Sung said he wants to be
my legal guardian
I thought I was going to be
a burden on him.
That lame burden that causes him
all the trouble.
But...
I started to think the same thing
he thought of me.
Even though I'm sick and weak
I want to give him comfort.
Then I realized what made him say that.
I envy you guys.
I became braver after I had delirium.
After letting everyone see
my weak side, I feel free.
This is a secret.
I also had delirium after surgery.
You too?
Do you know what I did?
I acted like Batman. I ran around
the hospital in my underwear.
Batman!
- You're telling stories.
- It's true.
At first, I was so embarrassed.
I couldn't keep my head up.
But what's wrong with that?
People who are healthy make mistakes.
You are fighting against cancer.
You can make such mistakes.
But I do have regrets.
I should have found the person I don't
like and punched him in the face.
That's right.
I should have done that too.
It will come back, right? Whether
its delirium or something worse...
We have to go though them all, right?
Don't get discouraged like before.
Let's be positive and endure it all.
Eat well, and cheer up.
- Okay?
- Okay.
What brings you here?
You made a trip to Yeouido.
There's something I want to check.
By any chance...
That story with our Attorney Choi.
That's not true, right?
If it is true,
what difference would it make?
Oh, there will be some changes.
Attorney Choi won't be able
to run for election.
What I was trying to say was...
I was shocked by your mother's
and your attitude that day.
You took that crazy woman's word,
and you treated me like trash.
That's nonsense.
We were too shocked too.
I thought about that.
I thought your family is upright.
But it was disappointing.
Trust and loyalty are the lifelines
of the political field.
But you guys do not own those traits.
I still haven't made my decision.
Should I continue to
lead Attorney Choi his way?
Is that a wise thing to do?
You must be very disappointed in us.
Please forget about that.
We made a huge mistake.
Please forgive us.
Should we have a drink together then?
That sounds great.
I will buy you something delicious.
But I can't settle things
that easily these days.
That diamond wine.
I loved that.
We should drink that wine then.
Yes, yes, sir.
I will come visit you soon.
Please teach me a lot.
Yes.
Attorney Choi, here.
Attorney Kim Sang Wook asked me
to give this to you.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I'm letting you know
that I'm resigning from my position.
As an attorney who fights for the weak
I now know the real dirty side
of Attorney Choi Jin Tae.
I'm breaking my contract
with your law firm.
About the contract signing fee
I received in advance
I added in five percent interest
and paid you back the money
you have given me.
What?
How can he be so impolite?
- Jin Sook.
- You crazy jerk. Geez!
What is wrong with you?
There are people out there.
Don't ever work with Lee Mi Do again.
- You know what I mean, right?
- Why?
Did you meet her?
- What did she say?
- Do you know what kind of woman she is?
She will try to order you around.
Stop it before Mom passes out. Okay?
Okay.
Did you see that wench?
What did she say?
She doesn't listen to me.
I think she has a man.
- What?
- If that is true...
I'm not going to leave her alone.
I'm going to crush everything.
So Hye, where are you?
Oh, you are at the hospital.
I put your dinner in the fridge.
Don't forget to eat it.
Brother.
What brings you here?
I came to visit my friend.
Oh.
I came to see someone too.
How have you been?
I'm not working
at that law firm anymore.
Why? Is it because of me?
No.
It was not the place I thought it was.
I'm searching for another job.
You are going to be a great attorney.
Thank you for everything.
You won't know how comforting that was.
I really wanted to tell you this.
It's relief that I had
a chance to run into you.
Sister.
Huh?
I love you.
Move out from that house.
I will help you.
Sister.
Huh? Oh. What did you say?
I was zoning out. I couldn't hear you.
I said it's a relief to me too that I
have a chance to see you again.
You look a lot better than before.
Really?
Brother.
No, your hand. I will read your palm.
Oh, okay.
Your love line is very good.
You will meet someone nice soon.
Brother.
I wish you all the best.
I wish you all the best too.
Now we are rivals.
I'm just going to produce Hitman.
I'm not good at business.
- If you've read it, sign it.
- Hold on a second.
I want my attorney to be here.
Attorney?
Hello, I'm Hae Sung Entertainment
Corporation's Attorney, Kim Sang Wook.
This contract puts Mr. Ryu Hae Sung
at a disadvantage.
You should revise several conditions.
Which ones?
About Ryu Hae Sung's secret story.
Whatever the reason is,
if it gets leaked to the media
you should be responsible for it.
And you have to pay him three times
the contract fee if you violate it.
I want that
to be added to this contract.
Why would I pay that? It's not like
I'm the only one who knows it.
If you are not the only one who knows
about his secret
there is no reason for us
to sign this contact at all.
And there is too little information
about the budgets spent on Hitman.
You have to include supplemental
information in your budget.
That way, we can plan our budget too.
This is the contract that I made.
Please take a look at this.
Then I can't sign this contract.
Then we will sue you for using
his personal information
to threaten him
and try to wring money out of him.
You look so pretty.
This is the one for you.
- Really? Do I look okay?
- Yes.
Should I take a picture
and send it to Hae Sung?
No, don't do that. It's no fun
if he sees my dress now.
Okay. Let's surprise him.
I will do your makeup that day.
I will cook.
Our So Hye looks so pretty.
Oh. Why did you not go to bed?
Oh. I saw you at the cafe.
Who was that handsome guy?
Oh.
I was riding my motorcycle
and I just came to know him.
We are just like brother and sister.
Did he say he likes you?
It's all finished. I owe him so much.
It didn't seem like it's all done.
His eyes were full of love.
Do you think that makes sense?
I'm still married.
And I'm way older than him.
You should settle your problems first...
But there's nothing that can stop you.
You never know what will happen.
I'm being shameless.
I'm a divorcee. How could I start
a relationship with him?
Forget it.
He is a great person.
If you know someone,
introduce her to him.
Really?
Let's not do that.
It's great to live in a
house together, right?
Once my mom gets better
I will stay by your side
all day, every day.
Let's grow old together.
Okay. Until we become grandmothers,
let's stick tightly together.
So Hye is here.
Why do you want me to sneak out?
You can just come in.
Okay.
What kind of amazing present
do you have for me?
You asked Universal Top Star
to come here.
Joon Ki.
What is wrong with you?
My body doesn't listen to me well.
Backseat. I can't reach...
- Give me that bag.
- Bag?
Should I call 911?
No.
In the bag...
- Orange bottle.
- Orange.
Give me one pill.
Joon Ki.
Hong Joon Ki. Hong Joon Ki!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever