Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[EPISODE 13]
It's nice!
Your company name is Hyesung?
Combining So Hye and Hae Sung,
it's Hyesung Entertainment.
A big star that appears like a comet,
Hyesung Entertainment!
I like it.
This President and Director
of the company are busy filming
so the office is mostly empty.
So Writer Lee
can make herself comfortable
and use it as her work space.
Of course. Only a space of this caliber
will help me write.
How did you remember
all the details here?
Writer Sang Hwa advised us, of course.
I see, I knew it.
Once Hitman is done, I plan to have
a company field trip to Uyuni.
Really?
I should work hard!
Do you know the first thing I have to do
as the president of this company?
Sign a contract with Writer Lee So Hye.
Write down any number you want!
What should I do?
I am a little expensive.
Writer Lee,
please make a good deal for us.
It's the first business that
your future husband is running.
You're right. I will take time
to think about this, President.
Hi, Bro.
So Hye is here.
Why are you asking me to come out
in secret? You can just come up here.
Okay.
What amazing gift did you bring that you
asked this universal star to come down?
Bro, what's wrong?
My body doesn't listen to me.
I can't reach the backseat.
My bag, please.
Your bag...
- Shouldn't we call an ambulance now?
- No.
- The orange pills from the bag...
- The orange pills...
Get me just one pill.
Here.
Bro.
Bro! Hong Joon Ki!
Hong Joon Ki!
Bro! Bro!
Why are you making a fuss?
- Seriously...
- Calm down and quietly...
Check the breathing and pulse.
Don't shake the patient.
That's what I taught you last time.
You get no points!
Are you really all right?
Yeah.
I'm a good actor, aren't I?
I made you practice
for a real situation.
What kind of doctor acts better than me?
Shouldn't we call the hospital now
and ask for an ambulance?
Let's go to the hospital
quietly on our own.
Okay.
Let's switch seats.
Careful! Watch out.
Careful.
Hold on. Hang in there.
We'll get there quickly.
This punk has finally reached my brain.
It's progressing quickly.
It was clean last time.
- Don't tell Jamie.
- Joon Ki, but...
Just for a few days.
I will tell her myself.
Okay.
Hi.
Where are you? You left suddenly
and didn't even call.
- Oh, I had an errand.
- What kind? Did you meet with someone?
It's...
Mr. Hae Sung, you're slacking off because
you don't want to organize, aren't you?
Yeah... Writer Sang Hwa is sharp!
Dr. Hong wanted to play
a game of pool with me.
What? A game of pool?
Yes, he lost last time, so he really
wanted to get back at me.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Stop organizing. Go home and rest now.
Yes, I will head home. Okay.
Hong Joon Ki!
Dr. Hong, wait for me!
Have a seat. Don't stand like that.
There is a way, right?
Surgery or something...
You'll get treatment, right?
When I was little, I had this music box
that I really liked.
Its song was three minutes long,
and when it was over
I kept rewinding it
to listen to it over and over.
Then it was broken.
I cried to have the spring replaced,
but it didn't make any sound.
The music box had already worn out.
I am that music box now.
It's no use,
even if I replace the spring now.
I stuck it out for five years.
I enjoyed everything without any regrets.
I don't want to hang on
with IV lines coming out of everywhere.
That's what I've been thinking.
A week, if that.
What should I do
while I can still walk on my own?
What should I do first?
Mr. Ryu Hae Sung! Let's not be sappy.
Do you like me that much?
Then will you make my wish come true?
Let me borrow Writer Lee for three days.
So that I can have a passionate
relationship for the last time.
What's this? You were crying, but you're
not even granting my final wish.
That's...
What I mean is...
I'm joking.
Can you help me prepare for my funeral?
It's my final party.
Do you plan to do it yourself?
It's the last item on my bucket list.
I wanted to plan it with Writer Lee.
But I think you'll be better
for me to order around.
Let's do that.
You're back?
Who won?
What do you mean?
You said you played pool with Dr. Hong.
After a fierce fight, we were even.
You should've let him win.
Dr. Hong is a really warm person,
the more you get to know him.
Yes.
If I didn't have him,
I couldn't have lasted like this.
I am lucky to have my doctor!
- Were you working?
- Yes, it's going well.
By the way,
when will we have a wedding ceremony?
My friends were asking.
I think it'll be in a few weeks.
I ordered a suit from Italy
but it takes time
because it's made by an artisan.
Why did you order a suit from Italy?
We're having a small wedding.
I'm the universal top star!
No matter how small it is,
I have a base scale to uphold.
Trust me.
I will show you how fashion can explode.
Seriously, you talk about
that explosion every day.
Did you tell Dr. Hong about our wedding?
Not yet.
Once it's set, I'll tell him then.
Okay.
Why does my universal top star
look so down?
I spent all my energy playing pool.
My Princess shouldn't work too hard.
Let's go rest.
I will write just a little more.
It's fun. You should go rest.
I understand, Writer Lee.
I will let you in on the best medication
not just for patients,
but also for guardians.
You don't need a doctor or a pharmacist.
You can do this on your own.
On top of that, it's free!
Everyone, open your mouth wide
and take a deep breath.
This is the natural health booster,
oxygen.
Don't worry about others,
just take in as much as you want!
When we're stressed out,
we take short breaths.
With short breaths, we don't
get enough necessary oxygen.
And the toxins don't leave the body.
That's when cancer cells
come straight up.
Now, one more time!
Slowly, take a deep breath!
Make your money quickly,
make your money quickly...
By the way,
Ms. Pyo Mi Sook is missing today.
She went for prayers.
She wanted to try again.
My goodness.
You should not fast.
You have to eat a lot of good things
so that the good cells
can fight against cancer cells.
If you want to pray,
go to the early morning prayer.
Go after you have good breakfast.
It will also be an exercise.
Isn't it nice?
Do you know this story?
A devout person prayed to God.
"My lord, I believe only in you."
"Please spare me.
Please cure me from cancer."
But, unfortunately he died
and went to Heaven.
And he asked God, "Why did you not
listen to my prayer?"
What do you think God said to him?
Do you know this story?
A devout person prayed to God.
"My lord, I believe only in you."
"Please spare me.
Please cure me from cancer."
But, unfortunately he died
and went to Heaven.
And he asked God, "Why did you not
listen to my prayer?"
What do you think God said to him?
"That's why I sent you a good doctor."
"Why? Did you not listen to the doctor?"
Please, you have to keep
listening to your doctor.
- Do you understand?
- Yes!
You haven't exercised recently,
have you?
I've been busy recently.
It was also a big shock
to have the delirium.
If you don't exercise because you're busy
your body will deteriorate
before you know it.
Make sure to walk twice a day,
30 minutes at a time.
Tell me if it's too much for you.
I'll prescribe oxygen for you.
Yes.
Let's walk together with Seol.
You must be bored to walk alone.
No, I go for walks
with Dr. Hong once in a while.
Should we start the walks again?
I think it's better for you
to walk with your friends.
I'm busy with school work.
Are you eating well,
following the regimen?
Yes, I am trying.
What's the use of trying?
The listed amount here
is the necessary amount.
You have to eat this at least
in order to hold the medication.
Is it hard for you to digest food?
Then tell me.
I'll prescribe digestive medication.
Is there something going on, Dr. Hong?
You're really scary.
It's because a bad patient
doesn't listen to me.
I'll become really busy
with school work now.
So I can't check on every little item.
I got it!
We'll keep her disciplined by her side!
Yes. Please take good care
of this bad patient.
Dr. Hong, do you have any plans?
Should we have lunch together?
I have school work.
Let's take a rain check.
Sure. We'll get going then.
Let's go.
Dr. Hong is a bit odd today.
Is there something going on?
Was he? He seemed to be really kind.
- He has a killer smile.
- Right? He is a great person.
Thinking about it, he couldn't have
been in good condition all the time.
But he's always smiling.
I always whined and moaned.
I've always received a lot from him.
You must feel really secure
to have a doctor like him.
- You should give him a small gift.
- Should I?
- What would be a good gift?
- Does he like anything particular?
It's really true that I've only
received from him.
I've only given answers to, "What would
you like?" and "What do you want to eat?"
But I've never asked him even once.
That's because he's the doctor
and you're the patient.
We call each other a dozen times a day.
But I didn't even know
Dr. Hong's birthday.
I am a really bad patient.
I should write a letter of apology.
Should I bake a cake?
Why would you make it hard for you and
bake it? Just buy one for him.
The ones that are sold
are not good for patients.
I should make one with rye
that's good for health.
Let's go buy the ingredients!
It'll also be my exercise!
Sounds good!
Yo, Bro!
This universal top star emptied out
his schedule until the evening.
How are you doing?
I'm not making a big deal.
Okay, got it.
What's this smell, by the way?
Ouch!
Wait, So Hye! So Hye!
What's this?
I'm baking a cake, but the temperature
is not quite right because it's rye.
Cake...
- Were you baking a cake again?
- Yes.
But this is for Dr. Hong.
Dr. Hong?
Don't be jealous!
It's a gift from a patient to a doctor.
- But...
- Okay, I got it!
I will also make one for you.
Excuse me, it's okay, Writer Lee.
Hae Sung needs to go on a diet.
This is fine because I make a healthy
cake with rye and no sugar.
You don't add any sugar?
Let's please add something in there.
It's okay to add lots of sugar.
But this one is a failure, right?
- Here, perilla seed oil.
- Perilla seed oil! It's so nutty.
- Are they still together?
- They are not.
Where is this punk now?
It's really yummy.
- What is your name...
- Older sister.
- But it's still some connection...
- You are a little brother.
Let's just be brother and sister.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What's your blood type?
Type O.
I have A blood type.
And?
Type A and Type O make the best match...
Don't think about useless things
and study hard!
I'm not a student!
Then make a pretty girlfriend
and go on fun dates.
I left it there!
Sister, did you sleep well?
I didn't know your size...
I will be waiting at the cafe
in front of the hotel.
Hey! What's going on?
Why did Jin Tae
drink so much last night?
He must be really upset these days.
He still went to work on time.
Where is this wench
and what is she doing?
Her mom's at a nursing home.
She moved her to a really nice place.
With what money?
Has she had a secret stash
this whole time?
What's with that?
How can you possibly clean
with that thing?
This is a really rare, old wooden floor.
You should use a rag and polish it
with your hands!
You want me to polish this wide floor
with a rag?
Of course!
Did you think you'd take someone else's
money after doing such a hack job?
Who would clean this two-story, old
house with a rag for that money?
There is no dish washer
or rag cleaner in this big house!
I cannot bear the sight of this!
Why would you look for a dish washer
when you have two normal hands?
No wonder you live that way.
You're so lazy.
Then why you hire someone when you
have two healthy hands yourself?
Look, how can you
talk back at her every time?
Why do you speak to me so rudely?
I'm older than you!
And what?
You can't bear the sight of this?
You're making no sense at all.
Oh my!
That, that...
Where did you find that lowly woman?
Mom, enough is enough! They don't want
to come work at our house!
Seriously.
Whether you have
to give her money or candy...
bring your sister-in-law right now.
She broke all those expensive wines
and crawled out of here.
How can she possibly
stay out so comfortably?
She paid for a year in advance
for the nursing home?
Yes.
Who did? Did Ms. Baek Seol pay herself?
I cannot tell you that much detail.
Are you her family?
Of course.
Ms. Baek Seol is right over there.
Why would you come? I'm on my way out.
Have you been well?
I'll call you back.
I didn't know you had
this kind of audacity.
You know the value of the wines
you broke that day, right?
Mom says she'll forgive you because
you're still her daughter-in-law.
Come back.
They say that the love from hate
is stronger.
The spot you left feels too big.
This is for surgery. I saw that you also
paid for the nursing home in advance.
I don't know what kind of money you used,
but pay it back with this.
I don't need it.
Do you think I'm doing this because
I'm scared of that ledger book?
That's nothing.
Will you take it to the Prosecutor's
Office? Go ahead then.
You'll be the odd one.
Let's just say that what's written
in the ledger is true.
Unless you're an idiot, who would still
keep the items in the ledger?
I made Jin Tae end things with her.
It won't happen again.
It doesn't matter. I told you that day
that I'd get a divorce.
Who'd decide that?
I don't have any more to hear or to say.
Sit down!
Did you have fun with Kim Sang Wook?
You're pretty good
at seducing a younger man.
I thought something was weird that day.
Don't be ridiculous and come back
while I'm being nice to you.
I've never done anything that
goes against my conscience.
You should leave
while I'm still being nice to you.
Secretary Yang.
- Come with us, ma'am.
- Let go of me! Let go!
- Let go!
- That's Seol!
Hey! Hey, Hey!
Lady, are you a gangster?
Why do you force someone
when she doesn't want to go with you?
What's this?
CEO Choi, we meet again here.
Writer Lee...
What kind of picture is this?
We're best friends from high school.
So this was your scenario, Writer Lee.
I knew it...
My sister-in-law is not capable
of starting something like this.
What do you mean, something like this?
What are you talking about?
Stay out of this.
I believe you're not in the condition
to meddle in someone else's business.
You could get hurt really badly.
You're the one to stay out of this.
It won't even take one punch
to take you out.
Who do you think you're threatening?
Step aside! How dare you block my way!
I'm glad I got you today!
I'll pull out all of your hair!
Wait! Wait, Mi Sun!
Stop! Stop!
Don't bother my friends.
I'm going to pull out all of it
next time!
Really, that wench!
Please calm down. Let's go.
How dare she!
What could've happened
if we weren't around?
We can't stay like this.
Let's look for a lawyer first.
I'll look into it.
Thank you.
So, all legal issues regarding HyeSung
Entertainment have been resolved, right?
Yes. The contract with the broadcasting
company has also been signed.
Oh, check this last part please.
I was looking at this part just now.
I feel really secure to have Sang Wook.
You should've been there, Chang Seok.
In front of CEO Choi...
"It's not enough.
In that case, I will file a lawsuit!"
When he said that,
my indigestion of 10 years was gone!
Really? That's awesome.
This is like a great king
earning a flying horse.
You're too kind.
Then what about me?
Was I just a donkey?
Why are you getting upset?
You are...
An arrow of a great archer.
An arrow!
By any chance...
can you take care of a divorce case?
Yes, it's possible.
Oh, that's right!
We were looking for a divorce lawyer.
Are you the one...
Me?
I'm still single!
He doesn't look like he's married!
Here she comes!
Princess So Hye, you're home!
Say hello to our lawyer.
- Hello.
- Oh, you're Sang Hwa's friend.
Hello.
I think I've met you before.
I've heard a lot about you
from Sang Hwa.
I'm your fan, Writer Lee.
You are? Thank you.
Writer Lee, he says he can help
with Ms. Seol's divorce.
Oh, that works! We came together anyway.
Really?
Why are you carrying something so heavy?
You came!
Hello!
Sis!
What brings you here, Brother...
Do you know each other?
Who is he? He's really good looking.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
So we meet again like this.
Were you preparing for a divorce?
You keep catching my embarrassing side.
Divorce is not an embarrassment!
I will help you.
It won't be easy to get a divorce
from the owner of JS Law Firm.
I was going to contact you anyway.
He is suspicious of you and me.
From this moment, just forget everything
that happened between you and me.
Don't call or text me.
Don't answer a call from him either.
I also have the responsibility
in that situation.
I can't do that.
That's why you can't!
Listen to me.
Just shake it off.
Even if he's the owner of JS Law Firm,
I should be able to get a lawyer.
I don't want to get you involved
in things like this.
Let's make sure
we don't run into each other.
Kim Sang Wook is the guy with the
motorcycle you mentioned before, right?
Yes. I will tell you the details
next time.
Since you're already here,
you should sleep over
and have a strategy meeting with So Hye.
I'm nervous that my mom's alone.
I should go.
Okay. Call me if anything happens.
I will look for another lawyer.
Okay. Get some rest. Bye.
Did you meet with her? What did she say?
We need to wrap this up quickly.
Some horrible girls are with her.
There is more, other than Kim Sang Wook?
Writer Lee So Hye!
She's not easy to deal with.
Before it becomes a bigger problem,
we need to sort this out.
- Don't worry. Who am I?
- Do you have a plan?
I do have a plan. Don't worry.
Hey, get in!
What? "Hey"?
Come here!
I'm getting in only because
the color of the car is blue.
Here.
Do I look okay?
But... doesn't he look like a priest?
- Here?
- Yes!
Isn't it nice, just like a priest?
It's noble.
- Yes, you need a tie or a bowtie.
- Put a butterfly or something.
Buy me this one! I like it!
Isn't it too ordinary?
With a bowtie!
- It's too dark.
- It is?
- A bright color.
- A bright color...
Pink!
You're doing this on purpose, right?
This is really...
Yes, the color matching!
- Isn't this pretty?
- It is pretty!
- Put this on.
- I wanted to try this.
It's nice!
- No socks... Take off your socks!
- My socks?
This is not important.
You look great!
Please give them to me.
- Didn't we buy too much?
- Chang Seok likes carrying things.
I like it.
You look great. Great!
You!
Socks!
- Isn't it too much?
- Don't worry.
Now... if we can't find it here, we have
to consider that it doesn't exist.
I have to have it.
You should look in the next section.
How can you say it's not here
after searching for a bit there?
This one is pretty!
Two lovebirds.
What would you like written in there?
Here it is.
2016. I'd like to invite you to
Hong Joon Ki's adieu party.
It looks like we've covered
just about everything.
Do you have anywhere else
you want to go?
[WATCH A MOVIE WITH THE ONE I LOVE
WHILE EATING POPCORN FOR A COUPLE.]
I saw paragliding and skydiving in
movies. Do you want to try those?
I've already done them.
I completed the last item
on my bucket list.
To prepare for my final party,
the funeral.
Dr. Hong! Where are you?
I'm at the hospital.
Why? Did something happen?
No, I was just curious.
Then have a good day.
Did you come to see Dr. Hong?
He's off today.
He's off? Did he go to some conference?
Conference? No, there is no conference.
I see.
Hong Joon Ki! Dr. Hong!
Dr. Hong!
The call cannot be connected, so you
will be transferred to voicemail...
He said he was at the hospital.
Where did he go?
Dr. Hong, you said you were at the
hospital, but you're not around.
This is a healthy cake
that I baked myself. Enjoy!
From Lee So Hye, the good patient.
I bought lots of clothes,
and I feel great!
You can go again next time and buy more.
So Hye was here.
A cake she baked herself!
Lee So Hye, really...
Wow, it looks delicious!
This must be me.
Bro, wait.
Don't eat this.
What? Are you jealous?
Since So Hye made this for me,
I will eat all of this by myself!
But she made an effort.
It's her effort, so here.
I don't know what she put in here...
But I'm sure the ingredients
must be the best quality.
Are you pretty much done
with your party preparation?
Just about.
It was a lot of fun today,
thanks to you.
I still have about two hours
before my filming starts.
Do you want to go anywhere else?
I want to go hang out
at the filming location.
At the filming location?
I'm curious about how
Writer Lee's script gets filmed.
Hello! Hello!
Hello!
This is what a filming studio looks like.
This is really nice!
Bro, since you came all the way here,
do you want to be an extra in the drama?
Why don't you stamp your face
on Writer Lee's drama?
You're dressed so nicely.
It's a waste if you don't.
Really? I do want to try it.
With a line to say, if possible.
Bro! Acting is not that easy.
Why do you think people still
refer to me as "foot acting"?
I have over 10 years
of acting experience.
I know I can do a good job.
Really?
Then you should read a line.
Chang Seok, remember that scene?
Your foot. Oh, yes!
- Your foot...
- It's not that bad.
Here it is! This part.
Here.
Choose one. Do you want to die?
Or do you want to kill me?
Awesome.
He's good.
Should we go straight to the studio?
What studio?
How can you be so sneaky
and attack my stomach?
What the heck is this?
I will protect here!
Receive the power of wind!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What's this?
You looked upset yesterday,
so I made one for you, too.
You liked it last time.
What are you doing?
My So Hye is so pretty!
I'm not interested in a cake like that!
Are you free tomorrow, So Hye?
Until we watch the first episode.
Yes. Why?
Let's go on a date.
Dress nicely...
Don't dress too nice.
Forget it.
Wear something really beautiful.
What are you doing?
- Wear something beautiful.
- Okay.
- Let's go.
- My goodness.
Mister, here.
You should wear socks!
Chang Seok!
What?
So I have to be there?
I have no choice. Okay.
I said, okay!
I have my filming scheduled
all of a sudden.
Really?
You two should watch the movie.
Buy groceries before you come home.
We have no choice. See you later.
Don't eat a meal together.
Juice is as far as you can go!
Bye.
You should wear socks!
Chang Seok, bring it over here.
This is a garden? It's awesome.
- Hurry! Be careful.
- Okay.
Here, this way.
It's nice. Nice.
Oh baby.
Slow...
Hey, then... the energy of death
that the tarot reader mentioned...
You're talking nonsense!
I was just...
I was quoting the song...
Really? Why?
- It doesn't make sense.
- Really.
What do you like, Dr. Hong?
I like ramen.
Dr. Hong, how do you like this one?
I like it.
Are you a good cook?
I'm not good at it, but I enjoy it.
What kind of pasta do you like?
I like oil-based pasta,
something a little spicy.
Okay, then... I should buy some
spicy peppers and jalapeno peppers.
They were over there.
Let's go.
I've really wanted to do this.
"What should we eat?"
"So this is in season these days."
To talk about mundane things, pick
groceries and make a meal together...
An ordinary everyday life.
I think that's real happiness.
I wanted a relationship with passionate
endorphins in my 20's.
But as I got older,
I like subtle love like serotonin.
You're right. I can't be in a passionate
relationship anymore because it's tiring.
You get all of your energy taken out.
Only for the next 10 minutes, herring
in season is on sale for 30 percent!
- Thirty percent?
- It's only for 10 minutes. Where is it?
- Let's hurry.
- Over there.
Are you done with filming, Hae Sung?
You're not eating together, are you?
You're grocery shopping, right?
Hang up please. You're interrupting us.
Buy enough since you're there.
You said you have a lot of money.
Fill up the cart with the most
expensive, best stuff.
The timed sale is almost over.
I'm busy! Bye!
Come home quickly!
- He told us not to eat together.
- Really?
Watch a movie with the one I love
while eating popcorn for a couple.
Shop for groceries until
the cart is completely full.
Feed the one I love and my friends
the food that I cook.
- So Hye, have you ever been on a diet?
- No.
I've been on a me-me diet.
I think you should be on it too.
Why? Did I gain weight?
No, you're too skinny.
"Who wants to eat bread?"
"Me!"
"Who wants beef?"
"I do!"
"Who wants more rice?"
"Me, me!"
This is what the "me, me" diet is about.
It's a necessary diet
for cancer colleagues like us.
No matter what kind of situation it is,
we have to say, "me, me" and eat more!
That's how... we can live.
Yes.
The market is full of cold air.
So you have to wear a scarf
to come here.
Keep yourself warm at all times, okay?
I will. Thank you.
We should go buy eggplants.
Let's go buy eggplants now.
- Scalpel.
Why don't we go with an eggplant dish?
You're trying lots of things.
You can do everything.
Right?
I intimidate a lot of people, right?
What a nice picture!
- You're home!
- Did your filming go well?
For the 3 hours, 26 minutes, and
42 seconds since I called you last time
where have you been and
what have you been doing?
Tell me in 10 minute segments
according to the Five W's.
Has it been that long?
I know. I was having so much fun,
I didn't know time was passing.
My friends will be arriving soon.
What do we do?
We're almost done anyway.
Have a taste of this for me.
How is it?
It's good!
But for me, there is something...
I should add some salt.
But we shouldn't eat salty foods
so let's tell other people
to adjust their taste buds.
Yes, let's do that. I like it.
You two, seriously, what are you doing?
What eggplant dish? I've been watching
you talk about eggplants.
I'll show you what an eggplant dish
should be. Watch me.
- Be careful.
- You should just go.
- Hello!
- We're here!
- Writer Lee!
- Welcome!
- Hello!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Yes?
Sir, how did you find this place...
You must be surprised
that I came to see you all of a sudden.
Can you give me a cup of tea?
I didn't come here to get angry at you.
I came to talk with you.
This evidence has no legal grounds.
Other than the fact that a man
and a woman went into a hotel room
there is no way to prove
what they did in the room.
But things change if the woman is
the wife of the law firm owner
and the man is an employee
of that law firm.
A man went into a hotel room
with his boss' wife?
It is enough evidence to prove
damaged dignity as a lawyer
adultery, and immorality.
With this one photo,
your life as a lawyer is over.
Are you threatening me now?
No.
Despite all of it, I trust you.
That's what I'm telling you.
My wife? She's a good woman.
I also trust my wife.
So, please help me.
I...
I can't live without my wife!
Please convince her to meet with me.
She doesn't even answer my calls.
Please ask her to come out.
No, let's meet together.
The three of us should meet together
and resolve any misunderstanding.
There is one thing I want to check.
What about her bruise that night?
My mother hit her.
They don't get along at all.
My wife can't get pregnant,
so my mother is upset.
That's why I plan to move out.
I already talked to my mother.
Once you get married,
you'll understand my position.
I'm having a really hard time.
I'd rather give up being a politician
than losing my wife.
Please protect my family.
I'm begging you here. Please?
The call cannot be connected, so you
will be transferred to voicemail.
Sis, it's me.
I have to talk with you
about Attorney Choi Jin Tae.
Please pick up the phone.
Sis!
Attorney Kim.
Really? She's coming?
Okay, let's meet there.
Yes, I'll head out now.
My district is near here,
so I use this room
to sleep over in while running
my campaign for election.
You came a long way.
Please get some rest and wait. I'll call
Attorney Kim Sang Wook to come here.
My goodness, you were here?
And you, too!
Have you gone insane?
How can you bring him over to my room?
Kim Sang Wook, you rascal...
- Is this true?
- Yes.
I'd like to request he be removed
from the attorney's list.
But I really do care about your son.
I can't block a young man's bright
future over one mistake.
Sir, please convince him
to change his mind soon.
Father!
What about my wife?
Where did she go?
I came as
Ms. Baek Seol's representative.
- Is something wrong?
- Huh?
Kim Sang Wook!
- Father.
- Why on earth...
did you work for some trash like him?
I turned in my resignation.
I'm sorry I couldn't tell you sooner.
You did well.
Then get back to your work.
I am notifying you
as a representative of Ms. Baek Seol.
We will initiate the official procedure
for a divorce.
What? Are you going to be her lawyer?
I'll see you in court.
[REPRESENTATION AGREEMENT]
I told you not to go.
You didn't need to go!
I wanted to see how he'd act.
I can fight when I know about the enemy.
- Brother.
- I cannot stay out of this case now.
Please sign this now.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes.
We're supposed to watch
the first episode of Hitman today
so we have a lot of guests.
I see. I'll leave now.
- Yes, then...
- Why, why, why?
He's the legal counsel for our company.
Have a seat!
We're going to watch
the first episode here.
Yes, you should watch it with us.
How can you leave now?
You should. What are you doing?
You're stretching my sweater.
[HITMAN]
It's fun!
Ryu Hae Sung's acting is good!
I get at least one good cut
when I do it 10 times.
Was it really good though?
- It was really interesting.
- You'll have good ratings.
Our Writer Lee worked hard
to write the script!
Hae Sung, your action scenes
were really awesome.
That's my specialty.
He's right. Editing was good,
and the music was great!
Since we're all here together,
we should make a toast!
Bottles up!
Hey, hey!
Our good friends here together!
To the next 50 years
that we will share together!
- Right, for the next 100 years!
- Cheers!
Across the bridge
where starlight is flowing
Across the reed field
where the breeze is blowing
Your apartment where no one is around,
where no one is around.
One, two, one two three four!
When the bright moon comes up
A lady's heart is fluttering.
That sound of harmonica
The love song that Sam Dol sings.
That sound of pounding rice cake
the fluttering of this heart.
The fluttering of Yi Ppeun's heart.
Ta-da!
Somehow, tonight...
I feel like you'll come to me.
I don't regret it now.
You're the only one for me.
I hurt because of you.
I can't get you out of my mind.
My love in my eyes...
One day I met you
And I realized the joy of love.
It taught love to even a guy like me.
One day I met you...
One day I met you
And I learned the meaning of love.
And I fell in love.
I tried and tried as I called out
your name again and again.
Even when the tears held my hands and
tried to stop me
I was grateful to have someone like you.
I loved her!
My heart...
I tried and tried
as I called out your name.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
The one who loved only me,
the one who watched over me
[FANTASTIC]
Resolve your family issue today.
Otherwise, I will break that ice.
You're having a cozy time.
Should I put her in a psychiatric ward?
Should I run her over with a dump truck?
If I can be born again, it'll be nice
if three of us were born together.
Ms. Baek Seol! I'm going to call you
Ms. Baek Seol from now on.
To marry someone who has no tomorrow?
How is that possible?
You should tell her.
She should say good-bye.
Let's make sure to meet again.
Stay there for a long time and have fun!
From number two.
Everyone, bye!