Did she get hurt?
Someone call 911.
Baek Seol?
Gosh, it is Seol.
- Seol!
- Seol. Seol!
Seol! Just a moment please.
Step aside please.
Seol, Seol.
- Oh my.
- It's Seol.
Seol. Wake up, Seol.
By any chance, do you know her?
[Episode 2]
[Husband]
- Hello?
I'm Seol's friend Lee So Hye.
Seol got in a car accident.
What? An accident?
What about my wife?
- Did she get hurt a lot?
- I'm not sure.
I will call you back from the hospital.
- So Hye, here.
- Okay.
Where are you going? What about me?
- What about my car?
- Call me later.
- Isn't he Ryu Hae Sung?
- It's Ryu Hae Sung.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Okay. I will call you back.
You guys must have been very surprised.
It's a relief that she wasn't too hurt.
There must have been something wrong with
her car. It was speeding like crazy.
It could have hit her.
She's not good at driving.
She's a coward.
I told her I'd send her a driver.
But she couldn't wait for that.
- Her guardian? Please come in.
- Okay.
She's a coward? She used to ride
a motorcycle with one hand.
Our Ms. Baek Seol.
She must have been coy.
Baek Seol.
Seol.
You guys must have been very surprised.
I met you guys after so long...
I'm only causing trouble for you guys.
What do you mean, trouble?
It's a relief that you are okay.
- Did it hurt a lot?
- I'm okay.
It's a relief that
your pretty face is okay.
- I thought I was going to lose my baby.
- No wonder...
You must be having a late child.
That's not what I meant.
Let's go to her room first.
- We could have just gone home.
- What are you talking about?
You should stay in hospital for few days
and get complete medical examination.
You can't get out of
the hospital until we make sure
that you are okay from head to toe.
That's right. Get checked up.
After effects from traffic accidents
can be scary.
How sweet. I envy her.
My husband said he will get rid of me
if I get sick. So I can't get sick.
He wouldn't mean it. What can be
more precious than a wife to a husband?
You look very tired.
You should get some rest.
You guys met after so long.
And we only caused you guys trouble.
What do you mean?
We are friends. Don't worry about it.
We should get going then.
This fast? Okay, take care.
Call me.
We will invite you guys to our house
once she gets discharged.
Okay.
- I will call you.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you?
People might see us.
Stop. You are disgusting.
I feel like I'm going to throw up.
- How could you say that?
- Get it right.
I only remained silent because
I didn't want to be embarrassed.
I was drunk. That was just a part
of my business. I made a mistake.
You know men do that.
Stop it now.
It's one of the few mistakes I've made.
Are you flawless?
You are infertile, and your father has
debt. Your mother is bedridden.
- I endured all of that.
- I can't wear a mask
and put on a show like you.
- Don't force me to do something.
- Okay, okay.
Take some rest for a few days.
I will talk to Mother.
Secretary Yang. Did you find
a nursing home for Mother-in-law?
Find a place nice and close to Seoul.
And find a good caregiver too.
Okay.
- I will get going. Bye.
- Okay.
- Writer Lee.
- Oh.
Chang Seok.
Oh my. Welcome.
- You should have just called me.
- You should see it in person
and see how serious this is.
My friend Baobin.
Doesn't it look horrible?
It needs a complete makeover,
and it's internal organs are ruptured.
Let the insurance company
take care of it.
Universal top star.
They write articles on pneumonia when
I cough. Why would I cause that trouble?
You go ahead and get
the repair fee from her.
- 16.45 million won.
- What?
I didn't even include the rental fee.
I told you I'm going to
replace the hood too.
- Sir!
- Okay.
- I will take that.
- You have to get that money from her.
- You are responsible for this.
- Don't worry, I won't run away. Then.
Where are you going?
We need to have an idea meeting.
- What?
- Well. I gave you Hollywood-level ideas.
So it's time for you
to show your abilities.
Then I will be waiting for a revised
script for a multidimensional
romantic melodrama.
Baobin...
What? "Universal top star?"
You're a universal dummy.
Why did he follow me there
and cause an accident?
A revised script for a
multidimensional romantic melodrama?
He's not even funny. He won't be
able to handle it even if I write one.
- Hae Sung.
- Your name?
- I'm Park Jung Ah.
Ms. Park Jung Ah.
I love you.
Hitman looks so fun.
Don't miss it. Put it on your SNS.
Spread the word.
Only the main characters will be doing
a script reading today.
Did the revised script come out already?
- When is the reading?
- 6 o'clock.
6 o'clock.
Make a reservation at the beauty shop.
To get my hair done and get a message.
And call my stylist and tell her
to bring a fancy outfit for me.
Let's show Writer Lee
how fashionable I can be.
Okay.
What do you think?
The "Hitman" that is in your mind is
- standing right in front of you, right?
- You prepared a lot.
After the script reading, we will also
be having a style concept meeting.
- Give him the script.
- Okay.
Wow, it looks fresh.
Well then. Let's focus on
the added mellow scenes.
Since those are emotional scenes,
please be focused and be more realistic.
Writer Lee, does this mean I will be
acting as two different characters?
That's right. It says you look just like
K's first lover.
This will be interesting.
Let's get it together then.
Let's begin.
On a cliff near the seashore.
The open car stops. K looks like he
just popped out of a magazine
and gets out of the car.
He stares at something.
Mina is standing at the end of the cliff
and shedding tears.
K gets close to her.
So you did you finally decided to do it?
That marriage?
Mina cries without response.
K starts to tear up,
but he tries to hold it back.
Tear.
K cries as he sneers to himself.
So this is it? It's the love you
talked about? Is this destiny?
- K cries out.
- This isn't it!
That isn't it.
What?
Well. You should...
You should put more feeling into it.
- Let's keep going.
- Okay.
We will keep going then.
Mina looks back at K
with tear-filled eyes.
Please leave me.
That's all you can do for me.
No way. Don't go. Stop.
K becomes more emotional.
Stop there. Stop. Stop.
Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop!
Oh.
I'm sorry. I think I got too emotional.
I felt dizzy.
I will try again.
Okay.
Let me get into the mood.
I will try.
Stop.
That wasn't the right tone of voice.
Again.
Stop. Stop. Stop!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Keep going.
I feel bad, Writer Lee.
I want really want to do well.
My partner must be able to support me.
It must be because
it's his first time acting that role.
He will improve.
I heard he botches a lot of his scenes.
I'm scared.
Really?
Gosh, it took two hours
to do a script reading.
Aren't you thirsty?
What are you doing?
Are you not going to go? Huh?
- Stop.
- What? What did you say?
I said stop the car.
What? You can't understand me either
because I don't enunciate?
Stop the car. Stop! Stop!
- Stop the car. Stop.
- Hey.
Stop it now!
[Patient: Baek Seol]
[Nurse: Lee Yu Jung]
You must have been
very surprised yesterday.
Could you come
visit me before I go home?
To be honest, there are a lot of things
I couldn't say yesterday.
I have a lot of things I want to say.
I heard that you had an car accident.
And I just had to come here.
Put it there and leave.
Yes, I'm here.
I know I'm a bitch and I'm shameless.
I dare say I understand
how shocking it must have been for you.
Still.
I came here because I'm not the type
of person who runs away from my trouble.
Please be generous, and forgive me.
That day...
I drank too much that day.
Let's shake it off.
What are you doing?
I came here to apologize to you.
How dare you...
What's up with that attitude?
What's up with that eye?
Are you crazy?
You can't even do your job right
as a woman. How dare you...
Are you saying you are his wife?
If you had accepted my apology
you wouldn't have gotten hit.
It would have been very nice.
You didn't see anything that day.
Do you understand me?
If you babble about
what happened that day...
It won't end with just
a slap in the face.
I'm a scary person.
I got too emotional.
Let's shake it off.
Let's forget about it.
Let's act like grownups.
Then, I hope you get better.
Oh, Sir. It must be very hard for you.
- Get better soon.
- Thank you.
- Our cute young lady. Get better soon.
- Okay.
Please take care.
How pretty.
That isn't it.
My partner must be able to support me.
He botches a lot of his scenes.
Since you don't know where you stand
people call you "acting impotent."
Hae Sung.
CEO Choi keeps on calling me to
ask when you will be there.
Are you not going?
- Why... Why are you doing this?
- "Why are you doing this?"
What? What did I do?
No... It's because you are upset...
I'm not upset at all.
I was acting just now.
What do you think? Do you still think
I'm "foot acting"?
Gosh, I can't understand this.
Foot acting... Oh my.
That was a fast recovery.
That's an amazing victory of mind.
It's scary.
Wow.
Writer Kim.
Why are you trying to achieve
self-realization in my company?
Is this a script, or a poop?
You are talking too harshly.
I have a right to write
what I want to write.
Really? Then write whatever
you want to write.
I will file a lawsuit then.
See you in court.
Oh, you are here.
You love going to court.
Filing lawsuits must be fun.
Do you know what your nickname is?
I know. Ms. Lawsuit.
Isn't that nice? It's funny.
I've made a lot of money for you.
You should keep your dignity.
I heard you had a script reading.
Did Lee So Hye act up again?
Tell me if you don't like her.
I have tons of other writers
who could replace her.
- Stop it please.
- What?
I finally found an interesting script.
Don't get me distracted.
And don't try to add in those lame PPL.
What is wrong with you?
You are not a amateur.
- Producing a drama is also a business.
- Use something else to do your business.
If you cause a hassle about replacing
the producer or the writer again...
I'm not going to do any of my abroad
schedule next year. I'll disappear.
I heard you had a car accident.
You have Chang Seok.
Why did you drive yourself?
I took care of that with my money.
So don't worry about that.
I heard you were with Lee So Hye.
My nickname is Ms. Lawsuit.
Why do you think I got that name?
What?
Do you still have feelings for her?
Are you writing a book too?
Just continue filing lawsuits.
I'll be going.
I'm sorry. I got too emotional.
I will get into character.
This isn't the right tone of voice.
I will try again.
Was I too harsh on him?
[Top Secret.]
He never gives me a break.
Universal dummy.
Oh my.
What did you just say?
- Why did you come here?
- I came here to get my money.
I don't have a car. So I ran all
the way here. I'm very tired.
She's sick. I can't talk
about repair fees with her now. Hold on.
What about my friend? My friend Baobin
is sick in the body shop.
How long do I have to wait?
You give me the money, then.
Get it from your friend later.
Okay. Give me your account number.
My account number is...
- Didn't CEO Choi call you?
- No. Why?
She talked about some lame PPL.
Just ignore her.
You are good at ignoring people.
You just focus on writing the script.
Romantic melodrama.
- Give me some money to call a cab.
- What did you just say?
Do you want me to run
all the way back home?
Did you say that to me?
"Universal dummy?"
I only take luxury cabs.
I'm a top star.
Now you have 16.42 million won left.
Pay me back as soon as possible.
See you.
Please make me a reservation
for the first day of next month.
Are you finally going this time?
- You've always just asked for advice.
- Please get me a first-class seat.
And find the best hotel
and guide, please.
And show me a list of all the good
restaurants I should go to.
My destination will be Salar de Uyuni.
You said you were busy with work.
Were you trying to
get away without telling me?
I knew you would scold me.
So I didn't tell you. And I got caught.
Wow, I can't let this slide.
Do you have time? No, no. Let's go
together even if you don't have time.
I have to send a package.
Let's go together, and let's get you
scolded for every little thing you did.
Are you trying to go on a date?
Because of my wrongdoings,
I can't even run away.
When did you plan your trip?
It's been a few years.
"The place where the sky and
the ground meet. Salar de Uyuni."
I want to go stand at that place.
- Wow.
- Why?
Oh my.
Wow.
This is amazing.
Wow. I didn't know there was
a pretty road like this in Seoul.
I guess you're usually
stuck in your office working.
There's Dulle-gil Trail. When you look
into it, there are a lot of good places.
Yes. I trap myself in the office,
and all I do is write.
I guess I wanted to be at a beautiful
place at the moment I die.
Like Saint Exupery. The writer who never
came back from a trip.
Doesn't that sound so cool?
What? Don't you think that's cool?
I thought about the same thing
when I was diagnosed with lung cancer.
Did you not know?
It's the secret everyone knows.
You are kidding, right?
I know I'm a humorous man...
but unfortunately, this is true.
At first, I blamed God so much.
Isn't it so lame for a doctor who
specializes in cancer to have cancer?
Anyway. I can't envy you
for entering the cancer world.
But I still welcome you.
Wow, is this like a secret garden?
It's boring to stay in the hospital room.
This is my favorite spot.
Here?
It feels like it's touching the sky.
Right?
Wow, that's right.
It's like Salar de Uyuni.
Wow.
I feel sorry for you...
But it's made me feel better.
Doctors can get cancer too.
I'm not the only one who's sick.
But your days are not numbered, right?
I had stage four cancer too.
It metastasized everywhere.
I thought I would only live about a year.
It has been five years already.
With this rascal in my body.
In the beginning, when I passed out
once or twice
my friends came over and held my hands
and cried for me.
I got better, and I regained
consciousness. Again and again.
Now, it's like "You're still alive?"
As time went by, I realized this.
Living and dying is not
something I can decide.
To say it bluntly,
who's days aren't numbered?
No one knows how or when
he or she will die.
So, today.
You should be thankful for today
and live happily.
So I can go on this trip, right?
Of course.
There's no reason for you to not go.
But you have to go with your doctor.
My doctor...
- So are you going with me?
- Well. I'm...
It costs a lot to take me with you.
But since we are "cancer buddies,"
should I volunteer to go?
But...
Can we really go?
Will I still be alive next month?
What kind of symptoms
will I be experiencing?
Hm. If you don't get treated,
pneumonia will come first.
With high fevers and hemoptysis.
Let's just talk about our trip instead.
About Salar de Uyuni.
That's right. That's great.
One. To go to Salar de Uyuni,
we have to eat really well.
For patients like us,
altitude sickness is the worst.
Two. We have to eat really really well.
We have to boost our immune system.
Three.
Let's eat something delicious.
Okay.
I looked though the CCTV.
She went out about an hour ago.
She left her phone off.
There's no caller record.
- You are Baek Seol's guardian, right?
- Oh, yes.
My wife must have been bored.
She's at home.
She said she wanted to
go home, and I told her to wait.
She just can't wait.
That's a relief.
I was worried where she went.
Thank you for your concerns.
- Please let her get discharged.
- Okay.
Hurry and find her.
- Secretly. Quietly.
- Okay.
These are songs
that can help you find peace.
- Writer Lee.
- Yes?
You look a bit different these days.
- Really?
- How should I say this...
You look more lively.
You look healthier.
- I look healthier?
- Yes.
It seems like you got prettier too.
It looks like you might
be dating someone soon.
Okay.
When is she going to get discharged?
They want to do more tests on her.
She didn't get hurt that much.
She is just wasting money.
She can get checked up
after she comes home.
Don't be like that. She is sick.
Is she our servant?
Why? Did she say that?
Did she say that
we treated her like a servant?
Jeez.
What is wrong with him all of a sudden?
He's taking his wife's side.
He must have done something wrong.
Writer Lee. You are here.
Why are we having
a team dinner all of a sudden?
Let's console Hae Sung.
He was totally depressed after
the script reading yesterday.
Tomorrow is the title shoot.
We should make him feel better.
Totally depressed?
He was full of energy.
He only looks like he is full of energy.
He was embarrassed in front of everyone.
He must be feeling terrible inside.
He's not a kid.
Aren't you being too nice to him?
Forget it. I'm leaving. You said you're
going to manage Ryu Hae Sung.
Writer Lee. Yesterday's reading script,
I knew you wrote it that way
to trick Hae Sung.
But I let you slide on that one.
I didn't intend to do that.
That was not my intention.
You should carry fire in one hand
and water in the other.
Since you tricked him once,
it's time to console him.
Okay, okay.
Let's go in.
Surprise! Writer Lee is here.
Wow, our amazing Writer Lee is here.
- You are late. Have three drinks!
- No, thank you.
Gosh. Don't be like that.
Let's get the wave of bomb shots going.
The one who doesn't drink this is
the one who wants our drama to fail.
If you don't drink this,
you have to do a crab dance.
Crab dance.
Forcing someone to drink...
This is an anachronism.
Everyone should enjoy
the drink that they like.
Look at her.
Writer Lee hates me.
Okay. I will just take your drink then.
Even though tomorrow is only
a title shooting
it's Hitman's first filming session.
- Let's lift our glasses for our Hitman.
- Lift your cup.
When I say "Hitman,"
you guys say "amazing."
- Hitman!
- Amazing!
- Amazing.
Amazing.
By the way. Did you bring cash?
Cash?
Cash? What are you talking about?
Writer Lee's friend crashed into
my precious friend Baobin.
But she hasn't given me
the money to repair it yet.
I'm going to pay you back.
It's because I can't get
a hold of my friend.
What? You can't get a hold of her?
Isn't this a hit-and-run case?
It's hit-and-run. Let's make a report.
Okay. I will pay you now.
Are you satisfied?
What is this?
Where are you going, Writer Lee?
Universal dummy! Jerk!
Writer Lee.
You don't have to withdraw money.
- The repair fees are all paid.
- It's all paid?
Hae Sung told people at our company
that he paid it with his money.
It has been settled already.
He is just joking around.
What is this then? He is trying to
double up on the repair fee?
What? That's not it.
What do you mean that's not it?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
You're breaking our contract.
Contract? What do you mean?
Are you guys dating?
Why do you guys have so many stories?
It's nothing. What contract?
That's nonsense.
Hae Sung must have gotten drunk, right?
I'm totally fine.
You're really good at playing innocent.
Assistant Director.
Send me a text message.
A text message? Okay.
- It can be anything, right?
- Anything is fine.
I'm sorry. I will apologize.
Is that your text alarm tone?
That sounds like Writer Lee's voice.
That's right. It sounds like her, right?
My ringtone is a bit longer. Call me.
- Just a moment please.
- Don't do it.
- What are you doing?
- My ringtone is longer.
- Give it to me.
What's the matter?
My ringtone is longer.
Hey!
Oh my. It looks like
you have a broken nose.
It's broken?
That woman...
Let me take a look.
Tomorrow is the title shooting.
How could a writer break
the main character's nose?
I'm sorry. I must have been drunk.
So why did you make me drink?
I'm not a good drinker.
Shouldn't we postpone tomorrow's filming?
Of course we have to postpone it.
Hitman is not Rambo.
How could he do a title shooting
with that nose?
Okay.
What happened? How did he hurt his nose?
Well. That's...
Well. He fall.
You know Hae Sung has a high nose.
His nose hit the ground first.
What were you doing?
What were you doing when
your actor was breaking his nose?
Tomorrow is the title shooting.
How could you let him drink?
I'm sorry.
I have a call.
Hello?
Yes.
Is she sleeping already?
Seol.
She stole a motorcycle?
She was a so good at
riding that motorcycle.
Did she used be a stuntwoman?
She remained silent,
she wouldn't say a word.
We told her we have to get her
fingerprints. And she called you.
She hasn't made it easy for us.
She is my best friend.
But she has some
unavoidable circumstances.
She can't really tell you guys.
Can I get the contact information
of the owner of the motorcycle?
Yes. The owner doesn't want her
to be charged either.
- You should go and talk to the owner.
- Okay.
Mi Sun didn't even pick up her phone.
What must she be doing with Pil Ho
in this early evening? Gosh.
They are doing well, right?
Don't even get me started. They were
being lovey-dovey in front of me.
You know I have been single forever.
Was his name Seok Won? Their son is
a junior in high school, right?
Yes. He's very handsome.
He only got his parents' best features.
And he is doing well in school too.
- That's a relief.
- Right?
I came out to get some fresh air.
From the moment I saw that motorcycle...
I can't remember anything.
How did I get here?
I must have been out of my mind.
Hey. Nice job.
You are our legendary Baek Seol.
All this motorcycle talk
sounds more like you.
Tell me anything.
Your friend is a famous writer.
You saw me in the station. I can do
anything except for what I can't do.
Hey, eat it.
Why are you crying?
Damn it.
You're making me lose my appetite.
Bunch of girls crying...
The sun is out. Women should be at home.
- It's bad luck.
- What did you just say?
How dare you look at me like that?
What now? Are you going to beat me up?
- Come on. Get up.
- Seol.
Hey, you! Hey!
- Let go!
- Hey!
Let go! Let go!
- This is for our table.
- Hey!
So Hye. Leave. Go! Get out, So Hye!
Hey! You! Hey!
Let's go!
Put it on.
- Hey.
- Let's go!
Get off! Hey!
Seol! Step on it!
Step on it!
What should I do?
I've unintentionally stolen
this motorcycle.
It's okay.
- This is now yours.
- Huh?
I made a deal with its owner
and bought it from him.
Don't you remember?
You gave me a laptop for my birthday.
I've made some money off of it.
This is my present for you.
So Hye.
What do you think? Do you like it?
This is exactly like the one
that I used to have.
I should've gotten in touch
with you earlier.
It's not like I was doing anything
important with my life.
From now on, you just let me know
if you need anything.
I used to be your bodyguard.
Wow, Seol! So charismatic!
Where have you been?
What have you been doing?
I haven't done anything
that might ruin your reputation.
I heard you were at the hospital.
That woman has such a pitiful life.
I don't want to hear about it.
Anyways, let's put all of that
behind us from now on.
Don't rashly act out.
Mother, I'm back.
I see. Are you feeling better now?
Yes. I'm sorry for making you worry.
You seem to be perfectly fine.
I guess you've had a nice vacation.
- Jin Tae had a hard time.
- Sure.
A wife needs to be healthy
for her husband.
Make sure this doesn't happen again.
Yes, Mother.
Mom.
Jin Tae has sent me a humidifier.
He also said he'll take me
to a better nursing home.
That's good to hear.
I feel so shameless just
accepting all these things.
You be good to your husband.
I see you're in a good condition today.
I wish you could always be this healthy.
- Hey.
- Yes, Mother!
Mom, I'll call you back later.
- Go sleep in your bed.
- That's all right.
I got used to sleeping like this
when I was studying for the bar exam.
Should I get you some coffee?
Let's not drink coffee on
an empty stomach. Let's eat.
Should I get some instant rice?
Or instant ramen noodles?
Get changed. Let's go out.
What are you in the mood for?
Tell me anything you want.
Because I'm a meat lover,
I'm in the mood for some meat.
- How about pork belly?
- Let's get some premium beef.
Really? Yes!
Is today some special day?
It's the day we stuff ourselves
with beef until we barf it all out.
Yes!
Hey, Lee So Hye. Long time no see.
- I heard you're starting a new drama.
- Yes.
- You still look so chic.
- Really?
- It's from this new season.
- I see.
- By the way.
- Yeah?
- Give me some money.
- What money?
You've borrowed money from me for all
these events and haven't paid me back.
There's 100,000 won from
the funeral for Director Hong's mother.
100,000 won from
Director Song's wedding.
180,000 won from the birthday party
for Writer Kim's baby.
Oh, really?
- I thought I paid you back.
- No, you haven't.
That's right.
You've also borrowed 10,000 won from me
every time we've met at a cafe.
That by itself probably adds up
to about 100,000 won. Never mind.
Probably over 200,000 won.
You owe me 580,000 won in total.
Really? Oh no. I only have
200,000 won in cash right now.
- Text me your bank account number.
- No. That's all right.
Just give me what you have for now.
And that bracelet. I think that'll do.
No way!
I feel delighted for you.
I hate those people who borrow money
in little sums and never pay you back.
I guess that wasn't so bad.
I should set a date and go around
collecting money from people.
Have I done something wrong?
Is this my last feast
before you fire me?
You remind me of my old self.
Eating kimbap in front of
the computer to save time.
I have regrets.
I should've written fewer lines.
And eaten some healthy food.
I should've gotten some fresh air
and went out for a walk.
We don't even have enough time to
write our script. How could we do that?
Yes? What?
I don't need that. I said
I don't need that. I'm hanging up.
How could you answer a call like that?
Wasn't that your boyfriend?
He said it has been 300 days
since we first met.
He's crazy. Why would he count that?
Hurry and eat.
Go celebrate with him and do it.
What? Do what?
Do it. Do it a lot.
Do it a lot when you can.
This is my congratulatory money
for your wedding.
I'm giving it ahead of time.
Go somewhere pretty and nice with him.
This is amazing.
This is not retirement money
or something, right?
I'm proud of your boyfriend who endured
a workaholic writer like you
for 300 days.
That's why I'm giving that money to you.
You should date someone too.
You're pretty.
You're wasting your beauty.
What about Hong Joon Ki?
He's single.
Really? Would he be okay?
Totally. He is perfect for you.
He is a doctor and
a Director at the hospital.
He looks nice, and
he has a good personality.
Hey, hurry up and eat.
Stop talking nonsense.
Here.
So I have cancer right here.
You are still very pretty.
What a waste.
Did you listen to those songs?
[Writer Lee So Hye.]
[Doctor Hong Joon Ki. Good.]
Are you in the secret garden now?
[Yes. Hm... Writer Lee, make a fist.]
Why?
I'm going to say something embarrassing.
Kekekeke. What is it?
A poet said this.
God made the night to let everyone rest.
And God also made stars.
How could we rest?
I'm trying to make a tight fist.
[Hahaha. I'm sorry.]
There's probably shooting stars
in Salar de Uyuni, right?
I heard half of the sky
is covered with stars.
The night sky is very pretty here too.
It would be nice if
you were here to see it with me.
- How are you going to compensate this?
- Oh my...
How could you ruin this beautiful face?
It will take 10 weeks to heal.
Compensation?
What are you going to do?
I said what are you going to do?
Gosh.
May I kiss you?
Lee So Hye. My goodness.
I get the genre of the drama.
But what's with this kiss scene?
- She's so old-fashioned. Gosh.
- I'm sorry. Let me apologize.
That's right. She must be feeling sorry.
Text me your bank account number
and how much you want.
What's this? She didn't even apologize.
She just wants me to text her?
How could she be so shameless?
She's broken this famous actor's nose!
My goodness.
Why won't he text me
his bank account number?
What's this? Does he want to get
a big sum of money from me?
Let's not get involved with him.
If I get involved with this idiot,
it'll be my loss.
The night sky looks
absolutely beautiful here.
It would be nice if
you were here to see it with me.
- Are you going to sit here?
- Of course. I need to sit down.
- It's uncomfortable. Get a chair.
- Why? This is nice.
- We can't both sit here.
- This is comfortable for me.
My goodness. Lee So Hye.
What have you done...
to this beautiful face?
I don't want to upload
a picture on a day like this.
But my fans will get sad if I don't.
I have no choice. Let's take a photo.
Hae Sung, you can't get sick.
- Are you okay?
- Who did this to you?
Seeing you in pain hurts me too.
My extreme masculinity is hard to mask.
Then for today...
Let's go with a tough man concept
for an explosive response.
How's your nose? Are you okay?
May I kiss you?
- No. That's so gross.
- What?
- Gross?
- Stop it. Stop it.
- Come over here, Chang Suk.
- Stop it. No! Don't!
Chang Suk!
A leather jacket is the epitome
of man's toughness.
A leather jacket.
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
May I kiss you?
I've found it.
What do you think about this one?
- This one is nice.
- Try it on.
You look just like my drama's
main character.
Really?
Because you're such a great model,
that jacket looks so good.
You're the best.
Give it to me. I'll buy it for you.
It's for my drama anyways.
- No way.
- I'll think of it as an investment.
If you hit it big, be good to me.
Don't you dare brush me off
once you become famous.
- What if I do?
- Give it a try. You'll see.
He's not even worth it.
Ryu Hae Sung is horrible at acting,
he lacks basic skills.
He gained stardom because of his looks.
He won't last long.
Maybe one or two years.
Director, he's not even worth your time.
Wow. There are so many stars.
How useless. What do you want?
How was it?
Didn't my gaze make
your heart flutter just now?
Your heart was fluttering, right?
What the heck are you doing?
That is what a kiss scene
should be like.
I thought you should know
what kiss scenes in
romantic dramas should be like.
"May I kiss you?"
Then the male protagonist
starts to kiss her.
As the guy slowly begins to kiss her...
the female character
cautiously closes her eyes.
This is a kiss scene from the eighties.
Nowadays, you need to
have some shocking...
[Fantastic]
When I was finally on stage
after years of training
there's someone who saw my potential.
I'd like to gain recognition
from her again.
I'm not a strange man!
I'm not a criminal on the run.
If you just drive me to a place
with cabs, I'll pay you back.
Instead of paying me back with money,
could you look after my motorcycle?
Sure. If you just leave it here... Sure.
Lee So Hye. She's being so coy!
She seems all innocent,
but she has a fiery side to her.
Can't believe I did that...
This is a biological response.
All right?
Yes. Sure. So what?
If it has metastasized to your lungs,
there is this drug in clinical testing.
Do you know what my goal in life is?
A chair.
When I die
I want 3,000 men to die with me...
What are you doing right now?
You've made my heart flutter
with your kiss.
I can't waste my time
with that kind of stuff.
Every second is precious to me.