Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Your heart was fluttering
just now, right?
Your heart was pounding?
I'm right since you can't say a word.
I'm a fast learner.
Thanks to you,
I'll be able to write great kiss scenes.
Thank you for your ideas!
Crazy! What did you just do?
You're crazy, Lee So Hye!
I'm going crazy here!
That coy girl! You almost fooled me!
[EPISODE 3]
It's okay. I got back at him!
So why is my heart pounding so much?
I just haven't done it in so long.
Yes, it's only a biological reaction.
Okay, so what?
[WOMEN'S REACTIONS AFTER KISSING]
[1. ONE MORE TIME TYPE
2. GAS MASK TYPE]
[3. DIFFICULTY BREATHING TYPE,
STUMBLES AND CANNOT STAND STRAIGHT]
Good morning!
The first shooting continuity is here!
We will be shooting in Pyeongchang.
The offering will be held there, too.
- What? Where?
- Pyeongchang.
What's going on with you
since last night?
You know,
that was my first drama location.
Shall I say, it's like a sacred place
piled up with lots of memories?
- Memories? What kind?
- I have some.
Are you talking about Writer Lee?
What are you saying out of nowhere?
I'm not!
You're not, right?
Of course, I'm the only one he's got.
[FROM THE SHOOTING LOCATION
TO DESTINATION, 10 MINUTES]
Look at this...
It's 10 minutes by car.
Really... you're so coy!
You're so cold, but you would
write something like this?
So you want to take a trip down
memory lane, a pilgrimage of some sort.
- Writer Lee?
- Yes...
You wrote the main character's
name as "Kiss".
Huh?
[KISS MINA KISS KISS MINA KISS]
My gosh, I used the "replace" function,
but something must've gone wrong.
I'm really not feeling great.
I should go to the meeting first.
- With Dr. Hong Joon Ki?
- Yeah.
He asked me to come so he can tell me
something about the script in person.
Hold on!
Wear this for the meeting. You look
the prettiest when you wear this blouse.
Don't go overboard.
Dr. Hong Joon Ki is not my type!
Why do you say no first?
You never know what's going to happen.
He's just not my type!
Who is that?
My type! It's Ryu Hae Sung, Writer Lee!
Welcome!
I thought of my writers
as I was passing by.
Dumplings with glass noodle filling!
How did you know Writer Lee
is a glass noodle fiend?
Really? What coincidence is this?
We'll enjoy them. Thank you.
Out.
Oh, I saw the first shoot continuity.
I really love the location.
- The location? Where is it?
- I heard it's Pyeongchang.
What? Why did they do that?
I'm sure you'd never pick that location!
Sang Hwa, give him a cup of coffee.
How about coffee?
I wanted a cup of Americano just now.
Yes! One Americano!
Well then, I have go to an interview.
Enjoy your coffee and goodbye!
- Let me come with...
- You should drink your coffee.
This is Writer Lee's favorite place.
It's Salar de Uyuni in Bolivia.
By any chance, did Writer Lee
say anything about me?
Well...
She said that you should practice a lot
for the emotional scenes.
Do you know the actor Park Won Sang?
He's worked on four dramas
with Writer Lee
so he knows the tone
of her scripts the best.
He does?
Dr. Hong!
That's what we were talking about.
Hold on.
What's with this? Looking untidy...
- Writer Lee!
- Oh, hi!
I ran a little late.
Not at all. I asked you to come because
I wanted to introduce you to someone.
This is Dr. Jamie. She's dispatched to
the States for clinical research now.
I see.
- Hello.
- Hi.
[SKIN AGE: 20'S. NO NECK WRINKLES]
I heard a lot about you from Dr. Hong.
[HAIR: SHINY
BREAST: C-CUP?]
- Please come this way.
- Wait, I am...
- You should see her.
- Wait, Dr. Hong...
- I'm going to examine you.
- Okay.
It's playing hide-and-seek.
This is why you couldn't
have noticed it at all.
Yes.
If it's spread to the lungs...
there is a pretty good
clinical treatment.
Are you telling me to become a subject
of a clinical experiment?
Not an experiment, it's research.
Although both words
cause some resistance.
I'm not really convinced.
It can't have been vetted.
Of course I can't tell you
it's 100 percent effective.
It's not a complete cure, either.
But the quality of your life
will definitely improve
while you are treated for cancer.
How you live is as important
as how long you live.
Okay, I will think about it.
Yes, take time to think about it
and get your courage up.
Okay, thank you.
Welcome!
It's an honor to meet with you, sir!
No no, stop it! Have a seat.
Director Yoon Chul Hyung asked me,
so I am meeting with you...
But as you know, acting is not
something you can learn, right?
But I really want to do a good job.
And I'm sick of hearing
about my "foot acting."
That's good then.
You're all set.
Now...
that desperation you have right now...
That's the mindset of an actor.
I have been desperate
for a really long time...
but I don't know how. I mean it.
Please at least help me
find a tone for the script.
The tone is each actor's
unique character.
Hae Sung,
I'm sure you can do really well.
I will cheer for you.
Sir, wait. Wait...
This is a show of my innocent heart.
Put it down.
Put it down!
Hey.
You do mean it.
Let's work together.
My Hae Sung, since when did you
want to become an actor? And why?
It was when I was six years old.
Silent night, holy night.
All is calm, all is bright.
Round yon Virgin Mother and Child
Holy Infant so tender and mild
Sleep in heavenly peace
I still cannot forget how touched I was
right at that moment.
When I think about it, I do have
a talent for acting for sure!
We'll see if you have a talent or not.
Anyway, you've been dreaming about the
applause from an audience since then?
Yes.
But I've never gotten
that kind of applause since then.
Not even once?
No, there was this one time.
When I finally got on stage
after years as a trainee...
there was someone who saw my potential.
I want to be recognized by her
one more time.
Okay.
Now, which scenes
do you find so difficult?
This is the scene.
I've practiced so much,
but I still don't know what to feel.
First, no need to make it difficult.
All of the answers
are right here in the script.
Just immerse yourself naturally
in the script...
- Should we try this?
- Yes.
Are you going through
with the wedding after all?
Is this the love you spoke of? Destiny?
This is not right!
Wait, wait... Let me have it.
Okay, look, look... Look.
First, the emotion.
The feel.
Now...
Are you really going through
with the wedding after all?
Was this it?
Is this the love you spoke of?
Is this destiny?
This is not right.
I'm leaving.
No, don't leave. Stop.
Stop. Stop there. Stop there!
I admire you, sir!
No no no...
This is not the answer.
Right, this is not the answer.
This is just how I feel.
Now you need your emotions.
You're not doing this with your head.
Fall into your emotion.
I think I know a little now.
I'll try it again.
Was this it?
Is this the love you spoke of?
Is this destiny?
This is not right!
Fall into your emotion! Here, here!
Fall into your emotion! Your emotion!
I'm sorry to raise my voice,
but let's fall into your emotion.
- Yes, I got it.
- Not your head. Your emotion.
No! Don't go! Stop! Stop right there!
I said, stop! Stop... I said, stop...
Like this? I'm done.
Come over here! Come, come here!
How can you...
The rain...
What happened to your nose?
I got a nosebleed
from acting too passionately.
You know, they say people throw up blood
when they gain a voice of God.
But I got a nosebleed.
Really?
I should've watched you.
I guess it's definitely different
since you're the nation's
representative actor.
Yes.
What's with the shower all of a sudden?
[DID YOU TAKE AN UMBRELLA WITH YOU?]
[YOU'LL GET CANCER IF YOU GET WET
FROM ACID RAIN]
[BE CAREFUL! BECAUSE YOU ARE PRECIOUS!]
She's ignoring me again.
Playing hard to get...
What can I say? Women...
What happens if I push you away?
What are you saying?
My lines! I'm practicing my lines.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
This way, please.
You're home.
Mother, surprise!
My goodness, I'm so glad to see you.
I ran into her at a department store.
We have similar taste.
People might think you're sisters.
We've decided to become sisters.
I'm okay for your adopted daughter,
aren't I, Mother?
It's an honor and a happy occasion!
Seol, bring out something cold to drink.
Yes, Mother.
No, I'm hungry.
Give me some food please.
She gave me a government
content development project.
I wanted to treat her to a nice place,
but she really wanted to eat at home.
I used that as an excuse
to see you, Mother.
I'm glad you came.
Seol, grill the short ribs
and make the soybean stew and
a few of the vegetable dishes.
Yes, Mother.
By the way, will Jin Tae be late?
Call him and tell him that
Assemblywoman Lee is here!
Should I?
Jin Tae must've heard us.
How did you come so early?
Did you know we were coming?
No, I got your call as I was
getting out of my car.
- Wow, what brings you here?
- To surprise you!
I really didn't know about this.
What am I supposed to do?
She came as my sister's guest.
I can't leave now.
This will never happen again.
Just get through today, okay?
What are you doing?
- Wash some fruits. I'll peel them.
- Yes.
Everything is great. I'd like to come
here and eat this food every day.
- You should be careful!
- I'm sorry, Mother.
I admire you, President Choi.
To jump into the
entertainment business as a woman
and to come all the way here...
It's not easy at all. It's human victory.
Seriously, this is an industry
of the uncivilized.
I really had a tough time.
I'm tearing up.
Don't worry. I'm here for you.
Now, only good things
will happen to you.
You'll come out
at the top of the industry.
And Attorney Choi
will enter the Assembly Hall!
I have my faith in you!
Of course! No need to say the obvious
in the family.
I was told that a precious one
will enter our house this year.
And it is you, Assemblywoman Lee.
Mother, don't be so formal with me.
I am your adopted daughter.
- We're family!
Oh, do you have plans for vacation?
I'd like to invite you
to my vacation house.
I can adjust my schedule.
What about you?
He's the owner.
Of course he can find time for vacation.
I'll adjust my schedule.
My gosh, I get to taste Ms. Baek's food
three times a day?
I'm so happy!
Thanks to you, we get to go on family
vacation this year. It's been a while.
Let's go shop for swimsuits,
all three of us!
Oh my, really?
It'll be so much fun! Right, Mother?
Is this Traffic Control?
The lights in front
of the post office in Yeouido.
If it's not fixed quickly
innocent citizens can get hurt
and even die from auto accidents.
On top of that, the guiding sound for
the hearing impaired is broken.
Yes, please come quickly.
I will be waiting here.
I'm sorry. I'm late because I had to
take care of something important.
It's okay, I came a little late too.
By the way, you look better
in person than in picture.
- You look better in picture.
- Excuse me?
It's a joke.
I'm sorry if it wasn't funny.
You should order something.
You know, it feels stuffy sometimes.
I feel refreshed
when I drive this route.
Please stop over there for a bit.
If you really want me to.
What do you want to do on the road
where there is no light?
Your driver's license
should be taken away.
Sorry?
Four traffic light violations
and I can't even count how many times
you went over the speed limit.
You didn't even turn on the signal
when you changed lanes.
You may think that it's okay
if you just pay fines.
But you could cause
a large-scale accident.
And in case of a big accident
responsibility also lies on the
passenger who didn't stop the speeding.
What the...
- It's no fun at all!
- It's not fun for me either.
Get out. I will drive.
What kind of shitty punk is this?
Get lost!
Look! Hey!
You should at least take me home!
[FOOT ACTING]
Look at this... She's ignoring me again.
Enough with playing hard to get,
Lee So Hye!
Fine, I admire your effort, so I will
gladly be pulled by you this time.
[FOOT ACTING]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Kim Sang Wook!
I'm not scared! I'm strong!
Hello! Hello!
Hello! Excuse me! Mister! Mister, Mister!
You're so mean!
I'm not a weird person.
I'm not a runaway criminal.
Something happened,
and I got left behind.
If you could just take me to an area with
cars, I'll make sure to pay you back!
If you want, my ID...
Thank you! Thank you!
Wait, wait! Wait!
Thank you so much!
You even brought me all the way home.
How much should I pay you...
What I have is...
Instead of paying me,
can you hold on to my motorcycle?
I don't have a place to park it.
It's good.
I mean, it's a good environment
to park the motorcycle.
Thank you!
Please take care of it.
Okay!
Your eyes have gotten a lot better.
You must've gotten acting lessons.
Yes. Park Won Sang helped me.
I knew it. Your eyes are different now.
- Really?
- One more time! Let's go!
Come out all the way here.
Then these people
can come out from here.
Let's make use of the stage.
Don't forget, okay?
Hey, I'm not here. If someone
looks for me, tell him I'm not here.
How do I turn this off?
Sir!
I'm here!
Oh... you came!
After you helped me last time,
everyone tells me I've gotten better.
Thank you!
That's great.
I'm glad to hear it.
It's a scene with only one line today.
But I'm a bit confused about the
pronunciation, and how to say it.
Okay... as you hand a gun
to the woman you love...
Try it, try it.
- Go ahead.
- Yes.
Choose one. Will you die?
Or will you kill me?
So you're asking questions.
I don't think all of them are questions.
Look at me.
Choose one. Will you die,
or will you kill me?
Of course you are...
No no, try it again. Try it again.
Choose one.
Will you die? Or will you kill me?
Leave!
Go, go, go! Leave, you bastard!
Go away, go! You bastard, go away!
Go! I said, leave!
Go away, go away! Go away!
That's good!
- That's good.
- Really?
Thank you, sir!
Thank you. Thank you, sir!
Go on now! Good luck!
Let's go!
Go, go!
- Thank you!
Writer Lee will faint from shock
at the first taping.
[LOOK FORWARD TO ACTION SCENES
PERFORMED WITHOUT A STUNTMAN!]
[IT'S A BREACH OF CONTRACT
IF YOU IGNORE MY TEXT AGAIN!]
The phone has been turned off...
What? She turned it off?
[DR. HONG JOON KI]
Did you sleep well?
How...
Your glands are swollen,
so you must feel pain in your throat.
You have acute pneumonia.
Now... the hell gate is open.
Come on, it's not that bad.
You're recovering well.
Now...
things like this will get worse...
and repeat themselves...
And then I'll die, right?
When you get better, let's talk again
about clinical treatment.
I'd like to be alone.
Okay. Get some rest.
One... two... three.
Did you eat?
Oops, I got caught up to deliver food.
Your meal is here!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
May I help you?
I'll take it!
So Hye!
- Isn't that pretty?
- Yeah.
- It's pretty, isn't it?
- It's really pretty.
I'll try this on.
It's beautiful.
Your hand.
- Ms. Baek Seol?
- Yes.
Thank you.
I'd like lots of shiny sparkles.
- Please make me look sexy.
- Yes, I got it.
This place is
really about Gangnam style.
Watch carefully
and put it to use in your shop.
Chefs go to all the famous restaurants.
I should.
Thank you, So Hye.
How can I pay you back for this?
It's really pretty.
Show yourself wearing it soon.
Let's go for a fun ride again.
Sounds good! I'll join next time!
I'll go for a fun ride in my truck!
Honey, I got waxing.
I said, I got waxing.
Forget it.
Just drink up the mulberry energy drink.
And tell Seok Won to sleep over
at his friend's house.
Mr. Pil Ho must be dying to see you.
You should go before traffic starts.
I look really sexy. Thank you!
Thanks to you, I got to have the most
luxurious time in my life.
When you're done, take a picture of
yourself and send it to me.
- I'll get going.
- Okay, bye.
Economy...
Article 8, Clause 1...
[JS LAW FIRM]
Oh my, I thought a model was walking in.
How can the top scorer from the bar exam
be so tall and handsome?
You're too kind.
Have a seat.
I'm sure better law firms
tried to offer you a job.
Attorney Choi Jin Tae,
you're my role model.
Really?
I feel honored.
You were born rich, but you live
an honest life of sharing with others.
It is my ultimate goal
to become a human rights lawyer
who helps people in difficulty.
So I'd like to learn from you.
You're a wholesome young man.
- Let's do better together!
- Yes, sir!
If you don't have plans,
let's have dinner together.
We have lawyers' dinner tonight.
I'm sorry, I already have plans tonight.
Have you been well?
You still can't reach her?
No. She must be writing the script.
When it's not going well,
she goes silent.
Do you know Writer Lee's friend
Jo Mi Sun's number?
She has a lettuce farm and a hair salon.
I don't know.
Do you have something urgent?
I just...
Lettuce from there is really delicious,
and I'm totally out of it.
She said she'd be leaving
for the offering tomorrow
so she'll be back before that.
Sure, okay.
See you tomorrow, Writer Sang Hwa.
Bye.
Please come often. If you come regularly,
you'll look like a celebrity.
Yes, I will.
I heard you were writing the script.
Is this where you go silent?
We should talk.
- I'm busy.
- I'm also busy, and I'm hungry.
Buy me a sandwich.
You still owe me 16.42 million won.
I'm a top star, so I can find quality in
a sandwich only from a place like this.
By the way,
where were you going all dressed up?
Mind your own business,
and just order a sandwich.
I also want a glass of wine.
Goodness, they only have
such expensive wines.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, ma'am.
Would you like to order?
Give me everything on this menu.
And the best one for wine, please.
No, I'll have the most expensive one.
- We will order shortly.
- Sure.
What's with you?
I want to settle my debt quickly.
Take the food and the wine
as an interest payment.
And I'll give you the rest later.
I have no money left
because I spent a little today.
You know, I got nothing
back then and even now.
I'll send the money as soon as I hand
over the script and receive my payment.
Why are you acting this way?
You're scary.
Mr. Ryu Hae Sung, you like money.
Why is it scary when I offer you money
that you like so much?
Order your food quickly,
and then eat it quickly.
I don't have a second to waste.
What are you doing right now?
You kissed me
and made my heart flutter...
Oh, that?
It was a joke, of course.
Was there ever sincerity between us?
Is this because of what happened?
You really have no shame.
Even an apology wouldn't be enough.
If I apologized, would you accept it?
I tried!
- But you wouldn't even hear it.
- Because it was worthless.
I'll pay the bill, so eat your food.
You want me to apologize,
but it's not worthwhile to hear it?
- It makes no sense!
- You don't make any sense either!
Fine, what should I do?
What can I do for you?
I'm sorry. I had no choice!
Let go of me!
Don't ever bring it up again.
I have no time to waste
over such petty things!
Writer Lee, we're in big trouble!
Ryu Hae Sung signed a contract
with President Choi.
It's just a rumor. It's not true.
The news is out.
He's on our rival show.
[FIERCE ROOKIE RYU HAE SUNG
MAKES HOME AT ADONIS ENTERTAINMENT]
Our director is up in arms and
the TV station turned upside down.
[CHOSEN AS THE LEAD
OF A MTC MINI SERIES]
Didn't he make a promise with you
that he'd do our series?
This is Writer Lee So Hye. Let me talk
to Ryu Hae Sung, it's urgent.
Writer Lee, this is Choi Jin Sook.
Listen up.
Ryu Hae Sung signed a contract with me
under the condition
he wouldn't do your series.
I'll speak to Ryu Hae Sung directly.
Let me talk to him.
Hold on.
He doesn't want to talk to you.
What the heck is this?
How can you make me look so ridiculous?
What are you going to do?
We even have a complete staff!
This is humiliating...
I'm sorry.
Just wait and see.
I'm going to bury Ryu Hae Sung alive!
He's not even worth it.
Ryu Hae Sung can't act,
and he has no basics at all.
He only got famous because of his looks.
How long could he possibly last?
A year or two, tops.
It's not even worthwhile
to deal with him.
Still, how can he betray
the writer who supported him
just because he got a little famous?
It's turned out better, actually.
Let's find a solution quickly.
How about Ha Yeon? I think he's good.
Sir, I'll head somewhere else,
not Bundang.
Welcome!
How many do you have in the party?
Are you by yourself?
- No, my friends are coming.
- I see, come this way.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
What are you doing?
My goodness, what brings our
Ms. Lawsuit all the way here?
I heard our ace was skipping dinner and
practicing, so of course I should come.
What is your real business?
Get to the point fast.
The CEO of a
Chinese entertainment company
invited you to
his daughter's birthday party.
I'll ask to have it scheduled
when there is no shooting
so let's go for two days.
We agreed that there won't be anything
scheduled while I shoot this drama.
Do I need to read the contract to you
again? I would've said no if I could.
You have to go to this one.
What do I have to do
to get away from you?
Can I do that if I retire?
That's also a breach of contract.
It's until I tell you to retire.
- It'll be over only when I die?
- I'm on your side.
Don't try to run away,
and hold on tight.
It hurts more if you fall from high up.
I'm leaving.
Jamie?
You got caught!
Here you go.
Hey!
Awesome.
Bravo!
Jamie, great! You're it!
Wow, I wanted to play around
just like you.
Two-timing! Multiple-timing!
How great is this?
You, that's how you should live.
You should keep
living on like that forever!
You seem to have had too much to drink.
Are you all right?
Okay!
Don't you worry! I'll keep this secret
from Dr. Hong Joon Ki!
You're awesome! Have fun!
Have fun!
I like it! I like it!
Go! Go!
Hi, Joon Ki. Your patient who disappeared
is at a night club now.
She's completely drunk.
We should hang out together!
You're having all the fun by yourself!
Are you looking for me?
She's my younger sister.
We don't look alike at all, do we?
My brother is really not my type.
Have fun now!
You're Jamie's older brother?
Brother!
Brother...
Are you okay?
Thank you, Brother.
I'm fine!
To tell you the truth,
I spent a lot of money today.
For the first time in my life,
really a lot.
I went crazy with shopping.
You did well! You must've
also gotten your hair done.
You look pretty.
I look pretty? Really?
I did this, too.
I have a secret. Should I tell you?
I got waxing done.
- What?
- Waxing!
Brazilian waxing!
Once you get treated for cancer,
you'll lose them anyway. Why?
Cancer treatment...
I didn't know that!
- You know I'm joking, right?
- Yes.
I canceled my trip to Uyuni.
I won't get to go anyway...
I'll just spend it all.
So I spent it all.
Do you know what my life goal is?
What is it?
Queen Uija.
Like Queen Uija, I want to have 3,000
male servants die with me when I die.
- All 3,000 of them?
- Yes!
But I really don't have time
to seduce 3,000 men.
I should've had fun sooner.
Queen Uija...
I'm Queen Uija because I've only been
sitting on the chair (WORD PLAY)
and writing.
But...
If I die alone...
I think I'll be so scared and lonely.
Other people have kids and husbands...
But I have no one.
By myself... I will be so sick...
I was so scared...
I'm here for you, your cancer colleague.
Oh, that's right.
Will you go out with me?
Why aren't you answering me?
Did I just get rejected?
Can't you just go out with me, Honey?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[FANTASTIC]
Writer Lee,
you'll watch the shoot, right?
I won't use a stuntman at all,
I'll do it all myself.
Watch me.
- What's that?
- What? What?
Am I still foot acting?
Really, he's giving me no break.
What's your blood type?
What's your ideal type in men?
Don't ask about my personal life,
let's just be brother and sister.
- I'll call you soon.
- Sounds good, Miss Sister.
Writer Lee, are you dating someone?
Dr. Hong is really forward.
- You are a doctor?
- I work at Sungdong Hospital.
So you're a hired doctor
who receives salary!
He's the director of the hospital.
I would've never made that decision
if I knew I was leaning towards it.
Come right now. If you don't come,
I'll do something to Lee So Hye.
You know that I'm someone who does
what she says she will.