Subtitles by DramaFever
By the way...
If I die alone...
I think it will be too lonely and scary.
Other people have kids.
And husbands.
But I have no one.
Alone... It will hurt a lot.
It's very scary.
You have me. Cancer friend.
Oh, that's right.
Will you date me then?
Oh. You...
Wait. What's your name?
No, your phone number...
Then give me your email address.
No! No!
[Episode 4]
Oh, it was a dream.
That scared me.
Good morning, Writer Lee...
Are you getting ready?
The car is waiting for you.
You have to hurry.
Writer Lee.
- Oh, let me take a shower.
- Okay.
You didn't pack your stuff yet, right?
I'll pack it for you. Take your time.
- Pack my stuff?
- Today is the first day of shooting.
And we have to do our rituals too.
There's a car waiting for you.
Oh, okay.
Oh my, Writer Lee, you got
your nails done. It's so pretty.
It looks chic. Are you dating someone?
She should get married.
Who is it, Writer Lee?
By any chance... Director Hong?
She is not feeling well.
She is dating someone, right?
I think so.
Just say it outloud.
I'm not dating anyone.
I went to get my hair done and
I did my nails just to refresh myself.
I'm getting carsick.
I'm going to take a nap.
I think she is dating someone.
We have today's schedule.
- Today's schedule is out?
- Yes, Director Yoon. Today...
You are looking at the wrong page.
- You're here.
- Yes, I'm here. It's going well, right?
Yes. Hae Sung has been here since dawn.
He's getting ready for the rehearsal.
- Hello.
Wow, our Actor Ryu.
You are really working hard.
You look very nice.
Shall we check the camera angle?
Wow, this looks great.
- What is this?
- You jerk!
You bastard!
This is my land.
What in the world are you all doing here?
I'm sorry. He's a neighbor.
He's been here for a while.
- Mister, you have to leave now.
- Leave.
- Buy him a lunch.
- You guys get out.
Hey!
Why are you looking at
me like that, you bitch.
Do you want to die?
Are you laughing?
Are you laughing? Huh?
What... What are you doing?
Jump off from there,
and we should use the helicam.
- And the next scene will be over--
- Yes.
Oh. What... What is that?
- Isn't that Writer Lee?
- It's Writer Lee.
Hey, Hung Jong, hurry and go over there.
So Hye, are you okay?
Lee So Hye!
I'm okay.
Actor Ryu! Writer Lee!
- Come this way.
- Oh, it hurts.
- Wow.
- Writer Lee, are you okay?
- You could have been in big trouble.
- I'm okay.
I thought I was going to
have a heartattack.
You ran all the way and jumped off...
You are really hitman K.
Just like a scene in thedrama...
- Then why did you all stay away? Huh?
- What?
Well...
You guys should have filmed
that fantastic scene.
No one filmed it, right?
Director, the camera was not on, right?
Gosh. That scene would have been amazing.
What is it like to be coming back
to life, Writer Lee?
The sky was very pretty and blue.
If I had died, I would not have been able
to see this pretty sky.
Since the weather is nice, our first
filming is going to be amazing.
That's what I thought.
Our Writer Lee is okay.
She is joking around again.
Director Yoon, filming will be over
before dark right?
- Hye Sung has to go to China today.
- Why is he going to China?
China's best Media Group President
sent a special invitation to Hye Sung.
The President's daughter is Ms. China.
I heard she likes our Hye Sung very much.
I will be there for just a day.
I will be back before the next filming
in two days.
We have no problem with that then.
- Hurry and go.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- What?
- Are you okay? Did you get hurt?
Oh my. What should we do?
Hye Sung, hold on. Excuse me!
I fooled you, right?
Do you still think I'm "foot acting?"
You scared me. What should I do with you?
Why are you hitting your lifesaver?
You should thank me...
Forget it.
Writer Lee.
- You are going to see me filming, right?
- Of course.
I'm going to do all my scenes myself.
No stuntman.
Keep an eye on me.
Hye Sung. You were amazing.
You guys say that every day.
I'm getting tired of it.
I said I'm okay.
Let's start filming. Standby.
- Be careful.
- Okay.
Ready.
Action.
Looking at it from here,
out at the set
it was a great idea to
become a writer, right?
Yes. My heart is full.
Whenever you get a chance,
come out to the set and look.
You will get fresh ideas and
you will feel more responsible.
Okay.
Going on a date. Please pick my clothes.
Do you want to get dumped?
- Please tell me I just didn't see that.
- This is terrible. Forget it.
There must be a right answer to this
multiple choice. But I don't see one.
You will get dumped 100 percent.
You could get slapped too.
- Get rid of that belt.
- I can't take this anymore. Stop it.
God, please save him.
Did he really pay for those clothes?
Oh, it's going to rain in the evening.
Excuse me. Did you not see
a motorcycle parked here?
Oh, that motorcycle? Follow me.
Why is this here?
Oh, well...
I heard it was going to rain today.
It could get rained on.
Since this is not mine.
I'm keeping it for you.
Oh. I should have asked
for your permission.
I'm sorry.
What?
I'm sorry. I'm just laughing.
You have a kind heart.
No, it's nothing.
You have a pretty smile.
I'm very thankful, but I'm causing you
too much trouble.
I will move it somewhere else.
What? No, no, no. You can't do that.
I already paid the parking fee.
If we leave that spot empty,
we are wasting money.
And the guard will be disappointed.
There's a high chance that
it will cause illegal dumping.
It will be monsoon season soon.
Are you going to keep it here?
- It will be inconvenient for you.
- Oh.
I bought a waterproof cover for
the motorcycle.
It is the "rocket delivery," so
it will be here tomorrow at the latest.
How much was it? I will pay for
the waterproof cover--
That's okay. Instead...
I would be very thankful
if you could give me a ride.
Your cell phone.
Oh, yes. Here.
You look way younger than me.
Is it okay if speak down to you?
What? Oh, sure.
I'll text you for a quick ride soon.
A quick ride. Wow.
I like that. A quick ride.
Then I will get going.
Okay. It's going to rain today.
Take an umbrella...
Bye!
Let's keep it down.
Are you the only one living here?
He scared me. Wow.
He's a funny guy.
- Yes?
- Where are you?
Mom told you to hurry
and unclog the toilet.
Did you call me to say that?
Everyone is going to Jeju today.
Including Mother.
Hurry and go home. Start packing
and unclog the toilet.
Mother doesn't like
strangers visiting our house.
Okay.
A quick ride.
Writer Lee.
I called a cab.
- Can you really go alone?
- It's okay.
I have some things to think about.
And I will finish writing Episode 11.
Did you find a place to stay?
Yes, I found one. There's a cabin
I stayed at the last time I was here.
Okay. Call me if you need anything.
Okay.
[Dr. Hong]
I waxed.
Waxing. Brazilian waxing.
- Do you want to date me?
- Why are you not answering?
- Did I just get dumped?
- Can't you just date me "Brother?"
Yes, she is right here.
It's Dr. Hong Joon Ki.
Yes, Dr. Hong. I'm in Pyeongchang.
I was going to give you a lecture,
but you are too far away.
Oh. We had to do a ritual ceremony
for our drama.
I guess you don't have a hangover.
That's a relief.
Oh, yes.
Then are you coming back tonight?
No, I'm going to take a break here.
That's nice.
Eat delicious food, and don't forget to
take your medicine.
If you are not feeling well,
call me whenever.
Okay, thank you.
Oh, Dr. Hong is very enthusiastic.
What did he say?
Did he ask you out on a date?
Stop it.
I'm not going to take it anymore.
I will get going.
Cut. Okay.
Thanks for the hard work, Director Yoon.
Actor Ryu, you are doing great today.
Keep doing what you are doing.
Hae Sung. Thanks for the hard work today.
You were amazing.
Gosh, that was nothing.
Well. Where is Writer So Hye?
She said she has a cabin
that she used to go to.
She will be writing her script there.
A cabin...
What are you doing?
Let's hurry and go.
We have to go straight to the airport.
CEO Choi is making a fuss.
She wants us to leave quickly.
- Okay. See you later, Writer Sang Hwa.
- Okay.
Gosh, what is this? The actor is acting
so hard and she is not even here.
Why was she in a hurry?
Why would she go to the cabin alone?
Why are you looking for Writer Lee?
You are hiding something, right?
I already told you no.
Who are you looking at?
I'm standing here,
right in front of you.
What the!
What is this?
Gosh, he never gives me a break.
Are you going to the cabin?
- Yes.
- What should we do?
Our cabin is under construction
until tomorrow.
Oh, really?
- Well...
- Let's just go in.
You came all the way here.
The room in the front is all done.
Thank you.
Why do I have nothing to wear?
I should have gone shopping today.
Just wear hanbok.
Reporters will be there too. If they take
pictures of you wearing luxury goods...
- it will cause a ruckus.
- It's a bazaar on the Jeju beach.
- Hanbok doesn't seem right.
- I don't like seeing middle-aged women
with bellies walking around
in tight clothes.
This could cover my belly.
What do you think?
- Are you ready?
- What should I wear?
- Should I wear hanbok?
- You should wear hanbok.
- Why are you not getting ready?
- Are you crazy?
How could you take her
to a place like that?
It's a bazaar that all the former and
present political officials go to.
Do you want them to
make fun of our family?
But everyone is coming with their spouse.
You are going to escort Lee Hyo Won.
It will look awkward
if you bring her along.
Forget it.
This is an important gathering.
Do you want to ruin everything?
Hey, fold it so that
it won't get wrinkled.
The skirt and the accessories. Don't
leave anything out. Put everything back.
- Okay.
- Mom.
Don't wear a diamond ring.
Wear a pearl ring.
Will you be okay?
I don't want to follow you guys at all.
Just leave.
Don't make me more miserable.
Yes, Auntie.
Attorney Choi's dress code? It's navy.
She should wear navy too.
You guys should dress like a couple.
I want to go too. It has been
a while since I have been to Jeju.
Please take good care
of our Attorney Choi.
Okay.
Be nice to Assemblywoman Lee.
Buy her a drink tonight.
- Do you need my credit card?
- Forget it. You buy her a drink.
I can't go to Jeju. I'm going on
a business trip to China.
You packed my travel bag too, right?
- Bring it out.
- Okay, Jin Sook.
Don't worry. Nothing will happen
even if I go there.
I'm just doing my business.
Do whatever you want.
I don't care.
Get my shoes too.
Mom, drop me off at my office.
Bye.
What are you doing?
You are holding onto it for too long.
Get over it.
Go out and eat something delicious.
Why are you not coming--
- You're going to spoil her.
- Jin Sook.
Don't wander around.
Pick her up on time from the tutor.
Okay? Come now.
Mi Sun. What are you doing today?
Are you busy?
Why does it have to be today?
It's my mother-in-law's birthday.
Who is it? The Snow White?
What? That's not even funny.
That bitch.
Your sister-in-law is hilarious.
Why does she want you to
pick her daughter up?
Hey, send her here.
I will make her bald.
Be gentle. You might pull my hair off.
This is disappointing.
It's so hard for you to make time.
That's what I mean.
So Hye is away too.
- Hey Seol, Seol.
- Oh, Pil.
I heard you guys are
still very much in love.
Totally.
But I'm not as good as I used to be.
She is taking all my energy away.
I'm getting weak.
I envy you guys.
Okay, see you next time.
Okay.
A quick ride now?
Yes.
Let's go.
I will be there in 20 minutes.
Get ready.
Yes, sir!
That had to hurt.
What do we do?
- Gosh.
You are still very humorous.
Our Writer Lee is napping too long.
You won't sleep at night then.
Get up. Okay?
You got up?
No wonder you looked familiar.
I can recognize her now.
Come here and eat some watermelon.
That's right. She didn't change a bit.
She looks the same.
You should have told us earlier.
- Come here.
- Please come here.
Didn't you say you were going to China?
Oh, that trip?
I canceled it. I'm tired.
Since I'm here, I came to visit them.
I really didn't think that
you would be here.
Hye Sung came here once every year.
That's why there was a panel of him
by the entrance.
After Hye Sung's fan club visited here
his fans from China visit here often.
Thanks to Hye Sung, we make a living.
That's because this is a good place.
It's not because of me.
Gosh.
You guys must be hungry.
Go get some lettuce.
I will cook some meat for you guys.
Lettuce. You know I'm good at that.
- Let's go. Hurry.
- What?
Wow.
They have some fresh lettuce, right?
They are all my kids.
- I sowed the seeds.
- No way.
He came here with his grandmother
and planted them all.
It was very nice to see his grandmother
and him together.
If I had a daughter, I would love to
have him as my son-in-law.
He would be the perfect husband.
Right?
Oh, and get some chili peppers too.
Pick large ones.
Are you crazy? Do you think CEO Choi
is going to leave you alone?
Just tell her my depression came back
and I got off the grid.
Disappeared to where?
If you tell her that, how is that
getting off the grid?
Do you think I don't know this?
You are going to see Writer Lee, right?
- Can't you trust me?
- You are making me not to trust you.
- Chang Seok.
- Forget it. Go.
Go. Go!
You go.
I need the car too.
You will be there. You are coming, right?
You are going to come late, right?
I trust you.
Don't say anything. Keep it shut.
Yes. I'm your man!
Go!
Go.
Hurry and come here.
The meat is burning.
Okay.
This place is like the Holy Land
to motorcyclists.
They have good food, and they sell
motorcycle gear and clothes.
Let's go in.
Huh?
[Notice: Closed three days
for summer vacation.]
Who goes on vacation in September?
They do.
I knew this might happen.
I searched for another place.
[We are going out of business.
Thank you for being our loyal customer.]
I have one more place to go.
It's a really good place.
I was going to take you there once
we got to know each other more.
It's the most popular place. Let's go.
- Should I drive?
- That's okay.
The address is...
This is the right address.
When did it change?
Oh, please don't misunderstand me.
This place had so many good reviews.
It was the place to go on a date.
So I... Gosh.
Hop on.
It's very delicious.
This was not my plan.
Why? It's the most delicious food
I've had in the past year.
Really?
Still.
The weather is nice today.
And the air is fresh too.
So...
- What's your blood type?
- Type O.
I'm type A.
- So what?
- Well.
I heard Type A and Type O people
get along easily.
What's your sign?
Are you going to check our signs too?
Oh, it's just for fun.
I was just curious.
Here you go. Aren't you going
to read my palm?
Oh, okay.
So this means...
I'm sorry. I don't know how
to read palms. I haven't study that yet.
What's your ideal type?
My ideal type?
I'm okay as long as
the person is not an attorney.
What?
Oh... Why?
Why do you not like attorneys?
It's a great occupation.
- I just don't like them.
- Were you treated unfairly--
Stop. That's enough.
You will get hurt
if you get to know too much about me.
Let me ask you just one more thing.
What is your name?
- "Older Sister."
- Gosh.
We should get to know each other.
I'm Kim--
You are a "Younger Brother."
Let's just be a brother and a sister.
Don't ask about each other's personal
life. Let's just be riding friends.
That's enough.
If you don't like that, I will move
my motorcycle to a new spot.
No. I like that. Good.
Okay.
- Let's get going.
- Already?
I still have a lot of ramen left.
This... Wait.
Then did you guys meet after 10 years?
- Yes.
- Why did you guys not keep in touch?
- Did you guys fight?
- Gosh. Why would you ask such a thing?
They are together now.
That's what counts.
But I'm curious.
Writer Lee is
the perfect person for you.
Why did you only bring "cutie" here?
Cutie?
Oh, there's someone. Cutie.
Gray-haired cutie.
- Hae Sung's grandmother.
- Oh.
Honey, stop that.
Look at that sky.
Finish your meals and
go look at the stars.
Take a ride in the open car.
- Open car?
- Sure.
You can play harmonica on your way there.
It's the special route that
we discovered.
- You will regret it if you miss it.
- That's right.
- Okay.
- Hurry and eat.
Is that the "open car?"
It is the open car.
Then where is the harmonica?
By the time you finish this,
you will be on the top of the mountain.
Go get a lot of stars.
- Do you like it?
- Huh?
- Let's go.
Why is this not working again?
Jeez.
What's wrong?
Did the tire pop?
It has been like this since this morning.
And it finally popped.
What do we do then? Can't you fix it?
Don't worry.
Jeez. I left my tools.
Gosh. Stay here for just a while.
Look at the stars. I will go down and
bring the tools. I will be back soon.
What about the car key?
I took it out of there.
You put some drinks and
a blanket there too, right?
I left them wine glasses
and some food too.
- Good job.
- We did everything we can do.
If he still can't tell her
that he likes her
he is not a man.
- Gosh.
- Let's go.
Oh no!
What was that?
I heard they have bears here.
- Really?
- Yes.
- Look at that!
- What? Why?
You scared me!
I...
Gosh.
- By the way...
- You can say it first.
- You go ahead.
Today on the mountain...
Thank you.
What did you say?
We're at a high altitude.
I can't hear you.
Thank you for...
saving me.
I was very remorseful.
A lot.
For a long time.
Every day.
Back then, I didn't know how important
of a decision that was.
If I knew that things would turn out
like this because of that decision...
If...
I could go back...
I wouldn't have made that choice.
Never.
Hello?
- No, I mean "roger"
- Hae Sung, It's me.
We have a guest here.
- A guest?
- He said he is Writer Lee's friend.
- What did you say your name is?
- I'm Hong Joon Ki.
Hong Joon Ki?
- He said he is Hong Joon Ki.
- What?
Give it to me.
What? Who? Dr. Hong Joon Ki is here?
Well. Press this and talk.
Where are you, Writer Lee?
Well. Oh, yes...
I'm up on the mountain. To watch stars...
Did you go night hiking?
That's great.
Take your time. I'll be waiting for you.
Okay.
I will be there soon. Hold on.
What is this? How did he come here?
Who is he?
You are all by yourself.
Who would come to the cabin?
He is a doctor and
an adviser for our drama.
Why would an adviser come here?
Isn't he a fake doctor?
You said you are going to work on your
script. Why did you call a doctor?
Are you sick?
What do you mean I'm sick?
Why would he come here then?
How did you come here?
Writer Sang Hwa gave me a special tip.
I have something to give you.
And I wanted to refresh myself.
Oh, this is Ryu Hye Sung.
Hello.
- He is the main character of our drama.
- Oh.
Nice to meet you. I'm Hong Joon Ki.
Do you not know me?
I don't really watch TV.
I'm sorry that I couldn't recognize you.
You are kidding, right?
- Do you really not know me?
- No.
I guess he only stays at home.
My pictures are everywhere on the street.
- Can we talk for a minute?
- Yes.
I just had to make a visit
because of this spoiled patient.
I'm really okay.
Sang Hwa shouldn't have done that.
What is he putting his hand on?
It's okay. Your patient had an emergency.
Your patient seems more urgent.
Take one now.
Then that jerk...
Hong Joon Ki.
- Doctor.
- Yes?
You should come here.
I'm sure you didn't eat dinner.
Let's have a BBQ party.
- Oh, okay.
- Let's do that.
Here, Dr. Hong.
So you are a doctor?
Yes. I work at the Sungdong Hospital.
You don't own a hospital.
So you take a paycheck home.
He's the Director of the Hospital.
Sungdong Hospital...
That Medical Center...
You are "high-class" then.
No, that's not it.
Celebrities are high-class these days.
He helps elders who are homeless.
He does a lot of charity work.
Hae Sung donates a lot
whenever there is
a huge earthquake or a flood.
That's nothing. That's what I should do.
Here. We have more beef.
You should eat some.
We had dinner already.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Give me one too.
- You should eat too.
- Okay.
Let me have a lettuce. A lettuce.
Eat this one.
One more.
- Go inside.
- Okay.
- When should we meet next...
- Next time?
We should go to the places
we couldn't go today.
Ms. Older Sister.
Ms. Older Sister?
You said your name is Older Sister.
Don't get distracted and study hard.
I'm not a student. I'm an attor--
No.
I'm an adult.
I work at a nice company.
And I'm not that young.
Then find a pretty girlfriend.
And go on a fun date.
I'm leaving.
You are crazy, Kim Sang Wook.
I miss her already.
What must she do for a living?
She always leaves when the time is up.
Like Cinderella.
She is attractive.
The beef tastes like a sausage.
Sausage?
- Didn't you eat sausage?
- Did I eat sausage?
We are out of firewood.
Can someone go get some firewood?
- Okay, I will...
- I will...
You are a guest. You can stay here.
I will go get some.
Okay. Eat some more, Dr. Hong.
Where is the firewood...
We have some here.
It's very...
- Oh my.
- Hae Sung.
Are you okay?
Does it hurt? Here?
Earlier today, I jumped off
from a high cliff.
Because of some woman.
- Relax.
- I am relaxing.
This is my muscle.
We should take an x-ray to be sure.
I think either you fractured
or broke your rib.
- What?
You must have been under a lot of pain.
A man should be able
to endure some pain.
- Hello?
- Ryu Hae Sung is there, right?
What? Who are you?
Don't you know your Company Director's
phone number?
Put Hae Sung on the phone.
- She wants to talk to you.
- Who?
- This is Ryu Hae Sung.
- Are you crazy?
You turned your phone off.
What are you doing there?
20 billion won is on the line.
Yes. Excuse me.
Yes.
I never said I'd go there.
Stop talking nonsense,
and come here now.
What? You don't want to drive?
Should I send you a helicopter?
This project is worth 20 billion won.
If we fail to merge with China Media,
are you going to be responsible for it?
Why is that because of me?
Why do I have to go to President Wang's
Daughter's birthday party?
Am I her boyfriend or a fiancee?
We could go that way. It's better than
causing a scandal with Lee So Hye.
Come here now. If you don't,
I'm not going to leave Lee So Hye alone.
You know how I do things.
It will be better for you
to come here now.
Are you sure you will be okay?
I'm a man. This is nothing.
Are you going to China?
They desperately want me there.
They said they sent me a flight.
I should get going.
Focus on writing your script.
Don't go watch stars.
Bye.
Our society is very conservative.
If this leaks out to the media,
you can't be an actor.
That will be the end of everything.
You don't necessarily have to
work with me.
But I found this. Do you think other
companies can't find this?
I think you will need
someone to shield you.
I'm really good at those things.
Mr. Ryu Hae Sung is a funny person.
Yes.
It seems like you have
known him for a while.
Hm... Yes.
- But, will it be okay?
- What?
He's hurt. I'm not sure
if he is okay to drive.
He should be okay.
How did he get hurt?
There was an accident
at the filming site.
I could have died from
falling off a cliff. Not from cancer.
It could have been very serious.
Then by any chance...
Is Mr. Ryu Hae Sung your Number One Man?
What?
Oh.
Please forget about
what happened yesterday.
Yesterday?
Did something happen yesterday?
Oh, this...
Did you not have trouble breathing today?
Yeah...
By the way.
I will go ahead with the clinical
treatment. I will receive treatment.
I want to give it a try.
That's a great idea.
But why did you change your mind?
The moment that I fall on that airbag
this came to my mind.
It's a relief that I'm alive.
If I can...
I want to live a bit longer.
But...
I'm not sure why it is hurting to say
that I want to live longer.
I'm scared.
I'm scared that I might become greedy.
I want to live longer.
I want to be in love.
I might find myself asking for more
things. I might look disgusting.
You are being truthful to your feelings.
Why do you think you might
look disgusting?
I think nothing is more important than
finding my own happiness.
What you said earlier...
Does that still hold true?
You wanted to start a relationship.
I want to be your Number One Man.
It's okay even if you have a cancer.
Let's go on a date.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Fantastic]
- Go to sleep.
- Good night.
- You should have done this earlier.
Mi Sun.
Actually, I have a boyfriend.
Really? That's great.
Lee So Hye.
- You are a nice person.
- Thanks a lot.
She will be disappointed if she finds out
that I'm seven years younger than her.
Should I grow a beard? To look older?
Why are you clinging onto me?
I'm getting sick of you.
I can't end it like this.
I'm going to hold onto you!
Then do you want to sleep with me?