Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
I want to be your number one man.
Are you okay that I am a cancer patient?
Let's go out.
[EPISODE 5]
My ribs were hurting so much,
I couldn't drive.
Could you give me emergency treatment?
Does it hurt a lot?
This area hurts so much that
I couldn't move the steering wheel.
Then you should go to a hospital.
A hospital nearby...
"Universal top star"!
If I go anywhere near an ER,
there will be reports of my death.
Since we have a doctor here,
I can get treated here!
Ma'am!
We're doing work in the building,
so we have no room.
It's cool out here,
so you two can sleep here.
Yes, that will be nice.
It will feel like camping!
A real man likes sleeping outdoors.
I have no reason to not like it either.
- Wouldn't it be uncomfortable for you?
- It's an honor for me!
I get to sleep
next to a famous celebrity.
I don't have to worry
about emergency situations
with a doctor next to me,
so I like it too.
All right, get some rest.
Good night.
Sleep tight, both of you.
The light is on in your room.
Don't work too late.
You should go to bed soon.
Do you remember the star we saw earlier?
You're not replying back?
Did you fall asleep with the lights on?
There is also a big star right here.
It's me, the universal top star! LOL
The stars are very bright here.
Just like a starry night in Uyuni.
Lee So Hye! You have to see mine first!
Reply to me first! You must!
Why aren't you sleeping?
I have to write the script, but the
sound of your messages is annoying.
If you have something to say,
just say it and go to bed now. Please?
Oh, it was disturbing you. I'm sorry.
I'm sure you need ideas for the script.
Should I help you?
No, thank you.
Don't work too hard. Go to bed soon.
You must be really tired
from watching the stars with me earlier.
Go to bed soon.
Both of you should go to bed, too.
Sleep tight.
Sweet dreams.
Okay, I'll turn off the light now.
- Dream about me.
- Be careful.
So this is how it feels
to be loved by two men.
It's nice.
I wish it had happened sooner.
Why after getting a cancer...
By the way,
will Ryu Hae Sung be all right?
He can't stand mosquitoes.
- Where do you think you're going?
- To the bathroom.
Let's go together then.
You'll be in big trouble if you stumble
into another room by mistake.
That won't happen.
All of the doors look similar here
so you could wake someone up
and disturb her.
Sure, let's go together then.
Shall we?
- He was standing guard all night.
- Standing guard?
He kept his eyes wide open and watched
me in case I went to your room.
Excuse me?
- Should we go ahead and go for a walk?
- Let's do that.
My goodness, wake up! Wake up!
- Another visitor came from Seoul!
- What visitor...
President Choi sent me here.
Mr. Oh Chang Seok got into some trouble.
Oh Chang Seok...
- My manager?
- Yes.
He's at the police station.
For embezzlement and theft.
What did you say?
Excuse me.
- Hello?
- Where are you now?
- I came out for a walk.
- With whom?
With that Hong Joon Ki?
Yes.
I have urgent business,
so I need to go back.
- Don't say anything stupid.
- What did you say?
What I mean is...
Even if Dr. Hong asks you out,
don't give him an answer.
Okay?
You're in a hurry, so you should go.
I'm hanging up now.
- Is Mr. Ryu Hae Sung leaving now?
- Yes, something urgent came up.
But he said he couldn't drive.
Is he okay now?
- So Hye.
- Yes?
You like Mr. Ryu Hae Sung, don't you?
Pardon?
I guess I should just be your guy friend.
It's fine. I like number two as well.
Since you want 3,000 men,
there will be 2,998 men after me.
Well...
- You're very cool about it.
- It's my survival strategy.
I'm also a special man who has to
live his life short and sweet.
It's obvious that I'll be
gallantly dumped.
So I should attack and retreat quickly
in cases like this.
So you should confess to him like I did.
That you like him. That you have cancer.
"Is that okay with you?"
Isn't it selfish greed?
Then if something goes wrong with me
it will leave a big scar
on the surviving person.
We're in no situation
to think about other people.
We have no time to worry.
Act on it first.
If he doesn't want a cancer patient
you have number two right here
ready for you.
Have you always been
this eloquent a speaker?
Don't you know me?
My specialty is giving dating advice.
In your case,
you should write your bucket list first.
A bucket list?
Not a grand plan, but a detailed plan
with trivial, ordinary stuff.
If you plan for about a year
your goal will become clear
and you will be motivated.
One year...
If I participate
in the clinical treatment
would I be able to live for a year?
You could live for over five years,
just like me!
Before the clinical treatment, we have
to run some tests and procedures.
- Why don't you come back with me?
- Okay, I will.
Thank you so much for everything.
Please remember number two!
I will always be loyal to the Queen!
Seriously, why did I... Really...
This brother...
Please stop!
You didn't mean to?
You should've told me
if you needed money!
I didn't want to trouble you every time,
as someone older than you.
I had something urgent in my family, so
I meant to use the money and pay it back.
I am sorry.
If you were going to steal the money,
you should've done it right!
He was the spy for President Choi.
That sly chef!
He was the one who told on
every detail that time.
What did I tell you?
I said I didn't say anything!
You came?
Do you really have to take it this far?
What the heck is this?
- Get him out quickly.
- What are you talking about?
It is the rule to be punished
if he did something wrong.
Rule?
Then there is no reason for me
to go to China either.
Do whatever you want. I'm leaving.
Get on the plane.
Then I'll get him out.
Get him out first.
Then I'll get on the plane.
You should've done that
from the beginning.
Tell them that
we're withdrawing the suit.
[WITH A BULLET FLYING TOWARDS MINA,
MINA LOOKS AT K, SMILING.]
[K LOOKS AT MINA...]
[ENDING OF EPISODE 11]
Even if Dr. Hong asks you out,
don't answer him. Okay?
Then he doesn't even call.
What urgent business does he have?
[RYU HAE SUNG]
[UNIVERSAL TOP STAR RYU HAE SUNG,
INDIFFERENT FASHION STYLE AT THE AIRPORT]
So he went to China.
You didn't answer him, did you?
I have something to tell you,
so you should answer only to me.
This is a special gift.
A totally rare item!
Are you all right? Be careful.
You should write your bucket list first.
If you plan for about a year
your goal will become clear and
you will be motivated.
Would it be all right if I fell in love?
Not a grand plan,
but trivial, ordinary stuff.
Just the things I've wanted to do...
[BRUNCH AT AN OUTDOOR CAFE]
[WALK IN NAMSAN MOUNTAIN]
[GO BACK TO PYEONGCHANG]
[FIRST KISS IN A CONVERTIBLE]
[RIDE A TANDEM BIKE]
[COUPLE MASSAGE]
[WATCH THE SUNRISE TOGETHER]
[MAKE EACH OTHER'S WISH COME TRUE]
[LOVE PASSIONATELY IN A SUITE
WITH A GREAT VIEW OF THE SUNSET]
[BUY SEXY LINGERIE]
[MAKE BREAKFAST FOR HAE SUNG]
[TAKE A BUBBLE BATH]
[THE FINAL AIRING OF HITMAN!!]
[FAREWELL PARTY FOR HITMAN!!]
[TAKE A TRIP TO SALAR DE UYUNI
WITH HAE SUNG]
Okay, I'll try it.
[WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF I FELL IN LOVE?]
You're 10 minutes late.
I'm sorry. By the way,
what kind of test is this?
We'll start with PET scan,
then MRI, and a few others.
It's to check if anything
has changed since last time.
I'm getting really nervous.
It can't be bad, can it?
- Of course not. Come this way.
- Yes.
Let's go!
The universal top star,
returning home this evening.
Wait for me!
It's too early for a hasty conclusion.
Let's re-do the biopsy...
Thank you.
Please tell me everything.
Don't hide anything.
New tumors are seen in the stomach
and the intestines...
The shapes and pace of them...
It's too early to come to a conclusion.
We will get a clear result
after the biopsy tomorrow.
I guess I shouldn't have had alcohol.
How could it spread
in such a short time?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
No self-blaming allowed.
No despair, either.
This is the time you need hope.
You understand what I mean?
Yes.
[WOULD IT BE ALL RIGHT
IF I FELL IN LOVE?]
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
You're laughing?
You messed it up and you're laughing?
I'm not a salesman for this company.
Why are you blaming me for
not getting the business?
You were dozing off and texting someone
at such an important event!
Are you going through puberty again?
Why are you acting out?
I just can't act! What can I do?
Didn't you know? I'm "Foot-Caprio".
You should watch out.
It could splatter on Lee So Hye.
Why are you bringing up Lee So Hye here?
What, about going to the lodge?
I told you! My ribs were hurting,
so I went there to take a break.
- And I happened to see Writer Lee...
- Shut up!
Blabbing nonsense...
Why don't you have any manners?
You're too mean to an actor
at the end of his contract.
Contract? You won't extend the contract?
Did you forget
what would happen if you don't?
The universal top star...
will become the poop star overnight.
I'll be slashed by scandals
that you spread.
And I will be kicked out
of this industry forever.
Then why are you throwing
a temper tantrum?
But there is a loophole
in your empty threat.
If the main character is killed,
the drama is over too.
I'll get going now.
I have plans. I almost forgot.
Bye.
Don't delude yourself!
I am the main character of this drama!
Hi, Hae Sung.
- Where are you? Where is my car?
- Your car?
I left it in the company parking garage.
Chang Seok, find a lawyer for me.
I'm not going to renew my contract
with President Choi.
Good thinking.
You should end it with President Choi.
And...
You should leave me, too.
- I'm not helpful to you...
- That's enough.
It doesn't matter how much it costs,
find a strong lawyer for me.
Oh, and where is there
a flower shop nearby?
Hello!
(IN CHINESE)
Do you have time today? I like you.
What's going on?
You don't understand Chinese.
What I said was...
"I haven't eaten anything all day,
so I'm hungry!"
"Give me some food." That's what I said.
The lettuce!
This is the lettuce! Mi Sun's lettuce!
Jo Mi Sun!
Paju is not that far from here.
Wow, look how green this lettuce is.
This is delicious.
Should we make lettuce wraps?
Joon Ki is supposed to come by.
I don't want him to misunderstand,
so you should leave.
Why is he coming here?
- We decided to go out.
- What?
I answered him yes.
Then what about me?
I don't know what you're talking about.
I admit that you saved my life...
But do I have to go out with you
because of that?
Then... was it only me?
On the truck that day...
I said "thank you."
We shook off all of the old grudges.
All we have to do is to make a good
drama together as a writer and an actor.
Isn't that right?
Why are you lingering around?
I'm getting sick and tired of it.
Thank you for having feelings for me.
But I'm sorry, I don't.
It's been a while, but I finally
met a nice guy and started dating.
I don't want him to misunderstand us.
Please leave now.
My cutie.
Cutie Hae Sung is here.
My gosh.
My baby...
When did you come?
I'm glad you came, my baby.
- Were you asleep?
- Yes.
You're good, my cutie.
Did you eat?
Did you come after the shoot?
I came here because I missed you.
All right, I'm glad you came.
My baby, I'm glad you came...
Grandma...
Do you remember when we met
for the first time?
I told you at the time...
that I had met someone
I wanted to marry.
After you saw her picture
you said she looked exactly like my mom.
At the time...
Really...
When I was so lonely,
without anyone under the sky...
she took my side.
I finally got to meet her again
after 12 years...
and I really wanted to grab on to her.
But she doesn't want me.
She told me not to linger around.
Not to linger around...
I was speechless.
She told me not to linger around...
I said I was really sorry...
But she doesn't want me.
She likes some other man.
What should I do?
Where did he go? Chang Seok!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Hae Sung, I'm only an albatross to you.
I'm leaving.
Thank you for everything.
Shameful Chang Seok.
Seriously!
What's with this rain?
It's almost midnight.
- Honey, I'm hungry.
- You're hungry?
- Let's go for a plate of grilled fish?
- With soju!
Oh my gosh!
Lee So Hye!
What is that? Isn't that a person?
Oh my, he's drinking over there.
Is that your friend?
Isn't that Hae Sung?
Oh my. It's you, Hae Sung!
- Hey, Jo Mi Sun!
- Hey!
- I finally found you!
I asked to go to a lettuce farm,
but he couldn't find this place.
But what brings you here?
All wet from the rain this late!
Your alcohol breath!
- Mi Sun.
- What? What's wrong?
Lee So Hye...
Huh?
- So Hye...
- So... What about So Hye?
So Hye! So Hye...
Hey, hey!
Honey, help him stand.
Oh my. Hey!
- Honey, let's go.
- My goodness.
Wake up! Hey, Ryu Hae Sung!
What's going on? What do we do, Honey?
What? Her blood type is O?
That's all you got?
That's enough. What more do you need
for a person to love another person?
Is she blocking you
because she thinks you're
an unemployed man
living in a dorm room?
- She's not like that.
- How can you say that?
Just tell her that you passed the bar
exam with the highest score.
- She doesn't like lawyers.
- What? Why doesn't she like lawyers?
- Is she an ex-convict, by any chance?
- What?
Then why doesn't she like lawyers?
Could she be a judge?
Or maybe she's a client whose money
was taken by her lawyer?
Or, she's a wife of a pervert lawyer?
That's enough.
This is a topic for a drama! A mystery
woman with twists and turns...
- I'm leaving.
- Hey, wait for me!
Of course she's a writer.
A married woman? Such nonsense!
- Welcome back, Mother.
- Take this.
Abalones and tile fish.
- Did you have a good time?
- Yes, I was treated very well.
Clean them
and make something with them soon.
- I'm hungry.
- Yes, Mother.
Mother!
You left this.
Oh, you were home!
Come in!
I'll be disappointed if you leave.
I have to go
because I have a meeting later...
Then I will have a quick breakfast.
- Come in, please.
- Yes, you should come in.
Thank you.
Seol, even when you're in a hurry,
you should put garnish on steamed fish.
What lowly manner is this
in front of a guest?
It's an equivalent of someone
sitting outside naked.
- I'm sorry, I will make it again.
- All right.
It's fine. Mother, I'm not a guest.
She's right. Let's eat, we're hungry.
- Be careful going forward.
- Yes.
Hey! Oh my.
My gosh. I'm sorry.
My late husband had a similar problem...
so my children don't know how
to be careful at the table.
Don't mention it.
He should relieve the gas right away.
You can't stop
the physiological reaction.
If the poisonous gas is absorbed
into the blood stream...
He'd be in big trouble.
Passing gas is like detoxing.
Should I also try detoxing so that
Attorney Choi doesn't feel embarrassed?
It's like we're a real family!
It's very hard to be so down to earth
at your status.
Should we register you
as a family member now?
Mother, you haven't done that yet?
I already changed my name to Choi Mi Do.
You should stop working and eat with us.
You won't even get to taste anything.
If you cook and smell the food,
your appetite goes away.
She can eat later.
This is for you.
Save it and have it later.
Jin Tae, what are you doing
in front of a guest?
Like an idiot...
This is why I like Attorney Choi.
He is considerate and warm.
You must be happy to get
so much love from your husband.
I said leave it! It's yours.
Take it away before we finish them.
It's okay.
I have to go visit my mom today.
I don't have time to eat.
- Is her mother sick?
- She is.
We are taking care of her
in a nursing home.
Of course, you have big hearts.
Is there any family that takes care
of the in-laws these days?
Is that right?
My daughter-in-law is also my family.
So of course I should do what's right
as a human being.
You must be very worried.
Yes.
Yeah.
What?
The script for Episode 11 is already out?
There is something strange.
Check on Lee So Hye.
What writer works so hard to hand
over the script before it airs?
It's not even pre-recorded.
I'm sure there is something fishy.
Find out what it is.
Yeah.
What's this?
Yes, I'm packing for Mom...
Let me see.
Why are you packing so much?
Great.
You're having a feast.
Mom! Mom!
My ears are blowing up! What's going on?
Look at this. She's about to pull out
the main column of this house.
Isn't this pickled pollack?
Didn't you tell me the other day
"Mother, we're all out
of pickled pollack"?
My my...
this is the expensive brined abalone!
I packed a little from the leftovers
as we were pickling a new batch...
Oh my gosh.
You have no fear.
- Give me your wallet.
- Pardon? Why...
I knew it.
What's this?
Jin Tae gave it to me.
What an idiot.
He acts like a complete idiot!
Mother!
It's my household.
Without my permission, you cannot take
even one grain of rice over the wall.
Do you understand?
I will be the one giving anything
and throwing away anything.
How dare you
with your uneducated, lowly behavior!
I didn't know about
the leaks in my house.
And I was only worried about the price
level and the national economy!
My my...
Mom, your blood pressure will go up.
Let's get out of here.
How could such a thing...
She's so-called my daughter-in-law...
Leave everything.
Before you get another word.
Mom! Let's go to a department store!
It's like new. I haven't worn it at all.
Please give me a good price.
Mr. Younger Brother,
are you at the dorm?
Yes!
Yes?
- Ms. Older Sister!
- Can I use the kitchen here?
The kitchen?
I have no place to cook.
I'll give you some too.
You're a really great cook.
- Share it with your friends.
- Thank you.
- Aren't you going to eat with us?
- I have somewhere to go in a hurry.
I will...
- Sis...
- I'm fine.
Thank you. Enjoy the food.
I will.
Be careful out there!
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
Ms. Older Sister...
Her name is Baek Seol?
She has a beautiful name. Baek Seol?
She's gorgeous in the picture.
Really...
81?
She was born in 1981?
I'm still hung over,
so I really can't eat.
- Eat. You have to eat to wake up!
- Stop.
This...
It's really good! Awesome!
Hey, don't worry.
I thought about it all night.
So Hye doesn't have a man.
I'm sure of it.
We hung out together
all day a few days ago.
I kept telling her to date a man,
then she said this to me.
"Do I go on a date by myself?
I need a good man to go on a date with."
Really?
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure!
She's playing hard to get to get over
the anger she had for you from the past.
I'm an expert
in noticing things like that.
Here, ah!
Here, here.
I'll make one for him.
You're being jealous!
Lee So Hye, really...
- You're sure?
- I said I am!
I'm so glad I came here! I will put your
lettuce on my social media every day.
I am the spokesperson of your lettuce
starting today!
My friend!
Wait!
But why did she get Brazilian waxing?
What? Bra...
That's right.
She got waxing done?
- When?
- A few days ago.
Never mind. She could've been getting
ready ahead of a date with you.
What if it's not me? If it's not me...
- Did she get it done for him?
- She didn't...
- But let's make this clear.
- What?
Let's say So Hye likes another guy.
And she got waxing done for him.
Then I can't help you. I can't help it
even if you're disappointed.
No matter what kind of universal top star
you are, So Hye comes first to me.
One more thing. Let's say So Hye flirts
with that guy and it doesn't go well.
Will you make a big deal out of it?
- Then I can't help you.
- Hey!
I used to live in America!
I'm a cool guy, American style. Okay?
Okay! Let's do this then.
Let's have So Hye over and
analyze the situation first.
- Okay?
- Okay, I like that.
Bravo, Jo Mi Sun! You're the best!
- Take them all together.
- Yes.
Do you not have a guardian?
You will feel dizzy when you wake up
from anesthesia.
I'll be fine. I will stay in bed
for a bit before I leave.
The meeting is running long.
I'll be down as soon as it's over.
Don't worry, and take care of your work.
[MI SUN]
Mi Sun...
This evening?
What secret?
I have something to tell you, too.
Tell Seol to come as well
if she can make it.
Ms. Lee So Hye, please come in.
See you later!
It's really delicious.
Sis, will you
give me this again tomorrow?
Of course.
Your nurse will give it to you tomorrow.
My daughter married into a rich family.
- Her husband is a lawyer.
- I see.
You're so cute! You're eating very well.
But she can't have a baby.
She had a twin brother
but she's a spiteful wench
who ate up her brother to be born.
She has a tough fate.
That's why she can't have a child.
But I'm sure she has a happy life.
Don't worry about her. Here.
What? Let's have one more bite.
Why did you bring things like this?
Your elders would be worried.
I should die soon
so that you can be comfortable...
How can you say that!
You have to stay healthy,
so that I can live a good life.
- Hello.
- Why don't you answer your phone?
- Where are you?
- I'm at the nursing home.
Why did you not take the car
and make Secretary Yang worry?
I heard the gist of it
from Secretary Yang.
You should've been careful.
You know Mother is sensitive
about the household stuff.
Take your time
and enjoy the time with your mom.
Yes. I will be home late because I am
going to dinner with the colleagues.
I will tell Mother.
- Okay?
- I got it.
What's this?
You're not going to thank me?
Thank you.
All right. See you at home later.
So Hye! So Hye!
Me too! Me too!
Choi Jin Sook is your sister-in-law?
That witch?
That says everything.
If the sister-in-law is like that, I'm
sure the mother-in-law is worse.
Are you upset?
I'm sorry.
I found out only after I got married.
I was going to tell you
before I went to the States...
Why would I be upset?
It's horrible that you're living
with her under the same roof.
It's bearable.
By the way,
she's having someone check on you.
Check on me? Me?
Is there something going on?
She must be looking for an excuse
because she doesn't want
to pay me for the script.
Money is everything to her.
Be careful! They are scary people.
Hey, they should be careful.
The three musketeers got together,
so what would we be afraid of?
You're right!
By the way, do you
have a boyfriend, So Hye?
- No. Why?
- Right? You don't?
Right?
What's wrong with you?
Mi Sun!
Oh no. What brings Writer Lee here?
What a coincidence!
Look at me! I was so glad to see you
I forgot to tell you
that Hae Sung was coming.
Hello. I'm the universal top star,
Ryu Hae Sung.
Nice to meet you.
My name is Baek Seol.
I'm sorry about last time.
Your car was ruined because of me...
Don't worry about it.
I took care of everything.
What happened?
Hae Sung came by a few days ago
because he really enjoyed our lettuce.
So I told him to stop by anytime.
And he came back so soon.
I know, I came back again!
Please sit down!
Why are you standing there?
I like standing up!
- Please!
- It's uncomfortable for me to sit.
- Come on, have a seat.
- I have to sit down? I have no choice?
Oh my. This picture of you two
is a work of art.
- Right?
- She's right. You look good together.
To be honest, I have been hiding this so
I can make a proper introduction...
But I got a boyfriend.
Really? That's great!
What kind of guy is he?
He is a doctor who gives
medical advice for my drama.
We fell for each other
while we were working.
A doctor? A doctor is great.
Do you have his number?
Do you have a picture of him?
Did you make up your mind?
Did you go all the way?
Of course! I'm so happy these days.
That's really great.
When will you show him to us?
Actually, he gave me a ride here.
If I knew if it was going to be like
this, I should've brought him.
- You should've!
- You should call him now.
By the way, it's nice that Hae Sung
is hanging out with us!
Let's all be friends
and get together once in a while.
Friends?
Friends...
By the way, when is Seok Won coming?
I'm really curious how he grew up.
- Should I show you his picture?
- Yes!
He's really good-looking!
So Hye, look at this!
Yes, I know he's good-looking!
What are you doing?
It's so good to see you!
- Let's get together once a month.
- Yes, let's do that.
I'll try.
- Mr. Pil, the food was really great.
- I agree.
Next time, I'll get a pig.
You have to come back.
See you again next time!
Sure.
Get in. I'll take you home.
Yes, take Hae Sung's car.
We'll take Seol home.
Sure. Should we do that?
- See you again.
- Okay.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[1981 - 1988. 7 YEARS]
[7 YEARS]
Hey, did you find any new clues?
You scared me!
No, you should go.
What's going on...
Hey, hey! That...
What's this?
No way, born in 1981?
Seven years older than you?
I'm in big trouble.
She'll be disappointed if she finds out
that I'm seven years younger than her.
What? The problem is that you're younger,
not that she's older?
I should buy a car. Like an adult.
Or should I grow beard?
So that I'll look older?
I'm sure you're a crazy man.
I'm leaving. Bye!
Bye.
I could've just taken a bus.
It's been such a long time.
I get to see you longer this way.
By the way, I'm really curious about
what kind of guy So Hye's boyfriend is.
Me too.
Ryu Hae Sung likes So Hye, right?
A lot. I wasn't sure at first,
but it's true!
He really means it.
It's for sure.
You can tell just by looking at him.
Ryu Hae Sung seems like a good man.
I feel bad for him.
So Hye is filled with fortune.
I envy her.
- I want to go on a date, too!
- What?
I'm just saying!
Seol, don't you want
to go out with a guy?
I'm tired of all of it,
whether it is dating or marriage.
I like you guys the best.
Me too!
Me too.
[YOUNGER BROTHER AT THE DORM]
Hello?
Where did my brain go?
I have never put in any gas.
You came already?
I thought it was lasting a while.
Were you filling it up the whole time?
I got a ride every time, so of course
I should add gas to it.
Oh, and this.
Thank you.
Here. For the gas.
No, thank you.
I'm not a poor unemployed man.
My salary is pretty high,
and I'm going to buy a car.
I hate owing anything. Take it.
I still wish you wouldn't give it to me.
You're a good guy.
You're embarrassing me.
Oh, and aren't you
going for a quick ride soon?
I found a really great place this time.
I have a lot of work these days,
so it's hard to find time.
- Thank you for everything today.
- Don't mention it.
But if you still find some time,
let's go for a quick ride.
- I'll be waiting.
- I'll get going.
Be careful getting home!
Thank you for the ride. Bye.
I thought about it, and I can't do this.
Do what?
"Let's be friends"?
I can't do that.
It took me exactly 12 years
to stand in front of you again.
Just because you rejected me back then...
Just because you told me to leave,
I turned away.
I regretted it to death.
I'm sorry.
No matter how much you push me away...
I'm not leaving.
Go on in.
Tada!
Oh my. You were sleeping?
Right, writers work at night.
But it's 3 o'clock in the afternoon.
Were you still sleeping?
Writer Lee.
"Mountain and Sea of People."
Do you not know what this means?
It means that there are a lot of people
like the high mountain and the wide sea.
There are so many, you can't count them.
That's what it means.
But you write this
all the time in the script.
How many extras am I supposed to use?
A thousand? Two thousand people?
Then do you know how much it costs
to shoot that one scene?
It's one, two hundred million won.
And the penthouse, the stage, and
a helicopter whenever you like it?
How am I supposed to fund it?
Blockbuster.
Don't you know what that means?
You said it's a blockbuster.
Not in a set. All location shooting.
An impressive scale.
That's what you asked for.
I forgot to tell you this!
Sorry. I changed the concept
when we didn't get the investment.
Hitman? It's a low-budget drama.
Since the production condition changed,
you should update the script.
It's written in the contract.
"If A requests the script to be adjusted,
B is obligated to adjust it."
You get paid a lot for the script.
You should earn your keep.
Give me a clear guideline.
What do you want me to adjust and how?
Achieve explosive ratings
with a minimal budget.
Make it obnoxiously interesting.
A script that requires bundles of money?
- I could write that.
- Watch what you say.
Don't speak with an informal tone.
You're not my boss.
Watch how you act, Writer Lee.
How can a writer
go to the shooting location
and invite an actor to your lodging?
What if the reporters find out?
Act cautious and update the script,
Writer Lee.
The reason I adjust the script is...
for the quality of my script,
not for the flip-flopping producer.
You should know that.
Yes, yes, yes...
I will engrave it in my heart.
Director Yoon,
President Choi was just here...
What? She said no to the penthouse?
Then where should we shoot the scenes
of the main character's place?
In some low-rent apartment?
Hae Sung's house?
My goodness.
Who can stop President Choi?
What do you think?
This place is good, isn't it?
Shoot the scenes of K's penthouse here.
Really?
Wow, you're the top in the universe
when it comes to generosity.
Your house will be ruined if dozens of
the staff come in with the equipment.
It's fine!
Why would I let this place go to waste?
The ceiling is high and it's wide.
It's just like a set!
Make yourselves at home and
shoot the scenes comfortably!
Thank you. It's a difficult decision.
This is no big deal at all!
Isn't this a given for a main actor?
Since you're here, you should check
the movement line.
Yes, I'll do that.
Then we'll go out to scout
the low-budget locations.
Thank you!
I have a meeting with a stylist,
so I have to go.
Take your time to look around.
If you need to work, feel free.
Okay.
Can I just shut the door when I leave?
Of course!
Feel free to use anything you need.
And there are drinks
and fruits in the fridge.
Then... I'll be back.
"I'll be back..."
What are you doing?
I was checking the movement
in the script.
Will you continue to work
with President Choi Jin Sook?
I don't know why you let yourself be
dragged around by someone like her.
I wonder if you have a reason
you can't say...
Why would you be curious about that?
You don't like that I'm being
dragged around by President Choi?
- Of course I don't like it.
- Why?
- It's because...
- Because you like me.
Because you're worried about me. Right?
It's a lie
that you're seeing Hong Joon Ki.
- It's not a lie.
- It's really not?
Why do you make me repeat myself?
What are you asking me to do?
Are you telling me to date both of you?
Okay, fine. Date me too.
I can't give up on you either.
But how does it work?
Should I divide days with Hong Joon Ki?
Monday, Wednesday, Friday, then
Tuesday, Thursday and Saturday?
But give me Sunday. I should get
four days even if you're dating both.
We have history together,
so I should get a higher stake.
Oh, and I'll take Tuesday,
Thursday, and Saturday.
It's nice to get an overnight
from Saturday.
That's enough.
Stop it when I tell you to stop it!
You can't handle me!
Why can't I?
I'm telling you that I will!
Do you like me that much?
Enough that you're okay
with me dating two men?
Yes. I'd rather hang on to even one leg
of yours than ending it like this.
I see...
Then, will you sleep with me?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[FANTASTIC]
She was flirting with me,
but she's meeting Hong Joon Ki here?
Then when is our D-Day?
Actually, there is someone I like.
I knew it!
If you keep refusing me, you're
being delinquent with your duties!
I'm supposed to sleep with the man who
has another woman's lipstick on him?
Is that the law?
Text message doesn't work.
Is there something going on?
- Tomorrow?
- It's nothing.
- Hello!
- Hello.
- Please come this way.
- Wake up! She's married.
Everyone in the know knows that you
wouldn't do such a thing as a writer.
Sang Hwa will call me.
She's not like that.
President Choi gave her money!
She fell for it.