Subtitles by DramaFever
[Episode 6]
Do you like me that much?
Then do you want to sleep with me?
Sleep? Now?
Here?
What is this?
Were you kidding?
Those jokes are not funny.
What are you doing?
Oh my.
Hey, I'm sorry.
- Continue what you were doing. Bye.
- Wait a second.
- Never mind.
- Why? Are you leaving?
- Yes.
- Finish what you were doing...
I'm going to leave now.
That jerk.
Why would he come now?
We didn't do anything.
I was just worried that
the kimchi might get rotten.
The kimchi refrigerator is set to
the "ripen" mode.
I was going to change that
to "keep" mode and leave.
We were doing a script reading.
Don't misinterpret this.
Bye.
Don't go.
Why did you come? Why?
Why did you come in at that moment?
How could you say that? I came because
I was worried about you.
If you were worried about me,
why did you disappear?
You are not helpful at all.
Okay, I'm leaving!
I'm leaving.
That cold-hearted fellow.
We haven't seen each other for days...
So Hye. So Hye.
You are crazy, Lee So Hye.
You are out of your mind.
How could you say that?
Huh? Dr. Hong.
You didn't answer your phone.
Sung Hwa said you were in a meeting,
so I've been waiting for you.
My phone ran out of battery.
- Did you wait long?
- Yes.
I have great news,
so I wanted to tell you myself.
I bought the diligence of
the examination techs.
I bought them some wine and meat.
And they volunteered to work overnight.
Your biopsy looks just fine.
You can join the clinical trial.
Are you okay?
What kind of scene is that?
She was making a move on me.
And now she's with Hong Joon Ki?
You've been through a lot.
Thank you for hanging in there.
- Thank you, Dr. Hong.
- I'm thankful you're okay.
I want to throw a party to celebrate.
But since you have to come to
the hospital tomorrow morning
you should take a rest today.
It would be weird if
I could hear them from here.
This is the clinical trial schedule.
Thank you.
I will repay you for your generosity.
Hong Joon Ki.
- Dr. Hong.
- Mr. Ryu Hae Sung.
- Let's talk.
- What about?
What's your relationship
with Lee So Hye?
Why are you asking me?
You should talk with Writer Lee.
No. I want to talk
with Mr. Hong Joon Ki.
What's your relationship with her?
Do you really want to know?
What are you doing?
I said I want to talk with you.
Beat me. Then I'll tell you
my relationship with Writer Lee.
Gosh. What in the world is he saying?
How good are you at pool?
You know how to play, right?
My average is 400.
- You?
- My average is 300.
But it has been a while
since I played billiards.
300 sounds like a good number to me.
- Let's do that then.
- This is ridiculous.
Why does he want to play billiards
all of a sudden?
Jeez.
What is wrong with this cue?
Why? It looks fine.
Let's switch it.
Look at him.
Sir, I won!
- Thank you.
- Now, tell me.
What are you two up to?
You guys are not dating, right?
We are not dating yet.
Look at him. I knew it.
But.
I haven't give up yet.
You are in trouble now.
How could you try to fool me?
Hey, Chang Seok.
Where did he go now?
Please just remember that I like you.
Never try to find me.
I'm going to chase after my dream.
Please forget about me,
and find a good manager.
Gosh, only if he is not older than me...
Oh my.
Hae Sung!
- Stop it. Come here now.
- How did you know I was here?
Gosh.
You.
What do you mean how did I know?
You sent me the address and the map.
Okay. I knew that you would come.
I'm not helpful at all.
Why do you like me?
When did I say I like you?
What is wrong with your face?
Why did you become so thin?
What do you mean I got thin?
Just get in the car.
No. I will only be a distraction to you.
- You can just...
- Gosh.
Then just stand here like this.
Why would a top star drive?
I will drive.
The ramen I made is the best, right?
You don't have to care
about CEO Choi now.
I hired you. I'm your boss.
Really?
Gosh. You rascal.
I will do everything for you.
Just tell me.
Writer Lee and I.
Please help us get together.
Is that all?
Hae Sung, it's me.
Don't worry.  You guys are in good hands.
Okay?
Really? Great.
Can I trust you?
I'm going to bed.
See you in dreams.
No, meet Writer Lee in dreams.
Your wife, Writer Lee.
Just wait, Lee So Hye.
I will hold your tumbling heart.
Then do you want to sleep with me?
Then that means she really meant it.
Hold on a second.
Then what was that?
Thankful for what?
What is she repaying?
By any chance...
It must be tough for you.
CEO Choi doesn't even pay you.
Yes, it's tough.
This is money.
Take this, and please date me.
I can't do that.
I like Hae Sung.
I just asked him to sleep with me.
That's okay. I'm not going to give up.
Please take it. There's no interest.
I'm a hospital director,
I have a lot of money.
I have more estates than Ryu Hae Sung.
Thank you. I will repay you
for your generosity.
That's right.
She borrowed money from him for sure.
She couldn't like
someone like him over me.
Okay. Now I can solve this puzzle.
Okay, that was it.
Now the game is over.
The game is over.
Lee So Hye. Wait.
I will hold you tight in my arms.
I will never let you go.
Lee So Hye.
This is tiring.
Thanks for your hard work.
I'm back.
- You must be tired.
- Yes.
Don't move.
What's wrong with you?
If you keep pushing me away,
it's dereliction of duty.
Do I have to hold the man who has
another woman's lipstick on his clothes?
- Is that what the law says?
- Huh?
Why are you accusing me again?
Where? Where is that lipstick print?
Lee Mi Do.
When did she get that on there?
She's so careless.
Jeez.
[Marital rape]
What are you doing here at this hour?
I couldn't fall asleep.
Why did you leave all these lights on?
No wonder the electricity bill went up.
Why would you waste it? You know our
country can't produce oil.
I'm sorry.
Our family treasures are here.
Don't come in here if you don't have to.
Okay, Mother.
- Good night.
- Okay.
Sister, are you asleep?
I have a fun quiz.
Oh, she read it.
If you get this right,
you will win 20 liters of gas.
What is the city that
the grocer dislikes the most?
The answer is, Sydney.
Next question. What is the seed
that will never grow?
"Brother?"
Brother.
The answer is vitamin C.
"Brother" is also a right answer.
Then did I win the prize?
Yes. I will give it to you.
Well. Sister.
What?
To be honest... I saw your name.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to see it.
Your name is very special and pretty.
So you did see it.
It's unfair if I know your name
and you don't know my name.
I will tell you mine.
I'm Kim Sang Wook.
Kim Sang Wook?
Sister, are you angry by any chance?
What are you doing?
Why aren't you sleeping?
It's nothing.
Jeez.
Huh?
The person can't be reached.
Please leave a message after the tone.
What is this?
Sister, your motorcycle is not here.
Did you go for a ride?
Please be careful. We're in trouble if
we scratch this expensive wooden floor.
Okay.
Be careful when you
put your equipment down.
Director Yoon, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hae Sung said he has
something to tell you.
- He is waiting for you in his room.
- He has something to say to me?
Cuckoo, cuckoo.
Okay. Got it.
Oh, Writer Lee. You're here.
I hit the jackpot with my stocks.
- Why did you want to see me?
- Oh...
About that car accident.
- Let's forget about that.
- Really?
As you can see, I'm swimming in money.
Let me know if you need money.
I'll give you a low interest rate.
Lower than the bank.
Actually. Forget that. No interest.
I'm too lazy to collect interest.
I'm having trouble using all this money.
Why would I need interest?
I don't need it. Don't waste time
on those useless things.
Practice reading your lines.
You have long lines today.
Did you memorize them all?
Of course.
You don't have to repeat yourself.
You're not exposing your body today
on the set. Why are you doing that?
Oh. I was exercising, and I forgot...
You're done talking, right? Bye.
Hold on.
Then...
When is our D-day?
- D-day?
- You made a suggestion yesterday.
"Do you like me that much?
Let's sleep together."
Are you out of your mind? This is
the filming set. People might hear us.
It feels nice to be close like this.
Forget about what happened that day.
Okay?
It was a great suggestion.
Why would I forget about that?
Okay. Let's talk again after the filming.
I have an appointment.
I'm going talk about editing points
- with Director Yoon and leave.
- An appointment?
With who?
Don't tell me... Hong Joon Ki?
- We are ready. Please standby.
- Okay.
Good luck.
Oh, I will be there soon.
Since it's our first meeting together,
I just wanted to say hello.
I brought sandwiches for everyone.
We will see each other a lot.
Let's eat lunch and introduce ourselves.
Hello. I'm Kim Yeo Eun.
I had breast cancer, and
it has been metastasized to bones.
I have stage four cancer.
After chemotherapy
my cancer cells got bigger.
That's why I joined this clinical trial.
Nice to meet you all.
I have stage four breast cancer, and it
has metastasized to my lymph nodes.
It relapsed after three years.
I was at the public bath
and an employee there
told me that I had a lump in my breast.
And my useless husband ran away
with another girl.
From chemotherapy to surgery...
I have experienced
everything except for dying.
So you guys have to let me be the boss.
I'm the boss of this team. Okay?
- Okay.
Hello, I'm Kim Mi Ae.
I also have stage four cancer.
It hasn't metastasized yet.
My husband had a car accident, and
he is paralyzed from the waist down.
I have to raise the kids.
And I have to run
the business by myself.
It can't relapse. I can't die.
Let's fight though this together.
- Let's do this.
Hello, I'm Lee So Hye.
I have stage four breast cancer.
It has metastasized to my lungs.
I was diagnosed with cancer
not too long ago.
After listening to your stories
I realized that I have been a crybaby.
It was a chance to reflect on myself.
I will take the courage and
fight through this.
Have you told your family and friends
that you have cancer?
No, not yet.
I had a hard time because of that.
I didn't want to make them worried,
And I didn't want to be pitied.
But you have to tell them quickly.
You can't fight cancer alone.
You have to rip it, chew it,
and fight it.
That's how you can win this.
It was a strange experience.
It felt like I met my fellow soldiers
in the middle of a battle field.
People who have never had this disease
don't really know what it's like.
How's your condition now?
Are you cancer-free?
I'm still fighting.
I'm still on the battlefield.
And I get bombarded.
You don't look like
a cancer patient at all.
I guess you get used to
cancer after awhile.
By the way. When are you going to tell
Ryu Hye Sung about this?
I'm not going to tell him.
That might change if I get a good result
in the clinical trial.
When I was diagnosed with cancer,
I had a girlfriend.
No matter how hard I pushed her away,
she stayed by my side for two years.
Then she left.
She's married now,
and she is doing well.
I think about this from time to time.
If I let her go without telling her
about my illness...
How great would that have been?
She wouldn't blame herself,
and she would be happier.
But if I was her,
I would have wanted to know it for sure.
"Even though I couldn't stay by his side
until the very end"
"it's a relief that
I could do something for him."
I think that's what
she might have thought.
Yes.
Oh, Attorney Kim. Welcome.
Have a seat.
- Take a look at this one.
- Okay.
This is the case
from a woman's  organization
that we are defending for free.
Marital rape, assault.
The client is from Vietnam.
What's your opinion on this case?
Three years ago, a man who met his wife
though a marriage broker
purposely assaulted and raped her.
He was sentenced to jail for five years.
But he appealed and made an agreement.
He was sentenced to jail for three years
and was on probation for four years.
Since they are still married, it won't be
easy to prove that it was forced.
But I think we might be able to win.
Great. You take that case.
Okay. I will do my best.
[Sent from Web: New insurance plan.
12 months, seven percent.]
Girlfriend?
What? No.
You seem like you have a girlfriend.
Should I introduce you to someone?
Actually...
- There's someone I like.
- Right?
I wonder who that is.
- Introduce her to me.
- Okay. If I get a chance...
Should I tell you how you can
get her to be your girlfriend?
You have to respect her.
Men back in the day
protected their women.
But men these days respect their women.
Oh, respect.
Thank you for your words.
To make it simple, it's a give and take.
You will be respected
if you respect her.
Your wife must be very happy.
She was lucky to meet someone like you.
Make your girlfriend happy too.
Pick a date. I will buy you guys a meal.
Okay. Thank you.
Did Writer Lee go to the set?
Yes. She said she has to edit the script.
Why did you want to see me?
[Hitman]
You wrote this, right?
No, Writer Lee wrote it.
Your name is on the file.
Oh, I was editing it,
and I put my name in.
You must have come up with a lot of
ideas in the meeting.
You made a big contribution.
I should make some contribution.
I'm an assistant writer.
But why are you saying this?
You are way behind
your father's hospital bills.
Take care of that with this money.
Let him receive surgery.
- How did you find that out?
- I heard you were studying for
the National Exam and you decided to
become a writer. To earn money.
You are competent and smart. Are you
going to stay as an assistant writer and
waste your ideas away?
You should make a debut.
You should write your own drama.
Writer Lee said she is going to
help me debut.
Huh? She said that again?
That's a lie.
Why would she let you have her job?
She's written ten dramas. Have you
ever seen her help anyone debut?
She took everything for herself.
This is a brutal field.
You have to compete with everyone.
If you want to go higher,
you have to  step on someone.
That's how you survive.
Sign a contract with me.
A hundred-episode drama.
I'll give you 8 million won per episode.
What? Then...
It's 8 million won.
You should buy an apartment and
pay back your debt.
How much longer do you want to live
in that tiny room?
Take the money and visit your father
at the hospital.
I'll get the contract ready.
[So Hye]
Hey.
Are you a kid? Why are you looking
at your cell phone all day?
- I'm sorry.
- Gosh.
- Come here.
- Okay.
Oh my.
I learned about everything in here.
Even the tiny little details.
I'm starting to forget them.
I guess I'm becoming dull.
I should write everything down.
- That would be the wise thing to do.
- Yes.
Let's take a note on that drawing first.
That's the expensive one.
From there, name one at a time.
Okay, Mother.
- Yes, Sang Hwa.
- When are you coming back?
I couldn't focus.
So I'm working outside.
- Okay.
- What's wrong with your voice?
Are you sick?
- That's not it--
- Don't work too hard. Take a rest.
I can't talk long now.
Let's talk later.
The person can't be reached--
[Mi Sun]
It's me. I have to call So Hye.
But her phone is turned off.
By any chance, do you know
Mr. Ryu Hae Sung's phone number?
Yes, it's urgent.
Gosh, you just stay here.
I want to go too...
Hello.
We are in the middle of filming.
What's the matter?
It's nothing.
This way please.
Cut. Okay.
- Thank you.
- Thanks for the hard work.
Hae Sung.
You are here. Welcome.
Writer Sang Hwa.
- The assistant writer?
- Yes.
She has family issues.
She won't be able to refuse it.
Even so, how could she
fall over some money?
She should show loyalty.
Her father is sick, but she doesn't have
money to get him surgery.
She's not answering her phone.
I think she made up her mind already.
Why can't we get a hold of So Hye?
Is she writing the script
and turned her phone off?
By any chance, is she with that doctor?
I'm just saying.
You shouldn't care
about those things now.
Don't you know his phone number?
I will find out.
Is this Sungdong Hospital?
Can I speak with Director Hong Joon Ki?
He's off today?
Please tell her to call me
when you get a hold of her.
Okay.
Bye Mi Sun. Say hello to Pil Ho for me.
I'm still on your side.
Take this chance and become her hero.
It's time to make a move on her. Okay?
- Let's do this.
Bye.
- Where are you going?
- Huh?
Who is that brilliant woman?
Wake up.
She's married.
We have time until
the next night filming, right?
I think I have to go somewhere.
Married?
Why?
I have an urgent matter.
I have to contact Director Hong Joon Ki.
Director Hong is not
in this office today.
Oh. His personal phone number.
I want to know his phone number...
I'm sorry, but I can't tell you
his personal phone number.
Just a moment please.
Yes?
What?
What brings you here?
Do you know where Writer Lee is?
Yes. I know.
You know?
Yes.
Where is she?
Well. I can't really tell you.
Gosh. You are doing this again.
I have an urgent matter.
- Where is she?
- I can let you see her in an hour.
This way please.
Why do you want to take
an x-ray all of a sudden?
We should take a look at your rib
when you have time.
If you leave your broken rib
like that and if it
pokes organs or blood vessels nearby,
what are you going to do?
Is that so?
I think I have some pain on this side.
So since you are here,
let's hurry and take some x-rays.
Let's draw some blood too.
- Why all of a sudden...
- Let's do a check-up.
You can be in love only
when you are healthy.
Being healthy is the best happiness
that you can give to your woman.
- Here we go.
- Wait, wait. Okay.
Don't move.
Your ribs are healing well.
I will let you know about your blood
test results as soon as possible.
What about Writer Lee?
Right... She's taking too long.
What is that urgent matter?
I can't tell you either.
Gosh. I have to go film now.
You can just go then. I will call you
right away when I see Writer Lee.
That was your phone number, right?
You have to call me right away.
Well.
My cell phone number.
You shouldn't tell that to anyone.
Okay. I'll preciously keep it to myself.
Why does he keep smiling?
I might become attached to him.
He's a funny guy.
[Assistant Writer H: Writer Lee So Hye
Plagiarized My "Hitman" Synopsis.]
Oh, I slept too long.
You're up. How are you feeling?
I feel great.
That's my first good nap in a long time.
I think that clinical trial
is doing me good.
That's a relief.
So Hye, make a fist.
What are you going to say this time?
It's not one of those embarrassing jokes.
It's to help you not get surprised.
What is it?
While you were asleep,
a surprising thing happened.
It's on the internet.
Things like that happened all the time.
That's how I got this far.
Show me.
[Assistant Writer H: Writer Lee So Hye
Plagiarized My "Hitman" Synopsis.]
Sang Hwa, I'm not trying to scold you.
So please call me back, okay?
Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
Dr. Hong Joon Ki told me to come here.
- Why didn't you answer my call--
- I want to be alone now.
Where is Writer Sang Hwa's house?
I don't know.
I have been working with her
for three years
and I don't even know
where her house is.
I'm always like this.
She called me and she sounded terrible.
I just hung up on her.
A lot of people know
that you won't do something like this.
Let's send out an article.
Let's make a counterargument.
Sang Hwa will call me back.
She wouldn't do this either.
She must have had some reasons.
CEO Choi gave her some money.
And she fell for it.
So let's make a statement on this.
No, I'm going to wait.
If I make a careless statement now
it's like fighting against Sang Hwa
in front of everyone.
Don't act like a fool.
We are just revealing the truth.
Reporters will be here soon. Leave.
[Sister are you on a trip? I can't get a
hold of you. Did something happen?]
[I'm worried you got your motorcycle
stolen. Please give me a call.]
By any chance... You're not mad
because of the name, right?
[By any chance... You're not mad
because of the name, right?]
- Well--
- Don't talk to me.
I don't want to talk now.
I was just going to tell you
not to talk to me.
Welcome.
We were grilling some meat.
Writer Sung Hwa said she likes meat.
That's great.
- Enjoy.
- Thank you.
It makes me feel better
to see you eating.
Eat it slowly. We won't take yours away.
I was surprised by the article.
I never did an interview.
But my interview was in that article.
We have to be quick
with this kind of issue.
I told you. We are living in a jungle.
If you don't want to get caught,
you have to catch somebody first.
But why are you
doing this to Writer Lee?
She only takes money,
and she is not doing her job.
- And she doesn't listen to me.
- Why?
She never sent you an unfinished script.
She really works hard.
I want a new and fresh person like you.
One who has a fresh brain.
You are scared of Writer Lee, right?
Don't worry. I will protect you.
Trust me, and focus on
writing your script. Okay?
You said you are going to give me
100 episodes and
eight million won per episode, right?
- That's right.
- She is clever and meticulous.
She knows how to sign a contract.
Then what's going to happen
to Writer Lee now?
What do you mean? She will go to a
different company, and make a living.
You know, it takes three generations
for the rich to fail.
What is that bag that you have there?
Are you a beggar?
A writer should have
something like this.
- It's my gift.
- Wow.
It's a luxury brand, very cool!
And this is very delicious.
Ma'am, I'm sorry.
Please excuse me.
Oh my.
Choi Jin Seok, you are a bitch.
You can have this bag.
Oh my. What is wrong with you?
Do you know what this is?
I recorded everything you said.
If you don't want to be embarrassed
send out a revised article
and apologize to our Writer Lee.
Otherwise, I'm going to spread this
all over the internet tonight.
Got that?
Look at her.
That's a illegal recording.
Secret recordings can't be
used as proof.
I went to law school for four years.
Protection of Communications Secrets Act
punishes people who
records a conversation
between other people.
As long as the recorder
is part of the conversation
it is not illegal.
Did you understand me?
Idiot Ms. Lawsuit?
Why are you standing there? Go stop her.
- Secretary Yang, go stop her.
- Okay.
What's going on here?
- CEO Choi.
- It hurts.
- Did you complete your mission?
- Yes.
I even have the video recording.
Okay.
Writer Sang Hwa.
I'm sorry.
I'm never going to betray Writer Lee.
But.
I'm embarrassed that I fell for
her words and contemplated it.
The one who gave you such a dilemma
is the bad one.
I'm going to tell the truth
and quit being a writer.
A person like me has no right to write.
I'm going to go back to my hometown
and get on a shrimp boat.
Do you think working on a shrimp boat
is for everyone?
Don't do that.
Sign a contract with me.
- What?
- But I have some conditions.
First. On your first drama,
you must cast me.
Second. Don't leave me out because
of my "foot acting."
And third.
Root for me instead of Dr. Hong Joon Ki.
Let's take some
fantastic revenge on her.
Don't you know this?
To face someone fierce,
you have to be fiercer.
- Sang Hwa.
- Writer Lee.
Don't forgive me.
Don't ever do something like this again.
It's too dangerous.
What would you have done
if something went wrong?
I didn't do this alone.
Mr. Hae Sung helped me.
- Ryu Hae Sung?
- In the past
I was in a similar situation.
Back then...
I made a foolish choice.
And after that, I was never at ease.
Our Writer Lee.
It will be very hard for her
if she gets betrayed again.
You don't want that, right?
I heard from the Assistant Producer
that Hae Sung told each and every staff
member that we have to trust you.
And he gave allowances to people
who left good comments on your article.
Writer Lee, you are on top of
the search engine word list once again.
What?
[Writer L's plagiarizing issue.
It was only a small incident.]
Seol, thank you. Thanks to you
I'm out of this mess. I love you.
I love you too. Cheer up.
["Universal fool"]
Yes, Writer Lee.
I'm Hae Sung's Manager Oh Chang Seok.
Oh, yes. Is Hae Sung filming now?
No, he is at a fishing spot.
He said he is going to go fishing,
and he left his phone behind.
- A fishing spot?
- Yes.
He said he has something to think about.
Oh, is it something urgent?
No, it's not...
Writer Lee, you're here.
Hae Sung is having problems with
signing a contract with CEO Choi.
He goes fishing when he has problems.
Oh, okay.
You can go straight this way.
Okay, then.
I won't go anywhere near there.
So don't worry about me, and do...
I will just go home. Don't worry
about me. You two just go ahead...
He must be happy.
That's right.
Cuckoo, cuckoo.
Cuckoo!
Ryu Hae Sung.
Can't he hear me?
- Ryu Hae Sung.
- Oh my.
Gosh. Why are there so many mosquitoes?
You scared me--
Oh.
What brings you here?
How did you know I was here?
I called you, and Chang Seok said...
So why did you call me?
Did something happen again?
Did CEO Choi try to
get you in trouble again?
What is it?
It's not that.
Thank you for helping Sang Hwa.
Oh.
I just did what I had to do.
Do you like fishing? Since when?
It has been several years.
I come here when I feel down.
I've been to fishing spots
several times.
- To bury someone.
- What?
It's a great place
to have a murder case.
I have killed my people,
and threw them in the water.
- That's what I did.
- You are scary. Why are you doing this?
Did I do something wrong again?
I mean that's what I did in my drama.
Did you not watch my dramas?
It's strange. You coming here all of a
sudden and talking about those things.
I'm sure you didn't come
all the way here to say thank you.
It wasn't because
you wanted to see me so bad.
It's Saturday.
Saturday?
You said you are going to do that.
Tuesday, Thursday, Saturday...
Oh.
Two-timing?
So are you saying you are
really going to do that?
Since today is my turn, do you mean
you want to go on a date with me?
Forget it. I'm leaving.
Hey, where are you going?
Let's finish our talk.
Hey, Lee So Hye.
So Hye.
What?
So. Did you really come here to
go on a date with me?
I said forget it. I'm leaving.
Where are you going?
It's a great place for a date.
You... Is there another twist to this?
You're going to say strange things
to me, right?
Yes.
Let's do it one more time.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[Fantastic]
A movie-like scandal with a top star
before I die? That's a good idea.
- Five more minutes.
- Let's go out now.
Did you get a new man?
Did you not hear what Mother said?
10 times, 20 times. Respect me.
You stopped our family line.
And now you are hurting my son.
If you don't want to hear what
I'm about to say, leave.
Are you trying to have it all?
So you two were together
- when we were talking on the phone?
- I heard Hitman is looking for a writer.
- What's going on?
- Ryu Hae Sung.
Were you this kind of person?
Lee So Hye, I didn't know
you could be worse than this.