(THE FOLLOWING CONTENT MAY NOT BE SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.)
(VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.)
(EPISODE 14)
He was given two litres of saline.
His blood pressure is 80 over 50. He has multiple gunshot wounds.
Gunshot wounds?
- We need to...
- I'll take over.
You need to take the critical patient.
How is the patient?
Si Jin.
Look at me.
Please look at me.
Do you hear me?
Why are you doing this to me?
Wake up.
Senior Lieutenant Ahn Jung Joon.
Why are you here?
I couldn't trust my side.
I came a long way to see a friend.
Send me...
back to North Korea.
You want to go north instead of seeking asylum?
Reporting from Zone 17.
A firefight has been engaged.
We need backup.
The target seems to be, Senior Lieutenant Ahn, Sir!
Let me go!
He's in cardiac arrest.
150 joule charge.
Clear. Shoot.
- 200 joule charge.
Shoot.
His vital signs...
are not changing.
One, two, three.
Come back.
Please come back.
Do you any rounds left?
I have one left in the chamber. I will halt the vehicle.
10m left.
There's 5m left and closing in.
Now.
Please don't do this to me.
You can't do this to me.
Please wake up.
Please wake up, you fool!
That really hurts.
His heartbeat has returned.
Si Jin, can you hear me?
Do you know where we are?
Can you see me?
Can you hear me?
What about Senior Lieutenant Ahn?
What?
The other wounded patient...
who came here with me.
Is he alive?
Who is he?
Who on earth is that?
This is not the time to worry for others.
You just came back from the dead.
If the cardiac arrest had lasted another minute, you'd be dead.
I wouldn't have been able to save you.
Your pretty face...
seems very familiar.
You jerk!
Anyways,
what happened to the other patient?
Don't you dare get up right now.
Who on earth is he?
Did you fight against him?
Is he the person who made you like this?
No.
He's a friend of mine.
We're not too close though.
Where is he?
The patient who came here with Captain Yoo...
is making a fuss.
Step aside.
Don't come close.
If you touch me,
I'll kill all of you.
If you don't receive medical attention,
you will be the first to die.
You have lost too much blood.
Keep quiet.
We will put the gun down.
Let's get you treated first.
I can't trust a doctor from South Korea.
What if...
I die in the operating room?
You should be worried about what's outside the operating room.
Doctors are the only people...
who don't care about which side you're on.
I don't care.
Don't move.
- He's in shock from blood loss.
- Dr Song is on call in room four.
- Send him there immediately.
- Okay.
Let me ask you a favour.
I want you...
to conduct the operation.
Listen to me.
After his scans are complete, keep him restrained.
Put a cast on him if needed.
Use force if he resists.
Fortunately, there is no tension pneumothorax or cardiac compression.
His cardiac rhythms are normal, too.
Scalpel, please.
What is that? It doesn't seem to be a bullet wound.
There is something implanted under the skin.
Ahn Jung Joon is from the 11th Corps of the North Korean Special Forces.
He's assigned to guard dignitaries.
I heard he would be off duty during the second meeting.
A furloughed soldier got caught...
in a firefight in Seoul in broad daylight?
Senior Lieutenant Ahn was being pursued.
They were pursuing him.
Given the arms, mobility, physical conditioning...
and tactics that they displayed,
it is evident that they received special warfare training.
They don't seem to be from the US.
Maybe they're of Russian origin.
They have been identified.
They're military attached to the Matagonian embassy.
They're embassy security?
They said that Senior Lieutenant Ahn counterfeited a Matagonian passport.
Hence, they were chasing after him.
Embassy security personnel started a firefight over a false passport?
That's the worst excuse I've heard.
I'm afraid we have no choice.
We don't have the authority to arrest them under international law.
We should dig into Senior Lieutenant Ahn.
The hospital has contacted us, Sir.
Senior Lieutenant Ahn's operation is over.
How did it go?
What are you talking about?
The operation?
We have preserved his life.
He's been moved to a rehabilitation ward.
He is still unconscious.
Let's not talk about him.
I have another patient who I just saved.
That patient seems oblivious to his girlfriend.
As far as I know, she was devastated...
to see her boyfriend under cardiac arrest and covered in blood...
just an hour ago.
I'm sorry.
Is that all?
Are there no explanations?
Is there nothing again?
Are you not curious about how I feel?
You seem to care much more about that other friend.
Just wait until you recover.
I just might kill you then.
Maybe I shouldn't give this to you.
What is this?
Why is he coming here?
Salute.
We will cordon off this room from now on.
Even doctors are unauthorised to enter without consent.
Your cooperation will be appreciated.
I heard you wanted to speak to me.
I think Captain Yoo wanted me to perform the operation for this.
It's from the body of the North Korean patient.
- Really?
- Yes.
There's a rumour that he's a North Korean.
Should we be treating North Koreans?
Of course, he's wounded.
We took an oath.
Weren't you scared?
He was covered in blood with gunshot wounds.
I'm pretty sure running into billboards drunk can't do that.
I've seen worse at Urk.
I've witnessed men staring down their gun barrels.
Screaming, "Alert, alert."
I've heard triggers clicking.
"Hands up. Move and I'll shoot."
Stop messing around. You made that up.
I really want to kick you.
Check the news.
Politicians make me so angry.
Hey, Ja Ae!
I heard you were taken hostage.
Are you okay? Are you hurt?
Where is he?
I'll kill him myself.
He was half-dead until you saved him, Sang Hyun.
Was he the man I operated on?
Heo Jun.
Albert Schweitzer.
I don't get it.
I heard your boyfriend came in with the North Korean.
There are men in black suits in the hallways.
How can you date someone like him?
What on earth does your boyfriend do?
I wonder that myself.
I don't know what he does.
I'm off to see the director.
What about these?
Why didn't she comment on what I said?
What are those?
They're the personal belongings of the unidentified man.
Then were all these made in North Korea?
It's not working.
A little lick can revive any dead pen.
I'll take these.
I'll be off then.
What did he say?
He said that the pen is actually a poisoned syringe.
I almost killed myself...
just now.
Doctor Song, are you okay?
Step aside.
I told you to move.
Gangnam has countless hospitals.
Why does it have to be Haesung?
It's the most expensive hospital.
This is official government business.
Please cooperate.
Here's their request, Sir.
This should've come first.
Right, Sir.
What on earth does your boyfriend do...
to merit an injury as official business?
And who's the guy with him?
Did those two fight?
Who won?
- I don't know.
- He lost, didn't he?
It seems like he lost.
I can fight, too. I served in the army.
Did you really?
- Who do you think I am?
- A draft dodger, Sir.
That's not what I asked.
Please be quiet.
You quiet down. This is my hospital!
You sort this out,
whether as his physician or as his guardian.
Yes, Sir.
- Move.
- Yes, Sir.
I'm Captain Yoo Si Jin...
of the South Korean Special Forces.
Senior Lieutenant Ahn Jung Joon.
What is your affiliation?
Why did you enter South Korea illegally?
What is your mission?
Whatever it is,
the fact that you're here implies that you've failed.
Is that correct?
Senior Lieutenant Ahn Jung Joon.
Under the Geneva Conventions, I'm charged to ask...
if you wish to seek asylum.
It's too difficult to hear your voice.
You should've stayed at home if you were going to be this shy.
Has he said anything at all?
What I've reported was all, Sir.
He asked to be sent North.
He galloped all the way down here to ask to be sent back North?
That makes no sense.
I can't determine the reason.
But since official routes through China or Russia were blocked,
he chose the most dangerous and direct route south.
Asylum is the only way out of this situation.
We will welcome you warmly if you spit out the truth.
We'll give you time to think. Make the best choice.
Give him a hand.
These were his personal belongings.
If his holiday was a cover for a black operations mission,
then this will give us an answer.
I'll take this and decrypt it as soon as possible.
The summit is coming up. Gosh, this is crazy.
Has he said anything?
Senior Lieutenant Ahn's still quiet. Captain Yoo's doing the talking.
What's he saying?
Is he urging him to negotiate by mentioning his family?
Well, Sir...
He's saying that adding vinegar gives it a zing...
and mustard gives it a zap.
What?
They're talking about naengmyeon.
It's Senior Lieutenant Ahn's exclusive recipe.
Are you all out of your minds?
There's a report due soon, and they're discussing condiments.
How can a captain be so clueless about official protocols?
Do you hear this?
What am I supposed to do about this?
This is Lieutenant Colonel Park Byeong Su.
Okay, so...
we don't know anything yet?
Do you call that a report?
The summit is tomorrow.
The North Korean representative moved up his schedule...
and is on his way right now.
If we don't hand Ahn over by tomorrow morning,
they will call off the summit.
What should we do?
The North Korean representative has just entered Seoul.
Already?
Is Pyeongyang that close to Seoul?
I got it.
Hello? Report in as soon as you have something for me.
Understood?
He's just a senior lieutenant, not a top general.
It's ridiculous to think...
that he's keeping leaders from both North and South up all night.
Does this even make sense?
What's his identity anyway?
It is very likely that Ahn is wanted...
by Interpol as a murder suspect.
A murder suspect?
It's not for terrorism or assassination?
Two days ago in Tokyo,
the main witness to a yakuza case...
was going into court to testify.
She was gunned down by a long-range sniper rifle.
Is Senior Lieutenant Ahn a suspect for that murder?
No, Sir.
The sniper was found dead in an adjacent building,
which was suspected to be his vantage point.
Ahn is wanted for...
murdering the sniper.
Who was the murdered gunman?
It's someone we know.
It's Staff Sergeant Rhee Seok Jin.
He served in the same battalion as Senior Lieutenant Ahn.
He killed an ex-subordinate involved in a yakuza murder.
It seems that was his mission.
Why?
Did you find anything from the chip in his arm?
It's protected by a very sophisticated code.
It'll take a week to break it.
The North wants us to hand him over by tomorrow morning.
We'll most likely comply.
- We don't have time.
- Getting him to talk is best.
He knows you're listening in,
so he's reluctant to open up.
This is usually when...
photos of his mother and family should come in handy.
Let's try something else.
I need Mo Yeon's help.
I also need the chip.
Do you mean the chip which is being analysed by NIS this very moment?
Will it be hard to steal?
I think we made a mistake.
We should've made a copy first.
Do you mean something like this?
You're so smart.
Shall I send the doctor up?
In your wrist and thigh, I found pieces of bone...
that were not removed after previous fractures.
You have four gunshot wounds.
Four new ones, I mean.
What concerns me most...
is the piece of shrapnel lodged close to your spine.
If you leave it there, it can harm a nerve...
and paralyse your lower body.
Mr Ahn.
It's a wonder you're still alive.
Don't waste your one and only life.
The fellow next to you is just like you.
He's someone who's just as crazy.
I wasn't going to say this,
but remember the soldier I met in Urk?
- Who do you mean?
- You know,
the one who yelled at me for operating on a dying man.
That ugly person who disciplined you for it.
He came to my team earlier...
and interrogated us about every medicine and pill.
Are we his subordinates or what? How dare he treat us like...
What are you doing?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(THE ROOM'S BUGGED. DON'T SWEAR.)
What should I do?
What I'm trying to say is, don't you think...
he noticed?
I was so happy to see him.
I almost ran up to hug him.
I'm sure he knows.
He's a great man.
He truly is.
How is your mother?
What? Well,
she boasts about what she cooks for me and spends my money.
I need a private place to speak to Senior Lieutenant Ahn.
She's very well.
I wasn't able to greet her properly.
Let's set a date.
You pick the place to meet.
Must I really?
I don't want to.
My mum won't like it either.
I won't worry you.
You don't keep your promises.
It's a special request.
From now on, don't abandon me because you're drunk.
Mr Ahn, please come to the CT room in half an hour.
I need to run a few more tests.
Be on time. There's a long waiting list.
My goodness.
Lieutenant Colonel?
How can we meet like this?
It's so good to see you.
Let's just say that you hugged me.
Pardon?
We always meet whenever there's an issue of national importance.
We do. Excuse me, then.
What is it?
I have a long list of patients.
I need 10 minutes.
This is the only probable place without listening bugs.
Listening bugs?
What are you talking about?
It's best if you don't know.
Right now,
I work for the government.
Does the government know about this?
Promise me one thing.
Even if the government denies me,
promise that you will remember me.
Watch it.
What's going on?
They can't listen in now, so speak freely.
I betrayed my own side to arrange this.
We have 10 minutes at most.
I'm trying to help.
This is your final chance.
What's the issue?
It's about Staff Sergeant Rhee Seok Jin.
Why did you kill him?
Return my belongings first.
Do you mean this?
Now it's my turn to ask.
What's in that chip?
We received a tip that our best Special Forces personnel...
were being hired...
by crime syndicates like the yakuza or mafia...
as hit men commanding very high prices.
The 13th North Star, mission accomplished.
Confirm the transfer account.
My mission...
was to eliminate the traitors...
and to find out about the person arranging the hits.
Did you discover any evidence of the mastermind suspect?
Why do you ask me?
You must've seen for yourself.
The code is too hard to break.
What's the password?
Even better, just tell me what's in it.
No thanks.
My government will take care of its own issues.
Your government...
is already up to something.
Commander Choe is on his way...
to collect you this very instance.
Tomorrow morning,
we will hand you over to the North.
Is this place bugged by any chance, too?
No, not now.
I can barely breathe in the ward.
It'll be over soon. Thanks for your help.
I really hate your guts.
Did you get to speak to your friend?
Yes, thanks to you.
Oh, right.
His name is Ahn Jung Joon.
He's a senior lieutenant.
I see.
Are you sure you're allowed to drop his name like that?
I was hoping someone would remember him.
It would be better if it were someone as brave as you.
He was given a painkiller and a sedative,
so he'll sleep for about five hours.
Where are you going?
In our country,
you can't leave without a doctor's permission.
Step aside.
I have a mission to finish.
I think I told you you'll be transferred in the morning.
Are you trying to avoid...
Commander Choe who is coming to get you?
I thought about why you came looking for me.
I'm your friend from far away,
because your enemy...
is also my enemy. Am I right?
Did you betray your country...
or...
did your country betray you?
A warrior...
never betrays his country.
Who survived?
The North Star...
or Pluto?
Commander Choe?
It's you, Pluto.
I see why you're the instructor.
Are you...
the traitor?
How could that be?
The traitor...
is you, Pluto.
Please.
Help me escape.
You'll die if you go back.
Regardless of who betrayed whom.
There is something I must finish.
I said you'll die.
Even if I do,
I'd rather die on home soil.
Please let me go.
I'm also a soldier carrying out a mission for my country.
I cannot let you get away.
I have already repaid you for the naengmyeon...
you bought for me at Pyeongyang in that firefight earlier.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
This is my farewell gift to you.
It's tasty,
so I hope you savour it.
Did you see your friend off?
Your friend left the hospital without physician approval.
Through that, I suppose.
He's not close enough to bid goodbye.
I feel the pain again.
Sit up straight.
Yes, Ma'am.
Did you break that window yourself?
It wasn't me.
The fellow who left did it.
Then did you break the window downstairs?
That was also the other fellow's doing.
Then I suppose that you, as friend of that fellow,
will pay for the repair?
As I told you before, We're not that close.
Do you know how much the director scolded me for the windows?
Where's the director now?
He has no right to treat my girlfriend like that.
My boyfriend was hospitalised with a North Korean soldier.
Okay.
I'll be back in two hours.
Wait until your IV injection is complete and stay put.
Don't you dare think of running away.
Hello?
Your antenatal education seems to be about anatomy.
You said your baby is due in a week, right?
Yes, next week.
Did you see Doctor Kang's boyfriend? I heard that he's handsome.
What's the use of being handsome...
when he got hospitalised with a North Korean soldier?
I heard that the North Korean soldier is also handsome.
I hope reunification will happen soon.
Hey, you.
Shouldn't you get changed?
You obviously look pregnant in your scrub suit.
Don't you think you'll worry your patients?
Did your bad surgery skills get any better?
You should always wear your doctors gown.
Otherwise there'll be no way to tell if you're a patient or doctor.
What?
What did you just say?
What do you think you're doing?
My water broke. I think it's about to come out.
I thought you had a week left?
Please call Doctor Jung at the maternity unit.
- She's having a baby.
- Let go now.
Squeeze harder.
Here?
- I mean your hand.
- Take back what you said.
Keep it up.
- Hospital administration?
- Yes.
I'm here regarding the cost of the broken windows.
I heard that you're a guardian of Mr Yoo Si Jin.
I don't think he's a man in need of a guardian.
Two windows have been broken.
The damage wasn't incurred by emergencies or natural disasters.
Someone needs to pay the fine.
I don't think that should be me.
Director told me to bill it to you.
I also think...
that's the right thing to do.
Clench your teeth shut.
By the way, why are you here?
I'm the doctor in charge of the ward below the ward...
that Yoo Si Jin broke.
It wasn't Yoo Si Jin. It was the North Korean soldier who broke it.
But the North Korean soldier went back to his country.
So you should...
You're showing teeth.
Excuse me.
Hello?
The baby?
Already?
- The baby is on the way?
- Okay.
I'm leaving right now. I'll be off now.
All right. Go. Be on your way.
The baby is on the way. Isn't that great news?
Doctor Kang. Doctor!
South Koreans...
drone on about separated families or economic cooperation.
They think the future relies on peace negotiations.
However, the higher the fences, the safer it is.
It's better if the North and South are on distant terms.
Wait outside.
My thoughts...
haven't been wrong.
If you want to get what you want,
threats are better than talking,
and tension is better than peace.
It's nice...
to see you again.
I will now debrief my mission.
I have punished the 13th North Star...
who tainted the honour of the nation.
I've also identified the voice who made the order.
Great.
I heard that you've also obtained the file of the transaction.
Where's the file?
Seeing that the South is quiet, they must have not broken the code yet.
You must have it safely hidden in your body per your training.
I will bury the secret forever along with the traitor.
Say your last words.
Please prepare a bowl...
of Pyeongyang naengmyeon on the table during my memorial.
If it's possible,
I would like the Ongnyugwan naengmyeon from Koryo Hotel.
If that's what you want.
Is that all you have to say?
Since I'm done,
I'll finish my last mission, too.
In the name of my country,
I will eliminate the traitor Commander Choe...
of the State Security Department.
(SECOND MEETING BETWEEN SOUTH KOREA AND NORTH KOREA: DEMANDS)
What is this?
The preconditions before settling...
the issue of separated families.
I think we showed good faith by sending Senior Lieutenant Ahn back.
I thought South Korea liked to hold conversations.
I'm suggesting that we keep on talking.
Before the terms on the document are met,
there will be no agreement.
I believe that these terms...
state that you don't care about the reunion of separated families.
North Korea wants to quit all dialogue with the South.
That's what it sounds like.
Am I correct?
The good thing about our bilateral talks...
is that we don't need translators.
Then,
I will take that as your answer.
Excuse me. I'll be off now.
Please take a seat.
I think...
you need to take a look at this before you leave.
(NSB STATEMENT LIST)
I see that you made quite a lot of money by betraying your men.
How many zeroes is that?
What do you think you're doing?
We've been ordered to take you and Ahn Jung Joon back to Pyeongyang.
Senior Lieutenant Ahn...
is still alive?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
I will...
bury the secret forever...
along with the traitor.
If it's possible,
I would like the Ongnyugwan naengmyeon from Koryo Hotel.
I cracked the password.
The password is...
It's the GPS coordinates for Koryo Hotel in Pyeongyang.
(SEARCH FOR LOCATION, PYEONGYANG, KORYO HOTEL)
The South Korean Special Forces shoot very poorly.
I didn't get shot in the fatal area.
You'd better come along without saying a word.
I was told to bring your dead body if you try anything rash.
Let me have just two minutes.
Don't I have some time to eat a snack?
I will compensate for this snack...
even if I have to compensate for it after I die.
Thanks to you,
I can go back to my country...
and die as a warrior.
Thank you.
(SETTLEMENT OF THE SECOND NORTH AND SOUTH KOREA MEETING)
Commander Choe's party cancelled the luncheon and left right away.
I'm sure they did.
Do you think it's all right for us to give them the original copy...
as a part of our political negotiation?
Why does it matter? We have a lot of copies.
General Park is in bad terms with Commander Choe.
I already sent him a copy via e-mail.
South Korea is strong with technology, you know.
Politics need to be built on top of morality.
People who do bad things should pay for their actions.
Justice will prevail, and the evil will pay.
Then what about the morality...
of keeping your promises about that political negotiation?
You're so naive.
Do you think politics can always work with morality?
What time was the press conference?
I need to choose a tie.
She's coming. There's 10m left.
Hurry up. There's 5m left.
I can't take off my pants because of my cast.
My gosh, why did you get it done again?
I wanted to commit a perfect crime.
She's here.
Hurry up.
He just fell asleep.
It's good to sleep a lot.
I hope he didn't go out or anything.
Of course not.
- I'll be back once he wakes up.
- Okay.
My gosh, that was bad.
Help me.
Why did you get another cast?
I didn't get hurt because I wanted to.
He just fell asleep.
It seems so.
You must be having a hard time taking care of him, Dae Yeong.
I can't believe I lost sleep for people like you.
What brings you here?
A perfect crime?
How will you pay for the window?
I have a great idea, actually.
Why don't we split it like real men?
Is that a great idea?
My salary is reduced right now.
Well, I am not a real man.
What are you doing here?
It's been a while. How have you been?
Every day is filled with incidents.
Are you here to see Si Jin?
Yes. He's not dead, is he?
Not yet.
I'll probably end up killing him soon, though.
Go ahead. Dae Yeong is there, too.
I saw his car parked while I was parking.
- That's why I'm here.
- What do you mean?
- Did you two fight?
- No.
We broke up.
We have nothing to do with each other any more.
Really? Why? When?
Well, I understand.
What is with your conclusion?
I mean that I understand.
His room number is 710.
They are like the characters from "Dumb and Dumber".
I hope the country never finds out they are like that.
Dae Yeong isn't hurt, is he?
I thought you had nothing to do with him.
I'm asking you as a doctor.
I will get going, then.
Your love life is complicated, too.
Am I the only one who feels awkward?
If you're here to see me,
you should be more caring about the one who's sick.
I saw your girlfriend who is very concerned about you.
Do you want me to get her?
No.
She already went away concerned.
I can see that you're doing well.
I'll get going.
Hey.
We're friends. You didn't have to bring something like this.
If she brought something, you should at least ask her to sit.
You two can talk.
I'm leaving.
- I'll leave.
- I'm leaving.
Who will I be with if both of you leave?
It would've been better if he was lying down in bed.
He did lie down in bed instead of me a while ago, actually.
Did you know?
Dae Yeong is very feminine.
He even ran his fingers through his hair and...
I was just joking.
Right, he had this facial expression on, too.
He said, "Oh, my" as he ran his fingers through his hair.
I didn't say "Oh, my."
My goodness.
You really are like "Dumb and Dumber".
Rest well.
You fool.
I tried my best to get her to stay, okay?
That's why I stopped you.
I see. Is this a fight which can't be resolved like this?
What is it?
Why did you break up?
I applied to get discharged.
- What?
- That was the only choice...
I could make.
You did what?
I am sorry.
How could you make that decision by yourself?
I'm disappointed.
I am sorry.
Does Commander know?
Myeong Ju was there when I went to see him.
Go after her.
You gave up your life for her.
Don't make her wait too long.
What do you think they're doing?
In my opinion,
they fought, and Myeong Ju probably broke up with him...
for Dae Yeong's sake.
That's why Myeong Ju can't give in.
Because Myeong Ju is a good woman.
In my opinion,
Dae Yeong knows where Myeong Ju hid.
He wants to go after her, but he can't do that.
He wants to keep Myeong Ju's pride because she hid it so well.
Because Dae Yeong is...
a good man.
What are you doing tonight?
If you don't have anything special, come help me shop.
What are you getting?
Were you shopping for a car?
I told you I was going to buy a new car when I returned to Korea.
What's the point of saving up when you don't know when you'll die?
I'll die after using all my money.
I won't leave it for anyone. I'll use it all.
What if you use it up and don't die?
I haven't thought about that, but I will buy a new car.
Choose one.
What do you like?
I like this one.
Hey, you just interfered with my life.
Why did you do that? Do you like me?
The employee recommended this one, too.
You were watching me.
- Why? Do you like me?
- Yes.
You said you like me. Why? Do you like...
Wait, what?
My goodness.
Buy it quickly. I'm hungry.
Could you give me the contract? Quickly, please.
North and South Korea...
decided to hold a meeting for 100 people...
with separated families.
The two governments came to terms...
during a highly confidential meeting held in Panmunjeom...
since yesterday.
Thanks to this, the meeting between separated families...
will finally resume after five years.
The North and South Korean governments have decided...
to hold this meeting...
(NORTH AND SOUTH AGREES TO HOLD A MEETING FOR SEPARATED FAMILIES.)
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Don't be scared. I'm off duty.
Why didn't you go home?
I am your guardian until today.
When do I get dismissed?
Can I stay here for a week?
I love seeing you once every two hours...
for a checkup.
If you love it so much, why did you go out?
Where did you go?
I went to the rooftop to get some air.
I went there to check.
I didn't say I went to the rooftop of this building.
Were you at the department store again?
Did you go with your friend?
Why did you come back alone?
We had different paths.
I'm not feeling too great.
Could you comfort me instead of scolding me?
What happened?
I've kept the peace,
but I'm not sure if my friend is dead or alive.
And your girlfriend is...
concerned about you.
Have you ever lied down on a patient's bed?
Come on.
How can she say no?
Will you be that uptight?
I'm the patient, you know.
I won't be able to do anything.
The patient was well enough to visit the department store.
This doctor needs to protect herself.
- What are you saying?
- I'm not sure.
I'm sleepy.
Chi Hun became a father today afternoon.
He has a son.
Just for your information, if you're going to get him a gift.
He must be adorable like his dad.
Tell him that I am happy for him.
Copy that.
I am sorry...
for worrying you.
Thank you...
for saving my life.
Why do we...
always thank each other for saving one another's life?
Other couples...
thank each other for dropping one another home...
or for doing something special on their anniversary,
don't they?
I am sorry.
Are you sure?
What do you mean?
I saw the kind of peace you have kept...
on the news.
But...
if you are really sorry,
don't ever appear before me covered in blood.
Please.
Copy that.
Do you want to watch a movie? That movie we missed.
Here?
I saw that VIP rooms have something very nice like that.
And there's this nice thing, too.
My gosh, we finally get to watch this.
This is something I couldn't even imagine.
We finally get to play this.
We stopped after making the payment last time.
It's starting.
I can't remember who fell asleep first.
It was a long and a tough day,
and I was in his arms.
I shined brightly through the night in his arms...
like a woman who was deeply loved.
Did that movie we missed...
have a happy ending...
or a sad one?
(DESCENDANTS OF THE SUN)
I thought you were washing up.
You're dressed.
Let me see from the beginning.
- You filling up the tub.
- You wish.
Did you know?
We never said that we loved each other.
We did it with our body language instead of words.
I am thinking about sending you to this operation.
Or I can approve your discharge application...
right now. What should I do?
I want to go, Sir.
I will be back when the season changes.
Dae Yeong is back, right?
Woo Geun, what brings you here?