[THE ENTERTAINER]
[EPISODE 15]
What the heck?
Who are you!
Lee Joon Suk!
Why did you do it? Why did you do it?
Why did you do it!
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
What did you say to Sung Hyun?
What, exactly, did you say to Sung Hyun?
What do you think I said to Sung Hyun?
What do you think I said to a man
who couldn't even control his body?
Don't do it!
Hey, this guy called you a...
Hey, say it again.
Just try and say it again!
If you do this, Suk Ho...
I become a pitiful person.
I won't make you a pitiful person.
It is quite comical
to see you behave this way.
I don't know about anyone else,
but it's funny for you to be this way.
Do you have the right to act like this?
My life depends on that song.
Jin Woo can release something next time.
Are you this stupid?
What good would come from this?
This money is much more than the pay
for composing one song.
You can make more than this.
There's the next album too!
You will be punished.
No matter how crappy this world is,
you will be punished.
You will receive the punishment
that you deserve.
As for my punishment...
I will get what I deserve.
What will happen if Jo Ha Neul
sings "It's Okay to Cry"?
Don't give up on "Legend Again".
I'm looking forward to seeing
a comedy show.
I'm sorry.
It must've been so hard for you.
It must've been so difficult...
It must've been so hard...
I'm sorry I couldn't
be there with you, Sung Hyun.
I'm so sorry.
Gosh, that punk.
Look at the time. Geez.
Hey, are you just getting in now?
Did you spend the night
in the office again?
Seriously, what's wrong with you?
I guess he's really tired.
Get some rest. Sleep well.
I'm going now.
President Shin's phone is turned off.
Is something wrong?
He's home now.
He came home half-dead this morning
and fell asleep on the sofa.
I asked him what was wrong,
but he wouldn't say a word.
He's not the type to act like this unless
something is really wrong.
This is bad timing.
We have to prepare for "Legend Again".
Can I go over there and check on him?
Let's leave him alone for today.
It must be something
he can't talk to us about.
Gosh, he's still lying there like that.
Suk Ho, what's wrong with you?
You didn't eat anything all day, did you?
Seriously, get up and talk to me.
Yes, finally!
The arrangement is finished.
We can practice it
in the studio tomorrow.
Wow!
Why don't we show it to President Shin
and start practicing?
Geu Rin?
What? Me?
What is it? Are you sick?
No, I'm not sick.
I said that the new arrangement
is complete.
Can we start practicing tomorrow,
Manager?
President Shin is a bit sick.
He's been in bed all day.
The President is ill?
What about the hospital?
I was going to visit him today,
but we thought he should just rest.
It's a big problem if our leader is sick.
I'll go out and buy some porridge.
The water is over there. Give him some.
Okay.
President. It's me, Geu Rin.
Are you very sick?
What is this?
Our leader can't be like this.
I'll go get you some water.
Drink some water.
Yes?
How is the President?
I don't know. He's still sleeping.
He won't drink water or eat anything.
He's just sleeping.
That's worrisome.
What about you, Sis?
Have you eaten anything?
Yes, I ate with Man Shik.
Did you really?
I did. What about you?
We always eat just fine.
Let's practice Kyle's
new arrangement tomorrow.
We can't just sit around like this.
Okay, I'll let the others know.
I'm asking you as a favor.
Make sure you eat all your meals, Sis.
Lately, you have been calling me Sister.
Have I?
Why? Should I stop?
No, it reminds me of when we first met.
I really liked it back then.
I had a cute younger brother,
even though you were much taller than me.
I feel the same way now.
I'm really happy to have
a cute younger brother.
Go to bed soon. You look tired.
Yes, you must have been in pain.
Just like my heart that has burned away.
- Hi.
Hello!
Is President Shin here yet?
Is he coming?
He told us to meet him here.
Hello!
- You're here?
- Yes.
Did Suk Ho contact you too?
I see he's not here yet.
Is something going on, President Byun?
Lately, both you
and Suk Ho look really unwell.
Oh, he's here!
Suk Ho.
President.
I've been going through a really
difficult time these past few days.
I'm sorry for making you all worry.
I think it's been over 10 years.
I had a friend that I was very fond of.
He was a great songwriter
and he sang very well too.
So, I introduced my friend to an agency.
I thought it was a waste
of his talents to keep them hidden.
He said he didn't want to
and that he couldn't do it.
I barely managed to convince him.
It was because... my friend
had a physical disability.
I introduced him to my company.
Then I had to go on a one month
business trip to Moscow.
When I returned...
my friend had died.
They said it was a heart attack.
My friend never ended up
releasing his album.
Over 10 years passed.
I ended up meeting his little brother.
Jo Ha Neul.
My friend, Jo Sung Hyun's
little brother, Jo Ha Neul.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you suddenly telling our story?
We should not... go on "Legend Again".
What?
But, I already finished
the arrangement. Why?
It could be a big performance for us.
Why would you want to lose it?
"It's Okay to Cry"...
cannot be sung by Ha Neul.
President Byun, do you know
anything about this?
That song...
That's enough.
I will...
I will explain.
Choi Joon Ha's second album.
It was released from KTOP
when Suk Ho and I were there.
Sung Hyun...
His songs were really great.
That's why they remain classics.
Didn't you say he never
released an album?
What are you saying?
Choi Joon Ha's "It's Okay to Cry" is...
It's Sung Hyun's song.
"It's Okay to Cry" is not
Choi Joon Ha's song.
It belongs to your brother.
It's Jo Sung Hyun's song.
Wait a minute.
So... was my brother's song stolen?
Is that what happened?
- One more thing...
- Suk Ho!
He should know.
He deserves to know
about his only family.
What is it?
What more could there be?
Sung Hyun...
It wasn't a heart attack.
Because of that incident...
he drowned himself in the Han River.
That's why...
That is why...
I think we should...
forget about doing "Legend Again".
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Hey, Suk Ho!
- President!
- Suk Ho!
Hey, Suk Ho!
Hey, wake up! Suk Ho!
Aren't you feeling cooped up in here?
Want to go for a drive?
Suk Ho must be
going through a tough time.
I know I shouldn't be...
But, I keep thinking "what if"...
Way back, long ago...
What if Suk Ho had never
been in my brother's life?
Would my family
still be alive and together?
My brother would be alive.
My mom and dad too.
You would be there, as well.
Would we all be leading normal lives?
Yeah.
I suppose your parents wouldn't have
been opposed to you singing either.
They wouldn't have gotten into
an accident to come and stop you.
I keep having those thoughts.
I want to turn back time.
You know what, Ha Neul?
When you and I were struggling,
and you were framed...
When you gave up on music
and you were having a hard time...
What if he hadn't come into our lives?
You would still be framed for that crime
and you wouldn't be singing.
Don't you think
that's how we'd be living?
Do you think I can face Suk Ho again?
When I see Suk Ho's face,
I'll only think of my brother.
Do you think I'll be able to bear it?
Ha Neul, I know both you and the
President are going through a tough time.
What about my brother?
He had no one by his side.
He was all alone...
in that cold place.
He left in such a lonely
and miserable way.
Suk Ho and I are still here.
My brother... is gone.
[ENTERTAINER BAND]
I thought about it on my way here.
I wish we hadn't had
such a big age gap between us.
It would have been better that way.
Then you could have
come to me for advice.
You wouldn't have been so lonely...
and died like that.
Sung Hyun.
This relationship with Shin Suk Ho...
I don't like it.
[IT'S OKAY TO CRY]
Sung Hyun...
Sung Hyun!
Sung Hyun.
Should we go home now?
Or should we go get some food?
I think I should see him.
Lee Joon Suk.
You're not saying
we should go to KTOP, are you?
- Ha Neul, why don't you wait...
- I have to see him.
I'll be back. It won't take long.
Let's go together.
He's not someone I will take long with.
I'll be back soon.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
Yes, I suppose you need
to shout once too.
This is the first time we've met,
isn't it?
How should I greet you?
You will find it awkward
to hear anything I have to say.
I don't want to hear a thing.
I don't want to hear a sound
out of trash like you.
My older brother, Jo Sung Hyun...
He died because of you.
You're too worthless to even hear about
the pain my family went through.
I have only one thing to say.
I assume Suk Ho did that to your face.
But, I'm going to kill you silently,
Lee Joon Suk.
No, I will make you want to die.
Just like you did...
to my brother.
I'm not only worried about Ha Neul
and "It's Okay to Cry".
I'm worried that he may not
ever want to sing again.
He just found out about what happened
to a family member that he loved.
Do you think he can get over it?
Ha Neul must feel like
his heart is going to implode.
Kyle, what are you doing?
Why are you ripping up the sheet music?
Kyle!
We don't need this.
How can Ha Neul sing this song?
Could you or Yeon Soo
stand to see that happen?
The President is right about this.
Let's not go on "Legend Again".
You're right.
Ha Neul must feel like he's going crazy.
Let's not do it.
There will be other performances.
I'm going to sing it.
Don't do it. How can you sing that?
Your brother is a brother to us too.
Are we insane?
Your brother wrote that song.
Someone claimed it as his, got a big hit,
and is living well somewhere.
Are we crazy? How could we sing that?
I can't do it. I can't play that.
- No, I'm going to sing it.
- Ha Neul...
Don't tell me that I can't
or that I should wait!
No... sing it if you want to.
Geu Rin, this decision
should be made by...
Yeon Soo, I don't think the President's
decision is important this time.
Ha Neul's decision is what's important.
I'll make arrangements with the station
in place of President Shin.
Let's show everyone and sing it well.
If you want to sing Sung Hyun's song,
you should sing it.
No matter what anyone says,
it Sung Hyun's song.
I'm going to go see the President.
- I'll drive you.
- I want to go alone.
Where is he?
Oh, he said he wanted to eat caramels.
I went to the store and he disappeared.
It's already night.
Why did he turn his phone off?
I stepped out to get him some clothes.
How could you lose him?
President Byun, my brother...
Which bridge was Sung Hyun
standing on before he jumped?
You should just wait for me
to come back before recording.
You think I'll release an album
just because I record?
President Byun and Chairman Lee Joon Suk
are all good people.
You don't need to worry.
Just show them how talented you are.
Honestly, people will faint
if you show them half of your talents.
Gosh, do all managers exaggerate
and lie as much as you?
What?
I guess you have to make
your actors and singers stand out.
You must've been so cold.
You must've been so lonely
here by yourself.
I'm here too late, Sung Hyun.
What are you planning to do?
You'll die if you fall from here.
Are you going to die?
Are you going to follow Sung Hyun?
Am I being left behind
while everyone leaves again?
Even breathing...
makes my heart hurt so much.
Jo Sung Hyun!
Sung Hyun!
Suk Ho! Where were you?
I went for a walk.
We thought something happened to you.
Min Joo and I were so scared.
I remember it all.
My brother wouldn't go
on outings with us.
My family never even went
out to eat at a proper restaurant.
Sung Hyun was uncomfortable
being around other people.
But... things changed
when he met a friend named Shin Suk Ho.
When he had a day off...
other managers would all be resting.
His friend Shin Suk Ho would come over
and take my brother out.
Cheers!
I thought that was the end
of our relationship.
Even though my brother was gone,
he came and found me.
Shin Suk Ho, my brother's
one and only friend.
And... he grabbed my hand.
He helped me sing again.
He cleared my name
and proved I was innocent.
Suk Ho, let's stop trying
to console each other.
Let's stop talking about painful things.
Geu Rin is right.
I thought about, what if you
had never met my brother...
What if...
you hadn't shown up in my life
after all those years?
What do you think would've happened?
I know it may take time.
Let's not talk about "what if".
I won't do it either.
Yeah, Suk Ho. Be strong.
The members of Entertainer Band
have come to a decision.
We...
are going to perform on "Legend Again".
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever
[IT'S OKAY TO CRY]
I'm going to sing my brother's song.
That's what we have decided,
so you need to get up now, Suk Ho.
Get back up.
My brother's song...
I want you to get it back.
I will die someday, right?
The one thing I have to do
before dying is this.
I have to reclaim Sung Hyun's song.
I'll help you however I can.
Have you thought about
how you're going to do it?
There is only one way.
Choi Joon Ha.
We need to find him before the show airs
and get him to admit the truth.
Do you think we can find him?
I went to a meeting at the TV station
and they've been looking for him too.
They wanted him to come on the show.
But, he's been hiding since the incident.
Which singer was the closest
to Choi Joon Ha?
Yeon Kyung spoke of Choi Joon Ha often.
Do you think they're still in touch?
So many people are looking for
Choi Joon Ha lately.
The TV station came looking for him.
I haven't seen Joon Ha in a long time.
He's no longer in Korea.
I think it was about five years ago,
we had coffee.
His father was sick
and he lived in a home.
I don't know how he is now.
So, I think he comes in
once a year to see his father.
Do you know where that home is?
I don't know.
Oh, but he did say he was on his way
back from visiting his father.
He was coming from Yeongwol.
Yeongwol.
[YEONGWOL SENIOR HOME]
Hello.
I'm looking for a patient
with the last name Choi.
I'm looking for one of my father's
friends. I owe him a big favor.
I'm not too certain of his name.
- The last name is Choi?
- Yes.
One moment.
Is it Choi Jin Goo, by any chance?
Is his son's name Choi Joon Ha?
I really need to find him,
so please help me out.
You won't be able to converse with him.
His Alzheimer's is very severe.
He can't even recognize his son
when he visits from Australia.
Australia?
Uh, Kyle...
I'm sorry, but can we try
a different arrangement?
Why? Are you not feeling it?
No, it's not that.
Hey, is this...
Yes.
It's the first version
that my brother wrote.
The original is a real work of art.
This isn't a different arrangement.
Let's go with the original song.
Thanks.
Sorry guys. We'll have to practice again.
It's fine with us.
What an honor.
We're going to play the song
using the original sheet music.
Kyle, what should I do? I'm nervous.
You're nervous?
Let's give the original a try.
Why are you calling me?
How have you been?
I'm just living.
Are you working with Lee Joon Suk again?
Yes.
Joo Han, after everything
he did to you...
I have to make sure
I screw him over before I leave.
You're looking for
Choi Joon Ha, aren't you?
Did Lee Joon Suk tell you
to look for Choi Joon Ha?
Yes.
Are you planning on going to Australia?
You're pretty quick, Kim Joo Han.
I am quicker than you think, Suk Ho.
Choi Joon Ha isn't in Australia.
I already went there.
I met his family and asked around.
He's in Korea.
Choi Joon Ha is here right now.
Why are you telling me this?
Why don't you just hit me
a few times and let's end this.
I betrayed you and bothered you
because I was obsessed with success.
I didn't care about loyalty and all that.
Just beat me up.
I'll take it as long as I don't die.
Do I have the right to do that?
I was the same kind of person.
I'm telling you before
I tell Lee Joon Suk because...
I want to repay my debt
to Jo Ha Neul a little bit.
Though I know I won't ever
be able to repay it all.
In Korea?
Look through all these hotels.
Choi Joon Ha could be
staying in one of them.
Let's split up and wait
in the lobby of each hotel.
Don't you think he'd come out
once a day, at least?
I'll head over to the senior home.
I don't think he's seen his father yet.
We don't know how long it'll take.
You just want to wait at the hotels?
We have no other way.
Yeah, hotels are so secretive.
They won't give out information
on their guests easily.
Which hotel should I go to first?
I should find pictures of Choi Joon Ha.
I don't want to miss him.
The anniversary of your death
is approaching again.
I come here every year
on the anniversary of your death.
I tell myself this is the last time
and return home.
But...
Every year, here I am again.
Don't you feel cooped up in there?
The land spacious and
the air is good in Australia.
Yet, I feel so suffocated.
No matter where I go in this world...
I'm in a prison.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever.
I don't think this is the place either.
I was there all night.
I thought maybe he was going through
the parking lot, so I tried the elevator.
But, I looked suspicious on the CCTV
and they kicked me out.
Gosh, I'm really starting to feel my age.
My joints hurt so much.
Splitting up like this won't work.
There are too many hotels.
I think I'll head to the senior home.
President Shin is alone and probably
hasn't even been able to shower.
Geu Rin, you're not feeling well. How
can you go that far at this late hour?
Every person here
is worried about Suk Ho.
We've all been with him a long time
and care about him deeply.
I don't think it's right to go all the
way to Yeongwol at this hour, Geu Rin.
Last time, you asked to borrow money.
Then ended up in some
weird pictures and came to explain.
Today, you want what?
You want me to play golf
with the chairman of every hotel?
My back hurts so I can't.
Then you can all get together
and you can buy them drinks.
Why would I do that?
Just help me out once.
I'll be a little bit obedient.
Not very obedient, but a little bit?
What kind of a deal is that?
Forget it. Forget it.
Okay, I'll be very good.
I'll come home two times a month.
How is that? Good, right?
You have to go on a marriage date too.
That's a no.
Forget it then.
Okay, I'll go once.
So, who are you looking for again?
Choi Joon Ha. He's a famous singer.
People in the hotel industry
will know him.
It's been a long time, Joon Ha.
I find Choi Joon Ha.
Kyungyoo Hotel, Room 2004.
But, I heard from my dad's friend.
Lee Joon Suk is looking for
Choi Joon Ha as well.
He used all his hotel connections.
Jo Sung Hyun's little brother?
Didn't you hear from the TV station?
A junior singer will do a remake
of your song "It's Okay to Cry".
They gave it to Jo Sung Hyun's
little brother.
Isn't the world a funny place?
Because of this show,
he found out what happened.
Do you remember Shin Suk Ho?
He was just a manager at our company.
Oh, Jo Sung Hyun's friend.
He introduced Jo Sung Hyun to me.
You wouldn't know his face
since you never met.
He's the President
of Jo Ha Neul's band's agency.
He's looking for you like a mad man.
The reason I looked for you...
is so you can continue
living like you are now.
Your kids must have grown a lot.
You shouldn't become
a shameful father to your children.
Don't show up now and let your
guilty conscious get the best of you.
The consequences will be very big.
Once Shin Suk Ho
reveals everything, that is.
The burden of those consequences
will be entirely on your shoulders.
Aren't you afraid?
Everyone is this country
will point their fingers at you.
You stole the song of a man
who was physically disabled.
Would you ever be able
to hold your head up again?
Don't delay any longer
and risk getting caught by him.
Why don't you leave today if you can?
I'm here to see Choi Joon Ha.
He's in room 2004.
Please call him for me
and tell him I'll be waiting here.
The guest in room 2004 checked out.
What? When?
He just checked out.
I'll confirm for you.
Yes, okay.
They're cleaning the room now.
He has already left.
Could I possibly get his contact info?
Please, I'm asking you.
I can't give out guest information.
I can leave a message for him
if you leave me your contact info.
He left an item in the room safe.
If he contacts the hotel to look for it,
I will give him your message.
Oh, then can I please have
a piece of paper?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Cheers.
Suk Ho, they say
it's really cold in Moscow.
You need to keep it together
and don't freeze over there.
Hello, I am Jo Sung Hyun's friend,
Shin Suk Ho.
I would really like to meet you
and that's why I'm leaving this note.
I know why you could not sing
the song you liked for so long.
I understand why
you have been hiding all this time.
I do not resent you.
I have no right to resent you.
I have wronged another the same way.
I used money and power to steal a song
from a nameless songwriter.
And I convinced a famous group
to release it as their own.
On the day that album was released...
that poor, nameless songwriter
left this world.
Because of me.
I haven't seen you in a long time,
and you're not drinking.
Have you stopped drinking?
I'm waiting for someone.
Oh...
How could I resent you?
I would like to meet with you just once.
The anniversary of Sung Hyun's death
is in two days.
I will wait for you at
the shabby bar we used to go to.
It's a hole in the wall
in Jinhae Market in Suncheon.
Let's share a soju
on the anniversary of his death.
I will wait until you come.
Please, I'm asking you to come.
Come again, next time.
I'll give you some delicious free snacks.
I have to get going now.
Oh, do you?
I'm sorry.
How much is it?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by DramaFever