Hello, I'm Jo Sung Hyun's friend, Shin Suk Ho.
I leave this message because I really want to meet you.
I understand why you couldn't sing your favourite song...
and lived in hiding for these many years.
I'd like to meet you, just once.
I'll wait until you come.
Please. I beg of you.
How much is it?
I thought you couldn't make it.
I'm sure it was difficult.
Thank you for coming.
This year,
so many people are looking for me.
Is it time?
I'm afraid.
- Sir.
- I know what you want.
The longer you wait, the more you'll be disappointed.
I can't do...
what you want. I came to tell you that.
Can you reconsider?
I know I have no right to say this.
Didn't you...
retire and don't you live in hiding because it's too difficult for you?
I loved singing.
However,
that one wrong choice...
made it impossible for me to sing any more.
I thought about what would happen...
to my remaining years if I were to come clean now.
It would be even more pathetic.
Please. Please, I beg of you.
A long time ago, I made a promise.
I promised to have Ha Neul sing Sung Hyun's song on stage some day.
I said it like a joke,
but now, that promise...
has become my life.
Please.
Please, I beg of you.
I don't want my family to know about my disgraceful act.
This is...
all the royalties I've received for "Go Ahead, Cry".
I didn't use a dime.
It should be quite a bit.
Before I found out about Jo Ha Neul,
I saved it to donate it somewhere.
Please give it to Jo Ha Neul, Jo Sung Hyun's brother.
I came to give you this.
Goodbye, then.
You give it to him yourself.
He won't accept it from me.
And this is my number.
I'm sure you won't want to see me,
but I will look for you again.
Please reconsider and give me a call.
I'll be waiting.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
If he won't accept it, donate it somewhere.
Is it someone's birthday?
Ha Neul, is it your birthday?
It's the anniversary of Ha Neul's brother, Sung Hyun's passing.
Stop doing this every year.
We went to see him in the columbarium today.
Your mum used to prepare much more when she was alive.
Half of these are store-bought. I couldn't cook it all.
Hey. I'm disappointed.
You should've brought us if you were going to your brother...
and introduced us.
He's right. I want to meet him.
Let's go in the morning.
I'm off tomorrow.
It's okay. Let's just rehearse.
Hey.
Aren't we family?
Do we need to have the same parents to be family?
Geu Rin.
Ha Neul is practising tomorrow, so take just us.
We want to meet Sung Hyun.
Imagine how good he'll feel if he meets me.
Let's go, Ha Neul.
The food's getting cold. Let's eat.
Thank you, Sung Hyun.
- Thank you.
Yum.
This is so tasty.
That's store-bought.
The soup is salty.
I made that.
Yum.
Thanks.
This is nothing compared to what your mum made for my parents.
Ha Neul's entire family must have been nice.
I guess that's why you are, too.
It's Mr Shin.
Hello?
I just met Choi Joon Ha.
I begged,
but it's as we expected.
It'll be hard.
He's known to be a singer-songwriter.
Asking him to tell the world his song was written by someone else...
is like asking him to strip naked in front of the public.
If he says he can't do it himself,
what if we play dirty...
and have Ha Neul go public with Sung Hyun's original score?
Who would believe that?
There's no way to prove the date of creation.
There is.
What?
Suk Ho...
had me record Sung Hyun play the song.
Wait.
Did you record it?
You said you couldn't.
Joon Suk doesn't know I recorded it either.
I'm ashamed.
I should've told you everything,
but I couldn't.
I wasn't as brave as you.
When I was your age,
why did I run away?
Are you saying the video has a time and date stamp?
It should have the date and time.
Then that settles it.
We have the sheet music and a video as proof.
Suk Ho, you don't look like you want to do it.
Why not?
This is the only way to return Sung Hyun's song to him.
It's the only way Ha Neul can sing...
his song freely on "Legend Again".
- Let's not do that.
- Mr Shin.
Think it over.
We have a way. Why would we not do it?
If we do that,
it will destroy Choi Joon Ha's entire life, not just his career.
Let's not kill Choi Joon Ha just to save Sung Hyun's song.
Choi Joon Ha is leaving the country tomorrow.
We need to find another way.
We don't have time.
Didn't you gather us because you had an idea?
What is it? What should we do?
An opportunity. We need to find an opportunity.
We need to make him want to sing again.
I'm sure he's just hiding but still loves to sing.
How will we find that opportunity?
He's leaving tomorrow. We don't have much time.
That's why I gathered you all.
We need to check all night.
Check all the portals and find every interview,
TV show, every song he ever sang,
whatever it may be.
Find the way to bring out...
the entertainer spirit within him.
It's too hard.
We must find it.
How many laptops do we have? Tablets?
We don't have time, so let's split up the years.
Okay.
Geu Rin, come with me.
Are you disappointed?
Yes.
If you only look at the results,
we'll become just like Lee Joon Suk.
I really want to convince Choi Joon Ha.
Please help me.
What if...
What if we can't convince him and he leaves?
Can you promise to reconsider then?
We will.
Let's have faith.
And...
here.
Give it to Ha Neul.
Thanks.
(YEO MIN JOO)
The resolution is poor.
Sung Hyun's audio recording is in there, too.
Listen to it when you want.
Sung Hyun...
sang so well.
I'm sure...
you've suffered a lot, too.
I'm sorry I couldn't give it to you sooner.
I thought...
I'd always keep this to myself.
I have a feeling...
Sung Hyun helped me...
meet you again...
and meet Ha Neul.
Seoul Theatre of the Arts.
What? What?
This was his first concert.
It snowed a lot, so traffic was paralysed.
Probably because it was Christmas Eve, too.
"I was very upset."
"The tickets were sold, but I wondered if the fans would come."
"The roads are jammed and the weather was terrible."
"I wondered if half would come. No, if even 10 would come."
"But I was truly moved."
"The seats were all filled."
"I started to tear up."
"It took me a while to calm my emotions and start the first song."
"It was a two-hour concert, but I think I sang for five."
"I was willing to stay up all night with my fans."
"That's how it went."
"I will never forget that day."
Min Joo, find out what time his flight is.
Geu Rin, wait with Ha Neul. He must be worried.
Man Shik, go to the airport with me.
We need to stop him.
You go to Seoul Theatre of the Arts.
I want to show him that stage again.
Okay.
Hey. Let's say we find him.
Then what? Will we abduct him?
We should show it to him.
Let's get moving.
I'll call the airlines.
Let's go.
What's this?
It's the royalties from...
"Go Ahead, Cry".
Did Suk Ho meet Choi Joon Ha?
- Yes.
- What did he say?
He explained and begged,
but he said he doesn't think he can undo it.
I know you're angry. So am I.
How dare he give this to him?
He must have struggled, too.
He didn't spend a dime.
I think he was going to donate it somewhere.
He's so selfish.
Everyone is selfish. Only the dead suffers.
He's trying to relieve himself of his guilt.
Why did Suk Ho accept this?
Are we leaving now?
Let's give Ha Neul some time.
Did something happen again?
What is this?
I'll explain later. Go back to sleep.
Okay.
Okay. Good night.
There are three flights throughout the day, but we don't know which.
We'll have to wait.
I hope we can even meet him, but can we convince him?
May we go onto the stage?
- What is this about?
- Well...
We'll be brief.
Someone really has to see the stage.
Do you have an upcoming performance?
No, that's not it.
Please.
Showing it to you isn't hard,
but you need to let me know in advance if you want to perform.
It's being torn down after this year and rebuilt.
I see.
I guess it's not the morning flight.
- I think they've all gone in.
- I guess.
Let's eat something.
We need our energy.
Okay.
Yes, Gil Joo.
Yes.
A reconstruction?
Okay.
Yes.
It'll be open until the end of the year and they'll rebuild it.
I hope Choi Joon Ha gets over everything...
and holds a concert there before it gets rebuilt.
That'd be nice.
Gosh.
Shall we go in?
Just wait.
You should drive.
Geu Rin stayed up all night.
I'm all right.
No, you're not. You look like a panda with those dark circles.
Where is Suk Ho?
- At the airport.
- And the envelope?
In your desk drawer.
Where are you going?
I'll go by myself.
Don't worry. Just stay home.
We meet again.
I understand...
that they are both very important to you.
But this is how far I'm willing to understand.
Please, step aside.
I said everything I needed to say. Let me just give you this.
Please, take it.
And...
please watch the video...
in this USB.
I'll go some place quiet and take a look.
Bye then.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
- I'm Jo Ha Neul.
- It's Jo Ha Neul!
- It's Jo Ha Neul.
- I'm your fan!
I'm sorry.
About what?
Are you sorry about what happened in 2005...
or for not setting the record straight now?
I'm not sure.
I'm sorry about both.
Are you trying to say sorry with this?
I'm returning that money...
because it isn't mine.
But why aren't you returning the song?
"Go Ahead, Cry" is still your song.
Even after your death,
that song will still be yours, Sir.
Why...
can't you return the song?
Don't call me "Sir".
I don't deserve...
such respect.
Also,
I don't have the courage.
This is the best I can do.
I'm not asking you to bring my brother back to life.
I don't want this money.
Taking this money won't bring my brother back.
I don't need this.
I don't resent you.
I blame myself...
for being too young and not being able to...
help my vulnerable brother.
I'm sorry.
It's time for me to check in.
If you won't take the money,
I'll donate it to charity under your name.
"Go Ahead, Cry".
I'll sing it.
I'll sing it on "Legend Again".
They'll applaud thinking that it's your song.
But I know,
you know...
and Lee Joon Suk knows...
whose song that really is.
I'll pray until the last minute before going on the stage.
That you walk out...
of your misery yourself.
I'll pray that the song I sing...
finds it's real owner.
Please,
prove that you are different...
from Lee Joon Suk.
Did you meet him?
Later.
I'll tell you later.
Let me take a nap.
Let's go practise.
Ha Neul says he'll sing the song.
Yes, let's go practise.
We'll go by ourselves. You should get some sleep.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Get some rest.
My worries are nothing.
You and Ha Neul...
This is terrible.
What about you?
What happened with KTOP?
I cancelled my contract and left.
There will be a press release soon.
What about Jackson?
They say they'll leave with me.
I told them they should stay.
They just need to find a new vocalist.
They wouldn't do that.
Because their trust must've been shattered.
Just worry about yourself and Ha Neul.
It was all a disaster.
I was busy getting ready to go study abroad without knowing that.
I was going to look into it for you.
Where will you go?
To England.
It's the country of the Beatles.
Jinu.
Let's...
give "Don't Touch" back.
Let's give the song back to its composer.
Suk Ho, I...
I don't have courage to do that.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
I'm sorry, Suk Ho.
Ha Neul's brother, Sung Hyun...
I saw a video of him singing and recording the song.
After seeing that video,
I was reminded of the composer who wrote "Don't Touch".
I'm sorry for making you feel burdened.
I'm sorry.
What's that? Is that for Suk Ho again?
My body aches, too.
Can't you see there are two?
You are taking care of both Suk Ho and me. Is that it?
Being an heiress makes you so generous.
I told you not to mention that.
Okay, I'll try.
Don't try. Just don't mention it.
If you say that again, I won't talk to you.
I'm going to take this.
Where's Suk Ho? Is he not back yet?
He's not. I don't know where he is.
Is he sleeping at the office again?
It has already gone up in smoke. He won't be able to find a solution.
I'll get going.
You're leaving already?
I need to take some rest.
I haven't slept at all.
Oh, dear. It's raining. I didn't bring an umbrella.
An umbrella? I should have one. Give me a second.
- There it is.
- Sorry?
No, no.
You can't take that one.
What's the problem? It's just an umbrella.
I'll give you another one. You can't take that one.
Is it yours?
Suk Ho cherishes it.
It's just an umbrella.
I don't know what it is.
I thought he only collects baseball caps,
but that umbrella is as important to him.
He was drying it up so that it doesn't rust.
Does he collect umbrellas?
He's odd.
Find another one for me, then. My car is parked far away.
Oh, all right.
I left the green umbrella at home.
Why is it raining?
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Hello?
This place hasn't changed.
Is this Mr Choi Joon Ha?
It snowed...
that day.
It's raining today.
Would I be able to come here...
and sing before this theatre disappears?
I'd like to plan a concert for you.
I'm not what people think I am. Who would come to my concert?
It'll be a full house...
like the day it was snowing.
The fans who were waiting for you then...
are still waiting for you.
I'll make sure...
that you perform in that concert hall again.
What must I do?
I met Choi Joon Ha.
Really?
Ha Neul met him, too.
Was he in Korea?
How did you meet him?
What did he say? Is he going to confess?
Geu Rin and Ha Neul played a big part in convincing him.
We just need to prepare for a great performance, then!
This is a relief.
We'll be at ease when we perform the song.
I didn't know you'll be able to do it.
You're incredible.
I didn't do anything.
So...
we're going to issue a statement containing the truth about the song.
Choi Joon Ha will not be interviewed.
That's too much to ask of him.
The press release will be written in Ha Neul's perspective.
We'll reveal that they're brothers.
The focus...
will be the fact that he got his brother's song back after a decade.
And that...
he will stand on the stage and perform his brother's song.
We don't have much time left.
I know you guys work hard but let's work even harder this time,
and make sure we can live up to the composer's legacy.
Start practising.
I have to meet some reporters.
Mr Shin, I'll drive you.
It's okay. Order something for these guys.
You should stay here today.
See you later.
Which one am I supposed to be more surprised about?
Are you saying...
that legendary song is not Choi Joon Ha's?
And the song was written by Jo Ha Neul's brother?
For goodness' sake.
I've never seen something like this in my years of working here.
What a coincidence. Or is this bad luck?
I'm discussing this with you before we release an official statement.
We have to perform on this show. Put in a good word for us.
I don't need to.
People will be talking about it even before we air it.
We'll take it any time.
Anyhow,
- did you actually meet him?
- Yes.
Did he really agree to this?
This sounds like a fraud at a national scale.
He had to think about it a lot.
He had a hard time facing the truth for over 10 years.
This shouldn't be featured on a music programme.
It should be aired on a documentary.
Can you set up the stage so that it creates a warm atmosphere?
Is there something that'll make news?
Yes, it's me.
How's the reporter who lost his chance at producing...
an exclusive article on Ha Neul last time?
This office looks so unique.
It's small,
but there are a lot of rare items.
Wow.
This is probably not a coincidence.
You fooled me last time but I heard you have something for me today.
Do you still write about scandals and get paid under the table?
Why...
are you bringing up what's happened in the past?
If I wrote about your past,
I could do it for a month.
I invited you over to reconcile with you.
Why are you in a bad mood?
What is it?
My boss told me you have something for me.
Is there more to Jo Ha Neul?
It's about Choi Joon Ha.
Choi Joon Ha?
Is he back?
What does he have to do with Mango Entertainment?
Did you talk this over with him?
I have a favour to ask of you.
It's not a report.
Make this an emotional confession.
It took him a lot to do this.
The composer...
is Ha Neul's brother?
Are you okay, Ha Neul?
We can take a break if you want.
Yes, Min Joo. Where are you?
At the office? That's good.
If you open the drawer by my desk, there's a USB.
Can you bring it with the laptop to the studio?
Yes.
There it is.
Suk Ho cherishes it.
It's just an umbrella.
I thought he only collects baseball caps,
but that umbrella is as important to him.
He was drying it up so that it doesn't rust.
I'll head to the nursing home.
I'm sure Mr Shin hasn't slept or showered in days.
Geu Rin.
The umbrella is green.
Drink this.
I'm okay.
You're here.
Suk Ho asked me to come.
There's a video in here.
He said I should show it to Ha Neul.
Sung Hyun.
Sung Hyun, why...
Why are you there?
Sung Hyun.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU.
Sung Hyun.
Why can't you sing?
Sung Hyun can, why can't you?
Sung Hyun's not here.
But this song must be sung.
Why can't you sing it?
There is only one person...
who should sing this song. That is you, Jo Ha Neul.
There will be a press release today.
"Go Ahead, Cry"...
is not Choi Joon Ha's, but Jo Sung Hyun's song.
Jo Sung Hyun is Entertainer Band's Jo Ha Neul's brother.
Sung Hyun lost his song to KTOP and passed away.
What shall we do now?
You'll be in pain,
your heart will break and you'll run out of breath.
But you must sing it well.
Because it's Sung Hyun's song.
(JO HA NEUL MUST BE FURIOUS. THE GUY KILLED HIS BROTHER.)
I'm going to drop by. Would you like to have a drink?
I'm planning on drinking tonight.
Julia,
are you still awake?
You must be in a state of shock.
Sweety, I always thought you were the best.
And today, you are even greater.
You've done the right thing.
James is really proud of your courage, too.
He kept telling me how much he misses you.
Thank you for saying that.
I really mean it.
So, please, come back.
Let's take a break and go somewhere.
Yes,
I'll be home in no time.
Get some sleep. Good night.
Love you.
We can have a drink when you visit me in Australia.
I have a favour to ask you.
Why is everyone being so stupid and causing trouble?
Why? Why?
I'm sorry, Sir.
Did you check on other singers' and actors' positions?
The studios notified us of cancelling...
all music programmes and variety shows with us.
The actors and singers who were planning to renew their contracts...
said they wouldn't.
Tell them we'll modify the terms all on their favour.
Make them re-sign even if it means giving them exceptional offers.
Yes, Sir. I'll meet them and discuss it.
Leave.
You heard that, right? He won't be able to handle it alone.
You should meet every one them and resolve it.
There's something I need to say.
This is how far I'll go with KTOP.
Please accept the resignation letter I submitted.
What will you do after you leave?
I didn't make you the director because you were competent.
Nobody will take you in.
Snap out of it, Joo Han.
Yes, Sir.
That's why I'm quitting.
I know that the director position doesn't suit me.
I want to start over...
like Suk Ho.
You are all crazy.
Do you think you're something?
I learned a lot from you, thanks.
I have a favour to ask you.
Can I...
be on "Legend Again"?
There isn't a day without crisis. What's wrong this time?
I need to go to the studio.
When will Suk Ho's life find peace?
Choi Joon Ha himself will be on stage?
That's perfect for us.
Would Ha Neul agree to this?
I was thinking if you can make it a duet performance.
A duet? For Joon Ha and Ha Neul?
Let's talk for a second.
Kyle, let's arrange this again.
Pardon?
I didn't really touch it.
We were just practising Ha Neul's brother's version.
Leave the same feel but make it a duet.
A duet? For whom?
We have less than a week left. Kyle, can you do it?
What are you talking about?
Whom am I singing this with?
Are you going to tell me to sing this with Choi Joon Ha?
No,
this is a joint performance...
between you and Sung Hyun like we've promised.
Sung Hyun.
These are my friends.
You know we're in a band together, right?
Hello, Sung Hyun.
We'll be performing your song today.
I'm honoured.
I arranged it a bit,
and it's much...
- Kyle.
- What?
Let me finish.
It'll never be as good as the original version.
Please cheer us on though.
Sung Hyun, I have to be honest about this.
Ha Neul looks better than you.
Hey.
- What?
- I agree with you.
I've never seen you in person,
but I saw many pictures of you and heard a lot about you.
I feel like you're my real brother.
Look forward to...
Ha Neul's performance.
Synced & ripped by bozxphd
Subtitles by VIU
(LEGEND AGAIN)
Sung Hyun.
This is it.
(JO SUNG HYUN, ENTERTAINER BAND)
You look more nervous than usual.
Are you nervous?
A bit.
It feels funny.
Thank you...
for letting me be here.
for returning my brother's song.
I gave it back after I took it from him. You shouldn't thank me.
I don't deserve it.
Thank you for dragging me out...
of a prison I built for myself.
I'll see you on stage.
You might beat me up for this but I'm going to say it, anyway.
He looks so cool.
You punk.
- What are you doing?
- What?
Shut your mouth.
The next performance is the one you've been anticipating for.
Not long ago, it was revealed that this song is not Choi Joon Ha's,
but belongs to a young man who is...
the brother of Entertainer Band's Jo Ha Neul.
Choi Joon Ha made the confession himself.
Today,
we have Choi Joon Ha here.
Let's welcome him on stage.
I'm sorry to be back on stage after 11 years...
and not being better off.
I know some of you may not want to see me on stage,
but I decided...
to be here for a reason.
I left...
without even saying goodbye.
My fans waited 11 years...
not knowing what happened to me.
And now, I'm back with disgraceful news.
I'm...
embarrassed.
But I wanted to summon up the courage...
to see you...
in person and apologise for what I've done.
I wanted...
to bid my farewell formally.
That's why I'm here.
I apologise for what I've done,
and I'll live...
the rest of my life...
reflecting on my mistake.
I don't deserve this honour,
but please allow me to introduce him.
He's the rightful owner of "Go Ahead, Cry".
It's Jo Sung Hyun.
(JO SUNG HYUN)
(ENTERTAINER BAND)
I miss you, Sung Hyun.