[The Entertainer]
[Episode 17]
Subtitles by DramaFever
Sign here, Suk Ho.
I'm old enough
to be your uncle, you know.
Okay, Jo Ha Neul.
[CONTACT: THE PRESIDENT WILL CREATE A BAND FOR ME...]
Shin Suk Ho.
Here is the contract.
I will do my best to make
your brother into a singer.
Oh, thank you very much.
He hasn't graduated elementary school
yet, so his future looks bleak.
Sung Hyun.
It took me too long
to keep my promise, right?
Now, it's my turn.
I will return the song that I stole.
I was waiting here
to take you to the airport.
I will drive you there.
I called a taxi. It's all right.
I should have call you earlier.
I guess I was too late.
We should say our goodbyes here.
Thanks to you, President Shin...
I've had this lump in my chest for
10 years and it's finally gone.
I'll do the rest myself.
Thank you for taking the first big step.
I've learned a lot from you.
I think it's my turn now.
Well, the taxi is waiting.
Call me if you ever visit Australia.
Drinks are on me.
I'll do that.
I don't think I'll forget today
for a really, really long time.
Ha Neul was really great today!
Suk Ho... President Shin worked so hard.
Thank you to everyone.
I had trouble holding back tears
while I was playing.
Where is President Shin anyway?
Is he somewhere crying by himself?
He went to say goodbye to Choi Joon Ha.
I enjoyed the performance.
It was really good.
Yeah, it was.
You act like you're talking about
another group.
Why did you ask to see me?
Oh, I'm looking into details
for you to study abroad.
Before I leave...
I want to return it too.
After seeing you and Choi Joon Ha...
I thought about
how I should live my life.
I got some courage.
As you suggested...
I want to give back "Don't Touch".
You might not be able
to go on stage again.
Either way, it will be hard
for me to go onstage again.
I feel too guilty.
It will be a bigger problem for you.
I looked into it.
We could both end up in jail.
What about Entertainer Band?
I don't know.
What should I do?
President Shin, are you
sick or something?
Did you get some sort of bad diagnosis?
I have lost some weight lately,
but I have no health issues.
Then why would you propose such a thing?
I am joking, of course.
But, why would you do this unless
you have a limited time to live?
Entertainer Band is done suffering
and is finally on their way to success.
Why would you throw that away?
How am I throwing that away?
I just want them to grow bigger
in a proper system.
Mango could join Wild Company.
However...
I may be away
for an extended time period.
Gosh, you sure are saying
some strange things today.
What? You turned yourself in?
Why didn't you consult me first?
What were you thinking!
If I had consulted you?
"Yes, turn yourself in."
Would you have said that?
What about the investigation?
How will it proceed?
Once they contact songwriter
Jang Min Soo's family
they will call me in again.
They can't get in touch
with his younger brother.
I guess my confession isn't enough.
And once they confirm everything?
Will you go to jail?
Maximum of one year in jail
or a fine of 10 million won.
Let's pay the fine.
We can get the 10 million won somehow.
Don't do that. I won't pay it.
Even if the money fell
from the sky, I wouldn't pay it.
I'm going to jail.
Is jail a game to you?
Min Joo.
How can 10 million won
make up for someone's life?
Even being in jail for a year is not
enough to make up for a life.
If they want to punish me more severely,
I'm willing to accept it.
Also, our Entertainer Band...
I've made arrangements for them
to join Wild Company.
I know you and Geu Rin could handle it.
But, I think it's best to send
the kids to a bigger company.
You should worry about yourself
before you worry about the kids.
What will you do for a living
once you get out of jail?
You have to keep Mango going.
How can you close it down?
I don't have the confidence to do it.
Sung Hyun, what did you think
of our performance?
I will be singing until I die.
But, I don't think anything
will top singing with you.
President wants to go
out for lunch. Let's go.
- Okay, be right there.
- Okay.
Oh, this is good.
I think it's even better
because it's been so long.
Oh, by the way.
Have you guys heard of a big company
called Wild Company?
It's a really big management company.
They have a lot of singers
and actors too.
Why are you bringing up that company?
I think Entertainer Band
needs to move on to stage two.
I had a meeting with them and
they are very interested in us.
So, Entertainer Band
will no longer be Mango.
We will be part of Wild Company
and work with Wild.
You'll get into Japan, China,
Southeast Asia, and the Hallyu craze.
I like things the way they are now.
We can work hard and make ourselves
into that kind of company.
Yeah, let's eat lots and work harder!
- Fighting!
No, you guys don't understand.
Mango is like a small, tiny store.
Most companies have about a hundred
employees overseeing one new group.
We're happy with the way things are.
Just keep an open mind and
think about this realistically.
Wild Company has a person in charge
of music, drama,
commercials, international...
Why are you suddenly acting like this?
I...
I don't have the right to be President of
the agency representing Entertainer Band.
We made a promise as a joke 11 years ago.
You did everything you could
to get me on that stage.
Yet, you say you don't have the right?
Then what would give you the right?
I don't know.
Both Lee Joon Suk and I are the same.
Why would you say something like that?
How are you anything like him?
Well, the thing is...
I've been doing this job a long time.
And no matter how drunk I got, I called
a designated driver or took a taxi.
I never drove myself.
President, why are you suddenly
talking about your drunk driving?
But, that night...
The reason I drove was...
That night...
an unknown songwriter
had committed suicide.
Jackson's "Don't Touch".
Jin Woo didn't write it.
It was written by that songwriter.
I stole that song from him.
He was a poor songwriter
who begged and pleaded with me.
I said cruel things to him.
That day he committed suicide.
I suddenly felt the need for speed.
I grabbed the steering wheel
and got into an accident.
I went to jail.
I couldn't protect Jackson.
Why would someone like me have any right?
How can I continue working
with nice kids like you?
I turned myself in.
Once the investigation starts,
I think I'll probably go to jail.
The police are tracking down
the family of that songwriter.
Once they find them,
the investigation will proceed.
I can't stay here with all of you.
So, go to a better company.
Work hard and make Entertainer Band
flourish even more.
Here's the pizza that you ordered.
Thank you.
Yeon Soo, give this to Chan Hee.
Chan Hee should be home
from kindergarten soon.
Let's get going now.
What are you all doing? Get up.
What's with the expression on your faces?
It's not like I'm immigrating.
You have to go
make money at a big company
so that you can give me
an allowance later.
Let's go.
He was killed because of
a low-life in this industry.
It happened while I
was driving to his funeral.
That must have been why he worked
so hard to get Sung Hyun's song back.
What do you think the President
was like in the past?
He's a really good person now.
I was about to give up on drumming
because of my mom.
If weren't for President Shin,
I wouldn't have had the courage.
I would still be working
in those karaoke club bands.
Honestly, who doesn't have
skeletons in their closet?
On the other hand...
that songwriter's family
probably went through a hard time
like Ha Neul's family.
You're very tired, right?
I can look at these alone.
Suk Ho.
I always thought I knew you better
than anyone except for your parents.
You probably do.
Seeing how much you're changing lately,
I don't think it's true though.
What do you mean, I'm changing?
I'm barely getting by trying to fix
the stupid mistakes that I made.
Yes, this is Shin Suk Ho.
Yes... yes.
All right.
I'll be right there.
What is it?
They got in touch
with the songwriter's family.
I'll be going now.
I'll go with you.
You'll just go and cry.
It's okay.
I'll go alone.
I need to organize my thoughts too.
Take care of the kids and make sure
they aren't too traumatized.
Oh, you're here. Sit down.
You're Jang Jin Soo, the younger brother
of Jang Min Soo, right?
Yes.
Shin Suk Ho has turned himself in
for misappropriation of copyright.
We need to confirm the facts.
Shin Suk Ho stole a song
that Jang Min Soo wrote.
Then, Jang Min Soo committed suicide.
Is that right?
I'm not sure.
Well, you need to let us know accurately.
I don't know anything accurately.
Excuse me, what are you saying?
You came to my office last year.
It's true that my brother passed away.
As for the reason...
I have no way of knowing why.
There was no suicide letter.
I'm busy trying to make a living.
Why are you calling me here
for something so unpleasant?
But, you came to me with that song.
You asked me why I killed your brother.
You came to my office.
Don't call me again
about such a painful family memory.
I only came because
I was told I needed to.
I lose a day's pay by coming here.
It's hard enough to make a living,
so don't call me here again.
So, you're not going to press charges?
If so...
There's nothing to press charges for.
This person?
I don't know him.
What is all this?
Wait, hold on.
You don't know me? You do know who I am.
You know what I did to your brother.
Do you want to go to jail that badly?
I don't want to go.
Why would you get punished? I will.
I came here all the way from Sokcho.
I won't even be able
to head back tonight.
Just buy me a drink.
I...
I am the one who killed your brother,
Jang Min Soo.
I even turned myself in.
Why are you claiming not to know me?
You came to me
with the song "Don't Touch".
You know everything,
so why are you doing this?
You've done something wrong.
Now, live with it.
As for the wrong I've done,
I'll have to live with that.
That song was his life.
I stole something he had put all his hope
into and pushed him into the afterlife.
I'm not someone you'd want
to sit and drink soju with.
He couldn't even support
his son's talents.
My father was so poor that he couldn't
buy us rice and we were malnourished.
That pushed my brother.
She said a man
who writes music has no future.
Then she dumped him.
She pushed him once too.
No, that's not it.
He told me he was getting married
after that song was released.
That was what my brother wished for.
It had been over a year
since she had broken up with him.
On the day that my brother died...
he told me was having a hard time
and was just so lonely.
He pleaded with me to come up here
and have a drink with him.
I told him it was hard enough
to make a living with my pay.
I said I would see him next time.
I pushed him once too.
He was standing on the edge.
You pushed him once too.
So, who should be punished first?
This doesn't change anything.
Why don't you get up if you're done here?
Let's go back to the police station
and tell them the truth.
Tell them that I was the one
who made Jang Min Soo commit...
Stop it!
After my brother left like that,
my father hasn't been able to get up.
He's finally getting up
and trying to live.
I can't have my brother's case
come up again.
My father won't be able to get up again.
Why is everyone so selfish?
Do you think it would make me
feel better if you go rot in jail?
Would my father feel better?
Just so you can feel better?
We've only just managed to start healing!
Why are you digging this up now?
Then what should I do?
I can't bring your brother back.
I just want to return the song to him.
I should be punished.
I should spend the rest of my life
in jail if they tell me to.
A person is gone.
A person has died and is gone.
Just...
remember it forever and live your life.
As if a thorn has been
pounded into your life.
Live in pain.
That's how I live.
Thanks for the drinks.
Wait!
That performance...
I enjoyed it.
That person who died.
He reminded me of my brother.
I cried a lot.
I enjoyed watching it.
It's hot. Be careful.
I'll call you when Suk Ho comes back.
Why are you here?
I can't do anything else
and I can't sleep.
What about you? Why are you still here?
I don't know.
I guess I feel the same way.
Do you know which police station he's at?
He wanted to go alone.
He didn't tell me anything.
Is that you, Ha Neul?
Where are you? Are you okay?
Our Ha Neul.
My little brother.
Lovable Ha Neul.
Where are you now?
Just wait, I'll be right there.
Ha Neul!
That's enough drinking, Suk Ho.
You're here?
Sit. Sit down.
You drank all of this?
Let's have a drink, Ha Neul.
Ma'am, one bottle of soju please.
It's all right.
Suk Ho, you've had a lot to drink.
Let's get up and go.
- Ha Neul.
- Yes?
You're dying of curiosity, right?
You're wondering why
I'm walking around like this, right?
I ought to be in jail right now,
so why am I walking around drunk?
Tell me tomorrow.
I told Man Shik to come to the office.
Why did you call Man Shik?
Let's go for round two.
You can come along with me.
Get on.
Jo Ha Neul, you're pretty strong.
You're strong. Look at this back.
You're heavy. Don't move around.
Ha Neul.
Stop talking. You reek of alcohol.
Sung Hyun saved my life.
They don't want to press charges.
He saw you on stage with Sung Hyun.
He liked it.
Sung Hyun.... our Sung Hyun...
He saved me.
Hey, you kept groaning in your sleep.
Did you hurt your back?
No, maybe I slept funny.
I wonder what happened to President Shin.
Is he still at the police station?
He's probably sleeping at home.
Did you hear from him?
He didn't go to jail, did he?
I don't know the details.
He was very drunk last night,
so I took him home.
What? He was drunk?
I've never heard
of President Shin drinking.
- They don't want to press charges.
- What?
Then we won't have to go
to Wild or whatever.
Of course not.
Eat, eat!
Ah, I feel like dying.
I really think I'm dying.
How much did you drink?
I haven't gone drinking in so long.
I feel sick.
Who did you drink with?
Is something wrong?
What did the police say?
Police?
- Hello.
- Oh, hi!
President, you feel sick, right?
I knew you would be like this.
This will make you feel better.
I had something. I'll be fine.
Why did you go to the police station?
Ah, later. I'll explain later.
- What about the kids?
- Back at home.
Come to Wild Company at 6:00 p.m.
I'll be there.
President!
I better go to a sauna. Thanks.
Gosh, seriously.
You have to eat something
in order get over a hangover.
I think my hangover is completely gone.
It's hard to say that everything
worked out regarding the stolen songs.
The world is so treacherous.
Everything worked out so why are you
sending the kids to another company?
Our kids would go to waste
if they stayed with me.
There must be some traffic.
There is a lot of traffic
into Gangnam at this hour.
It's all right. I'm sure they'll be here.
I'll call to see where they are.
Where are you?
- We're still at home.
- What?
Why haven't you left yet?
Well... they all refuse to go.
I'm sorry, Chairman.
They must be having
a hard time with this.
They must be very attached to you,
President Shin.
No, it's not like that.
I will arrange another meeting.
I'm sorry.
Get everyone to the office right now!
What's with you guys? Huh?
Seriously.
It's hard to get time with Chairman Choi.
We barely managed to book a meeting
and you throw it away like that?
What kind of first impression is that?
We won't be meeting him at all,
so why do first impressions matter?
- What?
- That's right.
Sit down, President. Sit, sit.
Everyone, sit down. You too, Yeon Soo.
President, you too.
Here.
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
Everyone calm down.
I have a presentation to make.
We all need to have a discussion.
Why are you talking?
It will relate to Mango.
Prepare yourselves for it.
It's okay to cry, okay?
That's the title of a song.
President Shin wants
to send us off to a better place.
I understand the good intention.
But... that means
you're throwing us away.
Stop saying nonsense.
Listen to what I have to say.
Don't interrupt me. I'm serious.
"I don't think I can raise you well."
"Meet better parents, get adopted,
and grow up in a better environment."
To that child, it's being thrown away.
It's not being sent away.
Why would you bring up adoption?
Pull yourself together.
You can't confirm if adoptive parents
are better or not.
I have never met my biological parents.
How could I know if they're better
or worse than my adoptive parents?
I grew up in a good environment.
I grew up happy, with good parents.
They supported me a lot
in doing what I liked.
And I got accepted into Juilliard.
I'm adopted.
When I saw Yeon Soo,
I thought he was amazing.
It also made me think...
why did my biological parents
throw me away?
My dad said I cried so much
when I was adopted.
He wanted me to live my life smiling,
so he named me Lee Bang Geul.
It might be a better environment.
Even if we're a little bit poor
and it's a little bit hard...
I wonder what it would have been like
to have lived with my biological parents.
I think about that a lot.
You want us to go to a better company?
What is better?
What's the criteria?
Who gets to determine that?
See, I knew you would need tissues.
It's okay to cry.
Gosh, that song title is just so useful.
What is this?
No one is crying?
I just told you my painful family story.
It was very touching.
Why is it that no tears are coming out?
You guys don't think I'm lying, do you?
Shouldn't you cry with me, Geu Rin?
You're adopted too.
I wasn't adopted.
I'm still legally registered
under my parents.
Ha Neul's parents took me in
because my parents passed away.
Huh! What the heck?
I thought Ha Neul's family adopted you.
I was so good to you.
You were? To me?
Regardless, Kyle is right.
Are you going to throw us away like this?
Gosh, I'm going to go insane.
I'm not throwing you guys away.
Entertainer Band will lose what
you've achieved if I leave for a while.
How can all of you
be so dense about this?
I think it's you who's being dense.
We all understand.
Why are you the only one?
We'll work really hard and make them
bigger than Wild Company would.
Yeah, that's right.
We don't even want to move fast.
Even if it takes us longer,
we want to do it together.
With you, President Shin.
To commemorate our fighting spirit,
let's go on a trip!
I've never gone on a trip.
Not even in college.
Sounds good. Let's go.
Dad, are we going on a trip?
I hope so.
President Shin, looks like
you'd better treat everyone.
We all worked so hard
getting over big hurdles.
We're all going, right?
President Byun, Man Shik...
and Section Chief Yeo.
What? Weren't you going to invite me?
What are you guys thinking?
If you're not going to Wild,
you should work hard and make money.
Let's go this one time!
Where should we go?
The ocean, a valley...
Or, Southeast Asia!
Wow!
Is your back okay?
Buy me some medication.
You're so heavy.
Our stock price is dropping too quickly.
At this rate, there's a good chance
our stock could be delisted...
Book a meeting
with the all station chiefs.
Chairman, I don't think the boycott
of the broadcast stations is the issue.
The actors and singers in our company are
preparing a contract termination lawsuit.
What kind of crap are you saying?
They are claiming that the agency
affected their image negatively.
How about this place?
It's nice. There's a barbecue too!
Wonder which one he'd prefer...
I like them all.
Oh, you were wondering
about President Shin.
No, I meant both of you.
Oh yeah.
Suk Ho has this pretty green umbrella
that doesn't suit him.
Did you give it to him?
Oh, that?
He was walking without an umbrella,
so I gave it to him.
Something that pretty
doesn't suit Suk Ho.
A big black umbrella like this
would be better for him.
Right? That's so true.
Oh, I totally forgot. I have a meeting.
- I'll be back.
- Bye.
I don't have my car keys or my wallet.
I don't want to go back inside.
Damn!
Where are you going?
Oh.
Is something wrong?
No, something is in my eye.
Aren't you going to the office?
Go on in. I'm headed out.
You don't have car keys or a bag.
Where are you going?
Are your shoes comfortable?
It's perfect for walking,
both your shoes and the weather.
Let's stop walking now. My legs hurt.
Why were you crying?
I cried my eyes out in front of you.
It was embarrassing for me as a man.
I told you why I was upset.
Can't you tell me?
Only if you can keep a secret.
I'm not Kyle.
Where should I start?
If I start from 10 years ago,
talking all night wouldn't be enough.
Where should I start...
about Shin Suk Ho.
You must like President Shin.
Funny, right?
You've known him for over 10 years.
Why didn't you ever tell him?
Because he might run away.
If I told him that I liked him,
I thought it might get awkward.
I thought it would be hard
to stay friends.
That was why.
But, why are you crying now?
Suk Ho...
I found out that he likes someone else.
I think I cried because
I was so taken aback.
You'll keep my secret, right?
Of course, I will.
But, I don't think it's love
you're feeling.
Love isn't something
that you can hide for that long.
If you truly love someone,
you can't endure not telling them.
I don't like you either.
You're too straightforward.
That's how it is.
Love is straightforward.
At my age, it's a little embarrassing
to be so straightforward.
35 is a good age to start a new love.
I'm 34!
You're not the same age
as President Shin?
I didn't want to acknowledge
that he was older, so I lied.
If I knew he liked younger girls,
I wouldn't have lied.
You're cuter than Geu Rin.
You seem to know more than I do.
Me? No, I don't.
Well, what I know is that
you are a very awesome woman.
You have looks, talent,
and even a good family.
You need a lot of courage
to be more straightforward.
That's about all I know.
Thanks for the kind words.
Let's go now.
Your legs hurt, right?
What should we do?
I'll walk it off.
I'll walk and think about
whether this is friendship or love.
Let me ponder on that.
We'll be in trouble if someone
takes our picture
walking around together like this.
Then I'll just say that I pursued you.
No way! Your fans will hate me.
I'm hurt. You should've
at least told me.
What's wrong with being adopted?
Well, I didn't care about it
when I was in the States.
It seems different in Korea.
I thought I might get looked down on.
You must have been
really upset back then.
When?
When I was giving up and leaving.
I asked you if you thought I was
the director of an orphanage.
Did I ask you to feed me?
I only wanted to make music.
I'm being treated like an orphan.
It must have been an inferiority complex.
I didn't know anything and talked about
being the director of an orphanage.
It must've been so upsetting.
Gosh, life is like a boomerang.
The important thing is...
Where are we going on our trip?
If we can't go to Southeast Asia,
can we go to Jeju Island?
One thing is for sure about both
your adoptive and biological parents
I am sure they are both very kind.
How can you be so happy
and talk about going on the trip?
I have to succeed, President.
My adoptive parents are still mad
that I quit Juilliard and joined a band.
We'll get into the Hallyu market.
We'll go to the States.
They'll love me there.
Yes, Shin Suk Ho speaking. Yes.
What?
Yes, of course.
Don't do it.
They want a commercial. Why not?
A band should be on stage,
not filming commercials.
Hey, then why do actors do commercials?
They should only act.
They say Yeon Soo is perfect for it,
so how great is that?
He can earn money and save up
for Chan Hee's education.
Yes, but why must it be...
Jaeo Group's With Me Apartments
is a big deal.
Why are you being like this, Min Joo?
I'm saying you should not ruin Yeon Soo's
good image by getting involved with Jaeo.
Aren't you taking this too personally,
Yeo Min Joo?
There are four more of Sung Hyun's
songs on Choi Joon Ha's album.
Section Chief Yeo was thinking
we should remake them.
Would Choi Joon Ha
be all right with that?
He was the one who suggested it.
I think we should discuss it with Suk Ho.
I will be working on some songs
on my own with Man Shik.
We should consider
writing some new songs.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Wow, Entertainer Band
working hard into the night.
You're in a good mood, President.
You must have good news.
Are we going on a Southeast Asia trip?
I don't like you.
Well, we received another request
for a commercial.
- Commercial?
- Wow!
Wait, wait, wait!
Is it a beer commercial?
- An apartment commercial!
- Apartment?
Wow, you need a really good image
to do apartment commercials.
Our image is really starting
to appeal to people.
The commercial offer is not
for Entertainer Band this time.
It is only for our Na Yeon Soo.
- What?
- Wow.
The news is full of terrible stories
about the irresponsibility
of young people.
Na Yeon Soo is raising a son on his own
and living out his dream.
With Me Apartments feel that you
suit their company image
and have selected you.
Wait, With Me Apartments...
Jaeo Group!
Hey, what is this?
Are you really dating Section Chief Yeo?
Section Chief Yeo
put in a good word for you.
There he goes again.
I told you I'm not.
How could I possibly be with her?
Stop saying nonsense.
Section Chief Yeo
was actually against it.
She feels that Yeon Soo's image
is too good for them and opposed it.
How do you feel, Yeon Soo?
I don't really know.
How can I shoot it on my own?
Can't we all do it together?
You're perfect for it.
That company's marketing team
is good at their job.
Can I stand in the back?
I can do it for nothing.
You'll look pathetic. Don't do that.
You better treat us big time
when you get paid.
First, why don't we go our trip?
Why don't we shoot the commercial
and then go?
So annoying.
Geu Rin, meet Jaeo Group's
marketing team to go over the contract.
No, we should go to the office first
and organize at Mango.
Okay, President.
You're dating Section Chief Yeo, right?
She helped you, right?
Stop it. Enough, already.
Give me an apartment then.
Ready... action!
How about it?
Should we...
live together?
With Me.
Cut!
All right, okay. It's fine, it's fine.
Yeon Soo, try to think about
the first time you started dating.
It was so sweet.
So, so, so sweet.
You know what I mean? You can do it.
Make up, please. Wipe away the sweat.
Come on, come on. Up, up!
Good.
Sorry, everyone.
Think about a girl you used to like.
Heart beating.
Right, okay?
No, that's not it.
You get all sad when you
think about Chan Hee's mom.
I'm so bad at this, right? What do I do?
Well...
Think about a celebrity that you like.
Who knows? You might end up dating
a pretty celebrity if you become a star.
That sounds great. Smile!
This is not the time for joking.
Focus, okay?
Okay, we're ready.
Did you come to see
because you were bored?
I came to see
just how bad the concept was.
Yeon Soo, let's try to do it
in one take this time!
Make it sweet!
Yes, sweetness coming! Ready?
Good, good, good.... action!
How about it?
Should we live together?
With Me.
Cut!
That was so good! Totally great.
But, you should be looking at the camera.
Where are you looking?
I'm so sorry.
- It was so good too.
- Should we live together?
With me, with me...
I don't think I can watch anymore.
Min Joo.
Shut up if you're going to say
something ridiculous.
That article is real, isn't it?
What?
Come on. Let's live together,
Section Chief.
Should we live together, Section Chief?
I told you to stop it.
I like you so much, Yeon Soo.
I can do it really well too.
How about it? Should we...
Just drive.
Okay.
Aloha, aloha!
We're going to Gapyeong.
You must think we're going to Hawaii.
Leave me alone. My heart feels Hawaii.
Don't ruin my dreams. Aloha.
Dad, are we going now?
Chan Hee, we'll go when
Aunt Geu Rin gets here.
Where is Aunt Geu Rin?
She went to buy groceries
to make you yummy food.
She'll buy Hanwoo beef, right?
Let's move everything into the van
and pick up everyone at home.
Is everyone else coming on their own?
They're coming in Man Shik's car.
Okay. This is going to be so fun!
- Are you that happy?
- Yes.
This is my first group trip.
I didn't even go in school.
This is going to be fun.
How far did you get in school?
One semester in my second year.
- Your major?
- Veterinary Science.
I was pretty good in school too.
I got into a college in Seoul.
Veterinary Science.
That suits you perfectly.
You would be good
at giving shots to dogs.
My professor did say I looked like
a puppy, so it was perfect for me.
Let's stop by one more place.
Where?
Sunglasses are a necessity for vacations.
How about these for you?
- Choose your own.
- Mine?
You'll complain that the sun
is hurting your eyes while you drive.
It's okay.
Pick a pair before I change my mind.
Even an expensive pair?
Choose a pair that suits you.
I'm pretty, so everything suits me.
That's true.
Pick a pair.
What do you think?
Looks good.
You're here?
- Hi.
- Hello.
Wow, this place is great.
What is all this food?
Who's going to eat it all?
People eat a lot.
Jump.
Wow, this place is great.
- Tada.
- Ginseng alcohol.
It's something similar to ginseng.
You should have brought
a 21 year-old whiskey.
This is like for old grandpas.
You have no idea
how good this is for men.
Man Shik isn't having any.
When did I say I wasn't having any?
How is it good for you?
There are kids listening here.
I'm here.
Yeah!
What did you buy?
I bought Hanwoo beef and lobster.
Wow, Hanwoo and lobster.
Billionaires are the best!
Hey!
Should we live together?
Hey, have you been hit
by a lobster before?
Oh, wait.
- Oh!
- Wow, that's big.
This lobster is so big!
You'll hurt your back.
This is the heaviest item.
Thank you.
- It's so nice.
- We could share this with everyone!
Dad, you have to win.
Kick it over here.
What are you doing, Man Shik?
I'm good at soccer.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
- Throw it.
- Go, Aunt Min Joo!
I got it.
Kick it.
Man Shik!
- How sad.
- What?
He feels like a teenager in his heart,
but look how bad he is.
I feel sorry for him. I can't watch.
I'm going to go inside to eat lobster.
Oh dear...
Seriously!
Kyle and that mouth of his.
He is so noisy.
I got this.
Yeon Soo is good at sports.
Yeah, he is. Aren't you going to join in?
I'm still injured from carrying you.
Who told you to carry me?
I'm usually good at walking around.
You're good at walking around?
Seriously?
I should have taken a video of you.
- Ouch.
- Oh, it's hot.
Okay, okay. I got it.
My ball, my ball, my ball!
Use your head.
Gosh, are you okay?
I'm okay.
President, when are you
getting your driver's license back?
Why? Do you feel bad for Manager Jung?
What are you talking about?
President Shin is here to work.
Why else would he be here?
I'm not adopted.
I'm still legally registered
under my parents.
Okay, okay.
My ball, my ball!
Why is she putting
so much effort into that?
- Be careful.
- Okay.
- Get it, get it. Okay?
- All right.
Subtitles by DramaFever
[THE ENTERTAINER]
Why is Jin Woo number one
in the search rankings?
"Don't Touch" was not written by me.
Are you okay?
- Did you read the book?
- Take it back.
Read the last page of the book.
KTOP no longer has any hope.
What do you want?
Come to my school.
You said there weren't
any pretty girls there.
- There aren't.
- I think there is one.
Jae Hoon will be leaving
for the third album.
- What?
- Sorry, I couldn't stay until the end.
A new drummer
will come to replace Jae Hoon.
I will work very hard.