[The Entertainer]
[Final Episode 18]
- Is it done cooking?
- So much smoke.
Looks good.
It looks so yummy.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Is it good?
Oh, it's hot.
It's so hot.
Drink a little bit at a time.
Oh!
Why is Jin Woo number one
in the search rankings again?
- Huh?
- What is this?
To all my fans. This is Jin Woo.
I saw Choi Joon Ha's confession
and I haven't been able
to sleep for a few days.
With a heart full of fear,
I would like to make a confession.
"Don't Touch", released last fall,
was not written by me.
The song and lyrics were written
by songwriter Jang Min Soo.
I found out about that
after it was released.
I'm not trying to absolve myself
of any wrongdoing.
I should have turned things around
when I found out.
I didn't have the courage to do it.
You are all
disappointed in me, aren't you?
I am sorry for showing you all
this side of me.
I wanted to give this song back to its
rightful owner, even if it's too late.
I am letting everything go
and will leave to study music.
I will start from the beginning
and study music.
Once time has passed, I hope a day comes
when you can forgive me.
I will dream of a day
when I can see you all on stage again.
I want to apologize and say goodbye.
Yeah, Suk Ho.
I told you everything was taken care of.
Why did you bother...
Are you okay?
I'm running away because I'm scared.
What?
I'm kidding. I'm at the airport.
Come to England when you get some money.
Why didn't you tell me you were leaving?
I want to go and learn English,
then look into schools.
Hey kid, you should have
come to see me before you left.
I didn't tell you on purpose.
I thought you might
come to the airport and cry.
You're a really bad kid.
How can you leave like this?
Call me if you need anything.
I'll fly over it you need me.
Also, call me when you arrive.
Suk Ho...
Thank you.
I'll do really well over there.
I think I'll miss you most.
Thank you so much.
Come back, Lee Jin Woo!
Jin Woo, we love you!
Wow, it's so pretty here.
- Geu Rin.
- Yeah?
I really liked you.
When you first came to our house,
I liked you so much.
After my brother left,
our house was so depressing.
But, my mom and dad started
smiling again after you came.
I think I should be saying that.
After living at my aunt's place, I moved
to your house and started to smile.
I'm the one who's thankful.
I think it was when I was a sophomore.
When my dad wanted you to be
Jo Geu Rin instead of Jung Geu Rin.
I was so glad that you said no.
If we had become real siblings,
my first love would have come to an end.
Ha Neul, I...
I watched you be excited with your
first love like I was with my first love.
So, I decided to let it go.
Suk Ho is good person.
Hey, what are you talking about?
You are really obvious.
Ha Neul, you are a really great guy.
You're tall, handsome, and kind too.
Are you trying to console me?
Later...
Later, I want to see your mom,
dad, and brother in heaven.
I want to be a good daughter
to them then too.
I want them to praise me
for taking good care of you.
I think I took better care of you.
Honestly, I'm more like
your older brother.
I was there when you went
through puberty and your voice changed.
Gosh.
Oh no, I'm in trouble.
What now?
I'm going to be so popular later.
Your parents and my parents will fight
over who gets to keep me as a daughter.
What should I do?
What are you talking about?
This darn popularity of mine.
You're not actually popular.
Did you just hit me?
Stop it, stop it.
- I got it!
- They sure are having fun.
It's Chan Hee's turn.
I knew you'd do that.
Your name has been removed from the list
of winners for this year's Asian Award.
We just received notice,
so we couldn't do anything about it.
I'm sorry.
There's no need to apologize.
I'm not going to cry over an award.
I understand. Thank you.
You know what the KTOP singers
and actors are intending to do, right?
You've been notified
that KTOP's stock will be delisted.
Yet, the talent you represent say
that they will stay if the CEO is gone.
Isn't that a relief?
I am planning on starting over
from the very beginning.
Your shares will take a very big hit
if the stock is delisted.
But, isn't this a big loss for regular
people who hold those shares?
What is it that you want?
Sell KTOP to Wild Company.
You need to avoid the stock delisting
and get what you can out of your shares.
You can open a store somewhere
and make a living for your family.
There is no hope for KTOP.
The only company willing to run it
will be us, Wild Company.
[CHAIRMAN LEE JOON SUK]
Writer.
If you're going to have them run,
all four of them should do it.
It works perfectly.
We can negotiate the guarantee later.
Then Kyle can do it.
He has the best feel for variety shows.
All right.
I'll come see you tomorrow
at the broadcast station.
Yes, bye.
You don't have an umbrella?
No.
Your mom's not coming?
She's at work.
I don't think it's going
to stop raining anytime soon.
[ONE YEAR LATER]
You're all wet.
I should've brought you an umbrella.
- Are they done shooting?
- Not yet.
Ha Neul needs to see
Writer Kim when he's done.
I'll take Kyle to his variety show shoot.
What about Jae Hoon and Yeon Soo?
What happened to the road manager
I told you to hire?
Section Chief Yeo
is still looking into it.
Tell her to get over here right now.
Yes, all right.
The Show's number one song this week...
Will it be Entertainer Band
for the fourth consecutive week?
Or will it be NowBoyz
who are in hot pursuit.
Everyone, you're dying to know, right?
Yes!
This week's number one is...
Congratulations, it is Entertainer Band!
Congratulations!
Yes! They won.
It is thanks to all of you,
that we've come this far.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Oh yeah!
- Oh yeah.
When I'm afraid, you hold me.
I just pick it up.
When I can't seem to do anything, yeah.
When everything seems so difficult, yeah.
I just pick it up.
Your hand grabs mine like magic.
You were always there like this.
Just like a fairy,
you carry me and fly.
To the edge of the sky and sun.
You will stay with me.
Come on!
Yeah!
You were always there like this.
Just like a fairy,
you carry me and fly.
To the edge of the sky and sun.
You will stay with me.
- I don't like it.
- I don't like it either.
President Byun, it's not just me
who doesn't like it.
None of our singers like it.
Putting Smiley Distribution on the album
makes people question our company.
Well, Mango makes us
sound like a fruit store!
Fine then.
I'll back off on the name of the company.
We'll call it Mango Music.
Let's discuss the next item.
What else is there?
We need a company representative.
Representative?
We have one, Yeo Min Joo.
That would be thievery.
We also have Byun Kil Joo.
President Byun.
Entertainer Band's second
and Park Sung Ho's third album
- you know I made them both, right?
- I know.
But, every company
has a critical turning point.
Don't you remember
Entertainer Band's "I See You"?
If Smiley Distribution hadn't used the
christian contemporary music connections
that song would have never
have made it out into the world, okay?
So, you want Mango Music
to be under your system?
That would be thievery too.
Yeo Min Joo and Byun Kil Joo.
Wow, we both have "Joo" in our names,
now that I think about it.
We should be co-representatives.
Co-representatives?
- What do you think of being a Director?
- How about Director Yeo?
Fine, we'll do it.
You have to have that on your business
card in order to get married someday.
Oh my! Then, let's make
business cards soon.
I have a arranged date next week.
Let's see...
Don't we need to hire more employees?
The two of us aren't enough.
I hear you're forming a girl group.
I hired one person who knows
everything about this industry.
Why did you do that by yourself?
I have to see what she looks like.
I like an Asian beauty...
Must be here.
Come on in.
Well, the office is very cozy.
It's very charming.
Did you finish up
at the chicken restaurant?
You insisted that you needed me here.
I had to leave that place.
What could I do?
Thank you for agreeing to come.
If you were going to hire,
couldn't you...
Maintenance man?
That's President Byun of Mango Music.
You have another President here?
How can there be two in this tiny place?
I oppose this hiring.
You look like a very good man, President.
Wow, you have great style too.
You're like Kim Kwang Seok.
I'm a big fan of Kim Kwang Seok.
Should we have a drink and talk?
This is Jo Ha Neul
and this is the writer.
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a fan of Entertainer Band.
Thank you.
I've seen all your TV dramas.
They are really fun.
I'm more thankful to hear that.
You have a kind face,
so you'd suit our character well.
Thank you.
Have you read the script?
He's a character who experiences
unrequited love. What do you think?
I know I'll be great at
an unrequited love story.
I told you to take him home
when he was done with his variety show!
I checked on him taking a shower
and going to bed.
Wait until I catch him. He's dead!
- Hey, find him!
- Okay.
I like this place better than home.
Man Shik, your bounce dance was like...
Wait, you're not a regular here.
I switched clubs.
The music is better here.
Of course, you're no regular clubber.
You're a true club maniac.
Cheers!
Put that bottle down now.
I must have been too close
to the speaker. I'm hearing things now.
Yeah, I have to suddenly pee.
- Me too, me too.
- Let's go.
Oh, you're here?
Did you bring him here, Man Shik?
No, this is my regular club and
I happened to run into him here.
I have to pee.
Let's go home.
President, there are pretty girls here.
Should we go out together? Oh yeah!
Using just words
don't seem to work with you.
You are dead now. Close the door.
Why are you closing the door?
You're working hard late into the night.
Yes, I am working a lot.
A new club could open
with all the money you've spent in clubs.
Aren't you tired?
Of course, I'm tired. You hit me.
Then why do you go to those clubs
every day like they are your office?
I don't know. I guess I'm bored.
Then get a hobby or start exercising.
Dancing is exercising.
You should've become an idol then.
Why did you join a band?
It's too late to become an idol.
All right, I'll cut back.
Don't cut back. Just quit.
Do you want to go to the States
to visit your parents? I can schedule it.
They're visiting me next month.
Go ahead and try being a club addict.
I'll just keep going there to catch you.
This is good.
We're done.
Let's go eat something good.
Okay, what should we eat?
Pork belly?
Yeah! Let's go.
Have you had pork belly with leeks?
It's good.
- Really?
- Unlimited refills too.
Let's go, let's go.
Wait up.
Okay.
Sorry, Geu Rin.
You looked like my friend from the back.
No one hangs out with me
because I'm older.
[DADDY LONG LEGS]
What about a place to stay?
The agency in China
will let us know by tomorrow.
- What about the flight?
- I took care of that.
I will fly out with this ticket
and report back to you.
How many times did you go
to Shanghai with Lucy Girls?
Three or four times.
Do a good job there.
It's open. No one finds out
where they are staying.
I understand.
You can go home now.
See you tomorrow.
You're not going home yet?
I'm going to read Ha Neul's script.
Then I'll get going.
"His Romance."
His Romance...
She must be excited
about something again.
President!
Why are you always here?
You wanted to finish school.
You said you should be on campus in your
20s and handed in your resignation.
You should go study.
Why do you keep coming here?
Be honest. You're happy to see me.
No, you're always complaining
about how hard school is. Go home.
It's just that I found something
very interesting today.
I thought you should know.
I have no interest in veterinary science.
Why do I need to know?
It's not veterinary science.
It's this.
[DADDY LONG LEGS]
Have you read this book?
I'm not interested in literature either.
I'm busy reading Ha Neul's script,
so you should go home.
Then just read the last page because
that's the most important part.
Take it with you.
- Have you had dinner?
- I'm very full.
Then I suppose I should go home
and have a sad bowl of cereal.
I'll have ramen if I'm still hungry.
I'll have rice if I'm still hungry.
Go home quietly and eat.
Why do I need to know your dinner menu?
You don't need to know.
I feel a bit lonely. Bye then.
Did you look into your own place?
No, I've been busy.
The kids are moving to a different place.
You need to tell the manager
if you're going to stay with them.
That way we can look into a place.
I should move out.
Did you really eat dinner?
I ate so much I have indigestion.
Anyway, make sure to read
the last page of this book.
Bye now.
[TWO PEOPLE EVENTUALLY BELONG TO ONE
ANOTHER. DON'T YOU THINK THAT IS GRAND?]
At the end of "Daddy Long Legs",
they marry and live happily together.
I just wanted to tell you.
Yes, Yeon Soo.
Here you go. My goodness.
His dad was supposed to be here
by nine, but he didn't show up.
He was waiting up
but then he fell asleep.
The shoot must have ended late.
It's nice that his dad is famous now,
but Chan Hee must be bored.
He's at the age
where he needs his parents.
But, he never ever complains.
He's such a good boy.
Just like Chan Hee's dad.
Once we relocate to a new place, we'll
hire someone to look after Chan Hee.
Please take care of him until then.
I can keep watching him.
You're too far away.
It's too hard to pick him up.
I'll be going now.
You should get married
and give us grandchildren too.
Okay. I'm going now.
All right! Here are your beverages.
We're sorry, but can we get
your autographs and pictures?
Sorry, but no pictures.
- I'm such a big fan.
- Sorry.
Sorry.
You must remember
your days as our manager.
It's just automatic for you.
If you have something to say,
why not say it at home?
Why are we out here?
She's even treating us.
She must need a favor from us.
I said I would pay.
I can't let you do that.
I'm paying, so enjoy your drinks.
Jae Hoon, what did you order?
Kyle, I want to switch.
You got your germs all over mine.
Mine tastes better.
Gosh, seriously.
Tell us what it is you want to say.
I need a favor from all of you.
Come to my school just once.
Think of your former manager
and come visit me at school.
I don't think it's
a very difficult thing to ask.
Is something wrong?
Wouldn't that be considered an event?
Are there a lot of pretty girls?
I haven't seen anyone prettier than me.
Then why would we go there?
Did you discuss it with our manager?
Wow! You guys have really changed.
You shouldn't do this to me, Kyle.
When you were crying at the police
station, I came all the way from Busan?
I wasn't crying!
All right, but still you guys,
can you come out just one time.
No one will play with me because
I'm a student who went back to school.
I sit alone in lectures and I eat alone.
Geu Rin, many people in my classes
go around alone too.
If Entertainer Band shows up,
my campus life will get much better.
I'll treat you all to dinner, okay?
I'll treat you all.
Hey! President Shin
wants you all at the office now.
Let's go, let's go. Hurry.
Oh goodness.
My shaved ice...
Give me an answer before you leave.
- Hey!
- Hurry up, hurry up!
Hey, give me an answer.
Really?
President Shin Suk Ho!
You have such bad timing.
So bad, so bad.
Drink these.
We're going to finish up our second album
promotion with a fan meeting in Shanghai.
Ha Neul will be shooting a drama soon.
Then what should we be doing?
- Let's rest a bit, Yeon Soo.
- What?
How long has it been
since you played with Chan Hee?
Yes, we should work hard
while the fans are there.
If our lives fall apart
while we do it, we won't last long.
Let's take our time
with the third album and rest a little.
I'm saying you should rest
and take a vacation.
I'm not saying you should
go clubbing every night.
I told you I quit.
Why are you saying that?
- I'm trusting you.
- Okay.
Also...
For the third album...
Jae Hoon will no longer be with us.
- What?
What?
Jae Hoon, why don't you explain?
Are you in on something
with the President?
Why would you leave?
I want to study now.
You see? Geu Rin has poisoned the waters.
Why is everyone leaving to study?
It's time for me to choose now.
I promised to keep up my grades
while doing Entertainer Band.
Now that we've become so busy,
my grades are a mess.
Then quit school like I did.
I was very resolute.
I got to do something I liked a lot.
Now, I want to give my mom her life back.
Did you discuss it with your mother?
No, she doesn't know yet.
She'll be very happy.
I'm sorry I couldn't stay until the end.
I'll join the fan club.
Then who will be on drums
for our third album?
We'll get a new drummer.
I can't play guitar
if the drummer isn't right.
There he goes again.
I'm just saying that I wish Jae Hoon
didn't have to leave.
I'm disappointed.
But, let's respect Jae Hoon's decision.
Then our last event with Jae Hoon
will be the Shanghai fan meeting?
One more thing.
The Asian Award show
will be held in Seoul this year.
We've been nominated for an award.
Wow!
Really?
- Wow!
- That's so awesome.
The Asian Award ceremony will be our
last event for our second album.
If we win the award,
I will speak on our behalf.
You can't do that.
I'm leaving so I should...
I said we were nominated.
I didn't say that we won it.
Who do you take after
to be so over the top?
We take after you, President Shin!
Yeah right!
A studio apartment
in a commercial building.
All the places near your school
are rented out.
Is it okay if it's a bit further out?
Show me anything on the subway line.
I'm mad at you.
I hear Jo Ha Neul is doing a drama.
Why did you ask to see me?
I heard you don't have a female lead yet.
Are you kidding me?
If I had Jo Ha Neul, I would have
no problem finding actresses.
The male lead is not
the issue for you, Director.
You need cast a good female lead first.
Don't you think I know that?
All the actresses in this country
are saying no.
You know that I really love you, right?
I don't know that at all.
The female lead needs to be an actress
who has nothing left to lose.
Actresses who have commercial deals
are too soft to do
a film as intense as yours.
- Then should I forget about it?
- Why should you?
You'll go to Cannes if you just make it.
You know this so well.
How come actresses don't know?
Dangerous... it's a dangerous character.
That character is someone
who has only one path to survive.
The actress needs to attack it
as if there is no tomorrow.
Yeah, so who is that?
An evil character who
the entire world is mad at.
What do you think of Lee Ji Young?
Lee Ji Young... what!
That crazy girl who tried to destroy
Jin Woo and Jo Ha Neul?
Don't get all worked up
and think about it.
Sit. Sit down.
Just cast Lee Ji Young and
it becomes an issue right away.
Hey, I'm trying to make a movie
not create an issue.
The director is important.
Even Venice has acknowledged you,
so just cast Lee Ji Young.
That character and Pork and Rice Soup
are one hundred percent in sync.
What more does she have to lose?
Her life is like a movie already.
Her method acting
will come out naturally.
Lee Ji Young...
Isn't that kind of dangerous?
Your movie theme is "dangerous woman".
That's true. Dangerous woman.
Dangerous woman, Lee Ji Young.
Oh, it's hot. So hot.
Hey, what's for lunch today?
Should we have vegetables
wrapped in lettuce?
We should eat some meat.
Why are you always feeding us grass?
Right, Ji Young?
I think you like meat.
I don't really like it.
You and I are just aren't
on the same wavelength.
Is Kyung Soo going to be late today?
He's going to eat dinner
at his friend's house.
That kid never studies
and he's always playing.
Hello?
Hello, this is Shin Suk Ho.
- Who?
- Ha Neul's manager, Shin Suk Ho.
Yes, what is this about?
Is Ji Young doing well?
Okay, I will ask her about it.
I'll discuss it with Ji Young.
I gave the director your number.
Talk it over.
The director will call you
and you can discuss it with him.
Yes, yes.
By the way...
thank you for thinking of my daughter.
There's no need to thank me.
This could be Ji Young's last chance.
Give her courage
so that she isn't afraid.
Yes.
Bye.
Do you want to meet him?
Don't bother if you're not up for it.
We're looking into
a nail shop in town too.
Living quietly like this is nice too.
Will you stay by my side?
Ji Young.
No matter where you go...
your dad will always be by your side.
So, don't be scared,
and do whatever you want.
Ah, the weather is great.
Where is the veterinary science
department?
There are so many buildings.
Excuse me. How do I get
to the veterinary science building.
Oh, it's a bit complicated.
Do you see that red brick building?
If you turn right there,
there's an ATM machine.
There's a split in the road there.
Don't go to the left but keep going up
and you'll see a white building.
It's the building on the very end.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
Oh, wait.
What did she say again? ATM...
I'm going to the building next to it.
Can you drive me?
The uphill is a hard walk.
Get in.
Thank you.
I'm sorry, but can you tell me
the directions again.
Go straight, for now.
Straight? Okay.
Thank you.
No, thank you.
Oh my gosh! It's Jo Ha Neul.
My phone, my phone.
Take a picture. Hurry!
Ha Neul, Ha Neul!
Did you come to pick up your sister?
- Sister?
- Ha Neul?
You didn't have to work today?
You didn't have to!
Why are you shouting right in my face?
I'm just upset I don't have a megaphone.
Did you eat lunch? I'll buy you lunch.
Geu Rin, can we have lunch with you?
Oh, but my little brother is here.
He's your little brother?
Did I not mention it?
Hello.
I'm very close to Geu Rin.
- Me too.
Hello.
This is my little brother, Ha Neul.
- Should we go eat?
- It's Ha Neul.
Should we go eat? What should we eat?
Huh? What should we eat?
Get in.
Gosh.
Are you that happy?
You saw how everyone
was pretending to be my friend, right?
Now, the news needs to spread and
my school life will be much better.
Look at the things I do for you.
My little brother is the best.
You showed up at school
to help me out.
I'll treat you to a movie. Let's go.
I can't. I have to go
to the rehearsal studio.
The new drummer is coming today.
Kyle wants to practice
in order to get the basics down.
He's really funny.
So, the drummer
to replace Jae Hoon is coming.
I want to go see too.
All right.
How exciting.
You said there weren't any
pretty girls at your school.
There aren't any. You saw them.
I'm the best of the bunch, right?
I don't know about that.
I think I saw one.
Let's open the window
so everyone can see you.
Come on!
Everyone, Ha Neul is here.
What are you doing? Enough already.
Kyle, what are you doing?
There is ranking system.
The new drummer is
the rookie of our group.
We need to put him in his place
right from the beginning.
That's how the third album activities
will be peaceful.
Do you think this is the army?
What are you talking about?
We should make it comfortable.
- No...
- That's what I'm saying.
I am a little worried though.
Kyle will have a hard time playing
if the drummer isn't as good as I am.
So, you should just do it.
Just thinking about Entertainer Band
without you makes me sad.
I think I have tears in my eyes.
We should've chosen a new guitarist,
not a drummer.
Geu Rin, aren't you going to the library?
Can you even give the puppies
a proper shot if you study so little?
I can give you a shot.
A shot for rabies.
What? Try it then.
Give me a shot right here.
- Oh, hello.
- Hi guys.
Oh, what are you doing here,
Jung Geu Rin?
A new member is starting
so I had to be here.
Of course, she is the former manager
of Entertainer Band.
Master songwriters
are on a different level.
You kids...
Is this how you greet
the master songwriter
who made your second album a hit?
I told you to say the words
every time you see me.
Victory to Pinky Toe!
Victory!
The nicest kid is leaving. I'm so sad.
Just keep playing drums.
- Where are you?
- Here.
What about the drummer?
Yes, come in!
Oh my! Welcome. Hello there.
Hello there. They call me Pinky Toe.
I'm the best songwriter in Korea.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Aren't her arms too thin?
I don't know if she'll play well.
President, you didn't only choose
from a video, did you?
Play for us, Soo Hyun.
I will play now.
Bravo!
President, we should release
the third album. Let's go!
Kyle, what were you saying before?
Didn't you say Entertainer Band
without Jae Hoon had no meaning?
Jae Hoon has to go study.
Thanks for the ride before.
Oh, you knew who I was?
A hat and sunglasses
can't hide your handsome face.
I'm Ha Neul's older sister. Hi.
Oh, hi. I'll work hard.
All right.
Aunt Min Joo!
Oh! Chan Hee.
- Aunt Min Joo!
- Yes.
It's been too long, Chan Hee.
I missed you, Aunt Min Joo.
Really? I really missed you too,
Chan Hee.
What brings you here?
I thought everyone went out
because there's a new drummer.
Everyone went out,
but you weren't there, so we came here.
Oh, I'm very touched.
Aunt Min Joo, Dad bought me this.
Wow, that is so cool.
Your dad's the best.
I heard that the new drummer
is very beautiful.
Everyone must be excited.
She is a pretty girl
and plays the drums well.
How pretty is she?
She's just... you are much prettier.
- Why do you keep doing that?
- What?
You shouldn't say things like that
so carelessly to women.
When girls your age hear it, they think
it's the beginning of something.
Really? Then I wish I could
start something.
Is there someone you like?
There is. There really is.
Who is it? Is it someone I know?
- Yes.
- Really?
Geu Rin is with Suk Ho,
so who could it be?
- The new drummer?
- No.
Then who else do I know?
Remember what I said to you
a long time ago?
Love is straightforward.
Yes, I remember.
So, I want to be straightforward
like a fastball.
That's really cool of you.
I... like you.
What?
If you ask me when I started
to like you, I don't really know.
At first, I just thought
you were a really cool woman.
Maybe that was why
you were always on my mind.
Yeon Soo, I...
Someone once told me
once you confess your feelings
to someone, they are no longer yours.
The rest is up to the person
who received that confession.
I once said that if you're in love,
it's not possible to hold that in.
You remember that, right?
I felt that I didn't deserve you.
So, I was going to keep
my feelings to myself.
But...
even though I know
that I'm lacking, this is love.
I can't hold it in.
I really like you.
Yeon Soo, I'm 35 years old.
You're 26.
We're nine years apart in age, so why?
Every day, I counted
the difference in our ages.
Thankfully, there is still one finger
left when I count with both hands.
I know I'm not the best catch.
You are beautiful and talented.
You're the daughter of a billionaire.
I'm young and I have a son.
On top of that...
you found out about my first love.
You found out about my first love too.
Thank you for thinking of me
in that way, but...
I'm not asking you to do anything now.
The one thing I have going for me
is that I am young.
I know I can wait.
I've told you how I feel,
so I'm going to sleep well tonight.
Then am I going to have trouble
sleeping from now on?
I have to think this over?
Don't think about it for too long.
If you don't sleep well,
you'll get wrinkles.
What?
Aunt Min Joo!
Chan Hee! Did it fly?
Did it fly like this?
Gosh, really...
Mister, you can't put that there.
- This is Kim's Ramen, right?
- Yes.
- This was delivered to me?
[KIM'S RAMEN]
[ENTERTAINER BAND]
[KIM'S RAMEN
ENTERTAINER BAND]
Shin Suk Ho... seriously?
Thank you, Suk Ho.
Make lots of money, Kim Joo Han.
It's raining. It's raining!
Was it supposed to rain today?
- Do you have an umbrella?
- No.
What should we do?
- I'm running for it.
- Geu Rin.
President.
Check the weather, would you?
Let's go.
You still have this umbrella.
It doesn't break.
You came just in case
I got rained on, didn't you?
No, I was just walking by.
Did you read "Daddy Long Legs"?
No, I don't like
sentimental books like that.
How would you know it's sentimental
if you didn't read it?
- Are you hungry?
- Yes.
Soo Hyun, you'll be
on the red carpet next time.
You must be disappointed this time.
I'm just starting out now.
They looked so good in their tuxedos.
They are all good looking kids.
No, Ha Neul looked the most handsome.
I'm letting you know one more time.
I'm Ha Neul's older sister.
That's why we should be close, Sis.
Shouldn't the agency handle matters
when members have relationships?
What is Suk Ho doing?
It's just youth.
There is no hesitation in youth.
Kids these days are too straightforward
and come at you like a fastball.
Straightforward?
I like fastballs.
I like baseball too.
Let's be really elegant out there.
Jae Hoon, this is your farewell.
Enjoy yourself.
I've even prepared an acceptance speech.
Hey, I said I would do that!
Just don't fall on the red carpet
from nerves.
Kyle is the most in danger of that.
Your dad's so cool!
Let's go.
Woo!
What are you doing? Go.
Just go.
Go in. Inside!
You guys are idiots.
We are...
Entertainer Band.
Let's go!
Subtitles by DramaFever
[THE ENTERTAINER]
President, have I shown you
my impression of Sung Yuri?
I don't want see it.
Hello, my name is Sung Yuri.
Let's do another take.
Where is it?
- Let's go again!
- Lights!
Why are you doing this to me?
What?
I'm very nervous.
Hit it, hit it. Hit your face.
- Good, right?
- Yes.
Does that hurt?
It hurts.
Were you not going to invite me?
Eat, eat, eat!
- Gosh, that hurts!
- Really?
Eat lots, okay?
Sit down, sit down. Sit!
Take one!
- Sit! Just sit down.
- Here.
That's good.