Why did she have to go?
I don't know she wouldn't say
I said
Something wrong now I long
For yesterday
Yesterday
Love was such an easy game to play
Now I need a place to hide away
Oh, I believe in yesterday
You're good.
I practised it a hundred times,
but it's hard to learn at my age.
Are you married?
I was widowed five years ago.
I have a son who is in university.
I was widowed, too.
It happened long time ago.
I'm alone now.
I have a daughter who's almost 40 years old.
Right. I have my parents and a brother, too.
I'm not alone, I guess.
The street lamps
On the alleyways
Are turning on one by one
Beyond the scarlet sunset
The day has gone by again
Everything feels like it was a dream
I miss you so
Just the way you were
As if nothing
Ever happened at all
Thank you.
Ma'am, your card!
- I'm sorry. Thank you.
- No problem.
Are there any tickets left?
I really have to go.
We only have business seats left.
I see.
I'll take it.
- Yes.
- Did I tell you that...
Jeong A is getting a divorce?
- You did.
- What do you think about it?
I think she's finally taking her revenge.
I don't think she'll actually do it.
What do you mean?
She already found a new place.
Seok Gyun doesn't know about it.
We're going over to clean the place tomorrow.
- Come with me.
- Not again.
Don't make me regret making up with you.
Just date a guy instead.
Don't be so obsessed with me.
Thank you.
Hold on.
What else should we take to help her clean?
I guess you and Wan talked it out.
It was a misunderstanding about Dong Jin.
Now, I'm the only crazy one.
It's her fault for making you misunderstand. It's not your fault.
Anyway, it feels good to pull out her hair.
She screamed and told me that she hated me.
She probably only said it out of spite, right?
Well, it's not like I adore her all the time either.
I guess it's the same.
Contrary to what most mums think,
kids usually hate their mums.
I like my mum.
That's because you got older. You weren't like that before.
That's true. Mum was a nightmare.
There is no truce between a mother and a child...
until you're on your deathbed.
When you're about to die, Wan will love you a lot.
She might even cry her eyes out.
Let's look forward to that day.
If anyone wants to be loved by their kid, I guess they should die.
Hey, Choong Nam. Should I start dating?
That's what I want to ask.
There's a guy, you know?
He's 10 years younger.
I've been just eyeing him.
I think he's quite all right.
This is amazing.
It's hot.
Here, you didn't even have dinner.
Fill yourself up with this.
Be careful, it's hot.
I wish it rained more.
I know, right?
I wish it would rain more.
It's just drizzling.
I wish it would rain...
like cats and dogs...
so that the two of us are stuck here.
I want to be stuck here for three months...
and just stay with you.
It's hot.
Eat or talk. Just do one at a time.
Why are you so rushed?
It's because I like you.
Gosh.
It must be good to like me.
I don't like or hate anything now that I'm old.
Hey.
You have some on you.
It's off.
You have some, too.
Back then,
we were doing something like this...
before we kissed.
I did the same thing with my late husband.
Why did you have to break the mood?
Why did you have to mention him?
Why did you bring him up?
- Gosh.
- Are you going to sleep there?
If you don't want to share a room with me,
go to that chilly room and sleep.
Gosh. Here.
If I go over the line...
I'll bring the axe from outside...
and cut you.
Your husband, Jung Cheol...
What was he like to you?
Other than cheating on me once, he was a good man.
I guess he didn't cheat on you more than once.
Are there such people?
Are you one of them?
No. I'm the type that women fell for.
I wasn't like that.
What was your wife like?
She was beautiful.
Tell me more. What was she like?
I just told you. She was beautiful.
She was a little sensitive,
but it wasn't a big deal.
I heard you quit your job for three years...
to take care of her when she was sick.
I did.
I loved those three years.
I used to love whistling, just like you.
If you're trying to charm me with your whistling,
she can here you from up there.
She would be cheering me on.
She'd think I made a nice new friend.
You wish.
What is it? Do you think your husband wouldn't like it?
Were you good to her?
Only after she got sick.
I didn't care about her much before then.
Husbands...
grow up when their wives get sick.
What morons.
When was...
the happiest day in your life?
The day my eldest was born.
When was the saddest day then?
When my eldest died.
Min Ho's my second son.
It was just a fever.
We lived near my husband's home town.
He was on a business trip,
so I carried our son all the way to the hospital.
But they said...
he was already dead.
I couldn't believe it.
I carried my dead son...
and walked and walked along...
a path lined by trees.
I kept walking.
He was so cute.
He had double eyelids, just like me.
Let's stop. I miss him now.
You know,
I don't fear death one bit.
I'll be reunited...
with my husband and the people I miss.
You aged so beautifully,
so I thought you'd had an uneventful life.
But then, no life...
is truly uneventful.
Did you really want to see me?
Every now and then...
I'd wonder how you'd be doing.
How honest.
I wouldn't have believed it if you said, "all the time".
Growing old changes you in a way you don't like.
If I were younger,
even if you slapped...
or attacked me with an axe,
I would've still tried to hug you until our ribs broke.
I can't now.
I'm just too sleepy to.
Let's see the sunrise tomorrow.
Okay. Goodnight.
Who's there?
(Sharpening the Blade of Revenge, Part 1)
Are you cold?
No.
If you're tired,
I can carry you.
I'm still pretty strong. Get on my back.
I'm serious.
Carry me, then.
- What?
- Carry me.
Just walk.
I used to be able to carry you.
Do you remember?
You were asleep one night, but I woke you up...
and carried you all the way up a mountain.
You kissed me first that day.
It must've been your wife.
We'd gotten into a fight...
and took separate buses to go home.
I don't like it.
You brought your wife to a place we went to.
This isn't the place I brought my wife to.
It's fine.
My memories get mixed up and I lose track sometimes.
You're right.
Wow.
The sunrise here is just...
Thank you for bringing me here.
I'm grateful that...
you're still alive.
Take my hand. You're embarrassing me.
Some other day...
No. We might not need to come back.
This alone...
is good enough.
Yes.
This is very nice.
Choong Nam, thanks to you, we had a great time. Thank you.
They're having fun.
What's that?
Are you jealous?
I should be the one there.
I know.
I'm off to pee.
Just go. Did you have to tell me?
It stinks.
Would you like me to set up your bed?
Hello.
Hi. Where are you?
Not me. Where are you?
At home.
What if he faints when he sees me?
It's just three hours from now.
What are you talking about?
Jeong A's getting a divorce?
What's the point of going against her? She made up her mind.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
I asked you if you're free this week.
Okay, check your schedule and call me back.
What's going on with Jeong A?
Did I tell you to take care of yourself?
No, I didn't.
Take care of yourself and Ha Neul, too.
Say something!
Why does Jeong A want a divorce?
Did Seok Gyun agree to it?
I haven't heard anything from him.
Whose side are you on?
What? What side?
I'll always be on Jeong A's side.
Keep your mouth shut.
This is nice.
Is she really getting divorced?
These cabbages are so fresh.
How much is it?
- It's 15 dollars.
- Okay.
Dad, you should pull the cart.
He's so annoying.
Stop complaining.
Where is the bracken from?
It's from Mount Bukhan.
Dad, they're fine. Let's just buy it.
Bracken from Jeju Island or Mount Jiri is the best.
- Give me a bag.
- Sure.
Bracken from Jeju Island or Mount Jiri is the best!
If you want to beat me for it, go ahead.
Enough is enough.
Bye.
Dad, we already got pollack. Why are you getting cod?
Three, please.
Let's just get two.
Let him be. This is the last time.
What do you mean it's the last time?
He nags at you all the time about money.
So why is he spending so much on the memorial service?
He even invited distant relatives.
We should make a lot.
Let's hire some help.
We can't make it by ourselves. Mum will get sick.
That's why we're shopping four days in advance.
I'm giving her time to take breaks in between.
Look at those arms. Your mum's really strong.
She's got so much energy in her. What's so hard about doing...
3 to 4 memorial services a year?
On top of that, your grandparents...
won't eat anything unless it's made by your mum.
Think before you open your mouth.
Hurry up.
He's so rude to everyone.
I got a call.
Yes, Nan Hee.
Jeong A, this place isn't going to work.
There's no end to cleaning.
Don't stop her from the revenge.
Let's go get chickens.
Mum, he wants to buy chicken.
We already got pork.
Tell him you can't. Tell him to stop.
He's your dad. Tell him yourself.
He's your husband.
Should I tell her to sue him?
I bet she'll get 200 to 300 grand.
It's not enough for an apartment, but she could get somewhere nicer.
This is too worn down for an old person like her.
It's worse to live with Seok Gyun.
I know. That's why she should ask for compensation.
Hey, it's not her who should ask for compensation.
Seok Gyun should ask for it if anything.
His wife and her friends...
got a place and is cleaning it behind his back.
He's going to feel betrayed.
Compensation is for the victim.
Looking at how it's been lately,
the one who deserves compensation...
is Seok Gyun, not Jeong A. Aren't I right?
That's true.
This is probably worth 10 million dollars in compensation.
Poor Seok Gyun.
What goes around comes around.
This is probably only the beginning of her revenge.
Why do you keep saying it's revenge?
It's definitely a revenge.
She's been sharpening her knife in silence all this time.
She was waiting for the right moment.
Come on.
No matter how I think about it, it still feels wrong.
She should get a divorce first then leave home.
She's stabbing his back.
Whether she divorces him first or later,
it's the same thing.
I saw Dae Cheol.
He only sent me flowers for two months.
Then he finally asked to meet up in a note.
What did he say?
I only saw him from outside a window...
for about 30 minutes.
If his wife is still alive, you shouldn't see him.
He probably came because she died.
He was a little...
aged.
Don't see him.
You should have had tea with him if you went out.
What's the point? It's just tea.
What's wrong with it if it's not a big deal?
Where's Wan? I miss her.
I don't know. Her phone's turned off.
Who knows what she does alone at home?
By the way, she broke up with Yeon Ha for sure, right?
She must have.
She can't marry a disabled.
That's the same thing as a married man for me.
What are you looking at?
Yeon Hee.
What brings you here?
I took a plane.
Right.
Come in.
Have you been well?
Yeon Ha's in bed.
Still?
He worked all night.
He works on a European timeline.
Why are you still single?
Gosh. Why are you?
I'm...
I don't know.
Can you leave?
I'll be in the office.
- See you.
- Bye.
You don't have to leave.
I didn't mean that.
She should've left sooner.
We met again after three years.
Is this the welcome I get?
Did I come here for nothing?
I flew for 18 hours.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
How about some milk tea?
Am I not welcomed?
Tell me. Am I not?
No, you're welcomed.
I was so excited.
I thought...
you would be so happy to see me...
that you'd faint.
I guess I was mistaken.
No, I'm pleased.
This is a bit weird for someone who's pleased.
It's like you're forcing yourself to put up with an unwelcomed guest.
You're really cold and distant.
I'm not.
I'm so happy I want to jump up.
I really am.
You have a nosebleed.
See? I have a nosebleed!
I fought with my mum and stayed up working...
for three days just to come here.
I took two flights, a taxi and a bus.
Gosh... And all I get is this from you!
It's like you're...
making me pay for upsetting you!
What was that about?
All of my stuff are still in there.
Even the photos.
So why were you so cold?
You scared me! I almost had a heart attack!
Seriously...
It only took me 18 hours.
It was so easy.
Do you live here?
You come without calling now.
I can't sleep because of Seok Gyun.
If you want to talk about that, leave.
Okay, fine. I won't, then.
Come here.
Sit down.
Here.
Look.
Ta-da.
- Isn't it pretty?
- It's lovely.
Here's the next page. Look.
You can colour in from here.
Drawing and colouring help prevent dementia.
Even if it's not for that, it's still fun.
You lose track of time.
I was painting at home yesterday evening...
when I thought of you.
I thought I should give this to you.
That's why I'm here.
Can I do this?
- No, no, no.
- What?
Use the darker colours later.
You have to start with the lighter colours.
Use the darker colours at the very last...
to add effects.
Don't spit on me.
- You're too loud.
- Did I spit on you?
- Let me.
- No.
- Let me help.
- I can manage.
- Mum.
- Who's there?
The door was open. Did you forget about our date?
Oh, right.
This man is a very old friend of mine.
Jeong A, Yeong Won, Choong Nam...
and even Ssang Boon knows him.
We met in primary school.
Are you her youngest?
Yes.
I should get going.
I'll see you at mass.
I'll go and get changed.
If you're hungry, eat the pastry he brought.
Hey, you.
I'll see you around.
You're nice and tall.
Let's go.
Leave it!
Yes, it was great.
How great?
Very.
Did you have to say that to me?
I said that on purpose.
Isn't this better than having regrets?
Why did you call?
I heard about Jeong A's plans.
I think it's wrong.
She sold her house without his knowing.
It was in her name. Seok Gyun has his own.
Are there legal issues?
No, there shouldn't be any legal issues.
If Seok Gyun and Jeong A get into a legal dispute,
I'll hire you for Jeong A's attorney.
How much will it cost?
Are you kidding me?
If there's an issue between a married couple,
they should sort it out by talking to each other.
Doing that won't solve the problem. It'll only cause chaos.
Just sit back and watch.
Seok Gyun will cry.
Then you can wipe his tears for him.
We'll all be gone soon.
Think about Seok Gyun. He's an old guy.
You really care for him, don't you?
You should just live with him then.
It will look disgusting.
Hey,
those jerks just drank 300 dollars' worth of drinks.
Artists don't have money.
Just give them what they want.
Please...
You should be nicer to my friends.
They're not your friends. They're only using you.
You're such a pushover.
Don't be so rude.
Am I having diarrhoea?
Come here.
Come on.
This looks comfortable. Let's do this one.
We'll take two pillows as well.
Sure.
- Why are you being like that?
- What?
That man is just a friend.
A friend and nothing else.
I didn't say anything.
Give us the pillows and the duvet.
Stay as friends, okay?
Don't see him too often either.
I won't. I don't see him often.
Here?
Jeong A.
What is it?
Why are you there?
Do you live here?
Are you crazy?
Are you sure this is the place?
No... No...
I remember now! I got it now, don't worry.
Mum, you have to come to your senses.
Are you sure it's in this neighbourhood?
Min Ho, I'm not sure.
It's not this way. We went up there... Then...
It's okay, it could happen.
I'll call Jeong A.
Don't panic. It's okay.
I love you, Mum.
Where was it?
We went that way...
Jeong A, it's Min Ho.
Yes. Mum got lost.
Do you want to go to the park?
Let's stay in.
We stayed in for 52 hours.
There's nothing to order in.
We finished all the sundae, japchae...
and dumplings from Korea.
I love your bed.
It makes me fall asleep.
Let's go out.
Let's stay in.
Aren't you going back to Seoul?
I am.
That's why we should stay here.
Then let's clean up a little.
Okay, then. Let's not clean up and go out.
Out?
What about your clothes?
Just like this?
Don't think about anything else. I'm right here.
Yes. You're here.
What time is your flight?
I don't know. I forgot.
Also, I'm here with you.
Yes, and bare-naked.
I'll bring your phone.
I'll bring more tea, too.
Yes, Yeon Hee.
I'm glad you had a good time.
But...
I'm sure Wan...
just came.
I know.
You know what I mean by that, right?
She has a mother and she's the only child.
She'll go back again.
I know.
She'll leave again just like before.
Don't expect anything, okay?
I won't.
When are you leaving?
Tonight.
I think I have seven hours left.
Then...
Let's walk.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Be healthy.
- To health.
To everyone's health.
That's right, I helped her out then.
Soo Young, bring more alcohol.
- Coming.
You're in such a good mood.
More japchae, too!
Coming!
- Have some.
- Mum!
Where's Mum?
Is she sleeping in the bathroom?
She stayed up all night making food.
Let's leave her to get a break.
Jeong A!
What?
Don't drink so much.
Are you going to get drunk again?
All right, cheers.
Gosh.
My mother is almost disabled.
What are you doing here if you're not pooping?
Don't just drink, eat some food.
- I'm taking a break.
- Where are the hwatu cards?
Underneath the television.
Just go and find them for me.
What is that?
My clothes.
What are all these? Is she throwing them out?
All right. Let's clear the tables and play some hwatu.
- Okay.
- It's 20 cents per point.
Gwang Soo, stop drinking by yourself.
I decided to see Dong Jin.
I sent him a text before coming here.
Apparently, he's moving to the United states.
It's not because of me.
His wife is feeling lonely. It worked out.
Right.
What do you think about the book I'll write about the old mules?
Do you think it'll be interesting?
Will it be too dreary?
Old people can be funny.
I didn't want to write about them at first,
but I thought it wouldn't be a bad idea to write about Mum.
That's what all writers wish for.
Her friends have a lot of stories of their own.
I finished a draft in my head.
I need to interview more.
I'm thinking of publishing it as a book.
Let's have some tea.
I'm amazed.
At what?
The tea or...
my wheelchair skills?
Both.
It's level ground.
I'm translating a book,
and writing a novel...
about my mum and her friends.
If I work 10 hours a day,
it'll take me 3 to 4 months.
It'll take 5 to 6 months at the most.
After that, I can pack up...
Don't make any promises.
Just leave.
I'll just think...
that you came back because you missed Slovenia.
I came back not for you but for Slovenia?
You're impulsive.
And you like me.
So you flew over.
But make this the last time.
Then will you...
stay here waiting for me?
I'll just be here.
No waiting involved.
I work here...
and the scenery's great.
If I meet someone, I can date her.
It didn't work out with Nikita.
I have to come back.
Right now,
I look at my legs...
and I think it's just a discomfort.
But if you say you'll come back and you don't,
I might really hate my legs.
I'll blame them...
for pushing you away.
I'm stuck with these legs forever.
Be more considerate.
Shut up.
Watch your tongue.
Hey.
Am I here because I'm impulsive?
After three long years, I took two planes, a taxi and a bus.
It took me 18 hours.
Wan.
We might break up over something else,
but it won't be your legs.
You work and can move around.
I'm strong and have no problem looking after you.
I'm tall enough to reach the top shelves, too.
Do you think you have the upper hand because I love you?
I said I'll come back. You just...
You still love me...
despite my disability.
So should I just say,
"thank you"?
You left when you wanted and then you came back.
Then you'll leave.
You should.
You should thank me.
What if I can't?
Listen carefully.
I will come back to you whatever my mum says.
I decided to do so when I came here.
And I...
I don't want to see you through the screen of a laptop or phone.
When I come back,
you'd better live much harder than you do now.
You need to increase your upper body strength...
and exercise your legs much more than...
I do enough!
You have to do more if you're to live with me.
My uncle walked again after being bedridden for seven years.
He drags one leg but he walks.
You have to do the same if you're to live with me.
I will...
never walk again.
Make it work.
You can't only do what you can.
Do what you can't.
My mum was adamant I don't marry a disabled man.
She says I'm all she has.
Give me a reason to justify myself for choosing you over her.
Help me say that...
you're stronger than anyone and that you never give up.
Help me do this.
I'll return when I'm done.
After I give her the book.
It's my mum's wish.
If you don't return,
I will kill you.
Such nice timing.
Go.
See you again.
Make him exercise his legs.
There should be plenty of rehabilitation clinics.
What about your mum?
Sorry about using her as an excuse.
I will come back.
Okay.
We'll wait.
By the time I come back, you'd better be married and gone.
What's wrong with me?
This is bad.
It's an emergency.
Choong Nam.
You're still young.
Don't panic...
like you did last time.
I love you
There is only you
I scream your name
But the sunset answers me back
Yeong Won is in a shoot right now.
Where's the tangsuyuk?
- It's coming.
- Yes.
- Here.
- Where's the tangsuyuk?
Coming.
- Here's hot water.
- Here you go.
That looks great.
Enjoy.
(Choong Nam)
The number you're calling...
Hee Ja is too old.
Jeong A has the memorial service today.
Even if it's an emergency,
I shouldn't call someone too old.
Professor Park, it's me.
- Where are you?
- You should call 911.
Yes. Where does it hurt?
What should I do? My kids are coming back to Korea,
so I have to go to the airport.
I'm sorry.
You should call 911 right away.
Why are you so late?
It's Choong Nam.
Don't pick it up. She's sick.
I should talk to her if she's sick.
Her voice sounds fine. She's okay.
Also, she has her nephews. Don't worry.
Anyway, is everyone here?
Yes, they were here for a while. Come on.
Sir!
Professor Park.
First,
I should get dressed...
then call 911.
I should call 911.
I can do it.
Don't lose it.
It'd be okay to go like this.
But if I don't go, I'll become disabled.
(Ssang Boon)
What happened? She called me, too.
I called her back, but she didn't pick up.
- You too?
- There must be an emergency.
I have to go.
Yes, Mum.
How can you go there with your tractor?
I was going to go,
but my leg...
All right. I got it.
I'm leaving now.
Gosh.
I can't go because of the group reservation.
You should go at least.
What if the old woman dies alone?
Are you going to be responsible?
Why is it always about life or death for you?
That's how it is with us old people.
Are you going to go or not?
Fine, I'll go.
Right now!
What's going on?
Why did you come out?
Because I'm a woman.
They won't let us stay in since we're women.
- Then...
- why do they eat...
- the food that we make?
What's with the bag?
I'm going to leave your father.
That's a good idea.
Are you going to throw him away?
Good idea.
Yes, you should throw things away in your life for a change.
I found myself a place. I'll live alone. Come visit me.
- Okay.
- Sure.
When can we go home?
Once they finish the food,
our uncles and the elders...
are going to ask me why I got a divorce.
If they ask you, just tell them you never got a divorce.
They probably won't remember.
Should I try that?
Yes.
- I will.
- Be good to your father.
He's your husband, so you should be good to him.
I agree.
Yes, Honey.
No, I don't know when I'll be home.
Is Ddollae sleeping?
Put him to sleep for once, will you?
Jeong A, underwear.
Jeong A!
Are you sleeping?
Jeong A.
Jeong A!
Water!
Give me water.
Water.
Gentle Jeong A finally left Seok Gyun alone...
after 50 years of marriage. She really left him.
Jeong A!
Hi.
It was your appendix. The surgery went well.
You should've called me.
I'm glad she didn't.
All your friends are here over one little appendix.
What a nuisance.
Ssang Boon was so smart.
I know that. I'm pretty smart.
You called me but didn't pick up when I called back.
So I called 911 and came straight over here.
I saved your life. Make it up to me.
Here.
We're having a great time without you, Professor Lee.
He sent it to you by mistake.
Get some sleep.
Choong Nam.
Are you feeling better now?
Are you awake?
You're awake.
I had you sent over here so you wouldn't feel lonely.
Aren't you pleased?
When it counted the most,
Choong Nam, who preferred younger people,
was surrounded by her old friends and even older relatives.
That quiet morning was when her will to get her revenge...
slowly rose to the surface.
Those fools.
I'll kill you all.
(Dear My Friends)
Jeong A. Jeong A!
This is how you get revenge.
Whack him in the back of the head.
We can't travel the world, but we can go to China or Japan.
Open your eyes and read this.
Open your eyes!
Everything you're saying is crazy!
- Life is crazy.
I'll make them pay.
Didn't I make that?
It's fine, leave it. Throw it away.
All you care about is money and fame.
You're the worst kind.
Are you two dating?
To ask what?
If you and I will get along.
Are you a playboy?