Jeong A!
Give me breakfast.
That's a lot of soup.
The rice is ready.
The setting is now on warm.
Why did she make so much?
Does she want me to die from overeating?
Jeong A!
(Sharpening the Blade of Revenge, Part 2)
Amazing.
That's so amazing.
Jeong A is so cool, right?
That's good. That's the way to take revenge.
She totally stabbed Seok Gyun in the back.
Isn't Jeong A so amazing?
What's so amazing about it?
She's against it and I'm for it.
And you, Mum?
What's the point at her age?
Here, Mum. Have some of this.
Grandma, what do you think about Jeong A and Seok Gyun's divorce?
It's not my business.
Get your phone.
Okay.
My goodness, it's him.
Why is he calling you at this hour?
Has he ever called you in the morning like this?
Maybe 30 years ago?
How can you remember that?
Forget things like that. It's tiring.
Hey.
Did...
Jeong A run away already?
No way, not this early.
We should never doubt.
- Is she not picking up?
- Is she not?
Jeong A left home.
She really did.
I'll take a taxi, don't worry.
Wait.
Gosh.
- Take care of yourself.
- I'll interview you this weekend.
- Okay.
- Call me when you pass...
- Gosh!
- Good job!
Mum.
I'm leaving.
Okay.
I'm interviewing you this weekend.
Mum, do you want a daughter like her?
I like you too, you shrew.
Why do you always talk so badly about your daughter?
What about you?
You called me something worse.
Forget about it.
No, I don't know where she is.
Seok Gyun's going to come here.
I'm at a shoot.
She must have ran away in the morning. My goodness.
What is it? Did Jeong A go somewhere?
I really don't know.
Why are you asking me about your wife?
Yelling won't help.
What do you think? I'm working at the restaurant.
Just tell him. I want to see how he reacts.
It's almost lunchtime. I have a customer.
Bye.
Don't get it. Don't pick it up.
What is it?
Choong Nam, just tell him.
She's not home?
It's obvious. She ran away from home.
Choong Nam!
She's done with you.
She's taking her revenge.
She must be fine now if she has the energy to talk.
Mum, I'm going to work.
You're done for.
How does it feel?
How does it feel to be left alone?
Hey! Did you lose your mind after living alone?
Why would my wife leave home?
You should get married instead of talking nonsense.
It was just one memorial service.
She must have gone around town complaining about the work.
What a whiner.
If she doesn't want to cook, she shouldn't have been a woman.
Anyway, I was a good son...
to my parents last night.
Soo Young?
Did your mum come to your place to clean?
Let me talk to her if she's there.
He didn't believe you?
No. He only screamed more.
(Professor Park)
I'll kill you all.
Who? The professors that left you out yesterday?
I'll take my revenge.
Mum, go home.
Wan, you should go, too.
My nephews are coming.
Choong Nam, that's wrong.
Just don't see them any more.
Don't bother taking revenge.
You'd have to see them again to take a revenge.
You're too nice. They'll be able to fool you again.
Listen to me. Okay?
Be quiet.
Grandma.
Your uncle...
will get married in two months.
I heard. Her name is Jacqueline, right?
What if she doesn't...
like us two old people?
Grandpa doesn't talk, so what's there to hate?
Also, you're a charming lady.
You can make her like you.
How?
Give her money.
By getting a loan?
Whatever you can afford.
The debt will go to them afterwards. You shouldn't get a loan.
Do we eat with them while giving her the money?
Wire the money to her.
Decline if she asks you to go out and eat.
If she asks you again, decline again.
She's only saying that.
Should we not even show our faces to her?
- What about talking?
- Don't talk.
Unless they ask you something first.
I shouldn't say anything?
If you can help it.
Should I just keep my mouth shut?
Yes, if you can.
Should I just die instead?
You little...
Grandma, I didn't mean...
What does that have to do with dying?
I was just talking about kids these days.
"Kids these days"?
Then what about you? What about you?
What I'm saying is, the adults should...
You're a mean wench!
Jacques will hate you.
Be understanding.
Be understanding
I have to write about them
Let's be understanding
I'm digging my own grave, aren't I?
Yes, Soo Young.
Hee Ja, where's my mum?
She's not home.
She ran away from your dad and left home.
Hold on.
Seok Gyun is going crazy and this is Soo Young.
What? Tell her I'll call back.
Hee Ja.
What do you mean she ran away from home?
Here's your pillow.
My goodness.
Sleep tight.
(Ho Young)
- I'm sorry.
How much?
I'm really sorry.
I didn't know you'd be sick.
We really won't go to karaoke any more.
You can go.
But you have to pick up your phone.
An old person can get sick at any moment.
I won't give you the cafe. Get lost.
Don't.
- Aunt...
- Let go.
You jerks.
I'll kill you all.
Seok Gyun.
Will you lay out the spoons and chopsticks?
Me?
Okay.
Get your rice.
How does this work?
Oh, I got it.
Do you eat red rice?
We do, too.
Eat a lot of it. It's good for you.
Seok Gyun.
Go and beg for forgiveness.
Ask her to come home.
What for?
She'll be back in three days.
She'll come back by the time I finish all the soup and rice.
Choong Nam is right.
If she really did want to leave me,
why would she have cooked me food?
It's because that's what she's like.
- What?
- She's a good person.
It's your last feast.
"Eat the rice and soup,"
"and stay away for the rest of my life."
That's what she means.
She's that sweet.
Where are the divorce papers then?
Aren't I right? I got you there.
My wife will never,
ever divorce me.
We were married for half a century.
You may think that...
I'm a jerk, but I'm not.
I'm a great husband. I support us...
and never had an affair.
You did.
Jeong A...
rented a house.
That's for show.
She wanted me to take her around the world,
so this is her complaining.
Think about it.
Humans now...
can live for 100 years.
Let's say we blow our savings on a round-the-world trip.
What will we do for the rest of our lives?
Should we become a homeless couple at our age?
You're a lawyer...
and your parents were rich.
Do you have 10 million dollars?
You act like it's an easy sum to come by.
My parents spent all their savings...
on their medical bills before they died.
I'm no fraud. I'm a lawyer.
No one can earn that much...
working an average job.
You're useless then.
I'd have earned that much...
if I'd gone to college.
I bet I could've earned 20 million, even.
You're a good cook.
You're better than Jeong A.
Shall I move in?
Are you impressed?
No, no. Wash your hands now.
Wash your hands.
It's fine.
What?
Smell them.
Let's drink.
You have liquor.
You can unearth some new talents there.
The staff here are quite capable.
Was Yeon Ha...
pleased to see you?
I thought he would be.
- But he played hard to get.
- What?
He said he's fine.
His life is perfect,
so he doesn't care.
He's always so cool.
And your mum?
She'll be fine.
It'll be hard on her, but she'll manage...
if you're happy.
What?
Did she punch you...
into realising what she's capable of?
She's incredibly strong.
I almost...
I'm sorry about what she did to you. I apologise.
Make it up to me.
One apology isn't enough.
I'll make it up to you with the sales of my book.
Go on, then.
Let's have a farewell drink.
This is just... It's not a proper goodbye.
My wife's on the way.
Let's keep our farewell...
a little bit awkward.
It's imperfect, just like our first meeting.
That suits us.
You're right.
Anything more is too much. Right?
This is just right.
Be happy.
Why would you get a divorce if nothing's wrong?
Mum, if something's wrong, talk it out with him.
What are you even doing here?
This is no time to wipe the floor!
Dad can't cook or clean.
Yeong Won.
Hee Ja.
Talk some sense into my mum. Please?
You aren't in the right.
Stop it.
Don't say what you can't take back.
Soo Young, you're just about to go too far.
She's just as responsible.
She's the reason our dad is like this.
Tell them what we told you...
before we got married.
We told you to keep Dad in line.
But you cursed us out for being ungrateful brats.
Why do this now when you're responsible?
Mum.
What should I tell my husband?
What should I tell my in-laws?
What's wrong with all the women...
in my family?
All three of you are divorced!
It's such an embarrassment!
Will you wash rags forever?
Say something.
Your girls might lose their voices.
Mum!
Thanks.
I'm glad you didn't say anything earlier.
If you did,
it would've only made things worse.
This is when I feel lucky.
I have no parents,
no husband and no kids.
That's why...
I envy you and Choong Nam a lot.
But I have cancer instead.
That's why we feel sorry for you, too.
I think Choong Nam has the best life.
She has at least 15 relatives...
who leech off of her, remember?
Didn't you see them?
I forgot about that.
Life is tough for everyone, isn't it?
Are you done with chemo?
For now.
Good.
Squash pancakes taste quite good.
Wait here. I have some cabbages.
She's smarter than the rest of us.
She's really scary.
Don't tell her that I said that.
You said that to her yourself.
Why do I sometimes do that?
You do it often, not just sometimes.
Oh dear.
A tangsuyuk on table seven.
One tangsuyuk.
Okay.
Hello, this is Nan Hee's phone.
(Seok Gyun)
Hello, Seok Gyun. It's Wan.
You're the useless brat who writes novels and smokes.
Why did you call?
Tell your mum to come and cook for me.
Mum.
It's Seok Gyun. He wants you to cook.
Say I'll be there after work.
What for?
I have to, at least once.
You are mine.
You can't go even once.
Seok Gyun.
Call Soo Young or Ho Young.
They're busy.
Then you should come over.
Why should I?
You brat.
I've known you for over 40 years.
Can't you come over and cook for me just once?
Your mum and I go back 60 years!
I'm a bit busy right now. I have to hang up.
Hey!
You scumbag.
Choong Nam?
Come and cook for me.
I just got surgery.
Do you want me to kill you?
Hello, dear Professor Park.
I'm fine.
Right now?
Well, I'm not in the mood to see you.
How about next week?
I have a huge gift for you guys.
Yes. It's a huge one.
Okay.
Ouch, ouch.
It's okay.
Ddollae, what's that?
Red rice.
Why are you being cranky?
I'm leaving.
- Aren't you eating?
- I have to meet a client.
- Bye.
Dad.
Dad, go and beg Mum.
Please? If you can't go on the world tour,
at least go on an Asian tour. Even a trip in the country will do.
Ho Young and I'll give you the money.
We'll get a loan if we have to.
If you have so much money, give it to me.
Dad! Please!
Why would I beg?
I'm over 70 and still working. Why should I beg?
You were always nagging at her for eating.
You treated her like a slave. You don't even get your own water.
Should a man get water? Should a man cook?
It'll be a month at the longest. Leave it.
What if that month turns into a year?
Make kalguksu for dinner tomorrow.
Do you want me to get a divorce, too?
What about my husband? What will he eat?
Kalguksu for tomorrow.
Give me my rice.
Seriously...
Hey, Hee Ja!
Hey! Where are you going?
I don't know you.
It's me.
It's Mark, the photographer. Remember the pictures?
I wanted to... I wanted to tell you...
that I'm leaving. I have to go. I wanted to say goodbye.
I don't know you.
Jeong A!
It's open.
Why are you here? Aren't you sick?
This is Choong Nam's last sign of friendship.
It's your favourite. Gejang.
You're nice for a change.
I take that back.
It's been five days since Jeong A left. What's all this?
You didn't do any dishes?
That's from the last two days.
The kids are busy.
If you don't want to do the dishes, don't eat.
- What?
- Don't stuff yourself.
Did you go deaf?
I can't hear things that don't make sense.
My goodness.
Read this later.
What is it?
You'll see.
(How to Be a Good Husband)
Hurry up.
Don't rush me.
We're both getting old. You're not that much older.
Don't tell me what to do. It's annoying.
Sorry.
You must be annoyed because of me.
Then tell Jeong A to come back.
Otherwise, you'll have to pick up after me.
I'll call you every day. I'll call you 12 times a day.
- Seok Gyun.
- What?
Do you think I'll come back again to do your dishes?
Do you think I'd come here in between my shoots?
Don't you dare.
Mark my words.
It'll be just once. Today and today only.
I'll call you again.
We'll mark you as spam.
What? Spam?
This is wrong.
If it's uncomfortable, you should go and beg her. This is wrong.
What's wrong?
You got her to do it, didn't you?
You told an innocent, old lady to get a divorce!
What is it? Female rights?
I did.
Hey, I'll wait outside.
Yesterday, my appendix exploded. But today, my head will explode.
Hey, Choong Nam!
She found the house and you lent her the money, right?
Sure.
I tried to stop her. I told her not to do it.
I told her to keep serving you until the end...
since that's what she's done all her life.
Are you on my side then?
But I change my mind.
I was too cruel to her.
If you're being like this to me, she must have had it worse.
She should live the way she wants for whatever she has left.
I'm glad this happened.
Also, if you need someone to do your housework,
call your siblings.
Call the ones you gave away all your money to...
and tell them to work for you.
They're all men.
I'm a woman! So what?
Be quiet.
If you're loud, I'll leave.
I won't do the dishes.
Let me tell you this.
Going to the same elementary school...
doesn't mean we have legal ties, okay?
We are legal strangers.
I'm going to get her. She called.
She told me to come over.
It's her final farewell, you idiot.
Clean the room and the basin!
You shouldn't be doing any housework.
I'm repaying the debt for when he beat up...
the kids who bullied me in school.
I hate myself for remembering all that.
Yeong Won. Right.
Help me get revenge.
Who's the target?
The professors who left me out.
Let's do it. We're in a foul mood, so let's do something about it.
Do you have a plan?
I'm thinking of one.
Where are you?
I passed the green gate. Where do you live?
Look up.
I cared for my parents.
What's wrong about that?
What's so wrong about me giving money to my siblings?
Tell me. Go on.
Nothing's wrong.
Just divorce me. Why move out?
What? Are you too scared to get divorced?
If this is what you want, let's get a divorce.
I signed the divorce papers. Sign it and hand it in.
Fine.
Let's get divorced.
But this house is mine.
It's in your name, but it's mine.
Do you want a lawsuit?
Are you scared?
Okay.
Let's go to court.
What did I do that's so wrong?
My parents told me to look after my siblings...
because it's my duty as the eldest.
All I did was obey their last words.
Is it terribly wrong for a son to do as he was told?
When my parents scorned you for not having a son,
I left home instead of siding with them!
I abandoned them like an old shoe for your sake!
You did not abandon them. You moved next door...
and I had to go over at dawn to cook and clean for them.
They pulled out my hair whenever they had the chance.
Honey. You did not abandon them.
Get your facts straight. You just moved out.
Don't call me honey if you want a divorce.
You're right. What should I call you then?
Should I call you by your name like Hee Ja does?
See you in court.
It's a long walk down. Take care.
What did I do that's so wrong?
Not take you around the world?
Is it so wrong that I want to save money?
Don't make me repeat myself. You did nothing wrong.
My whole life, parents were my first priority...
and my siblings came second. Is that so wrong?
If your siblings come after your parents,
then go live with them.
Before my mum died, she told me to live a comfortable life.
That's why I moved out.
I could barely handle my own life, so I sent her to a care home.
And I ended up taking her to the beach where she died.
But I will obey my mum's dying wish.
I can be just a good a child, too!
You weren't that great a wife!
I will do it.
Stay in your seat.
You're good at this.
My wife taught me well.
She was very strict...
for the last three years of her life.
She did that so you could survive on your own without her.
That's all done.
Now, I need some vinegar.
Okay.
Who made this mess?
Use salt instead.
- Salt?
- Salt.
Yes. That will work, too.
(Secret Garden)
Didn't I do well?
It's lovely.
Good for you.
It's a great way to kill time.
Yes. That's a problem for people our age.
Oh, gosh. You did so very well.
I did more.
You're having fun.
How did you get in?
I walked in. I'm too old to scale the wall.
Where's Yeong Won?
Parking the car.
I'll bring some tea.
Okay.
I meant to visit you,
but I couldn't because I crashed the car. Sorry.
It's fine. Be nice to her instead.
I'll kill you if you aren't.
What's wrong? Does your shoulder hurt?
Yes. I guess I clung to the walking frame too hard.
Let me massage your shoulders.
I'll borrow him for a bit.
Keep him.
Can I keep you?
How does it feel?
It hurts. Don't be so rough.
Is that you, Gi Ja?
Why are you writing about me?
It's for a novel.
I'm busy, so listen to my story first.
Let the eldest go first.
- We're all busy people, come on.
- She's right.
Will you all be quiet?
Wan's too confused to write.
Why would she be confused? She understands us just fine.
What will you write? I have to know.
- What's wrong?
- What is it?
Wan, I'm very busy.
Let me go first.
The more you interrupt, the longer she needs. Let her talk.
Hey. I mean, ladies.
I'm interviewing you to write a book.
I won't be writing about your sad lives.
It's just a novel.
- The concept is...
- What's a concept?
- What's that?
- It doesn't matter.
Why would she mention it then?
- Go on.
- Talk.
We're listening.
My book will target the younger generations.
Will it not be about us, then?
Young people aren't interested in old people...
whining about...
how tough their lives were or how sad they felt.
We get it. They don't care.
You want us to answer your questions and not add anything else...
because there's no time for that, right?
Bingo.
But don't you want to know about your mum's love life?
She's wouldn't know. She's not a mum.
What? I'm a virgin.
Let the childless be silent.
So you are saying that you came up with...
a theme or keyword for each of us.
I'm the actress who is the symbol of love.
I'm the friendly mum. I like that.
Don't forget to mention our fights.
Don't be hesitant to write in detail.
- You even threw a vase.
- A vase?
In front of her mum?
I'll mention that you pulled my hair out.
Can you add some romance for my character?
Or how about we just go all out and mention intercourse?
Do you want to discuss that with your daughter?
Why not?
I don't want to be the nice and generous mum.
That means I have to be generous until I die.
Wan, I don't want to represent the mum who sacrifices.
Write something else.
Don't mention my daughters' divorce or abuse, either.
Focus on me.
Jeong A.
What's there to write about you if not about your daughters?
You just have to write what I tell you.
Don't make anything up. Write whatever I say.
If I don't like even one syllable, scratch it out.
- Start with my crazy aunt...
- Come on, not again.
- She's at it again.
- Not again.
Because of her, my mum lost her mind and then died.
Then there's my brother whom I don't even remember.
During the Korean War, my mother fled while dragging my father...
who was shot in the heart. It's such a heartbreaking...
It sounds like...
it was during the Third Battle of Seoul.
That was during spring.
Cherry blossoms were in full bloom along the streets...
How is the Third Battle of Seoul in spring? It was winter.
- That's true.
- Don't lie.
I'm not lying!
That's what my mum said. She saw cherry blossoms.
- No way.
- It wasn't that battle then.
- Wan, where are you going?
- Hey!
What is it?
What's wrong with her?
- It's because of you.
- It's your fault.
Why are you all blaming me?
- Gosh.
- Go follow her.
My goodness.
Gosh.
Goodness. Can't you talk more softly?
Why are you all so loud?
What are you doing making us wait? Come back out.
Wait outside.
Give me five seconds.
I feel nauseous.
What a temper. Gosh.
Wan is upset.
If you want the book to be made, you have to listen to her.
Wan has a bit of a bad personality.
"A bit"? She's pretty mean.
She takes it after me.
- Gosh.
- Take her side.
- What?
- You won't write?
You won't write it?
No.
That doesn't make sense. Why did you bring us here?
She's right.
Hey, what's wrong?
If it doesn't make sense that I'm not writing,
does anything you say make sense?
You want me to record your 24 hours?
What good will that do?
Do you want your kids to know how bored you are?
I'm trying to package you to sound more beautiful.
It would be good. The book would sell.
It would be good for your kids to read it, too.
For 365 days a year,
the mother thinks of her kids.
However, she doesn't call them...
in order to be considerate.
Even so, she's still happy.
No.
That's a lie.
I'm disgusted by my kids.
If you're not going to write about me being lonely...
for 24 hours a day,
take me out of it.
- Hee Ja.
- What I do all day...
I...
- I...
- She was so bored...
that she made 100 rosaries...
in 3 or 4 days.
Make sure her kids find out.
If you don't, I'll kill you.
I'm small, but I raised four men including my husband.
They wore me out when they needed me.
Now that I'm old, they trapped me in here.
They didn't trap you in here.
You told them you didn't want to live with them.
Wan isn't trying to write about a mum taking revenge on her kids.
She's trying to write a beautiful story...
about sacrificing mothers and their lives.
Life is not beautiful!
Life is a war between kids and parents!
It's a war between the young and old.
I agree.
Yes, it's war.
Is this "Love and War"?
So in my opinion,
old people like us should just live together.
We made that promise 50 years ago.
We said we would live together some day.
50 years ago?
Everything is 40 to 50 years ago.
- I'd like that.
- All of us?
- I don't want to.
- When?
When should we start?
If you start on a topic,
I want you to finish it before going to another one.
Going back, I lost my dad during the Third Battle of Seoul.
My mum brought 10 of us...
It's three.
Including our cousins, there were 10 of us.
Whenever I hear that story,
it breaks my heart.
"Mum, I'm so sorry!"
I came here to tell you this.
My poor mother!
- I came here although I'm busy.
- Listen carefully.
That's because I wanted...
to tell my mother's story, not mine.
I came here with a fluttering heart.
Hold on. Did I tell you about my horrible mother-in-law?
Mum, did I tell you?
I died because of you.
I was playing a game.
All right. If I might add,
the kids I worked so hard to raise...
are sending me their kids to look after them.
My life is so sad.
I want my kids to feel bad when they read it.
Make the book break their hearts.
By the way,
my mother-in-law would snatch my bowl when I ate...
to throw to the stray dogs.
Make sure you include this.
That's a soap opera. It's ridiculous.
All your stories are for a soap opera!
- Life is a soap opera.
Of course.
"When I turned around after letting go of my mother,"
"the owl cried and so did I."
"At the mountain's peak, dead leaves rolled..."
"in a gust."
I want the elderly characters in my book to be beautiful.
The kids will read it and be happy.
Wouldn't that be better?
Why do I have to talk about all these stories?
It's all about your misfortunes.
It's a cruel fairy tale.
It's sad and miserable.
It hurts to hear just a minute of it.
You can't bear it. It's not fun to read at all!
Because that's the truth.
That is the reality of our lives.
That's reality.
This is why you haven't been able to write until now.
Soap operas are the best.
Why doesn't it make sense for me to run away from home...
because I wanted to drink beer?
I think it'll make a good story.
I want the novel to be beautiful...
Revenges are lousy.
What revenge?
I only came out to live freely.
I don't intend on taking revenge.
Really, Wan.
Mum, why don't you tell her about your husband?
You should make it into a revenge story.
I should.
I don't care if it's lousy. It's about revenge for me.
Fine! I'm lousy.
Are you better than me?
- Are you?
- Gi Ja, come here.
- Come with me.
- I am Gi Ja the Lousy!
That's my life!
- Come on.
- So what? What?
Grandma. Mum.
Everyone.
Something popped up...
and I need to write it down before I forget it.
You did great today.
- Good, good, good.
- Hey. We just started.
- I'm leaving.
- Where are you going?
- Good job, all.
- We just started. Are you leaving?
Where are you going?
She left because of you.
Me? Really?
You should reflect on it.
What should I do?
Yes, Hye Min. Where are you?
You're at the office?
Okay. I'll come over right now.
Life is a war between kids and parents!
It's a war between the young and old.
This is amazing.
Listen carefully.
My mother-in-law would snatch my bowl...
Isn't it pretty good?
Instead of the sad and beautiful...
story about the elderly you were planning...
It is a horribly, cruel fairy tale...
from the elderly to the young.
We'll start with how Gi Ja's mother-in-law liked pig heads...
and also how she threw Gi Ja's food to the dogs.
Then there's Jeong A who made all that food then ran away.
The bullying professors.
Then comes Grandma Sook Hyun and her cruel revenge.
She's Choong Nam's mother.
Is it really in the ten thousands?
I think so.
My grandma is pretty bad, too.
Is she really keeping this up just to take revenge on her husband?
Yes.
Don't we need at least a page of romance?
We have it. We have just that.
The lawyer Seong Jae and the odd Hee Ja.
No. Yeong Won is better suited for romance.
Oh, you mean the actress?
She's the actress, right?
- This is amazing.
- It's so good.
I told you it's amazing.
It's so cool.
Hey.
Come on, dance with him once.
He's been doing this for three days.
Be generous, please?
- Come on.
- I don't want to.
Goodness. You're going to be blessed.
Here.
Hello?
Rice?
It's in the cooker.
Money?
I don't have any!
Ma'am, what do you think...
I decided to write the stories of the elders...
as they are without sugar-coating them.
If this tiring...
and lousy life...
is really what life is like,
then there's nothing I can do.
I decided to only write what's true.
They're the protagonists of their lives.
So they have the right to choose.
Oh dear.
It's so hot.
Wan. Are you asleep?
What do you mean?
I made up my mind.
Can't you still change it?
I make rosaries every evening and I'm afraid that will...
upset the kids and make them worry.
Can't you say I'm doing it...
for the community and not out of loneliness?
I'm a mother...
so I shouldn't do anything to cause them concern.
Hee Ja.
Your life is already all about caring for others.
You did enough. They have to know...
about your long, lonely nights.
Hang up and go to bed.
Be strong.
What is it?
What I said earlier today?
I didn't move out to get revenge.
You said that's what it looks like.
I'm having some dark beer and now I feel...
all sad and bitter.
I want to leave my girls out because it'll cause pain...
for them, not for me.
Why else would I move out...
if it's not for revenge?
It really isn't about getting revenge at all.
It's just...
I just want to be able to have a beer whenever I want to.
I'm sorry.
You didn't move out to get revenge.
You slaved away for your in-laws, husband and daughters.
And you moved out to enjoy a beer. It's not about revenge at all.
I was too harsh when we talked today.
I'm too young.
She's right.
Revenge isn't part of her life.
She lived for her in-laws, husband and daughters.
And now, she finally got to enjoy a beer.
How could that be revenge?
It's the furthest thing from it.
Thank you very much.
Choong Nam, isn't this one of my works?
It's perfect as a fruit bowl.
Let's see how good a fruit salad...
in a 2,000-dollar bowl tastes like.
Sorry. This one cost 300 dollars.
Don't worry, it's fine. Throw the pieces away.
Over there is another one that costs 3,000 dollars.
It's the white one. Use that instead.
But...
That piece meant a lot to me.
Aunt.
These are Professor Yang's. You wished you could afford one.
I'm selling them at half price today.
Are you interested?
How could you...
even think of...
selling them at such a cheap price?
Choong Nam, I put my soul into my work.
How could you use it as a fruit bowl?
And I don't have cash. I only have a credit card.
You can pay me over 12 months. Do you want them?
Goodness.
How about 40 months then?
I can't believe you'd do this to us.
It's no joke.
You have great taste.
The artworks that you asked me to sell for you...
Some are worth 5,000 dollars and some even double that.
I guess you're destined to make a fortune.
I have neither a husband nor kids. I might as well have money.
Don't sell them. I just wanted to know their values.
What do you mean? Sell them all!
I just sent you the really nice ones.
Of course, they're worth more than what I paid for.
I'm Choong Nam.
They're the ignorant fools for not knowing how good they are.
They sold their masterpieces for a bargain price.
So what if they're professors?
Their brains and eyes are just for show.
This cafe's mine.
Okay.
Enjoy.
Isn't the weather lovely?
Why not...
get revenge?
If it would make their sad 60 or 70-year life...
worth living for even for a moment,
and if that were to make up for all the hardships they put up with...
If it comforts them,
then doesn't that make it all worthwhile?
They will die soon.
Their time is coming.
If we were to tell them...
to live their lives as they did so far,
wouldn't that be too cruel?
You forgot to write "I deserve to die."
Go on.
I'll have this carved on my tombstone.
So write it nicely and clearly.
(I am sorry.)
(I deserve to die.)
Mum.
What's wrong?
Mum?
Yeong Won.
Good evening.
What are you doing here?
Have a seat.
Did he send you those flowers?
- Yes.
- Meet up with him.
You missed him. You should see him then.
What if I'm disappointed?
If you are, then call it quits.
What does that make of my life?
A life full of disappointments?
My second marriage...
was actually just me trying to get over him.
But it didn't work.
Is that why when you left him,
you said it wasn't his fault?
Because you weren't over Dae Cheol.
If he hadn't gone back to his wife who drugged herself...
because he married me, we'd still be together.
I'm afraid I'll be disappointed in what he's become.
But then again, I also miss him terribly.
I'm so old now.
I'm not as pretty either.
Wan.
Isn't it boring listening to an old lady talk about love?
I think you're just beautiful.
Should I go see him?
Yes. I'm all for it.
Yeong Won.
I'm seeing Yeon Ha again.
I went to go see him last week.
I'm going to go. I have a night shoot.
Okay. When I finish writing the book,
I'm going back to Slovenia even if Mum disagrees.
Call me.
Okay. Bye.
Lips.
I'm suddenly so dizzy.
What is it? Do you have a headache?
No.
I miss you so much that I don't want to see you.
I miss you more now that I see you.
It's so annoying.
It's not funny.
It's hard for me.
I went to church today.
This is where you and I...
Don't put it down. I want to see it for longer.
It would be so nice to get married there.
(Passbook)
Do you want a drink since we got our pay?
No drinks?
I'll just get beer with my wife then.
Bye.
I left you some food at home.
I'll come visit in two days.
(Summer vacation's special promotion)
When are you going to quit? When can we go on our trip?
You'll really go this time when you retire from security, right?
Do you want me to finish your sentence for you?
You know I've been patient with you.
I took care of your parents until they were in diapers.
I raised and fed your eight siblings,
and married them off.
If you still won't take me on a world tour,
you'd be evil. You know that, right?
Let's drive on our trip.
The two of us can take turns.
(Discount and gifts included)
I'm really sorry,
but we used up most of the money you gave us. There's not much left.
We understand why Jeong A left.
She'll come back if you take this to her.
You didn't live so hard...
to turn out like this, right?
Go and bring her back.
Come on.
(Registration Certificate)
(Shanghai, Hangzhou and Suzhou)
(Osaka and Okinawa)
Are you happy now?
You won and I lost.
I took everything back from my brothers for you.
We can't go on a world tour, but we'll go to China and Japan.
Does that make you happy?
Take it back. I don't need it.
Hey, hey.
Do you know how much this is?
It may not look much,
but it's 60 grand in cash.
I'm sleepy. Go.
Hey. Did you even look at this?
Did you even see it before declining?
Look. Look at it.
Come on.
Open your eyes and see this.
Open your eyes. Ouch!
You're annoying.
How can I beg any more than that?
How can I go any lower?
Seok Gyun, you drank too much.
Go to bed.
That Jeong A...
She's evil.
She trained me so that I can't do anything without her.
She acted as if she would do everything for me like my mum.
I... I didn't...
just ask her to come back home.
I...
gave her all of this.
But she doesn't want it.
She says she doesn't need it.
All she does is sleep.
She really left me behind...
and went off on her own.
(Dear My Friends)
I let her have it easy and now, she's gone crazy.
What on earth did I do wrong?
All women like things like that.
- Goodnight.
- Okay.
We're all old.
If we live together, everything has to be fair.
It looks like you're in the army.
Hit the gong if you see me face to face.
Come get yourself some skate.
Watch your mouth.
"If you have to go, smile."
"If you get dementia..."
Should we just live together?