(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Jeong A!
Jeong A, my back. My back.
Scratch my back.
More, more.
No, no. You can't do that.
Sit down. You drip all over.
Hey, how can a man pee while sitting down?
I peed sitting down since I was 40.
You're over 70. Who cares about pride? Come on.
Just sit down.
Mum, you should make up with Dad. This is ridiculous.
Do you want to taste it?
The day-care's not doing well,
and my husband is stressed because of work.
I'm...
on Mum's side. I'll be fine even if she gets a divorce.
You can only say that because Dad doesn't call you.
I went to clean two days ago, too.
It's not as often for you.
He would tell me to make siraegiguk instead of ugeojiguk.
Then he'd ask me over to make him guksu.
Mum. Let's end it after a month.
If that's too short, let's do three months before you go back.
I'll ask Dad to come and beg you.
Do you really think Dad will beg?
Then what do you suggest we do?
What do you think? She should get a divorce. Mum's a woman, too.
Right, Mum? You're a woman, too.
You want to live the rest of your life as a woman, right?
Goodness. How am I a woman?
My uterus was taken out after I had that cyst.
Also, who cares if I'm a man or a woman at this age?
You are both wasting your time blabbering away.
How can we not?
How can you leave after all that? Your life would be a failure.
Why is her life a failure?
It's Dad who can't do anything on his own that's the failure.
I agree that Dad's at fault, but...
There's no reason for you to talk about your dad like that.
When he was young, he worked so hard to raise you.
He worked at that helmet factory. To make a dollar more,
he'd work late until midnight while his nose...
and ears froze in the cold winter.
He's over 70 and still works so that he can support himself.
You have no right to talk about him like that.
You don't want to cook for him? Then don't.
Just buy it for him. You're so ungrateful.
- Mum, that's...
- It's not what I meant.
Be quiet and just give me my money.
I even cleaned your mosquito net, so give me 20 dollars more.
Take all of this.
I'll give you 100 dollars from now, so go back to Dad and...
Why would I take more money from you?
Do you think I left home to bother you?
Usually, it's 60 dollars, but today, it's 80 dollars. That's it.
I know how you feel,
but you shouldn't talk about your dad like that.
Also, don't you dare nag at me any more.
I'm sick of hearing it.
You're spending a lot ever since you moved out.
Yes, I'm splurging. I spent a fortune worth of eight dollars.
Can you digest all this?
You can't because you stay indoors all day.
You need to walk more.
My stomach hurts all the time.
I don't even eat much, but I poop 3 to 4 times a day.
What's wrong?
Stay for the night.
Okay.
I love that you moved out. You can sleepover whenever.
Shall I call the others?
Okay.
Nan Hee.
What are you doing?
What a place this is.
Are you dating him?
Not really.
He invited her over to listen to him sing.
He flung his fishing rod and caught her.
And you took the bait.
After wasting all your life,
you took the bait now?
Don't smile.
You're still very young.
You should date men.
Like you?
How are things with Seong Jae?
We aren't dating. We just meet up.
If you just meet up,
what should she do?
She can grope him all she wants.
Why can't she?
I bet her skin's still smooth.
What?
And yours isn't?
My skin is like leather.
- Yours must be soft.
- Come on.
Don't. Not in public.
Don't you dare touch me.
If you do, I will pinch you until you burst.
You talk such nonsense for people your age.
Choong Nam.
Us?
We're at a live café.
Did Yeong Won and the others...
see the man you like?
I feel left out.
It's your fault.
You said you couldn't be bothered to join us. Are you jealous now?
Don't have too much fun without me. Go home early.
(Jeong A)
Jeong A, don't forget that the next few days...
is our trial run of living together, okay?
I haven't forgotten.
She's talking about us living together.
You'll end up pulling each other's hair out. Give me that.
Hey, Choong Nam, wake up.
You may think we get along, but we don't at all.
Who doesn't get along with whom?
You and the rest of us.
You need to live alone.
You're too old to try to get used to living with someone.
No.
This time, I will try to make things work.
It's like my last piece of homework.
Haven't you heard of something called "a bucket list"?
Why? Are you planning to die?
I want to live with you.
Me, too.
Him?
He's pretty.
Who is?
That guy.
He's young and handsome. Quite fresh.
I can't stand the way you talk.
All she does is wipe the floors with rags,
- so she talks like one.
- Hey.
He looked at Nan Hee.
Okay, see you then.
He must really like her.
Hi, In Bong.
Why did she vomit?
I envy Nan Hee. She's seeing a fresh, young man.
She's living the life I never got to.
Hang on.
If we decide to live together...
If that happens...
Shall I make them pay 300 dollars a month for expenses?
Is that too much? 200?
Wait. Water, electricity...
and gas bills...
We'll have to take turns doing the laundry and cleaning.
Washing the dishes.
Hee Ja can do it on Mondays.
Jeong A will do it on Tuesdays.
On Wednesdays...
Yeong Won and Nan Hee work, so forget about them.
Do I have to do it for the rest of the week?
Shoot.
Mum, Grandma will be okay.
It's bound to happen one day.
It is.
She's 90 years old.
We should prepare for the worst.
How can a daughter prepare for her mother's death?
Should I cut wood and make a coffin?
Don't say that because she's my mum, not yours.
Then again, you wouldn't blink an eye if you heard that...
I were dead.
You're evil. You only agreed to come along...
to write your book.
You told me to write something.
No matter what I say...
What?
We never get along.
We never will.
We're polar opposites.
My wife and I...
got along very well.
I loved her more than anything.
I reported to her whenever...
I left the house and returned.
And any money I earned, I gave to her every month.
If I thought my parents were giving her a hard time,
I put them aside for a while and focused...
all my energy on her.
I was a good husband.
Shortly before she died, she said,
"Honey, let's meet again."
That's what she said to me.
Will Jeong A appreciate that?
If I call her...
and ask about things?
Are you willing to try?
Of course, she'll like it.
All women like that.
Do they?
The cotton candy
Is as white as snow, and clean and fluffy
It's just like the cotton candy I ate
When I went on a walk with Mum
Hello?
Sleep well.
Okay.
I said, "Sleep well."
And I said, "Okay."
You should tell me to sleep well.
- What is it?
- If I tell you to sleep well,
shouldn't you say it back?
I even called to say that.
Who told you to call?
Don't call if you want to show off.
(Power Off)
Jeong A.
(100 Things I Know I Did Wrong,)
(10,000 Things I Didn't Know I Did Wrong)
He's trying really hard to be nice...
I never asked for a phone call.
Then what do you want from him?
I don't know.
I don't mind cooking for him...
and I know he can be frustrating.
And I do feel sorry for him.
But right now,
I hate everything.
But I don't know why I feel this way.
I'm upsetting the girls...
Are you hurt?
I don't know.
Sit down.
Sit down somewhere.
Are you okay?
Now that I'm old, my legs keep giving up.
Forget about our legs.
Our kids want us to keep our heads on straight.
A newborn can't walk even if it can think properly.
It's all about our age.
Let's take a rest.
I'd carry you if I had the energy.
Do you think they'll think we're weird?
Two old ladies are sitting in the street...
late at night instead of being in bed.
I can't do this with Seok Gyun.
If we were walking along and I felt weak,
he could suggest a break.
If I get hurt,
he could tell me to be careful like you just did.
Instead, he complains and scolds me by saying...
mean things like, "Get a grip. What's wrong with you?"
I spent all my married life with him,
so it'd be cheap to curse at him.
Do it.
You jerk.
All those years together...
and that's the best I can do.
Both he and I...
will die sooner than later. So what would I want from him?
You don't need a husband or a man.
It'd be nice to just live like best friends.
Kind of like you and me. Good friends. Right?
It's a tough life.
It's hard to have a friend that's not a burden to you.
A cotton candy
Got hooked on a branch
Like a thread
The cotton candy
Is white
As snow
I have to go back to the United States next week.
Let's meet on Thursday, Yeong Won.
I'm so hungry.
Why is she sleeping here?
Jeong A, why are you sleeping here instead of your place?
Well?
Stop bothering me and just go to sleep.
Why is she sleeping here?
Did she fight with Seok Gyun?
All right.
Sure. Even that little guy is running away to live.
What are you doing here?
Working, what else?
You acted like you were sleeping last night.
It's time for lunch. Why are you working?
Let's get you tested in Seoul today.
It'd be good news if I died.
Yes, it sure is.
Hey. When I die, make sure you hit the gong.
"Oh Ssang Boon is finally free."
Play the trumpets, throw flower petals and slaughter a pig for me.
Are you kidding me?
Grandma, do you want us to bury you with a skate?
Of course, you fool.
Skate is a necessity in any mourner's house.
Sure. If it's for my dear grandma,
I'll get you domestic skates instead of the Chilean kind.
I'll invite all your neighbours and even people over there.
"Everyone, come get yourself some raw skates!"
Are you serious?
Not again! You're weak to me anyway.
Let go of me. Let go.
Grandma isn't dying. She's not sick.
She says she threw up because she ate too much.
She threw up during the day and at night, too!
Don't worry. She won't die.
See? I'm right. She's not dying, right?
That guy agrees with me. What's wrong with you?
He's your uncle. Show some respect.
Mum won't die even if everyone in the village dies.
She'll have a long life.
Don't curse me.
Grandma, it's true.
Your mum and your grandma...
all lived until their 90s and 100s.
That's why Mum and I are healthy, and we don't even get a cold.
Shut your mouth!
We're going to the hospital.
I'm not going.
You can't die. What will happen to Dad and In Bong?
I'm not doing this for you. It's for me.
I can't live with Dad and In Bong.
I'll live happily with Jacqueline and Dad.
Shut your mouth.
Sorry.
Why are you scolding him?
Mum, if you cared even the slightest for me,
you'd go to the hospital!
Do you want your widowed daughter to take care...
of your husband and your disabled son?
It's not fair you get to go alone! How can you be so irresponsible?
Do you want me to talk like that, too? "I wish I could die."
Don't talk that nonsense.
Come eat!
I knew you'd get yelled at.
Just tell her you'll go.
Goodness.
It'll cost us.
In Bong has to get married soon.
I have so much work I have to do as well.
- Mum!
- What?
She'll go to the hospital after she finishes work and on your day off.
Okay. Don't work too much and bring her home after.
I'll make some sujebi.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to do what Mum says.
I love you, but you talk too much.
If you make her upset, I'll scold you.
You!
Be good to your mum.
Okay?
Uncle.
Did you do any of this with Jacqueline yet?
Twice.
He did this with Jacqueline!
Look at him. He's so happy.
I didn't know you did such a thing.
No, hold on.
This isn't right. Hold on.
I think this would be better. I just bought these.
That's way too big.
Just try it.
My...
Gosh, these are huge.
You can't tell at all.
Make sure he doesn't touch them.
You can tell that it's fake.
What are you talking about?
Hey, you know that everyone will come today, right?
I do. I'll be back early.
Come late. We won't wait for you.
You can see us any time you want.
He probably has a wife, right?
Tell him to get a divorce.
Tell him it's wrong to live with one woman for so long.
I love you.
That's why we should live together.
I wonder if he's as excited as I am.
If not, then forget him. Don't hold him back.
I'll get going.
Why did he leave such a beautiful girl behind?
Wretched jerk.
Hey, Choong Nam!
You were home.
Why are you here?
Well...
Someone gave us a call.
What?
He said he wanted to buy my work.
He said something about an exhibition in America.
The pieces you sold through your friend's gallery...
I sold what was mine. Is that a problem?
Not at all.
It's just that someone wants to show our pieces in America,
so we were wondering...
if we could buy or borrow what you bought from us.
No.
Choong Nam, this opportunity...
It's the first opportunity in our lives. Please, just once.
I liked you when you were young.
When you were part-time lecturers.
You came here every day to talk about art,
and then you cried because you couldn't support yourselves.
Why are you mentioning that?
I liked you then.
I wasn't educated...
and knew nothing about art.
But seeing you cling onto it even when you went hungry...
made me think that art was something great.
Just get to the point.
All you care about now is money and success.
You are fools and losers.
Let's go.
Wait.
Choong Nam, you shouldn't say that.
You bought our pieces for cheap and sold them for way more.
You should thank us.
You just won't stop, will you?
Forget it, then.
Leaving me out...
and mocking me is probably the least terrible thing you did.
The worst thing you did...
was not realising your true value.
Don't sell pieces you spent time and tears to make so easily.
I'll make the exhibition happen.
I'd have proposed to you if you were 10 years younger.
If you were 10 and I were 30 years younger.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Give me time to park.
No. I'll call you.
Excuse me. Can I have another herb tea?
Sure.
You haven't changed.
Not really.
How is your wife?
How is your health?
We haven't met in over 30 years.
I think so.
Go.
Let's have a meal and a drink together.
No thanks.
I'm a noisy eater and I don't want you to see that.
Go home.
It's good to see that you seem well.
Let's eat dinner together.
No, I want to go.
I'll go first.
Look after yourself.
Yes, it's me. Can you come and get me?
Yeong Won's reunion with her first love whom she never got over...
ended just like that.
When she saw him again, she didn't feel the need to ask...
why he had left her or say that she missed him.
And then, she said this.
Until now,
I thought that people grew old...
but that their spirits or hearts didn't.
But?
Today, I realised...
our hearts grow old, too.
He suggested we eat out.
But I thought, "What's the point?"
He suggested a drink.
But I thought, "What difference would that make?"
That's my heart growing old.
You silly.
But what Yeong Won said to me before leaving for the States was...
the complete opposite.
"I wish I ate with him."
"I wish we had that drink."
She just added one more thing to regret...
in her not-so-eventful life story.
Can I really believe every single thing you said?
That you were pleased to see Dae Cheol?
Of course. It was nice. It really was.
Okay, then.
- Is she evil?
- The other one's worse.
She's so mean.
Be quiet. I can't hear a thing they're saying.
- She grabbed her hair.
- Look.
Oh dear.
- She didn't like it.
- Did she say so?
Before she washed her face, I saw her make-up was a mess.
She can't fool me.
She said she had a nice time and I pretended to believe her.
Well done.
- Good riddance.
- She had it coming.
Television time is over.
- Let's keep watching.
- Just a bit more.
- Come on.
- Hey!
How mean.
What should we do now?
(Monthly expense, cleaning duties)
We're all old,
so if we live together, we need to be equal.
There's no respecting elders here.
I was never like that.
- What about Mum?
- Are you going to make her cook?
Ssang Boon is an exception.
If we're going to be fair, why do I only pay 200 dollars?
The rest of you are paying 300 dollars.
The wealthy should pay more. That's what's fair.
Don't you know what fair means?
I see. That's why.
All right, now...
I told you about cooking and living expenses.
Next up is cleaning duties.
The cleaning duty is...
We're just trying it out today.
Why are you planning so far ahead?
And I can already tell after spending half a day together.
We won't get along.
Take television time as an example.
You could have waited until the show was over,
but you turned it off.
Hold on.
Get the blankets out.
We're not here to just sleep. Can't we chat and play?
Old people should sleep early.
Get washed up for bed.
We'll do it in the order of age.
What's with her?
You're at an army.
You better move fast...
if you don't want the drill instructor to yell at you.
Also,
I'm just a shadow today. I won't be helping out.
All that I'll do today is observe. You know that, right?
Do drill instructors in the army do whatever they want?
How would I know?
You probably don't know.
Choong Nam, where are the blankets?
Yeong Won.
Please wash them well.
Okay.
Hey, help out.
No, I'm observing today.
You're so mean.
Come on, clean it well.
- Don't just skim over it.
- Yes, Ma'am.
Where should I put these?
Where do you think?
In the living room.
Good girl.
Choong Nam.
- What?
- Toothpaste.
It's right there in your hand.
Sorry.
What?
- Towel.
- It's on your neck.
Goodness, this is why old people should just die.
Have this.
Here.
I'll pour it for you.
Okay.
Here. This is good for you.
I only have enough for you.
Drink up.
- That's mine and that's yours.
- Okay.
Here's your water.
There's one more.
What a sight.
They're chugging pills to live on.
There's so much.
They'll be full from all those pills.
Turn it off.
Stop being so loud.
Sorry.
Hee Ja, come back.
Do you need fresh air?
You'll catch a cold if you go out now.
Come back and sleep.
Why are all of us sleeping at your place?
What are you talking about?
Just sleep.
Hee Ja, let's sleep.
Sleep.
I'm hungry.
You shouldn't eat in the middle of the night.
Go to sleep.
Where are you going?
To the bathroom.
It's not that way. It's this way.
This way.
Come here.
Choong Nam,
don't live together.
Shut your mouth.
I can tell after today...
that you're like Mother Teresa.
What's that?
It's someone who lived kindly and died.
Did she go to a good place?
I think so.
Thank you.
This way, this way.
Sleep.
Are you regretting it?
Should we not live together?
Gosh, she can snore.
Come on, let me sleep.
You're the only one actually getting sleep.
She's the only one that slept.
- My goodness.
- Goodness.
We'll stretch to the left first.
Look towards the sky.
Now, the other side.
Fold to the front.
Go as low as you can.
- More, more.
- That hurts.
Don't do that. You're going to kill her.
Just don't do it.
You're the one who wanted to do it.
Hey, take a break.
You can't do it. I'll do it.
Come on.
Are you going to leave us like you did to Seok Gyun?
Do you enjoy slaving?
Go rest.
Okay.
Let me try what my actor friend can cook up.
See you tonight.
- Okay.
- Bye.
- Wan, drive safe.
- I will.
Bye.
- Hee Ja!
- Yes?
Hee Ja! Your diaper bag.
Jeong A, your phone!
Jeong A, Jeong A.
- Nan Hee!
- Jeong A, Jeong A.
Your phone. You forgot it.
Right. Yes. That's mine.
Nan Hee.
You wore my aunt's shoes.
Right. I'm so forgetful.
Oh, right. Yeong Won, your pills!
Yes, I forgot.
- Let's go.
- Okay.
I asked Choong Nam...
why she thought about living with them.
She said the thing she regrets the most in her life...
is never having had someone to get along with.
So before she dies,
and although it may require extra work and effort,
she wanted to try to get along with her friends.
That's why.
Really?
That doctor was evil. He gave you a painful shot.
I'll be there the day after tomorrow.
Yes, I'll be there in two days.
Come on. Don't cry now.
I'll see you soon.
Bye.
Hee Ja.
Don't be silly.
You didn't bother me at all. I had so much fun.
Let's do it before winter comes.
Of course. Before winter.
By the way, where were you trying to go last night?
Hee Ja said that along with looking after her extended family,
this was the next best thing she had done.
I said I agreed with her.
And for the first time ever,
I gave Choong Nam a big hug.
Excuse me.
- Joseph.
- Yes?
Our caretaker saw this last night and informed me.
It looks like...
she just came in to pray.
Can we watch it again?
(Seok Gyun)
Did you say there were more footage?
The phone is...
Why isn't he picking up?
Is he busy working?
(Jeong A)
Excuse me. Can you help me?
Sure.
It's okay.
Are you okay?
You're so pretty.
Oh, my. It's a new chair.
Could you carry it?
It's quite heavy.
You shouldn't work if you can't carry that.
Madam.
I'll carry the dog while you carry the chair.
How dare you touch my baby with your dirty hands?
It's a dog, not a child!
Gosh, why did you yell at me?
Do you want to get fired?
I quit before you can get me fired.
I'm a security guard, not your servant.
Your husband works for someone else, too, right?
I'm old enough to be your father. Know your manners.
- Hold back.
- I won't!
Do you take me for a fool?
I do this to make a living.
I work for my pay!
How dare you treat me like you pay me for doing nothing?
Would you like it if someone treated your husband like that?
I hope the dog's fleas end up all over you!
What's wrong with you women including my wife?
Sir.
Sit down before you get hurt.
I'm about to sit!
Everyone abuses elders these days.
Get up.
What are you looking at?
- Seok Gyun.
- No. I don't want to.
You're such a loser. Man up.
Gosh.
Look.
Help...
Dad, Mum made extra and told me to give you some.
I cleaned up, but I'm too busy to stay.
Dad, I'm not that nice to you, but that's not how I feel.
I respect you. Take care of yourself.
Let's go travelling.
Go alone. I'm cleaning up.
You wanted to go travelling.
I'm cleaning now.
Gosh.
She's acting up because I let her.
What did I do wrong? What did I do so wrong?
Forget it.
I don't need you.
Hey, you scumbag! Drive properly!
Don't you care for old people?
Do you expect us to put up with everything...
and sacrifice what we have when you need help?
I can kill you all!
What?
Jeju Island is too far for a honeymoon,
but we should have at least gone to a nice hot spring.
It's nice here, too.
When I get rich,
we'll go on a world tour.
I'll take you.
We won't have to sleep over at a friend's old house...
in the countryside for a trip.
Promise me.
I promise.
Once my brothers get married, we'll go.
I think it'll be 10 years from now.
I can wait.
But...
How can we travel without our parents?
Let's go after we finish taking care of them.
We'll go in about 30 years.
30 years is too long!
20 years.
I won't even be 50 by then.
I can definitely wait until then.
By the way,
we have to leave here early in the morning.
Their grandmother is returning from Seoul.
I'm just grateful that we can stay here on our own...
without your parents and siblings.
That house she was so grateful for...
only collected dust.
She could have come just to pray.
Pray at 2am?
She was wearing slippers and her pyjamas.
She just had a cardigan on.
I only told you because that bothered me.
You should keep observing her and let her kids know.
"The nursing home is your second home."
"If you have to go, smile while you leave."
"If you get dementia..."
Try this.
Okay.
It's good.
I'm glad you like it.
Should we just live together?
Are you crazy?
I would never do something my kids hate.
What is there to hate?
They'll be glad to get you off their shoulders.
At least my kids will think so.
If I was sick, maybe. But for now, I think they prefer me to be alone.
If I picture my mum with another man,
I think it'd be awkward, too.
If it weren't for the kids,
you'd be interested?
It'd be nice to have someone to talk to if you're not hitting on me.
- Hit on you?
- Yes.
Are you telling me not to touch you?
Are you going to touch me?
Don't you have the instructions for those cameras?
Why?
I like reading manuals.
It's there beside the pills somewhere.
Okay.
Yes, there.
Yes.
All right.
Let's take a look.
Let's see if it's working right.
Let's see if the cameras...
are protecting my first love well.
Yes, Min Ho.
It's the cotton candy you had when you went on a picnic
With your mum's hand in yours
- If you blow it, it'll make holes
- Look.
If you blow it
Look at that.
It'll make holes
A big cotton candy
With your mum's hand in yours
The cotton candy
Look at this.
That mum bought you
I was wearing pants...
but he still did it!
Dad!
Honey.
What? What is it now?
Could you take this home for me?
I'm working here. Do you want to die?
I think the baby...
So...
I have to go to the hospital.
They said it's a boy this time.
Don't make a fuss. Why would there be anything wrong?
Just go home!
Both the mum and the daughter are driving me crazy.
You came to ruin our family, didn't you?
Where did my clothes go after you washed them?
You threw it out because you knew I liked it, didn't you?
Well? Get up.
Mother, please! I'm so sorry!
Please don't pull my hair!
Where is it? Go find it!
You threw it out, right?
It's just a cold. Why would she call her mum about that?
What did you teach your kids?
They're such whiners. They take after you, you know that?
What is this?
It's such a waste to throw it out.
Then why did you pay money to buy it then make it go bad?
You are well out of your mind, aren't you?
If anyone saw you eat your three meals for a day,
they'd think you're a wrestler.
A fat wrestler at that!
Stay here for 10 more minutes.
What about the world tour you promised me...
when I took care of your eight siblings?
If I didn't hold you back with that promise,
you would've left me already.
I don't want to die in a hospital...
like my mum did.
I want to fly free like a bird...
and die on the streets.
Mum...
Okay.
If you won't come over, I'll go.
Where do you live?
Shall I ask your mum?
Just tell him to come over.
He wants to give you something to write about.
Just spare him an hour.
And get rid of this.
You guys broke up.
Be quiet.
I only have an hour. Will that be enough?
Okay.
I know where you live. I dropped Jeong A off before.
It's block 409, flat 505.
Do you know where?
I'll come over.
He's so annoying.
Don't be like that to the old man. You're such a brat.
He should be more thoughtful.
He acts like old age makes him special.
By the time I'm done with the book,
I think I'll hate talking to old people.
They act how they want just because they think they'll die soon.
It's obvious what he'll say.
He'll either brag or complain about his life.
Or he'll curse others.
I have a feeling you're talking about me.
What was that?
I started exercising my legs at the pool.
It's you.
How are you?
Wan's not in. She just left.
Oh, that's fine.
I can talk to you.
Are you well?
My brother can walk now.
You can't, can you?
It was a serious accident.
I see.
You still have to exercise your legs.
I bet they hurt a lot at night.
Take care.
And date women.
How's your mother? I heard she's ill.
I'm going to take her to the doctor.
Let's talk again.
I have to go.
She said, "My stomach feels strange."
She was carrying groceries on her head.
But I just got mad.
Blood was dripping down her legs.
So...
she stayed at a hospital for two days.
I felt bad for her.
After that,
I should have kept my mouth shut.
But I said, "Get up and cook for me."
I said that.
After that,
we both acted like nothing happened.
We were together.
But now, I'm alone.
Others, and even Soon Young,
think that I was mean and arrogant...
even though I knew I was wrong.
But I had no idea.
It was so long ago...
and my focus was on making a living.
I did so terribly wrong, didn't I?
The biggest sin...
is not knowing what you did wrong. Being ignorant.
You can't count the mistakes you didn't know you made.
That's why...
I will let my wife go.
You can write about everything I said...
if you want others to know there are people like me.
Well...
Seok Gyun.
Just like how you talked to me so freely just now,
tell Jeong A...
I can't cook or do the washing.
No.
I won't work her any more.
Go.
And quit smoking, Kid.
You should eat lunch.
Shall I cook something?
Seok Gyun.
Just go.
Okay, then.
Someone said that...
we do more bad than good...
during our whole lives.
That's why...
we have much more to gain than to lose,
and we are blessed.
So instead of having regrets,
we should be grateful we're alive.
Is life really a blessing we should be...
grateful for?
Even to my mum and grandma?
I sincerely hope that this will be...
the ending to the book that I'll leave to my mother when I go...
live with Yeon Ha.
Ms Jang Nan Hee is...
That's me.
(Dear My Friends)
"The husband must speak in a small voice..."
"and always be kind." What a joke.
I pressed the button.
At least, he won't starve.
Do you like me or him?
Did you sleep with him?
What?
Don't fall for anyone else.
You sound like an evil boyfriend...
who sells your girlfriend.
I'll be waiting.
I should tell Hee Ja's kids, right?
She's not at church?
How are we going to find her?