Mum, where are you?
The hospital?
You'll get checked up too while you're there, right?
How can I not when your grandma's here?
I registered, too.
I did.
Oh Ssang Boon and Jang Nan Hee.
We have to go in now. Bye.
It'll be fine, Mum.
I know.
Please come this way.
Who is Jang Nan Hee?
Me.
How are you for time, today?
What did he say?
We have time. What is it?
You should get CT scans while you're here.
Nurse Kim.
Can you prepare CT scans for Ms Oh and Ms Jang?
These big headed doctors won't let you ask questions.
They just say what they want and then leave.
If they try to leave, you can hold them back and ask.
You act like you know everything.
Why did you act so stupid?
You must feel lucky to have a stupid mum.
Ask them everything.
Ask them how Grandma is,
why you have to take a CT scan...
and what they saw in the x-ray.
Ask them how Grandma's diet should be if her stomach is bad.
All right, All right.
Ask them in detail.
Right.
Record it on your phone.
Record what the doctor says.
Record it?
How do I do that?
How can you not know how when you know how to take pictures?
I've never done it before.
I'm not a spy. Why would I ever record anyone?
I'm just worried about you and Grandma...
If you're so worried, why didn't you come with us?
When did she ever worry about me?
How do I record it anyway?
Ms Jang, it's time for your scan.
Did my mum finish?
Yes. She's done.
Shouldn't you go to the hospital?
My mum's smart.
She'll be fine.
Grandma is turning 90 soon.
My mum's really healthy.
Didn't you see her beat up Dong Jin?
Don't spray on me.
I'll kill you. Swallow it.
Don't laugh so hard.
Right.
Did you read my manuscript yet?
A hole?
Yes, it's a hole.
You have to take your pills.
Otherwise, they have to open you up to fix the hole.
What?
Why would you open me up?
Are you crazy?
If I had money for that, I'd die while eating it!
- What a joke!
-  Goodness.
One moment.
Are you mad?
I won't get a surgery.
I'd rather die.
Okay, we won't.
Just take the pills the doctor gives you.
Don't go anywhere...
and play your game here.
Stay here.
The goblins will kidnap you if you leave.
A bigger hospital?
Why?
I'm completely fine.
You need to get an MRI,
but we don't have the equipment, so...
What is there on my photo?
There's a malignant tumour on your liver.
On mine and not my mother's?
A tumour? Malignant?
Do I have cancer?
I'm not 100 percent sure,
- but in my opinion...
-  Why tell me if you aren't sure?
I don't want to know your opinion.
What do you see on the photo? What is there...
that would make you say that to someone who's never been sick?
That's why you need an MRI.
We can't tell for sure with a CT.
Why take a photo if you can't be sure?
What's wrong with you?
Explain slowly. What's on my liver?
Where are the tumours?
"A husband must protect..."
"himself and his family,"
"and not be a tyrant."
"Eight."
"A husband must not interfere in..."
"or nag about the housework."
"Nine."
"A husband must not purchase furniture or clothes on his own,"
"or make important decisions without discussing with his wife."
Why are there so many don'ts?
"Ten. A husband must always speak in a low voice,"
"and be soft, kind and gentle."
What a joke.
What's the fun in life if we can't shout to our wives?
Soft and kind?
I have to act like a player then.
What do I do next?
I put food in the rice cooker.
Are you crazy?
Is he crazy?
Why would you put food in there? You put in rice.
You have lost your mind.
I know, I put rice in it.
But...
there are so many buttons on it.
Press the one on the top right that says "plain rice".
Gosh.
What now?
I pressed the one that says "plain rice".
Will it cook?
How do I know if it's done?
You'll know when it's done. The cooker makes a noise.
It'll tell you.
He's actually cooking so he won't starve.
I guess he won't starve then.
He must really like you a lot.
He keeps calling you.
He just needs me.
They took their clothes off. They're both naked.
They're bare naked.
I can't watch this alone.
Look at that.
They're naked from head to toe.
Everything on them is so big.
Hee Ja, you need to watch this.
Don't, it's gross.
They're now...
stuck to each other.
Watch the movie with me. Why are you so strong?
I really don't want to watch now.
Stop it.
- Leave me alone.
-  Your face is so red.
Why did you want to watch this movie then?
Oh dear...
How do I make doenjang jjigae?
Is this all I need?
Should they be squares?
That's finally done.
So based on this,
she started going out at night...
two months ago.
The average time of her outings...
is 90 minutes.
Hee Ja lives two stops away from church,
so that's about 1.5km.
She makes the round trip in 90 minutes...
and prays at church for about 15 minutes.
That means she doesn't go anywhere else.
I guess Jeong A isn't with her.
Hello?
Doctor Lee, hello.
It's me, Seong Jae.
I want to ask you something.
Well...
It's about a friend of mine.
I think she could have dementia.
You lunatic. Are you living together already?
Why are you eating with her at home?
Bye.
Are you happy?
I am.
How's Dad?
Mum told him to write something 100 times a day.
I have to go.
They're wasting so much money to keep these lights on.
They're all crazy.
They're spending their money, not yours.
My money is their money.
Do you want to get out to turn the lights off?
I will if you'll let me. I can, you know?
Mum.
I took some important tests with you.
Why won't you ask if I'm sick...
or why I had to take the tests with you?
What?
She blamed her own hardships to ignore others' grievances.
Now she uses her deafness.
What?
There's a malignant tumour in your liver.
Give me your hand.
Oh, come on.
Not watching TV for one evening won't kill you.
Put it over your hands.
Put some on your face, not just on your hands.
Oh dear.
Let's see your feet.
Right, the vitamins.
Here.
Maybe I should have bought...
some good supplements for myself too...
instead of saving money.
What is it?
It's nothing.
Why do you keep on yelling at me?
I didn't.
Did you take your pills after dinner?
Yes.
You have better memory than me.
Dad's going to have a hard time getting to sleep without you.
He deserves it.
You're always getting your revenge, aren't you?
Are you mad because I made you use money?
I should die,
but I made you use money at the hospital.
Yes.
That's why I'm mad.
What are you doing?
Are you playing?
What do you mean? I'm working.
I'm interviewing...
Soo Young, Ho Young,
Min Ho and Ha Neul.
It feels like a watermelon is coming out of your nose.
They all came over.
I'm telling you, that's how it'll feel.
Hey. Hey, hey.
Take these over yourselves.
If you run out of food, get it from the fridge.
How can you make me do all the work?
Yes, Sir.
I'm working.
Hey, not the jerky. Those are mine.
- Hey.
-  Yes.
Talk on the phone or go chat. Just do one at a time.
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't drink so much.
How can I interview you if you get drunk?
You're not here to party.
What is it?
"What is it?"
I went to the hospital, remember?
Right.
What did they say?
Grandma's stomach ulcer is bad.
She'll have to take pills for a few months.
It's because of the chilli.
She always eats that spicy stuff every meal.
What about you?
I'm...
fine, of course.
You wasted money.
That's right.
Don't say that. You should be glad.
I was worried.
I feel good now.
It's nothing, right?
Did you listen to them properly?
Can you finish up early...
and come over? Grandma's here.
Come on, Mum. I asked them over for my work.
How can I go there now? That would be wrong.
What's so wrong with it?
Why are you being whiny again?
You need to date someone instead.
I'll get married soon,
so you should find yourself a boyfriend...
instead of being so attached to me.
Whom are you marrying?
A man.
I love you, Nan Hee.
Go to bed, Nan Hee.
Bye.
Hey, hey! I told you not to drink so much.
Give me one, too.
What is it? Are you coming?
No.
I just had a strange feeling. You sound really down.
What is it?
Really?
Did something happen?
No, nothing.
Looking at how irritated you are, you must be fine.
You're so full of energy, you might eat me up alive.
I'm hanging up. I'm sleepy.
Goodnight.
All right, put your glasses down.
To pay back for all the food I gave you...
This is my favourite snack for drinking.
You'll have to answer honestly to the questions I ask. Okay?
"I like my mum all the time."
What's wrong with you guys?
Listen carefully to what I say.
It's not, "Do you like your mum?"
I asked you if you like her all the time.
Then I'm out.
You can take me out.
I don't like her all the time.
Good, now you're being honest.
It's the same for me. I like her in the end,
but the process is like torture.
Let's...
talk behind our mums' backs today.
It'll make us feel better,
and my writing will be more realistic.
I'd appreciate it.
Here's my second question.
What do you like...
the least about your mum?
- Mum went through tough times.
-  She went through a lot.
- But she looks...
-  Her appearance...
What about you?
Me? My mum?
She loves me too much...
So much that it's an obsession.
- I don't like that.
-  That's horrible.
Obsession?
One time, I was sleeping with my boyfriend.
Then I saw my mum's head sticking out from the ceiling...
and looking at us.
Gosh.
I got the chills then.
I'm getting goosebumps.
You're a mama's girl, though.
Be quiet, mama's boy.
I agree.
All right, focus.
What would you ask of your mum?
Just one thing that you want.
Ha Neul, you start.
I want her to live long...
even if she's sick.
My goodness.
Let's all have a toast for our mums.
- For Mum!
-  For Mum!
Cheers.
The drinks are going down
Gulp, gulp, gulp
Do I have to get up?
- Of course. It's a must.
-  Dance.
- How long will you make me dance?
-  Good.
I'm going to dance forever.
Dance to this music.
No, not this song.
Come on.
- Thank you for the food.
-  Yes, please enjoy.
- I already started.
-  Thank you for the food.
Yes. Go ahead.
- Enjoy the food.
-  Enjoy.
Yes, I'm sorry.
I had a shoot today.
We're out having dinner now.
What? A university hospital? For what?
I heard your mum was sick. Is it bad?
No, it's stomach ulcer.
By the way,
do you know any doctors specializing in liver cancer?
You do?
You didn't date him too, did you?
If I had two bodies, I would have.
What do you need him for?
Are you getting a test?
Good idea.
We're at an age to regularly check our bodies...
even if it costs us.
You've grown up.
You're finally using money on yourself.
All right.
I'll talk to the doctor.
He's a really famous guy,
so you might have to wait a few days. Is that okay?
I have no choice. I'll wait if I have to.
What?
Dae Cheol?
He's going to the United States.
He wants to see me before he leaves.
Should I see him or not?
I'm thinking about it.
You're digging yourself into a hole again.
You aren't just thinking about it.
You're willing to take back a man who left you.
My goodness.
How do you know me so well?
There's nothing I don't know about you.
You don't know me.
You're such a fool.
Dae Cheol?
What time is your flight the day after tomorrow?
It's obvious.
I want to see you.
I'm not over the man who left me,
and I want to see you even for just a few hours.
Didn't you know?
I'm such a fool.
Mum.
I'm...
scared.
(Forever Like A Mum And A Fighter, Part 1)
Heavenly Father.
How pretty.
Hi.
Hee Ja.
Why aren't you in bed?
Seong Jae.
I can't sleep.
Were you asleep?
I wouldn't pick up if I were.
It's barely 4am.
Shouldn't you sleep some more?
I should.
I should sleep some more.
Yes. People our age...
should sleep well.
Shall I...
sing you a lullaby?
Go on, then.
Listen with your eyes closed.
Sleep if you want to.
Summertime
And the living is easy
Fish are jumping
And the cotton is high
Your daddy's rich
And your mummy is good looking
So hush little baby
Don't you...
cry
I'm
Dreaming of a white Christmas
With every Christmas card I write
Where the treetops
Thank you very much.
If you make reservations again, I'll give you more food for free.
Come by again.
- Thank you.
-  Bye.
- Thank you. Bye.
-  Thank you.
Goodbye.
We're closing for the day.
- Okay.
-  Okay.
What happened to your mother-in-law?
She couldn't control her faeces and urine.
She died after suffering for three years.
When an old person gets cancer,
they get dementia with it.
Did it hurt when she found out about her cancer?
Of course. It hurt her a lot.
I'm not sick.
I know that.
Right, what about your mum?
Didn't I tell you?
It wasn't cancer.
What? Then what is it?
It's a cystis in her head.
- That's good.
-  What a relief.
She's completely fine after her surgery.
She's really excited these days.
She says she was given a second life.
Gosh.
You should live your second life with me.
Let's go on dates.
Look at him trying to make a move. What are you going to do?
I'm not crazy.
Do you have to go crazy to date me?
- Gosh.
-  That's enough.
The hospital told her that it was cancer, right?
But it wasn't when they opened her up?
That's right.
They thought it looked like cancer, but it wasn't it.
I see.
- That's great news.
-  Yes.
The hospital is at fault. They made the wrong diagnosis.
That's great. It's great news.
Is it serious?
It's hard to tell at this stage.
Assuming that she's having a hard time differentiating night and day...
Okay, assuming...
It means her dementia is severe.
Do you think you'll pass the exams?
Of course. Do you think you'll fail?
How dare you?
I really hope you pass this time.
Are you going to take these classes forever?
You little...
You...
Gosh. Seong Jae.
Are you here to see me?
I called, but you didn't pick up.
Let's get some tea.
I can't. I have the mock exam today.
I really have to pass my exams to go to university.
I can't have tea right now. I'm sorry.
Why are you here anyway?
Did you fight with Hee Ja?
I'll wait at a nearby café.
Call me when you're done.
Did you break up with her?
What is it? You look so down.
What's the problem? You can just date me.
Just consider yourself lucky and get yourself a new girl.
He's going deaf already.
What are you doing?
I'm praying to everything out there to help me pass.
It won't help, they're on my side.
And I have luck on my side.
I'm sure 50 dollars a day is a lie.
Even if it's half the money, it's worth it.
There.
What are you doing?
Why are you here again?
Your eyes are too dim for that.
How will you sew eyes on dolls,
put pencil lead into little cases...
and make jewellery?
How can you do all that?
You shouldn't have left home.
Aren't you going to work?
I was fired.
That's good.
Good for you.
I'm going to start picking up recyclables on the streets.
Don't steal that away from the poor people.
Sell the house for money.
If you're that bored, just sweep around the neighbourhood.
All you care about is yourself.
All right.
I won't pick them up.
Are you coming back from cleaning Soo Young's?
Where would I go other than Hee Ja's or the kids'?
You're washing a lot of rice. Are you cooking for me?
How can I only cook for myself?
Don't bother with cooking.
I made doenjang jjigae.
Try the doenjang jjigae.
It was weird at first, but it's not so bad...
after I tried it a few times.
How is it?
It's edible.
I...
went to the house where we had our honeymoon.
The place is still the same.
It's abandoned.
I fell asleep there accidentally...
and was reminded of the time when we miscarried our son.
You told me several times at home...
and even came to the factory to tell me that you were sick.
I'm so sorry that I didn't...
take you to the hospital.
Why are you talking about that now?
What's the point?
Are you trying to make me upset?
I told you I felt sick.
I'm not the type to be whiny.
Why didn't you take me to the hospital?
Why didn't you? Why?
Why didn't you take me?
Bring my son back! Bring him back!
Welcome.
I need to use the internet. Can I do that here?
Yes.
(Liver cancer)
(What are the symptoms of liver cancer?)
(My mum had liver cancer, but it was in early stages.)
(Can you get better from liver cancer?)
(What is the survival rate for liver cancer?)
(Tell me the survival rate for stage 3 and 4 liver cancer.)
(Can you get better from liver cancer?)
(Survival rate for cancer)
Hello.
My goodness.
What are you doing here?
I come here when I'm not working.
I see.
What about you? I didn't expect to see you here.
I had to check something.
(My mum has liver cancer...)
I don't have a computer at home.
My phone is too small.
Do you want to take a walk with me?
A walk?
Come on.
A walk? Where?
Hold on.
- Thank you.
-  Bye.
No. Use your mouth.
This is how you're supposed to eat it.
What's your name? I'm Lee Il Woo.
I'm Jang Nan Hee.
I just realised we didn't even know each other's names.
Lee Il Woo and Jang Nan Hee.
Let's have our fortunes told.
Let's.
A fortune teller comes...
and reads fortunes for free at the café we went to.
Let's go.
Wait.
But I...
But...
Thanks.
We're friends.
What did he say?
That I'm too old to be your friend?
No. He said you're pretty.
Are you a player?
No.
I'm pretty sure you are.
You tell strange jokes.
You look pretty innocent and I fell for it.
Hello.
What would you like to know?
How long will I live?
What about you?
Whether I have a chance with you or not.
I'm serious.
You're weird.
Be serious. I don't like that kind of humour.
Don't laugh. I really don't like it when men...
joke about such things.
My late husband was witty...
and he cheated on me.
What do you see in our future?
I'll go first.
How long will I live?
Until a ripe, old age?
What a pity.
We aren't meant to be.
She's a terrible fortune teller.
She's not.
She was quite accurate.
She said I'd live a long life.
I guess that's what you wanted to hear.
Why are you speaking so informally?
Did I? I apologise.
Let's get one thing straight.
I'm older.
I don't want you to call me anything corny,
but be polite at least.
Don't you do that again.
What are you looking at so closely?
Do you think they're married?
They could be friends, like us, or married.
As if. I bet they're having an affair.
They're married or just friends.
It's an affair.
You're quite corrupt.
I'd say you have an even dirtier mind.
Hi, Wan.
Don't bring any food.
I have to work all night tonight.
I'm calling so you won't interrupt.
I'm finally getting somewhere now.
Okay.
I won't be able to come by anyway.
Why is that?
I took your advice and am on a date.
With whom?
One of my customers.
You are insane.
You don't know what they're like.
Are you serious?
I'm going to have some fun from now on.
You are serious.
What does he do?
He owns a convenience store...
and has a son in college.
He's a widower who plays the guitar...
and he's handsome.
And he's also way younger than I am.
Why would such a man date you? You're lying.
I am not.
Yeong Won's calling. I have to go.
Go home.
You shouldn't be out late at night.
Hi, Yeong Won.
Hanyoung University Hospital.
Are they good?
Do they take good care of patients?
Tomorrow?
It's a present.
Okay.
What are you doing? I have to work.
Just for five minutes.
I'm very busy.
I have to finish this novel by July.
Don't you want to go to the beach?
I'll wear a bikini.
Will you...
actually come?
I will.
I'll be waiting.
I love you.
Don't fall for anyone else.
Keep working.
(Off to see Yeon Ha!)
Seok Gyun.
The next time you make doenjang jjigae,
add anchovies and...
Hee Ja.
Did you eat dinner?
I'll come by with doenjang jjigae full of anchovies.
I have.
Oh dear.
With what?
Something weirder than frog meat.
Have you ever had doenjang water with blocks of tofu bobbing on top?
I'm serious.
Don't be too upset.
There are drugs these days...
that help delay progression.
Watch your tongue. Don't act like she was diagnosed.
Going out and snacking at night...
is fine if she's aware of it.
You aren't the only one who's sad. I'm sad, too.
We'll deal with our emotions later.
First, we have to see if she knows...
what's she's doing or not.
What's wrong with you?
You look so mopy.
I'm not.
I'm fine.
Do you know why I don't date men?
Because men become so frail in old age.
I can't stand it. Cheer up.
It's me, Choong Nam.
Why are you brushing your teeth so hard?
You'll wear them away.
If I don't brush them properly,
I smell of old people.
Now that we're old, even our breath smells worse.
Make the beds. Let's go to bed.
Okay.
Why are they all sleeping at your place?
Choong Nam.
Do you want to go travel like them?
We could get a car...
and drive with Jeong A.
With Yeong Won and Nan Hee, too.
A car? At our age?
If you want to buy something,
buy your own casket instead.
You're so smart and funny.
You're so pretty, too.
Why did all the men leave you alone?
Of course they didn't leave me alone.
They were all over me.
It was me...
who declined them.
Why?
Why did you?
You should've let them win you over.
Hee Ja.
Do you go outside at night?
At night?
No.
You don't go to church or anything?
I hear a lot of believers go pray at dawn.
Don't you go to church?
I don't like walking in the dark. I don't want to go.
Why would you go at night? You can go during the day.
How many meals do you have in a day?
I don't know.
Two?
Sometimes three.
But I poop all the time.
Does this happen to you?
No, not me.
Jeong A says she doesn't either.
Yeong Won and Nan Hee doesn't go a lot, too.
Hee Ja?
Hee Ja, come back.
Come back to bed.
I'm Choong Nam.
Right.
It's Choong Nam.
Yes.
Let's go to sleep.
You shouldn't go out at night.
Come back here.
You shouldn't go out.
If you go, I'll be scared.
I don't like being alone.
Hee Ja, come here.
Let's sleep.
Where were you trying to go?
The church.
Why?
To repent.
What's there for you to repent?
You're a good person.
I don't want to talk about it.
Hee Ja...
doesn't remember...
what happened...
last night?
No. She says she slept well.
She doesn't remember what we talked about either.
We...
We should tell her kids.
Right?
Let's tell Jeong A first.
I think it's better that she tells Min Ho.
She's going to be so surprised.
All right.
Call her.
Let's go see Jeong A.
Choong Nam, come eat breakfast.
I need to make a call.
Okay.
Jeong A, it's me.
What are you doing?
What are you talking about?
Are you crazy?
How can you talk nonsense after a meal?
Hee Ja has always been strange.
Even when she was young,
she was always a little different.
It's not dementia. That's just her.
Jeong A.
- Seong Jae says...
-  What does he know?
I know Hee Ja the best. Me.
How long did he see her for?
Jeong A. He keeps looking at me every day.
Close the curtains.
Just don't open the curtains.
You're so sensitive.
Then what about the bulbs...
that broke when he winked?
Why did he knock on my door?
Do you have dementia?
What's wrong with you?
You said you'd meet me at the three way with the pollack.
- My goodness.
-  You forgot.
You're so out of it.
- Where's the pollack?
-  I was wondering why I had it.
What a mess. What happened?
What's the point of acting like you're organised?
It's all messy where you can't see it.
My stomach hurts so often.
I don't eat much, but I poop 3 to 4 times a day.
Why is that?
Sleep over tonight.
Okay.
Jeong A, why are you here and not at your own home?
Not again. Just go to sleep.
I saw her yesterday and the day before.
I see her every other day.
If she has dementia, then I do, too.
The doctor said...
it's delusion, not dementia.
it's dementia.
What stupid doctor said that?
She took medicine.
I reminded her to take it whenever I was there,
and she would take anything she found lying around.
She's old. So what if she forgets that...
we meant to meet up?
So what if she can't clean her kitchen?
What's wrong with that?
What should I do, Mum?
Poor Hee Ja.
What should we do?
You're wearing what I bought you.
I am.
What's wrong with you? Why did you want to die?
I can't even change a light bulb.
The doctor said I'm delusional.
If I end up with dementia,
Min Ho will get angry with me.
Then he'll get exhausted.
That's why.
You wanted to die with me.
What about me, then?
What about me?
You're a terrible friend.
You're right.
I have you, don't I?
What are you doing?
Church?
To give them the rosaries you made?
What will you do after that?
I want to see you, of course.
Watch out for the cars and be careful.
Go straight home instead of anywhere else.
I'll bring some tteokbokki. You like tteokbokki.
Okay. See you later.
She's going to church.
She goes there every Friday.
It's the evening trips I'm worried about.
She's fine during the day.
Let's go and see Min Ho.
Let's leave a bit later.
I'll wait outside.
(Hospital)
Then...
when can I have surgery?
You need it soon.
But my schedule's...
Hello?
What? Why are the onions rotten?
Throw them out.
Call the Jeju Brothers and ask them...
to bring some urgently.
Don't try to save anything. Throw everything out.
You'll just waste time.
I'm the boss, not you.
Basically, you're in the worst place possible.
It's not just the liver.
It has spread all over.
(Yeong Won)
If it's so urgent,
why must I wait three weeks?
He just wants me to die, not live.
But then again, I'm not his only patient.
(Wan)
What?
Mum.
Sorry.
"What?"
Is that all you can say right now?
I'll be there.
You know how busy this place gets at lunchtime.
I dropped by on my way to the publisher's.
I can't leave when everyone's so busy.
Where on earth are you?
What?
Shopping?
Take this.
Why did you go shopping?
Are you really dating someone?
Mum.
Where's our jjamppong?
It's coming.
Where's the jjamppong for table nine?
It's ready.
We had cotton candy
When I blew on it
It made a hole
That big blob of cotton candy
(Dear My Friends)
I saw it.
You have to be stronger than anyone.
Why do you keep calling me?
Answer me. Where are you right now?
Do you want me to tell Wan?
Or do you want to tell her?
Do you hate that I like your mum?
Well, there's nothing you can do about it...
because I like your mum...
a lot.
Who told you to bear it alone?
Why am I your baggage?
Of course. I'm doing well.
I'm so scared.
It's upsetting me.
I want to live. I do.