(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Basically, you're in the worst place possible.
It's not just the liver. It has spread all over.
(Yeong Won)
Darn it.
Nothing ever works out...
in my unlucky life.
Gosh.
(Forever Like a Mum and a Fighter, Part 2)
Jeong A.
What are you doing over here?
Gosh. I'm wearing two different shoes.
It's been too hectic. I didn't notice either.
Let's go to Min Ho.
Seong Jae will tell him.
Hee Ja isn't picking up.
I'll go wait at her place.
Don't worry, she comes straight home after church.
Don't bother. Let's just go inside.
Gosh. I want to swear.
Fine, I won't smoke. Happy?
Where can I smoke if not on the streets?
Hello. How are you?
It's okay. There's no need to greet each between us.
Sit down.
Where's Jeong A?
Hee Ja didn't pick up, so she's going to her house.
We should go, too.
I'll take my car...
It's okay. Leave your car here and come with us.
You shouldn't drive when you're emotional.
Go and get changed.
I just...
Sit down for a minute, Min Ho.
She was fine.
So I stopped checking.
But...
I should've known.
My wife's pregnant, so...
Stop.
Wipe your tears.
You have to be strong and think straight.
Get changed.
Okay.
This is the last stop.
Where is this?
The last stop.
I mean, which part of Seoul is this?
Can't he understand what I'm saying?
Why won't she pick up?
I want to know what the results are.
Goodness.
Are you leaving?
Yes. You did well today.
- I loved your acting.
-  Thank you.
- See you.
-  Bye.
I don't like her.
- How was I?
-  Amazing, of course.
What a joke. Are you the director?
She's good enough for her age.
She's pretty and young.
If she could act, too, what could I do for a living?
Leave the acting to me. She does okay for her age.
You're always so negative. That's not a good quality.
Hi, Dae Cheol.
Hi. Where are you?
I'm just about to leave.
Why are you rushing me?
We weren't in touch for over 30 years.
So what difference does 20 minutes make now?
Right, did you eat before you left?
I'm getting another call. I'll see you soon.
Bye.
Doctor Cho.
Thank you for taking the time to see my...
What?
Shall we go?
No, wait.
Go on.
I was looking forward to seeing you.
It can't be helped.
I wanted to see you off with a smile,
like I did once before.
I guess...
this is where it ends for us.
But still,
look after yourself.
Be happy with your wife.
And...
I'm glad...
I got to see you.
Yes, take care.
Look after your looks so that...
I'll recognise you if we meet again.
Okay?
Yes. I have to go to my friend now.
Bye.
Why do you keep calling me?
Where are you?
Tell me where you are!
This will be our last time, right?
I should've told her I got divorced.
Will you...
tell her...
after I'm dead and gone?
That I got divorced...
and loved her.
Only her.
Where's my key?
What are your eyeballs for?
Watch where you're going!
Where are you going? It's dinnertime.
I cooked olgaengi soup.
I said I was busy, but you wanted soup.
Where are you going?
He's helpless.
How do I know which road Hee Ja takes?
My goodness.
(Seong Jae)
Are you on your way?
Yes, I am.
But how would I know what route...
Hee Ja takes from our house to hers?
Take the road by Bisan Hill.
Jeong A says Hee Ja takes that road.
Okay. Wait, Seong Jae.
Are you sure she has dementia?
I was thinking. She's always been a bit weird.
You said she's normal,
but anyone would say she's dazed.
She always acted like she missed a few marbles.
(Seong Jae)
When did he hang up?
Okay.
Yes, thank you.
I'll come over, then. Bye.
Yes, it's me.
That thing I asked you to look into.
What?
Really? Can you help out?
Yes, you do that. Bye.
Yeong Won, Wan and Nan Hee won't pick up.
I called Nan Hee's restaurant.
The employee said Hee Ja didn't come by.
She was at church.
She left the rosaries at the office about 3 to 4 hours ago.
They didn't have a technician, so we couldn't see the CCTV.
When I checked with the police station,
they told me that there aren't any reports yet.
We should report her as a missing person.
She doesn't match the requirements.
I reported her as a missing person with dementia.
What do we do now?
Everyone should just stay here.
I'm going to visit the church.
I can't just sit around.
Sit back down.
He's already got it under control.
Let's just wait here.
Go to the market and the grocery store.
Your mum never goes to the market.
"The nursing home is your second home."
"If you must go, smile as you leave."
"If I get dementia,"
"always listen to Min Ho, Jeong A,"
"Choong Nam, Yeong Won..."
"and Nan Hee."
"Read it three times a day..."
"and memorise it."
Unless it's with you, Hee Ja would...
never go to the market.
She gets things delivered.
What's the point of staring at each other in the face?
We'll only be annoyed.
You're right.
I'm so upset that Hee Ja's head...
is so messy like this.
Don't talk.
Just clean.
Yes, Ha Neul.
It's okay. Her friends and her boyfriend is here.
The lawyer guy.
Yes. He's running around to sort it out.
Of course, I'm fine.
Ha Neul,
don't stress yourself. You should be careful.
I'm fine.
That's what you should do for Mum, okay?
I know.
Good girl.
Don't tell your mum. She'll be so shocked.
Don't cry.
Yes, I'm all right.
I'm trying to check if she went to the market.
I'll let you know if she comes back.
She's not here either?
Let's trying going on the route...
from Nan Hee's restaurant to Hee Ja's place.
What difference will that...
Anyway,
do you think you'll find her like this?
Yes.
Officer Kim.
I have a question.
Are you still working at the city's road traffic department?
One more bottle, please.
Okay. One more soju.
I should have never met you again.
I caught the cancer from you. You're evil.
When I was young,
I wanted to drink at wonderful bars...
like this while enjoying it.
It's all ruined.
It's messed up.
Where's my drink?
Doctor Cho called me.
He says he'll schedule your surgery two weeks faster.
He wants you...
to have the surgery in a week.
Why?
Did someone die in the meanwhile?
You have cancer.
You're the one who shouldn't drink.
I have at most 4 months if I don't get surgery.
Even if I get it, my chance of getting better is 20 percent.
I might die while they're opening me up.
Let's go.
Come on.
- Here.
-  Are you done?
She's an actress. She's my friend.
- You know her, right?
-  Yes.
Hey, give him your autograph.
Be generous.
Could I get your autograph?
- What's your name?
-  Yoo Jae Sang.
Tell your manager to go home. Let's go somewhere...
for another drink.
Let's sit here for a bit and then go home.
I can't drive.
You had one shot.
Are you scared of dying?
I think I'm struggling to live.
That's the same thing.
Do you want me to tell Wan?
Or do you want to tell her?
Do whatever you want.
It doesn't matter who tells her.
It's the same thing.
I'll do it then.
Your hands are still so beautiful.
It's not just my hands. My body is pretty hot.
Who cares?
No one is there to touch it.
We both have it bad.
It's really ruined.
My life's ruined.
I tried to live nobly as a good wife, a good mother...
and a good daughter.
I acted like I was strong.
This is such a shame.
If I knew this would happen...
We should have just slept with any and every guy.
Should we tell all the guys to line up? That we'll give ourselves?
Watch your mouth.
Even if we tell them,
no one would line up.
No way.
We're ruined.
Yeong Won.
When you got your first surgery...
No.
When you first heard the news,
how did you feel?
It was horrible.
Then was the second time horrific?
The third time was horrendous.
That's enough.
Look who's talking.
You little piece of...
Wan.
Where are you?
Why are you looking down?
Because I'm that frustrated.
She wouldn't have jumped.
She has that much sense in her.
Dementia...
doesn't come suddenly.
It progresses slowly.
My mother had dementia, remember?
Didn't your mother have it, too?
My mum died on the street.
There was no medication for it back then.
That's the first time you said something sensible.
Where are your manners?
Are you memorising the ten rules of a good husband?
What's the first one?
"A husband..."
"should not vent his frustration or anger from work..."
"on his family at home."
You're doing well.
Be good to Jeong A.
Look at Hee Ja.
One by one,
we'll all die.
Get in. Let's try another bridge.
Come on. Eat up.
No thanks.
It's cooked.
Don't waste food.
Did you...
tell your brothers?
Sort of.
So they wouldn't worry.
A sister-in-law has thyroid cancer.
I said I'd call back.
Drink up.
I'm fine. You have some.
I can't. I have to drive.
Okay.
Your mother...
will be fine. I guarantee you.
If something terrible had happened,
we'd have gotten a call.
That's what happens.
We haven't heard from anyone, so nothing bad has happened.
I like and care for your mother very much,
but we'll take time to eat.
We need the strength to protect her.
Does my liking your mother...
bother you that much?
Even if it does, it can't be helped.
I like your mother...
a lot, you know?
But even so,
we're just friends.
Best friends.
Okay.
Now, talk less and eat more.
Eat up. A man should be confident and strong.
Eat up and cheer up.
- Okay?
-  Okay.
Hello? Yes, hi.
Yes.
Okay.
I was killing time...
at a nearby police station.
Okay, I'll be right there.
Stop eating. We have to go.
- They found your mum.
-  What?
Can we pay quickly?
Pack this up. We'll come back for it.
Thanks.
Hello, Mr Lee.
Did you find my friend?
Yes. Have a look at this.
I traced the person you sent a photo of.
That's her.
Isn't that Hangang Bridge?
What is she carrying on her back?
That's it.
We got too close today.
How's the novel coming along?
It's the first draft, but I'm 70 percent done.
Why did you call me? You should be working.
You're just delaying your departure date.
You sound like an evil boyfriend...
who abuses his lover.
I need breaks, too. I'm not a machine.
Here's your prize.
Have this.
- Do you want to die?
-  I'll eat it then.
Here's your real prize.
What's that?
I'm holding myself up with my arms.
I can't use my legs yet.
But it's important to try.
I'm always scared of falling.
I hadn't tried this, but I started recently.
For you.
Get back to work.
I can leave on this day.
I'm waiting.
(Off to see Yeon Ha!)
My arms hurt.
Let's hang up.
Hang up.
What? Yeong Won?
Yeong Won, what brings you here?
Why did you visit me?
The doctor that Mum saw...
Can I see him right now?
Dr Cho. I'm really sorry,
but could you meet with me right now?
You're available?
Okay, where should I go?
Okay. There?
Okay.
Your mum already knows.
She should know since it's her body.
You said earlier that...
60 to 70 percent of these people don't get surgery,
and the recovery rate with surgery is less than 20 percent...
Personally, I believe that they should get surgery...
if there's even a slightest chance.
20 percent is still a possibility.
That's what I wanted to hear. It's possible.
Thank you, Doctor.
I'm going to go.
Wan, I'll tell your grandmother.
Yes, Choong Nam.
Why didn't you pick up?
I know you are annoyed with us,
but we called because we can't get through to your mum.
Wan.
Hee Ja has dementia...
and she disappeared.
So tell your mum...
Choong Nam.
I can't tell my mum that right now.
So don't try calling her either.
She has cancer.
What is it?
What did Wan say?
Don't talk to me right now.
I'm dizzy.
What is this?
(Jeju Vegetable Store)
Jeju Vegetable Store?
Sorry to call you so late.
I don't think I can...
go to your store for a while.
I need your onions.
Can you prepare them for my restaurant and...
Hey.
My mum needs to get surgery.
I need you to look after the restaurant for a while.
I know it's busy. Hire someone.
Can you also call the chefs today...
and tell them that Mum's going to the hospital...
No, don't hire anyone.
Jeju Vegetable Store will have ingredients ready for you.
It's none of your business what I have.
All you have to do is listen to me.
It's not because of money that I don't want to hire.
If it was about the money, I wouldn't use expensive ingredients.
I'd tell you to prepare the onions yourself.
What will we do if the new person hurts themselves?
Then what? Are you going to be responsible?
Don't you remember what happened last time?
Just do as I say.
I know the inspection is next week.
But I can't do it next week due to personal reasons.
Could you come tomorrow to do it?
There's too much frost in the freezer...
and it freezes the stuff in the fridge.
How can I cook with that?
You'll come tomorrow, right?
Really?
You should have agreed earlier. Goodnight.
Stop with the phone calls.
You made over 10 calls.
Who will take care of the restaurant if not me?
Pal Dal and Sang Sook will.
What do they know? They only serve tables.
Do you think running a business is easy?
Why isn't Sang Sook picking up?
She must be sleeping. It's 1am.
Gosh, why does time go by so fast?
Bring me my clothes.
I'm already on it.
You should've gotten it for me before I asked.
Don't you know what I need?
You never pay attention to what I do.
I don't like it. I really don't. I don't like anything about her.
What will you do when I'm dead?
You'll cry at my grave and regret what you've done.
Don't you dare do that.
On top of that, you're old.
Other kids your age have two babies already.
They take care of their parents and also their husband.
Where are my clothes?
Do you need all day to pick out clothes?
You could just give me this. This one.
I really don't like it.
(Insured Jang Nan Hee)
(Jang Nan Hee)
Mum.
We don't want other people to see my account password.
Take it and put it somewhere safe.
I'll write down the numbers of my insurance representatives.
Make sure you get the most out of them if something happens.
Don't let them take advantage of you.
- Mum.
-  It's just in case.
It'd be great if it doesn't happen, though.
I heard you already knew when you went to the hospital last week.
We talked every other day on the phone.
Why didn't you tell me?
Would it have changed anything?
What were you going to do alone without telling me?
I was always alone! When was I ever with someone?
Why aren't you yelling at me?
Why are you acting nice? Is it because I have cancer?
You always screamed when I screamed.
What if I told you?
And told Grandma? How would that help?
I'm straddled with you forever.
Will you suffer for me...
or be operated on for me?
What?
I'm burdened with you all forever!
I have a daughter,
both parents and a brother.
But I have to care for every one of them.
Even if I were to die tomorrow,
I have no one to rely on.
Even now, when I have a date set for my surgery,
I worry about leaving you.
What about my parents...
and your uncle?
I can't stop worrying.
Who said it's all on you?
What?
Who's your burden?
Why am I a burden?
I lived just fine.
I'm in my late-30s...
and you made me sound like a useless pack of luggage.
Are you happy?
Who said we're your burdens?
Who said that?
I cared for them.
Your grandparents and uncle.
I'm the one who kept them alive.
You're wrong.
They lived this long...
because that was their fate.
It wasn't about you.
If they weren't destined to live,
they'd have died even if you prayed for them not to.
Do you have to do this?
Must you...
make your only daughter...
feel like a miserable piece of nothing?
Do you feel better now?
Wan.
I try hard not to.
Have the operation and chemotherapy.
You'll be fine.
Your doctor...
He's the best in the world.
The drugs are great, too.
I'm so scared.
It's so unfair...
and I want to live so badly.
I'm so scared.
That evening,
my mother, my refuge, fell.
My mother, as powerful as the sea,
failed to hang on.
She cried like a child in front of...
her daughter whom she didn't trust.
I'm scared.
Mother.
Oh my goodness.
You look like you're about to cry.
What's gotten into you?
You didn't say a word all night.
Even after you woke up.
It's not a serious operation.
It is.
They're cutting her open.
She's very sick.
I know that much.
Why else would she let herself be cut open?
Mum.
Did you tell her?
No.
Don't. She'll find out.
What if she can't handle the shock?
Mum.
You have such grand handwriting.
Good for you.
I heard about Nan Hee.
Poor you.
Hee Ja has dementia.
Poor us.
Come and eat.
Jeong A, have some nurungji.
No thanks.
It's just the beginning.
Old people have to eat.
Have you given up on life?
Do you all want to die together?
Don't give in.
I can't handle it alone.
Nan Hee...
Take some soy sauce.
You should eat.
Yes.
I'm not afraid...
of dying at all.
I'll get to see...
my husband, my eldest and the people I've missed.
This is the last...
we saw of her, on the outskirts of Seoul.
She's headed towards Misari.
Where could she be going?
We will...
call the Gyeonggi-do Police,
but it'll take some time to locate her.
Min Ho.
He needs some air.
When were you...
the happiest?
When I had my eldest son.
Then when were you the saddest?
When my eldest died.
It was just a fever.
We were living near my husband's home town.
He was on a business trip,
so I carried our son to the hospital.
What is she carrying on her back?
I carried our son all the way to the hospital,
but...
he was dead.
I carried my dead son...
along a road lined with trees.
I walked...
and walked...
and walked.
She walked and walked.
Along a road lined with trees.
Hee Ja's husband's home town...
Jeong A, where was Hee Ja's husband from?
North Korea.
Was it Hamgyeong-do?
51 Yangoh-ri, Yangri-myeon, Gyeonggi-do.
North Korea is where...
her in-laws were from.
My first factory job was there.
My factory...
Was near the mountain at Yangri-myeon.
Hee Ja lived with her parents there for 2 to 3 years.
That's when Jeong A took my parents to Seoul...
and lived here.
I stayed at the factory's residency...
for about three months. Do you remember that?
I told you that I went to visit Hee Ja's a few times.
Seok Gyun, let's go.
Let's try going there.
I have a good feeling about this.
- What is it?
-  What are you thinking?
I have great memory.
I know the place like the back of my hand...
because they worked me like a dog.
Min Ho, you should stay home.
Don't go anywhere and stay here.
Make sure to hold onto her if she comes back.
Seong Jae must have an idea.
- I'll call you.
-  Can I come...
Ha Neul might give birth any day now.
You should stay just in case.
Wake up and focus.
- Call me.
-  Okay.
Don't forget.
It's past Misari.
Do you know where Buim Intersection is?
You have to turn left there.
Okay, I'll turn left there.
You should turn right.
We'll go in a circle to go around.
What did you say?
The neighbourhood is split between the high and low areas.
What?
The neighbourhood is split...
What is she saying?
You take the higher region.
Let's just turn right.
Why are you saying that now? I'm old, too.
You should have said that before I tired myself out.
It doesn't hurt.
Really?
How can I eat when I'm sick?
I'm glad.
Maybe it's not cancer.
Do you think so?
I think so, too.
It doesn't feel like cancer.
Let's go on a trip.
A trip at this point?
What else would you do?
Are you going to work?
Can't you talk nicely?
That's how Jang Nan Hee's daughter, Park Wan, talks.
I'll just laugh it off. Where should we go?
Wherever our feet take us.
All right, let's do it.
I don't think I can smile at my customers.
Should we cash out? All of it.
We can stay at an expensive hotel. Just you and me.
A cheap hotel will do.
Do you...
even like your mum?
Other kids cry when they hear about their sick mum.
Why aren't you sad when I have cancer?
I look heartless, right?
Just eat your food.
Gosh.
What are you thinking?
I'm wondering what you're thinking.
That's the first time we ever thought the same thing.
Think of something that makes you feel good.
I'm trying to.
You said you're seeing a man, right?
Think of him. Maybe it'll make you feel better.
Shut your mouth.
Everything you say is useless.
I'm between life and death right now.
If I think of a man right now, I must be out of my mind.
You're crazy.
Mum. Let's be friends instead of being a mum and a daughter.
How do we do that?
We can just talk about anything.
Do you like me or him?
What?
- Did you sleep with him?
-  What?
I guess you didn't.
Since you slept with me and not him,
I'll assume that you like me more. Am I right?
Pull over.
I'm going to rip off that mouth of yours.
Stop the car.
My sweet Nan Hee is so beautiful when she's mad.
Are you crazy? Just drive! You'll get into an accident.
How can a daughter ask her mum if she has slept with a man?
I can't believe I have a daughter like you.
I'm not your daughter. I'm your friend.
Don't you talk about this with Yeong Won and Choong Nam?
- I know you do.
-  Stop it.
You leave me speechless.
How can a daughter ask her mum if she has slept with a man?
It's nice.
Don't act so innocent.
I think it's around here.
I think it was nearby these trees.
Hee Ja told me to come over when she lived here.
I never did.
We have a car now, but we didn't back then.
When I was here,
you and I couldn't see each other for three months.
I didn't get to see Hee Ja for two years then.
It's a beautiful road.
It sure is. It's nice.
I don't think I came through this way.
What's that?
What?
What is it?
Seong Jae, I'll go.
You should call Min Ho.
Where are you going?
- Why are you here?
-  Hee Ja.
You...
Hee Ja. Hee Ja.
- Hee Ja.
-  Why are you here?
Hee Ja.
I hate you. How dare you come here?
- How dare you?
-  Hee Ja.
- It's me, Jeong A.
-  Stop.
I hope you die!
- Hee Ja. Hee Ja.
-  What's wrong?
You wretch.
Hee Ja.
Hee Ja, wake up.
I called you.
I asked you to help me with my sick son.
I told you his fever won't go down even with the medication.
I asked you to help. I was scared.
Why is everything always so hard for you?
You're never there when I need you the most.
I couldn't reach my husband.
Do you know how scared I was all night?
When I finally called you, you said,
"It's hard for me as it is! Stop whining!"
And then you hung up.
You were all I had.
Why were you always having a hard time?
You're always struggling.
I could never call and tell you how I was doing.
Bring my son back. Bring him back, you witch.
You're a witch. You aren't even a friend!
Hee Ja.
I'm sorry.
We all wronged you.
We're sorry.
I hate you all.
My son...
died on my back.
My son died on my back...
Please stop, Hee Ja.
My baby...
I thought you were going to bury me somewhere.
Wait here.
What lovely service.
This is just the beginning.
Let's go.
- Give me that.
-  No.
I'm not in pain. You can carry things for me when I'm weak.
What do we do now to kill time?
We look at each other.
What?
Sing a song.
You used to sing a lot when you were little.
I'm sober.
Ta-da.
Are you crazy?
I brought it from home.
It's all for you.
I see. You aren't allowed to drink,
so you'll feed me?
Okay.
Will you look at that go down?
What shall we sing?
That song.
This one.
Oh, your favourite?
(The Name tag of Love)
Stick a name tag on my heart
Seal it with your love
Tell me you'll love me until the end of the world
Stake your claim on me
Love is like a glass ball that easily breaks
Love hurts
I gave you my affection, my heart and my love
We can no longer live like strangers
I love only you
So put your name tag on me
Stick a name tag on my heart
Seal it with your love
Tell me you'll love me until the end of the world
Stake your claim on me
Don't regret losing me once I'm gone
Love hurts
Wait here. Don't go anywhere.
You got your senses back.
I'll come by tomorrow.
She's fine. She's just embarrassed.
Go home. Come back tomorrow.
Stay with us.
You're old, too.
You don't have the energy to go all the way home and back.
You're right.
Seong Jae, I'll spend the night at Jeong A's.
You didn't even smile at me.
Where's your wife?
Eating chicken with her mum, I guess.
I will get help.
So go home.
I'm going to live here.
No. Why would you live with me?
You're married. Live with your wife.
The doctor said that...
delusional disorder isn't dementia.
I just need to take my pills.
Right.
Don't forget to do that now.
I won't.
I'll get dementia if I don't take my pills.
I forget to take it sometimes, that's why.
I'll see a doctor tomorrow.
You can go home.
Let's live separately like we do now.
Mum.
Shall we watch a movie?
I'm sleepy.
Let's sleep, then.
I'm sleepy, too.
Mum. Mum.
- Gosh.
-  Mum.
- What's wrong with you?
You only had one bottle. Why are you drunk?
Where did you learn this?
From a guy.
Go and pee.
I don't have to go any more.
Kiss me.
Go and throw up to get sober.
Are you scared that I'll be a bad drunk?
Stand up straight.
I'm not drunk.
Can you clean up the table? I'll go pee.
She's stupid and crazy.
What was that?
What was what?
I didn't hear anything.
Mum.
Can you sing me that song?
"Old Poet's Song".
Are you asking me to sing while you pee?
You're my daughter, but you're so weird.
I have cancer, come on.
Sing it for me.
A small leaf
Falls from
A dry branch
Even if you were
A tree
When I heard about Mum's cancer from Yeong Won,
I finally saw how selfish I am.
Instead of worrying about her,
I worried about myself...
and what I should do...
with Yeon Ha.
If you don't come,
I'll kill you.
All I worried about was myself.
What I'm saying is,
Jang Nan Hee's daughter, Park Wan...
No.
Every child in this world...
doesn't have the right to shed a tear.
We're all shamelessly selfish.