(The following content may not be suitable for viewers under 15.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
Did you break up with Dong Jin?
We didn't have to break up.
Why did you date Dong Jin when you left Yeon Ha?
Mum.
I'm here to interview you.
What?
Your wish was...
for me to write a novel...
about you and your friends.
So I'm here to interview you.
Why did you break up with Yeon Ha?
Did you like him?
Did you date him?
Where should we begin?
When you were born?
Or around your earliest memories?
Should we start there?
You dated him, didn't you?
I'm pretty sure you did.
Why did you break up?
Did he cheat on you?
Like Dong Jin did?
He's disabled.
You told me not to marry a disabled man.
So we broke up.
No, I pretty much threw him away.
I'm that obedient.
Shall we begin the interview?
How about this?
Your story should begin...
when we visited Grandma when I was six.
Let's start there.
Don't you remember?
I remember it so clearly.
Mum.
Why did you try to kill me?
Don't you remember? In the field.
What field?
What...
No... Have you lost your mind?
What nonsense are you talking about?
Did you really not date Dong Jin?
Then why did he kiss you?
Why did you hug?
No woman in her right mind would hug a married man.
Don't you dare like to me.
- That was a mistake. - A mistake?
That's an excuse.
Were you obedient?
Were you so obedient that you...
decided to play the other woman?
What a joke.
I'll wait.
I mean less to you than dog poop on the street!
How could you when you know what your dad did to me!
What? It was a mistake?
How dare you say such a thing?
Welcome.
- Hey. - Yes?
Clean the tables inside.
- We have new customers. - Okay.
- A tangsuyuk and three jjamppongs? - Yes.
How dare she stiffen her neck at me?
I'm her mother.
Where did she learn to give me a look like that?
I shouldn't be so lenient with her.
- That's hot. - Gosh.
Put ice on it.
We have a group of 30 coming in tonight.
Give them a lot of free dishes. I'm going home.
I told you I'd fry them.
- We're on our own tonight. - It's going to be crazy.
Work if you have time to chat.
Goodness.
That's tasty.
"Ma'am, it's Dong Jin."
"It's a misunderstanding. Wan and I are not what you think."
"We're not..."
What a lie.
Can't he make up his mind?
He's going to leave for United States with his wife soon.
I should just kick him again.
Do you sell these in single bags?
I just want one bag.
I just asked you a question.
Do you or do you not?
We only sell them in packages...
Why are you rude to me?
You were rude to her first.
I'm sorry.
Goodness. It's just a little bit further.
Jeong A.
Why did you tag along? Just go to church.
She's so annoying.
Jeong A.
(Dear My Friends, Isn't Life So Beautiful?)
Here.
Oh, my.
There will be ghosts here.
It has a good view.
Of course. We walked up the mountain for 30 minutes.
You're too old to walk up.
Come on. It'll be good exercise.
The bus comes up this way.
The water pressure is good.
No, don't get this place.
It's further from me than my kids in the Philippines.
I could ride on cars and planes to get there,
but here...
You asked me to find a place in your neighbourhood.
That's why I'm looking at this place.
Also, the Philippines is further than here.
Why do you only look at the bad things? I like it here.
I can't allow you to get this place.
Sir, can you show us somewhere else?
What?
Wait, I have to put my shoes on.
No, not this place either.
This is a really good deal for 50,000 dollars.
If it's that good, you should live here. I'll pass.
You're not living here. Where are you going?
Just live with me.
Go home and stop getting in my way.
Gosh.
I can't show you any more! That's all I have!
Goodness...
This looks tasteful.
I used to live in a place like this when I got married.
But you're not a mole. A basement house?
Will it be too dark?
You need sunlight when you're old.
You'll get osteoporosis and depression.
That's true, I need some sun...
What is it?
Pollack soup. Put in a lot of pepper powder.
Sir. Can you help me?
Here.
Not this one. That small one.
What's that?
Toilet paper.
What is this?
Bricks for decoration.
I hope you get hit by lightning.
What did Seok Gyun say?
He wants pollack soup.
What's all this noise? Go away.
I haven't been yelled at in a while.
You had a peaceful life.
Where are you going?
To buy pollack.
When are you going to get the divorce?
After I get a place.
Don't make him the soup or don't get a divorce.
You're so strange.
You should talk to him before moving out.
You'll shock him if you do this so suddenly.
Let him get a shock.
It won't change anything even if I do. It'll just be noisy.
Did you tell the kids? They'll get shocked, too.
I liked the first house.
You should go. I'm going to take a look at it again.
I'll wait for you at the three-way with the pollack.
I think you could see Han River.
Mum, why did you try to kill me?
Choong Nam.
Hey, Joo Yeong. Where's your aunt?
Professor Yang, you're really making masterpieces these days.
There are a million stories for each photograph.
I would buy all of it if I had the money.
Do you want to sell it to me for half the price?
Stop it. Poverty is what made me who I am today.
Poverty for an artist isn't a flaw.
I agree. People don't have such a philosophy any more.
All they care about is money.
These pictures are really great.
If I had bidders,
I would have bought that vase from you.
It's Nan Hee.
If it isn't about life or death, tell her to call later.
She says you should call back unless it's about life or death.
Her young professor friends are over.
I guess she's less interested in her old friends.
Hey!
It's not about life or death,
but tell her that old friends are important, too.
(Yeong Won)
Hey, Nan Hee.
Buy me a drink.
I can't, I'm shooting.
Can we drink tomorrow?
Ma'am. Over there...
I'm not off every day. Go back to work then.
Why is she doing laundry? She should go home.
Yeon Ha was perfect.
Where did she go? She said she would wait here.
Did she buy the pollack or not?
You look like garden cosmos.
Where did you come from?
Where is your mum?
Come here, come here.
Try and catch me.
Where are you going?
How are you going to wait for me here?
I'll be shooting until late.
Get up and wait in the car. Come on.
No, it's too stuffy.
Come on.
Ma'am, we're shooting!
Coming.
Go to the car.
Gosh, you're so stubborn.
Don't you know it's annoying to be an old, stubborn person?
- Hey. - Yes.
- Get her a chair and a drink, okay? - Okay.
Gosh.
Where are you?
I'm off to see Mum.
Why go there when you know I'm waiting for you?
I go wherever I want to regardless of where you are.
Do I need your permission to see my mum?
Since when did you care about me?
Seong Jae?
Jeong A.
Is Hee Ja out?
No, but she won't let me in.
What's wrong with her?
She can't keep a visitor waiting.
- Why are you here? - Why do you think?
You said you'd buy frozen pollack and wait at the three-way.
Oh dear.
"Oh dear"? You let your mind wander.
- Where's the fish? - I bought that.
Here.
On the way back,
I noticed some flowers by the road.
Then I saw a lost little puppy.
It was this big. I followed it and ended up at home.
I couldn't remember why I'd bought the fish.
Do you know how scary it is when someone disappears?
Why didn't you answer your phone?
Is the battery flat?
Keep a spare battery and your mind on you.
Who am I?
Jeong A.
You're fine now.
Why didn't you let Seong Jae in?
Choong Nam.
Bye, Seong Jae.
See you soon.
Wake up.
Go home.
Why did you do that?
Why film me?
Point it at the door to see if a stranger comes in.
Take these and put the rosaries in a bag.
The priest sent me.
I didn't feel comfortable coming here,
but our priest told me to check on you...
and collect the rosaries you made.
Apparently, some old people sell them and keep the money.
I have to bring them.
Are there 100?
- I'll count them. - Don't bother.
You don't have to.
It's fine.
Do you like...
not smiling...
and saying the bare minimum as if we're strangers?
If I were to leave,
would that make you feel better?
I'd feel less uncomfortable.
Did I ask you to move in?
Let's have fun. Not as a date.
As friends.
Rather than stay indoors all day,
wouldn't it be nice to join me for a drive?
And enjoy the sun?
Jeong A can drive, too.
We go out for a drive sometimes.
You always have the last word.
I give up.
Wait.
Did I give Jeong A the fish?
I'm starving.
Thanks.
This old man...
He's her friend.
And Jeong A's there.
It's for the better. Seeing her alone upset you.
Now, you just have to worry when the door doesn't open...
for a whole day.
Who comes first?
Me or your mum?
You, then Mum.
And when our baby's here?
You, Mum and the baby.
I'll kill you if you put the baby before me.
That will only spoil the kid.
My mum said so.
You mentioned her again!
- Won't you eat? - No.
It's beef.
Have some.
It's sirloin. It's nice and tender.
What a jerk.
Where are his manners?
I have to go to the market early!
Eat and let me do the dishes.
What a fool.
Chew slowly and carefully.
You don't want to choke.
Cough harder.
You have a working toilet at home.
At least something still works.
Do you think I'm not man enough?
It was a concern.
You could ruin a woman's life.
Not so long ago, you couldn't even move.
You only started walking...
2, 3 years ago after spending 7 years in bed.
Jacqueline might not like you.
What if you spend 20,000 on her and she runs away?
Isn't that what happened to one of your neighbours?
You can't buy a woman's love.
Jacqueline likes me, too.
I may be disabled, but I farm,
chop wood and plow fields!
What? Can't a disabled man fall in love?
In Bong.
He's disabled.
You told me not to marry a disabled man.
So we broke up.
No, I pretty much threw him away.
I'm that obedient.
In Bong.
You can't communicate with Jacqueline.
Don't give me the money, then.
Just stop saying stupid things.
I make a fortune.
Do you think it's about that?
You'll have children to raise.
Mum and I have a lot of concerns.
You aren't well.
In Bong!
Mum.
I'm a super star.
If it's about 20,000 dollars, you should have just called.
Why would you come all the way here?
You must have transferred at least three times.
Well, you have to use your money for cancer.
Come on.
I have enough.
Also, why didn't you ask Nan Hee?
She's a boss.
Does she not give you money?
She does, but I need more.
When In Bong fell from that telegraph pole,
she worked so hard to save him.
He had 12 surgeries up to 2 years ago.
She spent more than 100 grand.
She even made herbal medicine for us every season.
On top of that, her dad goes to the emergency every now and then.
What's the point of being a boss?
We're wasting her money away.
And I can't seem to die.
Why would you die?
We're not her mum, dad or brother.
We're ghosts who steal her money.
When I die, cremate me.
You can sell our burial grounds and keep the money.
Lend me your money.
Don't tell Nan Hee.
Once she gets nephews or nieces,
Nan Hee will be responsible for them, too.
That crazy fool.
All he can think about is that girl.
He's crazy.
Oh, Mum.
Why am I...
worried about money all my life?
Mum, take my car.
I have a driver.
Go.
Drive her home.
Where's the eye?
Good. The eye is the best part.
Sure. It's the best.
Why are you so nice?
I nagged at you to clean the fridge...
and now, you finally did.
I'm trying to be nice.
Why?
We don't have much time left.
You're finally getting mature.
Good thinking.
We won't live that long.
Let's be nice to each other.
That's the best for a couple.
Why aren't you eating?
To save you money.
Great. You can lose weight, too.
Yes.
Yes, I called.
Hold on.
Have this after you're done.
It's good for you.
I guess I'll live another 30 years.
Why are you asking me whom I'm with?
I'm with the professors, of course. Why do you ask?
What do you think I'm doing? We're having wine.
Great.
You're having wine with young men.
Hee Ja is making rosaries alone at home.
Hee Ja has you.
Do you still have feelings for Seong Jae?
What if I do?
You need to end it.
They like each other. It makes sense for you to give up.
Why?
Let Hee Ja hang out with Seong Jae.
I go out while taking care of my kids' places.
You also have your nephews while working at the cafe.
You even have friends to drink wine with.
But all Hee Ja does is watch television at home.
She talks to herself so that she doesn't lose it.
She must have been so bored...
to make 100 rosaries in four days. Even young people can't do that.
She has talent.
Won't you let her have him?
Are you upset because I'm asking you this?
You should meet Seong Jae...
in your next life.
He'll see her again in my next life.
Forget it. You should worry about your divorce.
Romance
For romance
- Welcome back. - Are you here?
Accounting book.
You have all the receipts.
This is for the burgers I had with Hee Ja last week.
Okay.
Come on.
Thank you for buying my work.
I'm sure it'll be worth a lot in time.
At the ceramics competition last month...
I know it won grand prize, but it's not that great.
I prefer the one you gave me as a gift last time.
You don't know how happy I am to have you as a friend.
A friend?
Be careful whom you call a friend.
For me, a friend...
is someone I can give up my lover to.
A lover?
I would've put up a fight had I been young.
I decided to give him to her, who's older than me.
Wow. If she's older than you, how old is she?
Can she even walk?
I'll pay for the taxi.
Bye, now.
It's me.
Your young friend, Choong Nam.
You cleaned the place spotless,
but your place is always dirty.
What's the occasion? You never do this.
What do you mean? I used to do this when I was young.
Don't you remember?
I used to clean my room and do the dishes since I was six.
I would even pick flowers so that you would smile.
I used to do anything that would please you.
It was after I grew up...
that I stopped doing it.
I miss those days.
How can you miss that?
I was so nervous all the time.
I was scared you'd leave me...
or try to give me drugs again.
Why do you keep talking nonsense since yesterday?
Leave. I don't want to see you. Also, Dong Jin...
Mum.
Don't get involved in my life again.
What if I do? What are you going to do?
What will you do if I do get involved?
How can you look at me like that...
for telling you to stop seeing Dong Jin?
Is it that important?
Why do you think I saw him?
Is that my fault, too?
Of course. It's your fault.
I wanted to be reckless.
Why do you think I broke up with Yeon Ha after living with him?
You lived with him?
I'm yours, so I can't do anything you won't allow me to do.
You don't like the disabled, right?
That's why I left him there when he got injured.
You had a stroke then, so I had a good excuse.
When I was six, in the field by Grandma's house,
when you poisoned me.
That's when I knew it.
I belong to Mum.
So...
even though I'm scared, if she tells me to drink,
I must drink it.
It's your fault that I left Yeon Ha.
I loved him more than anything,
and once I left him, my inner voice said,
"You cruel witch."
"Live however you want."
"Forget about your conscience."
"Waste your life away."
Say you're sorry.
Say you're sorry!
Why did you do it?
Am I yours? Just because you had me,
does it mean you can kill me?
Why did you do it?
Why am I yours? Tell me.
Tell me why you did it.
Why am I yours? Why am I yours?
Tell me! Why am I yours?
Tell me.
Of course, you are mine.
Let go. Let me go! Let go of me!
I hate it! I hate you so much!
I wanted to die and couldn't leave you behind.
How could I?
- Stop it! - Die! Die!
Die. Die!
Die! Just die!
Let go of me. I hate you!
Please stop it. You can hate me.
Now, I know everything.
You can hate me. I don't mind.
- Just don't do this. - Let go. Let me go.
Please don't do this, Wan.
Let me go!
Wan, please...
Wan! Wan!
Dad!
You're a coward, Wan.
Why did you bring up a 30-year-old story...
only to speak of it like a lunatic?
You understood your mum then as you do now.
So why do you blame her so much?
You're the reason...
I'm like this and broke up with Yeon Ha.
I'm like this because of you!
You're bleeding. Stop it, please.
I knew it then.
I'm sick of this.
I couldn't forgive myself for leaving Yeon Ha.
I wanted an excuse so that I didn't have to say I left him...
purely out of my own selfishness.
It was too hard to shoulder the blame.
So I wanted to blame another.
And the easiest and closest victim was my mum.
Stop doing this.
Let go of me!
Wan, stop.
I missed Yeon Ha so much.
Japchae with noodles?
That doesn't make sense.
Just have a bite.
You made way too much.
It's good.
I can't eat any more.
Give it to your son.
I don't do that.
It's best for everyone if we see less of each other.
They don't like me bringing food.
Then freeze it and send it.
I heard they don't like unwanted parcels.
Why?
In case their parents are inside it.
Did you make that up?
I understand.
Life for people their age is so tough.
It gives them headaches.
They regret it after their parents die.
And use guilt to call it even.
They're so cunning.
Seong Jae.
Bring your car over to Hee Ja's and take her somewhere.
What?
- What? - Didn't you hear me?
Then forget it.
What was that about?
I'm letting you have him.
Thank you, Choong Nam.
No thanks.
You were going to go travelling. Were you flirting?
That was just a split-second...
Wait.
I'm too old for that.
It's weird if people our age go on a date.
At our age, it's very possible...
that one of us could keel over and die mid-meal.
People our age can go travelling if they want to.
We could die of something at any moment.
What's so strange about going on a date?
What's wrong with a trip?
Burn the last of your embers before you fade away.
It's totally understandable.
Is it?
But you said you like him.
Not any more. He said he likes you.
I fell out of love for him that instant.
It's true.
You need to pack for your trip.
Let me see.
Take these.
They're facial masks.
Do you want to join us?
That would be even weirder than if...
the both of us ended up drowning in a saucer full of water.
Are you eloping?
In case of low blood sugar.
Take half this much.
What are these?
I'm incontinent.
- Adult diapers? - Move on.
We wore these as babies...
and again as old people.
Life really blows.
I need those.
Forget it. Tell Seong Jae that you need to pee every hour.
Tell him that's what girls do.
If he refuses to stop the car every hour,
call it quits and come home.
I still think I'll need those.
Even the gentlemanly Seong Jae will laugh at you.
"Hee Ja, I'll carry that for you."
Then he'll wonder why the bag is so light.
When you aren't around, he will open it up.
He'll be shocked if he saw half a bag full of diapers.
This is why I don't want to go anywhere.
Even for a short trip, I have to pack so much.
It's such a bother.
At least you can still walk. Think positively.
Do you always sleep out here?
I'm scared to sleep in my room.
Aren't you scared of sleeping alone?
I don't mind sleeping alone.
I'm just scared I'll die in my sleep.
The sooner the body's taken care of, the better.
A corpse smells.
It would be nice to have someone on standby at all times.
You silly thing.
You used to be so pretty.
You were so smart.
Sleep now.
Wasn't I pretty?
You still are. For a woman in her 70s,
you're the best-looking.
It's freezing. Goodness.
It's still freezing. What's wrong?
It's a beautiful day
I think that's too dark.
Liven it up a bit.
You need to hide the wrinkles on your neck.
Doesn't it feel nice to go on a trip with him?
It's nice to waste...
a day away.
With the scent of platanus beyond its shadows
I'm running with the dream of my youthful days
Seong Jae, close the roof.
Why? I like the breeze.
I don't like it. Close it.
Get some air.
Spring breeze is like a scent.
Just close it! Your hair-thickening powder is in my face!
- What? - It's all over the place.
Really? You're right.
I asked you to close it nicely.
I don't want to be like this either. I don't want to look senile.
But the hair-thickening powder started to fly away...
like flower petals.
Why is the powder flying away?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
All right.
We'll go where Ms Park tells us to.
Please drive slowly.
She's telling me to slow down.
Is there a curve up ahead?
Ms Park is so nice.
She has such a nice voice, too.
For the rest of my life
Underneath the grape vines
A beautiful lady
Wants to walk hand in hand
Filled with the fragrance of grapes
Food will be ready in five minutes.
I have to go work on something urgent.
The rice is ready. Eat before you go.
Wan.
What is this?
Mum. Give me my computer.
Okay.
That's great.
I was afraid you might not be able to make it.
Yes, it's next Monday.
You have to come for the memorial service.
Even my dad's cousin is coming.
You punk!
You don't have to fish every day!
You won't die if you miss a day!
Do you know why your life is so rough?
It's because you don't pay respects!
Why should I take it back?
Why should I? You punk!
I won't live that long anyway.
I'm going to do a huge ceremony...
for my mum, assuming it's my last one for her.
Last year was nothing.
That's not even a memorial service.
I was sick then.
I'm going to do it properly this year.
It's going to be huge.
Yes, bring your wife.
Bring your brother with you.
The more the merrier.
Why is he inviting so many people?
See you then.
He yells at me even if I get a little snack.
Why does her memorial service get more food than me?
She must be happy in her grave.
Yes. That would be good. You have to come!
Yes, Choong Nam.
I know.
- That's good. - All right.
- You're so nice. - Bye, now.
What should I do for you?
I'll do anything you ask.
Just don't die before me.
You have arrived at your destination.
Your GPS will now shut down.
I have to go to the washroom. Why are we everywhere?
Where are we now?
I only came to where...
Ms Park told me to.
I shouldn't trust her any more.
She would tell me to go this way then that way,
but she's making fun of me.
What a fox. She only has a good voice.
They say old people end up fighting with anyone...
including ghosts.
You're a lawyer. Why would you fight with a machine?
Hee Ja, can you hold it? Is it an emergency?
Hold on. Let me turn the car around.
Just go somewhere and do your business.
Go and look.
- Go away. - Okay.
I should have never left home.
I only have myself to blame.
I got it! Hee Ja! We came the right way!
We're not lost!
Gosh.
There are a lot more grass than there used to be.
Good. Ms Park was right.
She couldn't possibly lie with that voice.
I thought they would have built a bridge here by now.
It's still the same rock steps.
Hee Ja, we came here before.
We lied that we were going to church to our parents.
We kissed here for the first time.
We crossed over here.
After that, we followed the road and went to a little hut.
We should check it out. Let's go.
What time will it be when we go home after that?
Hey.
Take your shoes off.
It's slippery than it looks.
We'll go home, right?
Hold on. Should I piggyback you...
like the old days?
Get on me.
Take care of yourself.
Then give me this.
It's slippery.
Be careful.
The moment you slip,
you'll be long gone.
Be quiet.
Don't worry about me and worry about yourself.
Watch what you say.
Hey, don't you worry about me.
My lower body is really strong.
I could run over with my eyes closed.
I'll piggyback you like back then.
You're like feather,
so it wouldn't change much for me.
I wouldn't even know you're on my back.
You're so chatty like an old lady.
I should tap dance while I cross.
I'm going to tap dance.
That's refreshing.
You should come on your own.
I can't help you.
Be careful. You'll slip.
Hey, come over here.
Let's take a picture here.
- Hold on, let me take a breath. - All right.
- You'll take it, right? - I'm dizzy.
We need...
to leave an evidence.
Here we go.
- I'm dizzy. - Look. Look at the camera.
Look.
One here.
You have to keep turning.
That's the point of taking selfies.
- I'm so dizzy! - No, take it.
You'll regret it later.
I said, stop it.
That's enough.
- Look here. - Stop it.
Okay.
Wow.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Thank you.
Have a nice time with your wife.
I will.
- Goodbye, then. - Bye.
The owner's dead, but the house is the same.
Why are you chopping wood?
It'll get cold.
Did the owner tell you to?
Are we leaving after dinner?
We can't.
I drove for five hours just to get here.
I could cause an accident.
People our age shouldn't drive for too long at a time.
Hire a driver. That will do.
Who would come all the way here to get us?
Give me that.
Who's this?
Yeong Won, I'm in Jeongseon.
Can you come and get me?
Seong Jae brought me here and he won't drive me back.
He says he's too old to drive.
- Does that make sense? - It does.
Old people shouldn't drive for too long.
Spend the night with him.
It was all planned like that time years ago.
A man should plan ahead.
People who live without a plan,
that's just "que sera sera".
Warm this room first. I'll sleep in there.
There isn't enough firewood.
Do we sleep together?
The owner thinks we're married.
He only brought one set of bedding.
You should've said no.
It would look bad.
If we aren't married but travelling together,
we'll look like cheaters.
I won't sleep with you.
It's raining hard tonight
I'm sitting at a pier alone
No one will come for
It's raining, too?
This is great.
It is raining
In my glass
Tears fall with the falling raindrops
Your beautiful smile
Hee Ja, look at the rain.
Look.
That room is warm.
Go and sleep.
Look at the rain.
Why won't you answer?
You left the hospital after your accident,
and I flew over to see my mum.
But I'm still here, years later.
Why didn't you say anything for three years?
My mum had recovered,
and yet I didn't return.
I knew it all.
What did you know?
That...
you had left me.
Be honest.
I abandoned you.
I'm sorry. Very sorry.
Today, I finally found the courage to apologise.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
I miss you...
Here.
Keep your place this clean.
You don't have tea. Do you want some?
I'll be going.
Tea sounds nice.
Herb tea?
Herb tea.
I'm glad the Dong Jin incident was a misunderstanding.
You should just say you're sorry.
- About Yeon Ha... - It wasn't your fault.
I was selfish.
I was scared.
I saw you and Grandma suffer when it happened to In Bong.
Your uncle wants to get married.
He likes a girl.
That's good.
What happened with Yeon Ha...
wasn't because of you.
It wouldn't make sense.
I would never listen to you that well.
I lived with him without telling you.
I was just making an excuse. Don't take it to heart.
Also,
I'm sorry for not telling you.
It's better...
than having a virgin daughter your age.
I'm sure all mothers feel the same.
You should go.
Wan. You...
Why are you being awkward? We fight all the time.
Just go.
You should eat the crab while it's still fresh.
Bye.
Right, Jeong A is getting a divorce.
Isn't that funny?
If I miss him,
I should just go see him.
Right?
Hey, when is my deadline again?
The cover's delayed?
Could you extend my deadline for five days?
Taxi!
Hey! Taxi!
(Vacant)
Incheon International Airport, please.
(Dear My Friends)
Hey, should I start seeing someone?
Are you married?
This was how we ended up kissing.
She finally started her revenge.
It's probably only the start of Jeong A's revenge.
Soon Young! Jeong A!
What if he faints when he sees me?
I know.
You'd probably just leave like before.