(All characters, organizations, places, cases, and incidents...)
(in this drama are fictitious.)
(The train for Beomilsan is now approaching.)
Help! Help me!
Hey, watch out.
Who's the traitor here?
Ha Rang!
Hurry, please. Hurry up!
Who are you to tell me that I can't go in?
My baby...
- My baby... - Ma'am.
- My son... - You can't enter. Step back!
Don't you dare lay a finger on her! You jerks!
Please help my baby.
Please help my baby so that he can live. Please...
He's coming out.
Move aside.
- Move! - Move!
Wait! Where are you going?
Let go of me!
Where are you taking him?
Let go of me! Where are they going?
Ha Rang! Ha Rang!
My baby...
Ha Rang!
- Let go! - Ha Rang!
- Ha Rang! - My baby!
Let go!
Stop! My baby!
Where are you taking his body?
- Move! - My baby!
- Let go! - Move it!
- He's my baby! - Let go!
Let go!
My baby!
My baby...
We've taken care of most of it.
Yes, sir. I'll be sure to finish it off.
Sir.
A 19-year-old boy just died.
A boy!
Are you listening?
I...
have to live with dignity for my daughter.
I can't leave the world she'll be living in to be lawless.
If there is something I must do,
I will do it.
This isn't something you can act on your emotions.
I am going to act on my emotions!
And I'm going to see Seo Rin...
whenever I feel like it.
I'll file a lawsuit if I have to.
I...
will fight.
(TL Seoul Medical Center)
(Doctor Detective)
(Episode 2)
Hey.
I think the body was sent to the morgue.
But if they move it again without permission from the bereaved,
I won't let it slide.
Guard it closely.
And please have his mother hospitalized at another hospital.
Where are you going?
He had a chronic cough...
and loss of muscle strength in his legs.
He also had skin lesions.
What was it that made Ha Rang...
come running to the hospital?
It's me, Doh Joong Eun.
We have to perform an autopsy at all costs.
And please secure Ha Rang's records from the emergency room.
All right.
When will I get off today?
(Supply Room)
Where did everyone go?
Let's see...
(Safety First)
(Warehouse, Hanil SD)
It's a cement wall.
There's less than a 10 percent chance of it being properly wired.
It's fake.
(Beware of Falls)
(Emergency Measures)
(Notice Based on Article 41 of the Industrial Safety and Health Act)
(Warehouse, Hanil SD)
(Hanil SD Safety Training Logbook)
(Hanil SD Special Health Examination Results)
They have the same handwriting and forged signatures.
They're fake papers for inspections from the Ministry of Labor.
A company like this would try to cover up an accident for sure.
(Special Health Examination Results)
(Harmfulness of n-Hexane discovered. Substituted with IPA)
Excuse me, who are you?
This is a restricted area.
Oh, yes, well...
I was just...
checking...
to see if there was...
Oh, sir...
May I help you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I got thirsty, so I was looking for a water fountain.
I'm sorry. The door was open.
Excuse me.
Hey!
Please step this way.
You can have a drink here.
Oh, thank you.
(TL Seoul Medical Center)
Should I tell them to prepare your meal again?
Never mind.
Hello? Have you arrived?
Attention! Bow!
Don't worry.
All right.
I would like to express my condolences.
A moment of silence.
All right.
It wouldn't have been such an issue if he were four years older.
The press will rush in like crazy.
Now,
be prepared to work all-nighters for a week.
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I don't think so.
What if the both of us...
catch something fatal while working like this?
Hey, that doctor!
Give me her number, too!
Stop worrying and go to sleep.
(Main Operations Room)
(Report on Bui Station Screen Door Death Case)
There happened to be a malfunction in the surveillance camera?
- Yes, sir. - Some might suspect...
that we're trying to hide something.
It's nothing like that, sir.
Of course, not.
Mr. Moh, this was just...
a coincidence that happened at the wrong time.
Sir,
you can't show your anxiety from now on.
You have to show that you are confident...
in each word you speak and each gesture you make.
Do you understand?
Yes, sir.
- Yes, sir. - No.
Do you really understand?
I understand, sir.
Thank you.
I'd like to see the executives and Health and Safety Team in private.
(Bui S8)
(The Accident Was Caused by the Employee's Negligence)
What's that nonsense now?
The Bui Station screen door incident.
It's the first case we got...
where the victim is dead.
Half an hour ago,
the media said it was the victim's negligence,
saying it's unrelated to the safety systems.
He's the third worker that's died on the same subway route.
Understand? He's the third victim.
The big corporations, media, and police.
They only pretended to care right after these incidents.
But what did the police say after their long-term investigation?
Victim's negligence.
They blame it all on the victims.
We need to stop this, right?
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes, ma'am.
This has to stop, right?
- Yes, ma'am! - Yes, ma'am!
Examine and diagnose the victims if it is necessary.
And let's make sure these companies stop...
outsourcing dangerous jobs.
- The chemical team. - Yes, ma'am.
The analysis team.
- Yes, ma'am. - Yes, ma'am.
Where's Min Ki?
- He's still at the hospital. - Oh, okay.
All right. Let's get started, everyone.
- Yes, ma'am! - Hurry! Move it.
Breaking news.
According to the police, it seems highly likely that the victim...
of the screen door accident was drunk at the time of the accident.
Hence, many are speculating that the accident might have been...
caused by the victim's negligence.
This is from the security footage.
As you can see, the victim, Mr. Jung, is drinking something.
He puts it back into his backpack and starts walking.
The police stated that they found...
a plastic soju bottle among the victim's belongings.
Where are his belongings?
Where are Ha Rang's belongings?
Don't waste your time.
I just need to check something.
We've already checked and confirmed everything.
Please don't act emotionally like this.
You went through his belongings?
Ms. Doh, you cannot enter Chairman Choi's room.
Don't do anything rash, please.
Ms. Doh!
[VIU Ver] SBS E03 'Doctor Detective'
"The Screen Door Incident"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Chairman Choi)
(Caution, Tripping Hazard)
(Security Mode On)
(Domestic Call)
Did you order them to do it?
Did you tell them to fabricate evidence?
Don't react so emotionally.
Sir, how could you plant a soju bottle that he didn't have?
I won't let this slide...
(Huh Min Ki)
Hello?
Ms. Doh.
- Ms. Doh is okay. - Who are you?
Let me talk to her.
Put her on the phone if she's really okay.
Just because she was kicked out of the family...
doesn't mean a mere gatekeeping dog can bite her.
If you're this disrespectful to her,
people will assume you're on the same level as me...
when I'm the CEO of the company.
Mr. Kwon.
You'll ruin everything if you handle things emotionally.
Wait outside. I need to talk to her alone.
Get out.
Let me...
apologize to you on his behalf.
I'm sorry.
Did you ask if I ordered my guys to fabricate evidence?
Yes.
Joong Eun.
It's not like you don't know us.
Why are you asking such a question?
Because I know...
what you're capable of.
I know what you can do, based on my own experience.
Turn on the TV.
After drinking,
he walks through the turnstile...
without calling the station office.
In the security footage,
it looks like he just had 2 to 3 sips.
But judging from the amount of soju left in his backpack,
we think that he drank about half a bottle that day.
- The safety of... - Turn it off.
That kid drank.
Stay out of it,
or you'll get hurt.
Mind your own business.
Do you think I'm worried about you?
This is a threat, Joong Eun.
Seo Rin will cry if her mom gets hurt.
Choi Tae Young.
Why must you go so far as to use Seo Rin...
just to stop me?
What are you trying to hide?
Are you writing a novel or what? Stop it, please.
Just mind your own business.
Behave yourself and stay out of trouble.
Stay out of our sight,
and mind your own problems.
(VIP Ward)
Breaking news.
According to the police, it seems highly likely that the victim...
- of the screen door accident... - Ma'am.
was drunk at the time of the accident.
That is fake news.
- The accident might have been... - It's not true.
caused by the victim's negligence.
- After drinking, - I know it's not true.
he walks through the turnstile...
without calling the station office.
Then he walks into the station office...
and grabs the keys without asking for permission first.
The guy who died at the subway station was drunk.
- Seriously? My gosh. - Yes.
That's why he fell into the tracks?
May I see that for a second? I'm sorry.
Many are pointing out that the company...
should've followed the protocols on safety and employee management.
- Here you go. - Thank you.
I told you that we have to look into it more.
We don't know if he actually drank,
if it was an accident caused by a safety issue,
or if it happened because of an illness.
Forget it. Just put him on the phone.
Put him on the phone!
Darn it.
This is Gong Il Sun from UDC.
An expert must look into this case.
You'll only transfer disease-related cases to us?
Sir, we can't find out whether it was caused by an illness...
without the investigation rights...
Gosh.
(Flawed safety systems.)
(Possibility of exposure to toxic substances)
I made Mr. Suk work overnight.
To analyze the substances from Hanil SD.
This is a thesis on the cause of neural paralysis...
regarding laborer sanitation issues.
How did you know this was your seat?
Oh, my. Sorry.
He didn't drink alcohol.
I'm certain there was a water bottle inside his backpack too.
They're just thinking he drank soju because of the circumstances.
You brat. You never give me a chance to talk.
You'll start work here, right?
Your salary goes up annually, and you're a 2nd level official.
Let me warn you beforehand.
I can't guarantee you'll work less than 40 hours a week.
But instead, I'll make sure you get paid for overtime.
Your position will be a team leader...
It's an addiction.
What? Addicted to work? Me?
Ha Rang. I have a hunch.
Not only was there a lack of a safety system,
but he probably had a disease due to toxic substances.
Okay.
Then what's on your mind?
An organic solvent. There was a detergent he used often.
It's isopropyl alcohol. Ruled out.
That was an assumption.
It might be another type of detergent.
Okay. We need to rule out the fact that he drank first.
But how? The whole nation...
thinks he drank soju during work and got in an accident.
You can't even drink much. What did you drink for?
What? Are you saying you're a grown-up now?
He can't drink.
He was born with a lack of enzymes that can break down alcohol.
There's no way he would drink soju before going to work.
There's no way to prove that.
Ruled out.
TL Medical Center is probably keeping Ha Rang's blood.
His blood alcohol-level will be 0 percent.
That jerk Moh Sung Kuk will cover up everything.
Is this real?
"The chief of UDC..."
"shall carry out an epidemiological survey for substances or..."
"diseases that may threaten the people without hesitation."
"No one shall refuse or interrupt this process..."
"without a justifiable reason."
Is this real?
Of course, it's real.
Just like the prosecution's seize and search,
one day, I'll make it an important matter.
Well, I need to make a few amendments.
Bit by bit. Darn it, when will I get it done?
You need to find his belongings that the police took.
I'm certain there will be a water bottle among them.
For us to take action, we need proof that he had a disease.
Until two years ago, he received a medical checkup...
to check for the nephrotoxic substance, n-Hexane.
But this year, he didn't receive it. You take care of the rest.
(Medical Checkup Result)
(Harmfulness of n-Hexane discovered. Substituted with IPA)
We can't rule out the possibility of...
paraplegia due to a neurotoxic substance, so...
We need proof first.
Yes, Chief.
We'll investigate the cause thoroughly, sir.
Okay, thank you.
What about Huh Min Ki? Why isn't he coming?
Is he running late again?
- Yes? - Mr. Huh. Where are you?
I'm staking out in front of the police station.
You're just making an excuse for being late...
Look for the water bottle. You won't find it.
- I'll see you later. - Hey!
(List of Police Agency Teams)
This is Seo Jae Yeong of Crime Team 2.
I'm sorry.
I must've called the wrong number.
Seo Jae Yeong. Okay.
(Emergency Room Record, Jung Ha Rang)
This is Ha Rang's ER record.
Multiple skin lesions all over his body.
This isn't enough to determine what it is.
We must carry out an autopsy.
Ms. Doh.
I have the results.
We found a tiny bit of organic solvent.
Goodness, this isn't enough to prove he was poisoned.
It's going to be tough.
Of course.
He can't be poisoned just by being exposed at the warehouse.
There must be another way he got exposed.
I'm just checking whether it was there or not.
Okay, fine.
By the way, you can talk to me comfortably.
I'm younger than you.
Oh, I'll take my time.
(Safety First)
Ms. Doh.
(Evidence number 10, 11, 12, 13)
(Evidence number 14)
There's no water bottle.
They probably took it out. I'm certain.
Hey, do you know how difficult it was to take this case?
We don't even have proof.
How can we say they hid the evidence?
They really did hide it.
Hey, are you okay?
Yesterday, I was really...
Goodness.
You worried me sick.
I'm all right.
But what's your issue with that TL bodyguard?
It seemed like he knew you.
Is it a secret?
Wait. Let's talk about that next time.
What do you mean, they hid it?
I saw it with my own two eyes.
There was a water bottle inside his backpack.
My goodness.
Really? Did you take a picture?
If I did, it would already be on the news by now.
Are you sure? You really saw it?
I'm sure, I'm telling you. Wait.
Are you working with us now or is this a temporary thing?
What do you think? Of course, she's working with us.
Goodness. The police have fabricated evidence.
What can we do now?
Why...
do you think I was staking out?
I mean, there was a rookie officer at the police station...
named Seo Jae Yeong.
These type of guys are really determined...
and if we just make up an excuse and give him a slight nudge,
he'll talk about the water bottle.
But will he meet with us?
He won't.
That's why you have to go to the Police Hospital by 9am tomorrow...
and provide orthopedic treatment for outpatients.
It turns out he hurt his arm.
Since he's a cop, he'll go to the Police Hospital.
Finding out the schedule for outpatients...
is a piece of cake.
Hey, don't stare at him. He's showing off again.
That's because I'm really good.
They copied the medical records on the day of the accident.
The corpse is stored safely.
Did you get rid of all his blood and urine?
- Yes. - Then let's stick to the plan.
Call Hanil SD.
Yes, sir.
Yes, Chairman Choi.
Yes, don't worry.
If the public opinion keeps turning against us,
I will get rid of the metro.
We should cut off any risks.
Yes, sir.
Ms. Doh. I think TL has already pulled strings to stop the autopsy.
Ha Rang's mother isn't answering the phone either.
Can you please persuade her?
Okay, I will.
Ma'am.
I have something to tell you.
You can stop now.
You've done enough.
I should hold...
a funeral for my son now and send him off.
We must carry out an autopsy.
Ma'am.
Stop it.
We'll investigate a bit further.
If we can just do an autopsy...
I told you to stop!
I lost my child.
Just stop it already! Stop!
Do you even know how my son died?
But I'm sitting here...
eating when I'm hungry...
and sleeping when I get sleepy.
I've thought about dying hundreds of times.
Ma'am.
Just go.
(Soju)
Please don't say anything to my mom.
She'll just nag me more.
Ha Rang!
Ha Rang.
How did you die?
Do Young, why haven't I heard from you yet?
Did you have a fight?
There were a few people on the platform,
but no one saw the moment of the accident.
There is one person who might have witnessed it.
The yellow shirt. He's holding a camera.
Was the light on the camera flashing?
The light was on. It recorded something.
I have to find that young man.
Ms. Byun, please do me a favor.
I need you to find someone for me.
Listen to my voice.
(Recordings)
(Recorded Calls)
(Police Hospital)
Where do I get my medicine?
Go downstairs to the first floor and get it there.
Thank you.
Mr. Seo Jae Yeong?
This is just a simple survey.
It will be very helpful...
to the Occupational and Environmental Medicine Department...
and their research on officers with posttraumatic stress disorder.
(Where is the water bottle?)
Ta-da!
We're from the UDC.
I don't know what you're talking about.
You guys announced that he was drunk...
to close the case early.
I saw what was in his bag at the emergency room.
I saw he had a water bottle, and I even took pictures.
But I don't think this will end with mere criticism.
I know you're having issues with the prosecution.
I'll call the senior executives. You can talk with them.
Mr. Seo.
Put down your phone.
Hey!
Mr. Seo.
Any patient who comes to the ER has to have their blood tested.
Ha Rang's blood didn't have a drop of alcohol in it.
I'm sure the senior executives would have thought...
it had been disposed since it was at TL Medical Center.
But doctors and medical science...
are true to the rules and principles.
All right?
Wherever you go,
there will always be that one old-fashioned jerk...
who wants to go by the rules.
(TL Pathology Department, Kim Byung Hyun)
Hello, Byung Hyun? It's me.
Do you have Ha Rang's blood sample?
Please have it sent to the UDC...
as soon as the results come out.
Jae Yeong,
we have blood samples that can prove he wasn't drinking.
Then it must have been water that Ha Rang drank, right?
(Detective Kim In Seok)
Hey, you jerk.
Ha Rang was even younger than you.
You hid the evidence of that kid.
If this gets exposed, you'll have to take responsibility, you know.
Do you think they're going to help you out?
They'll ignore you.
Let's go.
You coward.
The chief's...
drawer.
(Exhibit 16)
I guess people make mistakes.
Sure.
We're all human, so we make mistakes and lie, too.
Have a good day.
I guess he's had too much fine dust in his system.
So, him being drunk has been completely ruled out...
and he was staggering due to exposure to an organic solvent?
It was n-Hexane. It's a neurotoxic substance...
which crippled 5 Thai workers 10 years ago.
I thought they stopped using it two years ago?
They're still using it illegally.
Even the slightest exposure to it every day...
can cause nerve damage, myasthenia,
and even blisters on your skin.
It's the same as Ha Rang's symptoms.
Okay. Let's continue on when you get here.
Yes, ma'am.
Did you see what I did?
There are only three things you need in this country to succeed.
The money, the style, and the talk.
From what I can tell,
you've got the talk.
The cleaning solution Ha Rang had...
is a harmless IPA.
It doesn't include n-Hexane.
That's just too bad
What Doh Joong Eun said...
was wrong
From now on,
I'm Doctor Detective.
Myasthenia in the leg.
Chronic cough.
Skin lesion.
This...
must be mercury poisoning!
Mercury...
But then again...
the mercury poisoning case of Mun Song Myeon...
that happened during the 1988 Seoul Olympics,
and now,
we have just finished the 2018 Pyeongchang Olympics.
- So why... - Hey!
Stop fooling around.
Focus on your work! Mercury, my foot!
I was working. Don't you see this?
I've been checking each pixel...
that my eyes could fall out.
Look.
They hid the water bottle...
and accused him of being drunk. Right?
That means it has something to do with it,
but I don't know what.
Mr. Huh.
Zoom in on this.
Where?
- Here? - Yes.
No, not there.
Here!
- Hey, it's a dual label. - Gosh.
- Let us in! - It is a dual label.
- You can't do that! - It was covering n-Hexane.
- The thing is though, - What do you want?
it's completely empty now.
I think they disposed of the whole thing.
I see. Thank you for your help, sir. All right.
We just need that container, then.
It can serve as firm evidence.
No, it can't. All of this is just circumstantial evidence.
There's no concrete evidence.
If they actually used n-Hexane, we just need to find solid evidence.
Darn it. Hey, show me that thing again.
Let's see.
This is...
Who recorded this?
Gosh.
[VIU Ver] SBS E04 'Doctor Detective'
"The Water Bottle"
-♥ Ruo Xi ♥-
(Soju)
Hello, ma'am. This is Doh Joong Eun.
The soju box... Are you the one that drank it?
What are you talking about?
Please answer my question. Did you drink the soju?
No, I can't drink.
Okay, thank you. I'll be in touch.
We have evidence.
(Soju)
(Global Inspection Agency That Leads Innovation)
(Safety First)
- Ms. Gong. - Yes.
- We got it. - Where is it?
- Really? Seriously? - Let me see.
This is the kind of firm evidence I was talking about.
It was found on the wooden chopsticks too.
Ms. Doh was right.
Seriously? n-Hexane?
- How did you know? - There was a half-empty soju box...
in the trash can at Ha Rang's place.
Once, I also saw him...
with a plastic soju bottle when I ran into him.
A soju box and a plastic soju bottle.
It's unlikely that he drank both.
He drank one,
and the other one had detergent inside.
But why was the detergent stored in a soju bottle?
I'm sure he knew it's against the law to use it.
Then what if the company puts the blame on Ha Rang?
They won't be able to because they switched the labels.
They're guilty of deliberately letting the employees use it.
Right, the label. Okay.
n-Hexane cleans well, you know.
Since Ha Rang was the youngest on the team,
I bet they gave him the stations where things break most often.
The strong detergent must've made...
his job easier because wiping just once would've been enough.
It was found on his utensils as well.
It means he ate it too.
That must've drastically increased the amount he was exposed to.
- Exactly. Mr. Ha. - Yes, ma'am.
Get the report and press release ready.
Got it.
Ms. Doh, I'd like you to join the UDC family starting today.
All right. Good job, everyone.
We can all get some rest now.
- Okay! - Great work.
Team Huh Leader Min Ki and a team member, Doh Joong Eun.
Exposure to n-Hexane...
can cause weakness of the limbs as well as skeletal muscle weakness.
Regarding the screen door accident which cost a worker his life,
experts are saying a comprehensive plan must be...
put in place to tackle occupational illnesses...
- and to revamp the safety system... - Well...
I have to say, things quieted down without too much trouble.
Well done.
This is about the site, you know.
I won't let my guard down, sir.
Why? Are you anxious?
Mr. Choi would probably know.
Well, about the past...
Oh, that.
You and I are the only ones that know about it.
I see.
You should get going now, Mr. Moh.
Yes, sir.
Bye.
There won't be any issues with the biotech complex, Father.
Make sure you wrap it up without a hitch.
I will.
I'll persuade Joong Eun and make sure...
she takes her hands off it.
All right.
Experts are saying a comprehensive plan must be...
put in place to tackle...
occupational illnesses and to revamp the safety system.
The Undiagnosed Disease Center found n-Hexane...
inside the plastic soju bottle,
n-Hexane.
(Search UDC)
(Undiagnosed Disease Center)
(Doh Joong Eun)
About that medical malpractice case...
The one involving Joong Eun.
Has the final verdict been made?
You see,
do you actually think you can persuade her?
Tae Young.
You can't fix people.
Have some tea.
We just worked hard. I didn't do anything wrong.
- Ms. Gong. - Yes?
Listen to Ha Rang's final words before he died.
His co-worker must've recorded the call.
Seriously?
That's the only thing people like us can do to survive.
We have to make this public.
Without this, no one will even be interested in this issue.
We must fight with science and data as our weapons.
You said we should change the system.
We can't change the system...
by measuring a substance and analyzing data.
Even if those jerks went over the maximum permitted amount...
of whatever substance they used,
do you think we can change anything by pointing that out?
No, we can't.
For us to make change happen,
we need public sentiment and support on our side.
Ha Rang is the third victim.
The cup noodles...
and the spoon in his backpack.
He was only 19.
Darn it.
The words that the 19-year-old guy left for us.
This is the truth.
Right, I guess I was too emotional.
Then let's take a reasonable approach.
I'm on board.
Me too.
Gosh.
Are we good now?
I don't even know anymore. You can send it to the media.
Don't mention the UDC though.
Whatever.
I'm definitely mentioning it.
We received a file containing a recording...
of the last phone conversation that Mr. Jeong,
the victim of the screen door accident,
had before his death.
Let's hear it right away.
Do Young, don't get angry and just hear me out.
The company...
won't change.
Hey, you're back.
They'll only change after a few people die.
If both of us...
die on the job,
will things change a little?
So just get out of the labor union.
The world won't change even if you keep protesting.
Let's just work hard.
(My friend, it wasn't your fault.)
That's the only thing people like us can do to survive.
Sir!
Ha Rang and I joined the company together.
He wanted to work hard and live a good life, but he died.
All he did was do what he was told.
Hence, we will no longer do as we're told.
Why? Because we don't want to die!
Don't touch me! Don't you dare lay a finger on me.
I'm human too, and I want to live.
I don't want to die!
I don't...
Why are you pushing her? You should be ashamed.
You jerks! How could you let a young kid just die like that?
(USB device connected)
(When will I become happy? My poor life)
Ma'am.
I knew about it roughly.
That my son...
wasn't working at an office.
That he was doing something tough.
He was a pretty quiet boy...
and didn't talk about himself often.
But once, he told me what was on his mind.
What are you doing? Why are you looking in my wallet?
Why?
Is there a picture of your girlfriend in there or something?
No, of course not.
- Mom. - What?
Can I quit work?
Why? Is it too tough?
Come on. There's no easy job in this world.
Still, there's no reason to do something so exhausting.
Son.
No matter how hard it is, you have to endure it.
You'll get used to it soon.
If you quit because it's too hard, you'll eventually quit again later.
Then you won't be able to do anything.
Okay.
What?
- Fine, I won't quit. - What?
- What? - All right.
- What? - Fine, I'll keep working.
I'll keep working. I'll really try my best.
- I'll work hard. - Really?
All right. I won't quit. Stop it.
Stop it, Mom!
Stop tickling me!
Why did I...
think of my debt at that moment?
When my son was in so much stress.
So...
I told him to just endure it and keep working.
I told him there was no easy job in this world...
and that he should try his best when he had the chance.
That he'd get used to it soon.
So...
I was the one who told him not to quit.
Me.
I was really crazy.
I lost my mind.
I didn't even know...
how hard his job was...
I was crazy.
I lost my mind.
Ma'am.
I can't agree to an autopsy.
After you left,
I thought it would be the right thing to do,
but I just can't agree to it.
Ms. Doh.
I'm sorry.
This is all my fault.
All I can think of is my dead son.
I heard they found the cause of his accident.
Isn't that enough?
I've never...
made him any nice food...
or bought him nice clothes.
He lived such a hard life and had to leave like that.
Just let me send him...
Please let me send him off in peace.
I'm begging you, Ms. Doh.
Okay, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
My son.
My baby, Ha Rang.
It's all my fault...
My son...
My son, Ha Rang...
Three years ago,
we saw another Ha Rang.
Yesterday afternoon at Line 2 Guui Station of Seoul Subway,
20-year-old Mr. Kim, who was repairing the screen door,
got stuck between the door and the train and died.
He risked his life to repair the screen door on his own...
and this 19-year-old man met his death alone.
(The late Mr. Kim)
He lived harder than anyone,
but being branded as a temporary worker for a subcontractor...
crushed the bright youth of this 19-year-old man...
and the lives of his family that he left behind.
He could barely eat a cup of noodles...
let alone a proper meal.
His last day was a few hours before his birthday.
If he was alive for seven more hours,
he would have been 20 years old.
But instead of congratulating him, we had to send our condolences.
We still remember that day from three years ago.
The screen door will open.
These doors were made for the safety of our citizens,
but became a door of death in reality.
The safety we enjoyed...
was actually guaranteed by someone else's life.
If the safety of everyone isn't guaranteed,
that means that no one is safe.
We learned that through Mr. Kim's accident.
It's not your fault.
You are right!
Not only are we outsourcing dangerous work, but in reality,
there's a saying that we're actually outsourcing death.
We want to tell all the laborers that passed away...
that it wasn't their fault.
We hope he knew that...
his death at the job site was never his fault.
(I want to live in a safe country where I won't die at work.)
We call him...
Mr. Kim of Guui Station.