(Entourage)
Are you sure it's here?
Well, this is the address I got.
Why do they want to meet here at this hour?
I don't know.
They're not picking up.
They told me to come to the basement of this building.
I want to go home.
By the way, I can't go in with you.
- You can go. - Come on, let's go.
No...
What is this?
- Gosh. - What is with this place?
Are we being sold off somewhere?
Is this a haunted house?
What if they steal our organs? Should we go?
Are you scared?
Don't be scared. You're not a kid.
Gosh.
What is going on? This is driving me crazy.
- I think this is the wrong place. - I think I hear something.
No, you go.
Gosh.
Cha Young Bin?
Welcome. It was hard to find your way, right?
- Sit down. - Okay.
Isn't it a surprise?
It looks like a worn-down house,
but there is a luxurious lounge in the basement.
This is our secret lounge.
We hang out like this all the time.
We have wine and champagne.
There are karaoke machines inside.
Also,
we even have bedrooms.
- Do you like it? - Sure.
If you sign with us, you can use the place freely.
You can bring people here.
No one will know what you do in here.
I was surprised. I didn't know such places existed.
That's what I mean.
I don't like him. He's the type of person I hate.
Really? Let's not sign with them then.
You care about what I think at this point in the game?
- Are you mad at me? - No.
I know Mr. Kim made a mistake, but...
He signed without discussing it with me.
You also made the decision without discussing it with me.
Well, that's...
Okay, I'll always tell you from now on. Happy?
Stop sulking.
Did you see the article on "War Terminator"?
They published that you're leaving the film.
No, Turtle told me not to read it.
He's worried I'd get hurt from the comments.
- I probably deserve it. - At least,
it doesn't say you left because of So Hee.
I thought Ms. Jo would do something, but she didn't.
- Isn't it weird? - A little.
Is she going to let it pass after taking the cancellation fee?
I wonder if Mr. Kim did something.
No way.
Let's go. Enough nonsense.
Hello.
What's wrong? Can't you get over it now?
Did you read the press release on Young Bin's dropping out?
You should be thankful we were civil.
Thank you.
You're so broad-minded unlike the rumours.
I'm still not in a good mood.
That's why I'm here to find you Young Bin's replacement.
Come here.
Their company will do it for sure.
The actor is very interested. It will work out.
How can I trust what you say?
You cancelled after signing the agreement.
It was a mistake. I'm sorry. I admit.
This is unexpected, though.
It shouldn't matter what happens since you no longer work with him.
You're strange.
I think it's this room. Come in.
We haven't decided yet.
What do you mean? You said you'd do it.
We need to think about it.
Since you're begging me,
I'm trying to think of it positively.
You're a smart guy.
Your talent was the main actor for a mini series.
It'd be good for him to step into film this time.
If we can get to work with Ms. Jo,
it doesn't matter what film it is. It's an honour.
We had a lot of heartache because of Young Bin.
We want an actor that's trustworthy.
That's great.
You two seem to get along, so you should work together.
This is so hard to eat.
Give it to me. Why are you crushing this expensive crab?
I'll help you.
- I heard you two worked together. - Yes.
You're not like Mr. Kim, are you?
We won't get along if you are.
Don't worry. We're completely different.
Mr. Kim yelled at me all the time when I worked for him.
He even came to our opening party and yelled at me.
I hate that.
He's so harsh to others but generous to himself.
Why isn't this opening up? It's so hard to break it.
Why aren't you eating? Do you want me to break it for you?
I'm eating.
I put some on your plate. Eat it.
Hello.
Hey, did you come to work already?
Hello. Are you back?
- What do you think of the office? - It's nice.
Did you meet with Kang Eun Sol? What did she say?
I didn't get a chance yet.
I'm about to meet her right away.
You have to hurry up and make her sign with us.
What are you doing?
This...
As you know, I just got divorced.
I've been so stressed ever since.
Doing puzzles makes me feel calmer.
I was in the middle of it. Can I continue?
Okay, sure.
Let's rush the contract. We have to make money.
That way, you can give them child support.
Right.
Eun Gab.
I'm so happy to be working for you.
Sure. Finish what you were doing.
- Thank you. - Sure.
Hey, Boss.
- Who is that? - An old friend of mine.
He's a manager that got kicked out by Ok Ja.
He's a good guy. It's just that he's too solemn.
- That's why I brought him. - Is that so?
Why are you looking at me like that?
Well, I feel like you've suddenly become nice.
Usually, if you found someone...
doing puzzles instead of working, you'd swear at them.
But you just told him to continue what he was doing.
Did you change after your breakup with Young Bin?
No, I didn't change. Do you need me to swear at you?
Also, don't bring up Young Bin's name for a while. Okay?
Then why did you bring Young Bin's plant?
This is expensive. Do you want me to throw it out?
Get back to work. Go.
Okay, Boss. Bye.
- Close the door. - Okay.
Is this the right way?
I think this lane is closed.
We're almost there. It's around here.
Did you text people to tell them it's your first reality show?
I sent it out. It's up on social media as well.
Today is like my birthday. Should we have champagne later?
As for birthdays, it's Young Bin's next week.
I know. I'm going to book a place. The three of us can split the bill.
Let's just have dinner with close friends.
I made too much noise this year.
Sure. I'll just buy you a gift.
By the way...
Nothing.
Why did you stop talking?
We always celebrated your birthday with Mr. Kim.
What do we do this time?
I don't know.
There you go.
Enjoy.
Here you go.
That's her. The legendary food truck lady.
She does catering for variety show shootings.
The show becomes a mega hit if it makes her laugh.
If it doesn't, the show becomes a flop.
- I've heard the story, too. - Are you sure?
That makes absolutely no sense.
- Yes, it does. - Yes, it does.
Why are you so upset?
- What's that thing you do? - That thing?
Yes, show us.
That's funny.
I can never get tired of that one.
Seo Jin is loving it.
Please laugh at my part.
Please.
The prank.
- There you are. - There he is.
It's a prank.
We got you.
I'm sorry, Joon.
The prank was actually on you, not Julien Kang.
Are you okay?
It's not that funny.
That was hilarious.
They got me real good.
How did you fall for that? And why did you get on your knees?
I was trying to be funny.
She's not laughing.
I'm doomed.
Don't you find that funny?
No, I don't.
"Cha Joon said he was fooled by Julien Kang's talented acting."
"He asks the viewers to stay tuned for the show..."
"as he will continue to show more of his funny side."
"Comments"
"Julien should've beaten up that Cha Joon guy."
(Comments)
"Cha Joon is so boring."
"I will remember him as the unfunny one."
"Boring."
"Who is he?"
"He should've got beaten up so people wouldn't recognize him."
It's four in the morning. What on earth are you doing up?
I'm doomed.
Look at all the mean comments.
Go to bed, Joon. They weren't all mean.
I saw some nice comments about you.
The fatigue is getting to me.
Don't worry too much.
We can do better on the next day of shooting.
- Bye. - I'm going to bed. You should, too.
Good morning, Sunshine.
What's wrong? Did you not get any sleep?
Of course not.
It hurts when I pee again.
Did your prostate thing get worse? Is it in a chronic stage now?
But I took good care of it. I even quit road cycling.
It's because of stress.
You look like you've aged a lot since last night.
What are you talking about?
You should go to the hospital.
No. I'll feel better after a sitz bath.
That's gross.
Gosh, it looks moulded.
That's disgusting.
Do you have any girl problems?
Not really.
Do you gamble?
- No. - What about drugs?
- I don't do drugs. - I've noticed that...
people are writing mean comments about you these days.
We can get rid of them all.
You should let them do that. Please do that.
I think actors are like wine.
I picture a vineyard in my head when I first look at their faces.
I wonder what kind of grapevines I should plant...
and how long I'll age the grapes after I harvest them.
I see.
I'll make you into the best kind of wine.
What I mean is that you'll be paid very well.
But I don't keep secrets between myself and the actors.
Can I take a look at your phone for a second?
- What? - What?
You're very handsome.
But...
your ears aren't your strongest forte.
Not to mention your jaws.
Let's do something about that.
- I'm against plastic surgery. - Why?
Actors these days get work done on their noses, ears, and jaws.
Our company is very well-connected with the hospitals.
We are very discreet about it. Oh, and one more thing.
How's your urinary system? I know a good hospital for that.
Where is that place?
One of our room-mates is in need of prostate treatment. Do share.
- What? - Stop it.
Let's have him undergo a procedure.
They do that now?
I feel exhausted. I need something sweet.
Was it that bad?
We can't find anyone we like. We should've stayed with Eun Gab.
Why is Joon taking so long in the bathroom? I'm hungry.
He's been in there forever doing a sitz bath.
This is hard.
This isn't looking good. It hurts even more now.
The pain won't go away.
Look at you. We're going to the hospital tomorrow.
- I'm fine. - You should go now.
Why don't you want to go? Aren't you a grown up?
You'll regret it if you don't go.
Your private part might fall off.
Please continue.
What's wrong?
You look like you just saw someone who doesn't belong in here.
Did you get an invitation?
I did apply for admission, but they didn't get back to me yet.
I came here to see all the executives of major agencies.
There has to be an evaluation,
but your agency is too small of a company.
I meet the standards.
I used to be a member here until not so long ago.
We all know the evaluation is just a formality.
We should still decide on the matter through an internal meeting.
Don't be like that.
Just last month, I was in here drinking tea with you.
Don't treat me like an outsider now.
Are you trying to leave me out?
Of course, we aren't.
What gives you the right to be here...
after starting an agency with someone else's money?
They'll get the wrong idea if you say it like that.
That money was my share and severance pay.
Which agency is Young Bin going to choose?
How should I know?
I'm sure he went to see everyone in this room, but nobody's talking.
They're very secretive.
Young Bin can look out for himself.
Look at you trying to be all nonchalant.
It's like seeing your divorced wife dating other men.
I have no idea what that feels like. I've never gotten a divorce.
Oh, you should know because you've done it once.
Watch it.
You little brat.
I heard everything worked out between you and Ms. Jo.
Did you have to crawl between her knees or something?
I did.
I got down on the ground.
Accept my application, will you? I'll be going now.
Why are you all so cautious of me? My agency is just getting started.
Are you scared of me?
I'll never lay a finger on my fellow executives' actors.
Don't worry about that. I'll manage it just fine.
The name of our agency is "Tiger's Den".
We're all tigers in our agency.
I'll eat you all up.
Goodbye.
Where is Mr. Han?
- Hey, Boss. - Did he go to that meeting?
He said he's going to a hospital for Lasik surgery.
- Lasik surgery? - Yes.
It's because he's always looking at puzzles.
Go find out which agencies Young Bin is making contact with.
Why?
Just do it.
Oh, Mr. Kim. Your family is in your room.
Okay. Got it.
- Honey, you're here early. - You wanted to have dinner, right?
Let's go eat something delicious.
I came a bit early to look around the place.
Do take a look. It's nice, isn't it?
- It's better than I thought. - I got a good deal on it.
Didn't that belong at your old office? It's withered.
Yes.
Yoo Bin. Take a look around my office with your mum.
Yoo Bin.
Aren't you going to say anything?
She's not in a good mood right now. She won't talk to me, either.
Why?
She broke up with her best friend.
Why did you do that?
You should make up with her tomorrow.
You heard what your dad said.
You should make peace with her. Don't wait until it's too late.
Are you intending on not talking to her for the rest of your life?
Answer me, Yoo Bin.
Why is she so stubborn?
Can you talk to her?
Why aren't you talking?
What are you doing?
Kim Eun Gab.
- Are you crying? - No.
What's wrong?
He's here. Come on out.
Why do we have to consult the pastor?
You said you didn't want to go to the hospital.
He'll be able to help us with his wisdom.
Gosh.
Thank you.
I heard that you couldn't renew the contract with someone close.
That's right. He's been depressed because of that.
On top of that,
he's even crying.
I wasn't crying. I'm just going through menopause.
Does that make people cry all the time?
I didn't cry all the time.
Aren't you sad that our daughter had a fight with her best friend?
It is sad.
It's not because of our daughter. It's about that contract.
His employee, Joy Jung, told me that he named a flower pot...
after that actor.
Nobody can keep secrets around here.
Do you name things now?
I named it before this happened.
I only named a few after the big-shots.
I'm going to throw it away. It's not a problem.
- Let's stop wasting his time. - I'm fine. I'm not busy at all.
Is there anything else?
He can't sleep at night.
He often looks dazed.
What are you talking about?
You're feeling a sense of loss after losing your favourite actor.
That is the reason why he cried.
- I didn't cry. - It's okay.
It's a natural, human emotion.
Ease your mind and accept the fact that he's gone.
I don't even have the time to feel depressed.
Watch the tone. We're with the pastor.
It's fine.
Please continue.
My work is going great. I'm very happy right now.
I could even hug high-school brats spitting on the streets.
I have a good appetite and I'm eating well.
- In bed, we're... - Honey.
I'm saying there's nothing wrong.
Please have some.
That's hot.
Every time I get myself tested,
it's a total humiliation.
I've never done anything like this before.
How do they do it exactly?
You don't want to know.
Mr. Cha Joon? Please come in.
Okay.
He's going in.
Please don't use anything too big.
I'll get started now.
Hold on.
Can you hold my hand?
One, two,
three.
You little... Hold on.
Hang in there.
It'll be over soon.
My gosh.
I think you're a very good actor.
If we end up working together,
I'll let you make the decisions.
I'll be supporting you from behind.
Okay.
What do you not like about her?
She's the complete opposite of Eun Gab. She won't force me.
He didn't force you to do anything. He was trying to help.
Let's not forget that.
Why are you taking his side now? You two never even got along.
Let's just sign the contract. We have to start working again.
We should.
I don't even know anymore.
What is it?
- Hello? - Hello.
Mr. Kim. It's me, Ho Jin.
What makes you call me?
I was just...
I was just wondering how you're doing.
- Are you doing all right? - I am.
We signed a couple of actors recently. We've been busy.
- What about you? How's work? - You know.
We don't have any work.
I thought you were going around meeting other agencies.
It's not like I was spying on you. I just heard some rumours.
Mr. Kim. Speaking of which...
What? You can say it.
Will Ms. Jo be fine with us after we pay for the breach?
I didn't notice anything particular about the news articles.
Did you do something about that?
I did introduce her to a different actor, but I don't know how it went.
I see.
I saw Joon on that show. What on earth was that?
Joon's been stressed out because of that.
He doesn't do anything right.
It was his first time. I'm sure he'll get better.
- Mr. Kim. By the way... - What is it?
Never mind. I was just calling to check on you.
Okay. Send Joon my regards.
- Okay. I'll hang up now. - Goodbye.
Come down and eat, Turtle.
He doesn't seem to care about my being sick at all.
I don't want to go to work today.
Joon.
I talked with Mr. Kim and he said he watched the show.
- He sends his regards. - Really?
So he did know.
Why did you talk to him? Did Eun Gab call you?
I called him.
We didn't talk about you. Don't worry.
I'm thinking of joining the agency we met yesterday.
Really?
- Do I have to call you down twice? - Stop.
Did you see the news?
That agency you met yesterday is involved in a stock manipulation.
What?
("An Agency's CEO Summoned to the Prosecution")
Do we have to look for somewhere else now?
Hey, Ji An.
These are some fancy clothes.
Are you nervous already?
Of course. It's my first time meeting her after we started dating.
Why are we shopping for clothes all of a sudden?
It is Young Bin's meeting after all,
but I want you to look nice in front of her.
How's this one?
Ms. Kang now knows that we're dating, right?
What do you think she'll say?
Don't worry about it. She always thought highly of you.
Try this on.
Do you want me to come with you?
In there?
No. To the meeting.
Wake up.
I can get changed by myself.
- Hello. - Hello.
- You're here. - Hello.
After that, we should go with this.
The viewers didn't like me that much, did they? I'm sorry.
You don't have to be.
It was just the pilot episode. We'll have to see how it goes.
No. I should've done better.
It's okay. I'll explain the concept of today's shooting. Take a seat.
Okay.
After that, we should...
Are you sick somewhere?
We need you to be very active today.
I'm not sick at all.
Why... Why would I be?
What's today's shooting about?
I heard it's about looking after horses.
No, you'll be riding them.
What?
I have to ride horses?
That sounds like so much fun.
I get to ride horses today.
Hang on a minute, Joon.
Your face is too erotic. You look like you could be in an adult film.
It's not that I'm feeling anything.
- Can I take a short break? - Again?
I think I need to go to the bathroom.
- Make it quick. - Okay.
Are you okay?
Are you all right? I'm worried you might be impotent after this.
I can't ride any longer.
I can't even begin to express the pain I'm in.
It feels like watermelons are coming out of my you-know-where.
You should just tell them.
Didn't you see how many female staff members there are? No way.
I can't leave a worse impression than I already have.
Some timing this is.
What should I do?
Isn't there any other excuse I can come up with?
Tell them you fell from a horse when you went out hunting as a kid.
Do you think this is some time of western development?
You do have a face of our earliest pioneers.
Can you look up if there are any phobias related to horses?
Some people could be allergic to horses.
How can someone with a horse face be scared of horses?
Stop messing around with me.
My private part is at stake here.
Do you want me to live the rest of my life as an eunuch?
So tell the producers the truth that your private part hurts.
I can't. Never.
Are you embarrassed?
It's just another body part that is hurting.
Which happens to be my private part!
It's my only weakness.
Every part of your body is a weakness. You're just weak.
It's hurting again.
I really tried to show them what I'm capable of this time.
Why did they have to make me ride horses today?
Darn my prostate!
Curse you, my prostate!
Curse you!
- I have to go now, right? - Yes.
No.
- I think it's bleeding. - It's not. Come on.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
I have something to say to the staff members.
When I was young,
I was eating a carrot in front of a horse...
and the horse took it away from me. I'm traumatized.
I see.
And ever since then,
I've been scared of horses.
I have equinophobia.
It's because of...
your prostate.
What?
We heard you mentioning your private part.
That was hilarious.
You should take the mic off next time you go get changed.
I left it on?
You heard everything?
Everyone here heard it all.
I'm sorry.
Am I making you uncomfortable again?
Not at all. I feel at home.
Right?
Yes.
Actors can't have a single drink with peace when they're outside.
So...
Did you find an agency you like?
No. Not yet.
That's good to hear.
You know why I wanted to see you today, right?
I want you to be a part of my agency again.
I see.
Why look somewhere else?
This is where you used to belong.
We know you the best and treat you the best.
I'll think about your offer.
How about you, Manager Lee?
I agree with him.
You're not very talkative today.
Empty your glass.
There you go.
Drink up.
Oh, I noticed that your birthday is coming up.
I'll personally throw you a birthday party this year.
It's okay. We decided not to party this year.
Why not? You've had it rough lately.
You broke up with many friends.
You should enjoy the time to get back on your feet.
You and me both.
We both parted ways with someone we worked with for a long time.
- Are you talking about Eun Gab? - Yes.
Things aren't the way it used to be after he left.
But we did have our differences.
We shouldn't let our attachments stop us from making decisions.
Cheers.
I need to go to the bathroom quickly.
Okay.
Ji An is running late on purpose so we could talk.
Right.
So...
How far are you willing to go...
with my daughter?
I'm sorry?
Don't act surprised.
Working as a manager can be demanding.
Are you going to marry her?
That's...
I haven't thought that far.
But you should.
My daughter...
had a lonely life growing up because of me.
To be honest,
I don't want her boyfriend to be a manager.
- I'll work on that. - Okay.
I'll...
keep my eyes on you, Manager Lee.
- Okay. - Pour me a glass.
Drink that up.
- What? - Bottoms up.
I want to see how you are when you get drunk.
Okay.
Gosh.
I called for a designated driver. Drink this.
I'm probably the first actor to look after a drunk manager.
I feel like I'm going to die.
I had to use all of my willpower.
Ms. Kang really tested your limits.
How should I say this? She looked like your mother-in-law.
- Did I do anything wrong? - No, you didn't.
What did you think...
about Ms. Kang's offer?
It didn't sound bad, did it?
It sounded good. The terms are nice, too.
Also, we can trust them more than other companies.
- Still... - Eun Gab?
It bothers me, too.
Do you care about him?
Gosh.
I thought you were still angry with him.
He's a nice person.
You'll probably tell me to stop, but I don't want to.
- Why don't you just... - Stop.
Let's just sign the contract. You should start working again.
Mr. Han, come here. Why are you so late?
What's up with you?
I got Lasik surgery.
I couldn't sleep at all last night.
It hurt so much.
That's why I'm late. I'm sorry.
By the way, did you meet Kang Eun Sol?
I can't meet anyone right now because of my eyes.
I can't even look at my phone screen.
Why did you have to get the surgery at this critical time?
Since I got divorced,
I've been feeling empty.
Are you crying?
My eyes hurt so much. They're supposed to be okay by now.
It's driving me crazy.
Did you have breakfast?
Breakfast? I don't have an appetite.
I'll meet Kang Eun Sol soon.
Eat well. I trust you'll finish your tasks.
- Go in. - I'm sorry.
Still, coming to work at 11am is...
You're acting really strange.
Why are you suddenly so nice?
I couldn't say anything to someone sick.
Isn't there a saying like this?
"If you change too fast, you might die soon." Right?
Are you serious?
Stop the nonsense.
Hi, Ms. Jo. What's the matter?
Are you eating something again?
It sounds like you're chewing something.
You're eating something every time we talk on the phone.
I'm not eating anything.
Fine. What's the matter?
I made a contract with Mr. Lim today.
We decided on the actor, too.
That's great. You have nothing to do with Young Bin now.
No. I'll never work with him again.
But you know how things work here. I'll end up working with him again.
Next time, I won't let him get away.
All right. Now, you can go ahead with your plans.
I can't. Another work is giving me a headache now.
It's a movie Young Bin was interested in again.
Do you mean "Lim Hwa Su"?
Yes. I don't know what's with Young Bin.
Why do you blame him?
Do you feel bad? He doesn't work with you anymore.
Right. Young Bin is going back to Ok and Gab Entertainment.
You must feel bitter.
I was expecting it.
Bye.
Gosh. Why did he choose them of all agencies?
What's all that?
It's our birthday present for Young Bin.
It finally arrived on the day before his birthday.
It's a beer-brewing machine.
It's his birthday. Why did you buy a present for yourselves?
We can all share the beer.
Young Bin said he was okay with it.
I told them to buy it. Let's make beer for tomorrow.
Hey, are you making a contract with Ms. Kang?
I'm thinking about it. The terms are nice.
Only if Ho Jin wasn't against it.
I'm not against it.
You didn't like the other companies.
What do you mean?
Are you taking your mother-in-law's side now?
Ho Jin is abandoning Mr. Kim.
Gosh.
He'll feel hurt if you make a contract with her.
I'm sure he already knows. This field is small.
I guess he'll feel hurt.
When is your show airing?
It's starting to hurt again.
I really don't want to watch that show.
It'll be fine after the editing.
Hey.
Should we tell Mr. Kim before we sign the contract?
Well...
You can tell him.
How can he do this? Why did they choose Ms. Kang?
They know what she did to me.
It feels like they betrayed me twice.
There must be countless agencies that want Young Bin.
Ok and Gab is not that competent, either.
Wait. They don't need "Gab" in their name anymore.
Stop it.
You've been only talking about Young Bin.
Why do you care whom he chooses? Do you feel jealous?
I'm not jealous. Ms. Kang is pulling my leg.
I can totally picture her smiling ear to ear.
- You're obsessed. - No, I'm not.
Then what's the problem?
Everything's over. Get over it.
Let's see the pastor once more. When is good for you?
It's so sticky here. I'll get the mop.
I can't predict what will happen.
That's what this show is all about.
This show is supposed to be a reality show,
but it just tortures people.
No one tells them what's happening.
I have no idea how it'll wind up.
All right. Now...
I've never been this serious about a show.
The show has been going on for 30 minutes, and he hasn't appeared.
I'm sure he'll appear soon.
I'll go out for a while.
Where are you going?
Do you need some air in your pants?
(Turtle)
I'm actor Cha Joon!
Come on, waves!
Come on, wind!
I'll never give in.
I'm Cha Joon!
Can you be quiet?
You're distracting us.
There are other people here.
I'm sorry.
- I'm sorry. - Gosh, it's so annoying.
Let's drink.
What are you doing here at this hour? Do you know what time it is?
I'm sorry.
I was all alone at home, and I couldn't fall asleep.
Do you think I can sleep well?
I was finally falling asleep after taking pills.
I'm sorry.
Now that I'm here, can't we have a little talk?
What's that? Take that off.
Let's talk.
Gosh.
What is it?
Hey.
Are you crazy? You have to drive.
I can call a designated driver.
I can't go on without alcohol.
After the divorce,
I started to miss my wife.
I feel so empty and in pain.
It feels like I lost an organ.
I understand.
I can imagine how you'd feel. Why did you get divorced?
It was my fault.
My wife doesn't let me meet my kid.
You can't meet your kid?
Go beg her right now.
I haven't seen my kid in a month.
I miss my kid so much.
I see.
It feels like my kid is still in her room.
I'm so sorry.
I have no one else to talk to. I'm sorry.
Mr. Kim.
You can't meet your kid?
Are you crying...
because of me?
You can't meet your...
Gosh, something's wrong with me.
You go home, okay?
Do call a driver. Gosh.
Mr. Kim.
Darn it.
Pastor.
- Hello. - Hello.
Did I wake you up? I'm sorry.
What's the matter in the middle of the night?
You were right. I'm depressed.
Sorry?
Is that it?
I thought something happened.
It's late now. You should go home.
Meet me at the church tomorrow.
Wait.
This is important for me.
I was crying just a moment ago. Do you see it?
As my wife said, I think it started when my actor left me.
Whenever I hear about people breaking up,
I burst into tears.
I have a new employee who is terrible at his job.
He came by in the middle of the night...
and whined about his divorce. I couldn't say anything to him.
What should I do?
Is that a problem?
Before, I'd insult and fire someone like him right away.
Insulting and offending others used to be my joy.
This is not the real me.
To me, it seems like...
you changed for the better. You're less aggressive now.
I want to go back to the old me.
My goodness.
I don't think you're just depressed.
Did anything special happen recently?
The thing is,
my close friends left me recently.
I did my best, but I apparently hurt them.
After that, I can't act as I wish...
because I'm scared people will leave me again.
- Are you falling asleep? - Sorry.
I'm pretty tired.
Do you have any idea what time it is?
I'm talking about something crucial for me. How can you...
A lost sheep is looking for water.
A shepherd can't fall asleep now.
I donated so much money to your church.
It's just so late.
Can't a pastor sleep?
It's two in the morning now.
It is late. My point is...
Just do what you want. Go back to your old self.
Get back what you've lost.
That will cure your depression. My goodness.
One more thing.
Do not skip Sunday services, okay?
- Hallelujah. - Amen.
- Go home now. - Okay.
Why did he have to come in the middle of the night?
My old self?
Okay.
You're here.
Your voice drives me crazy.
Kiss me.
Kiss me right now.
You brat.
You're here.
Was it your kid on the phone?
No, it wasn't.
Are you seeing someone?
Did you get divorced because you had an affair?
I was...
never going to meet her again,
but my wife didn't trust me.
I'm a human being. I've been lonely.
You've known me for a long time. I'm not a bad guy.
Cut it out.
Have you met Kang Eun Sol?
Not yet. My eyes are...
When my eyes recover...
All right.
You finished the puzzle.
I did it last night.
It looks quite nice, doesn't it?
- I bought something even better. - You brat.
Forget about the puzzle.
Do you want me...
to rip your face into puzzle pieces?
Why do you play with puzzles during working hours?
You got Lasik surgery? I'll scoop your eyes out!
You miss your kid?
You got dumped after having an affair!
You don't deserve to miss your kid! What should I do with you?
Hey.
Don't show up at night. Not during the day, either.
Don't show up here again!
Get out right now!
You little...
You jerk.
Boss, you're back.
You're back to being short-tempered, right?
Don't make fun of me.
(Young Bin's birthday)
"Young Bin's birthday"?
Why did you look? Go away.
Is it Young Bin's birthday today?
Apparently so.
Have you wished him a happy birthday?
Even though you don't work together, you're still friends.
You talk so much.
Do you have no work to do?
- Get out. - Okay, Boss.
Close the door behind you.
The phone is turned off.
His phone is turned off.
Should we report to the police?
What if he's been kidnapped?
No way.
He sent a text saying he wanted to be alone.
It's strange that he's not coming home on Young Bin's birthday.
- Is it him? - No, it's just birthday wishes.
Your phone is on fire. You're so popular.
I just get spams on my birthday.
- What do they say? - They want me to get a new bike.
- You don't have a bike. - They still want me to.
It's Ms. Kang.
- Hello, Ms. Kang. - It's your birthday today, right?
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
Today?
It works for me.
Already?
Okay. I see.
Bye.
What did she say?
She's throwing me a birthday party tonight.
She's already booked a place.
It's too much pressure.
I know. I just wanted to chill at home with some beer.
You can't.
You can't have beer.
Why not?
The instruction says it takes a week to brew beer.
What's the problem with you?
It's not for his birthday, then.
I didn't know it'd arrive so late.
It was Joon's idea. That piece of junk.
Why did he disappear, dumping the problem on me?
Isn't he too old to run away from home?
Does it run in your family?
Is Cha Du Ri like that?
- What did he do wrong? - What about Cha In Pyo?
Is Cao Lu related, too?
It sounds like Cha.
Look. I don't believe it.
Take a photo.
It's unbelievable.
- He's so tall. - What's going on?
(Convenience store)
What is he doing?
What are you doing, you wandering middle-aged man?
Are you shooting a movie?
How did you know I was here?
Why did you turn off your phone? We've been looking everywhere.
It ran out of battery. How did you know I was here?
Someone uploaded pictures of you having cup noodles here.
There were pictures of you sleeping in the car, too.
What are you talking about?
Here. See it for yourself.
Here. Look.
What is this? How do they know who I am?
Why are they talking about prostate?
Do you remember our conversation about your prostate?
It went on television. It was hilarious.
- Your name is being searched. - Along with "prostate".
People are talking about you on the homepage of the show.
You guys are lying, right?
- Gosh. - For goodness' sake.
Is this another prank?
It sounds like you've grown to love it.
Shall I show you the comments? Here, have a look.
"Mr. Prostate rocks." "Cha Joon and his package."
"Cha Joon is the new Mr. Big."
Joon, are you crying?
Gosh...
What's wrong?
I did it!
Hey, you're going to trip.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Ms. Kang is inside. - Thank you.
I see her over there.
There he is.
Happy birthday!
- Happy birthday! - Thank you.
- It's so awesome. - Thank you.
- Hello, Ms. Kang. - You made it.
Hello, Ms. Kang!
Why are you so late?
- I had to stop by somewhere. - I see.
Hi, guys. We met the other day, right?
- Yes. - Have a great time.
- Thank you. - Thank you. We'll have fun.
Why are you all just standing there?
Have a seat, guys. Make yourself at home.
- Okay. - Okay.
Bye.
What do you think of this place? Isn't it awesome?
Yes. But I didn't know that you were throwing such a big party for me.
I wanted to throw a proper party for the agency...
as well as for your birthday.
You were part of our family,
and I still think of you the same way.
Oh, right.
Speaking of which, have you had a chance to consider my offer?
No, not yet.
Yes, you have to consider it carefully.
There's no need to rush.
Let the agency know if you need anything in the meantime.
- No, it's okay. - Don't say that.
I know that you actors need the agency's help with many things.
We've been doing it all along, so it's not a big deal at all.
- Okay. - Thank you.
We're here for Young Bin's birthday, so we should toast him.
- Sure! - All right.
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
Ms. Kang, please stay healthy!
Cut it out.
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
Everyone downstairs is having such a great time.
It's your birthday party. Why are we so quiet?
That's what I'm saying.
I feel so uncomfortable for some reason.
It's not even our agency. Of course it's awkward for us to be here.
Do you guys want to leave?
- Shall we? - Can we?
No one would notice even if I left.
- Let's go. - Thanks.
Let's go for soju and samgyeopsal.
- Is it on you? - Sure.
I'll treat you guys since I'm in a good mood today. I'll hail a cab.
What do you think?
Shall I sign the contract with Ms. Kang?
I must say, it is better than other agencies.
But I don't know how Mr. Kim will feel about it.
By the way, I haven't heard anything from Eun Gab.
I thought he'd at least text me to wish me a happy birthday.
You two had a fight. Of course, he wouldn't.
I wouldn't text you either if I were him.
(Eun Gab)
What? Who's calling?
It's Eun Gab.
- Hi, Eun Gab. - Hey.
Young Bin.
Are you with the guys?
- Yes, I am. - I see. Then...
Where are you now?
Oh, really? Well...
Can I see you quickly?
Do you have time? It'll be quick.
Sure. I'll meet you there.
Does he want to meet up now? What for?
I don't know.
Restaurant Chun?
- What does that mean? - Is the owner's surname Chun?
- Is the owner Chun Li? - Stop talking nonsense.
It's possible.
(Restaurant Chun)
What a great timing.
- Hello. - Hi.
What's all this?
It's your birthday today. You should eat seaweed soup. Have a seat.
Have a seat here.
They're here. Please heat up the soup.
Okay. Right away.
My friend owns this restaurant. The food here is so good.
You've never been here before? I guess you haven't... There it is.
- Hello. - This is my friend.
You don't need to get up. Just take the soup. Sit down.
I don't see any customers.
I rented the entire restaurant because of Young Bin.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Hold on a second.
Before we start eating...
It'd be too much for him if we sang.
Blow out the candle.
- He's making a wish. - That's hilarious.
Applaud.
Okay. Let's eat now, guys.
- Thank you for this. - It looks amazing.
You must be sick of seaweed soup.
No, I haven't had it today.
Really? Joon, you didn't make it for him?
No, I was a little busy today.
I see.
Oh, right. I watched the show. You were hilarious in it.
- Gosh, you saw it? - You fool.
Who knew he'd crack jokes about his prostate?
It was a blooper, wasn't it?
No, it was all calculated.
Oh, really?
Do you have time to eat? Don't you have to be at your birthday party?
We were actually just there. Ms. Kang threw a party for me.
Oh, is that right?
Why did you guys leave so early?
She got pretty drunk, so we sneaked out.
She's like that. She dances around, too.
She's a piece of work.
So have you decided...
to go back to Ok and Gab Entertainment?
I'm thinking I probably should. I haven't made up my mind, though.
Eat up.
I'm sorry, Eun Gab.
It must hurt your feelings because it's Ms. Kang.
Not at all. Work is work.
I'm sorry. I feel bad about what happened with "War Terminator".
You don't need to apologize.
We just think differently.
Anyhow, let's do a good job even though we won't work together.
I really want all the best for you,
whether you work with me or not. I mean it.
I know. I feel the same way.
All right.
Guys, isn't it your job to lift up the mood?
- Right. - This soup is seriously so good.
Gosh, it's really delicious.
Your soup tastes like boiled seawater, but this is so flavourful.
That's because I don't use flavour enhancers. He has bad taste.
You have a bad face.
Cut it out, guys. You guys are two peas in a pod.
You haven't decided on Young Bin's next film or drama, have you?
No, we should pick one soon.
I should give this to you before I forget.
- I have something for you. - What is it?
You'll like it.
("Lim Hwa Su")
What's this about? Why are you giving this to me?
Gosh, this is...
Ms. Jo...
is no longer part of the project. You should be able to do it now.
I know how much you wanted to be in this.
(Entourage)
You can't persuade Young Bin with money.
The incentives must include...
I really want to do "Lim Hwa Su".
I'll be broke if this hiatus goes on for longer.
- It'd look like I'm luring him. - Go ahead.
Turtle needs to experience some hardships.
Why are you so clueless?
He looked like a complete loser.
He has no presence. I thought he was a ghost or something.
It looks like you'll need to apologize.
What did I do wrong?
What have you been doing all day?
Gosh, let's just break up.
Young Bin won't want to work with me.
We're strangers now.