BioskopKeren.ORG
(Entourage)
- Turtle. - How are you so good at this?
Have you been practicing?
This is fun.
About Eun Gab...
He probably gave me "Lim Hwa Su"...
just because I really wanted to do it, right?
Probably. Why?
Nothing.
I really want to do "Lim Hwa Su".
It'd be really nice if you got to do it.
You really should. How else are we going to pay for the breach?
I'll be broke if this hiatus goes on for longer.
This is nice and relaxing, though.
I make money now.
I finally made a breakthrough. You can count on me.
- Don't get ahead of yourself. - Nice.
Look at him all excited when our family is about to go broke.
I wonder if I'll ever see him make money before I retire.
It's not like I can't. I'm just not feeling like it.
Then start working.
I will, but you'll be bored to death without me.
It's really fine with me. You can work all you want.
Forget it. You aren't capable of anything other than playing games.
You said you're looking for a manager, right?
Yes. I have shootings every week, but I don't have a manager.
- What about him? - Him?
- Come on. - Me?
What's so hard about being a manager, anyway?
It's a very demanding job.
All you do is nag and complain.
Are you kidding me?
You should work for Joon if you think it's so easy.
- I will. - No way. I won't allow it.
Why not? You should work together. You guys always tag along anyway.
I just need to stay by his side, right?
We'll eat, sleep, and poop together.
You have to work hard.
It's settled, then.
We should talk to Ms. Kang about "Lim Hwa Su".
Okay.
So you're telling me...
that you want to be part of "Lim Hwa Su"?
Yes. The talks broke down once, but I really liked the scripts.
How do you like the rice cake? It's from a place I know.
Pardon?
It's delicious.
I need to get "Gab" out of "Ok and Gab" as soon as possible.
How does "Ok Entertainment" sound, Manager Lee?
I think it's good.
- You won't be able to do the film. - What?
What? Why?
We haven't looked into the details just yet.
Is it going to be that difficult?
The talks had broken down once. It's going to be difficult.
There's no director or any investors.
There's no way of knowing when you'll get to do it.
It could take years.
Let's do a Chinese drama.
Chinese drama?
The show has been scheduled already for early next year.
It's already been written.
What genre is it?
It's a romance.
I don't really want to do romance.
And I'd prefer to do movies over dramas.
You'll get paid 100,000 dollars per episode.
40 episodes in total.
100,000 dollars per episode?
It's not a small sum.
They specifically asked for you, Young Bin.
You have to pay for the breach, right?
I want you to be a part of my agency so we can do this together.
It's about time you make some real money.
We'll have to talk about it.
Of course.
Who made you that offer, by the way?
Eun Gab showed me the script and told me about it.
I see.
100,000 dollars per episode means...
You could purchase this entire store.
Do you think Ms. Kang is right about "Lim Hwa Su"?
Should I do that Chinese drama?
Speaking as a manager, that's what I'll tell you to do.
- But as a friend? - Do "Lim Hwa Su".
I'll have to do "Lim Hwa Su", then.
Do you think that will be okay with Ms. Kang?
Don't you think she'll be against it?
What should I do at times like this? Tell me as a manager.
You should join her. It is the best agency out there.
But as a friend?
Can I be honest?
You want me to work with Eun Gab? Forget it.
Why did you ask, then? Don't ask in the first place.
Let's just pick out Joon's clothes. He says he's not well sponsored.
We should get Turtle something, too.
I'm not into fashion. You can pick out their clothes.
- What are you doing this evening? - I'm going to see Ji An.
What about me? I'll be alone with Joon and Turtle gone.
Can't I go out on a date?
I'll be bored. Some friend you are.
Hold on. Can you buy me this? I want to give it to Ji An.
- Don't tempt me. - It's 1,400 dollars.
Let's do that Chinese drama.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello. Nice to meet you.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Bye.
Hey, Joon.
- Hello. - Hey.
Do you want to hear a joke?
What do you call an unemployed strawberry?
What?
Strawberry syrup.
It's funny, right? Do you want to hear another one?
What do you call the poorest king?
I don't know.
Minimum wage.
Joon.
Aren't you too young to be making middle-aged men jokes?
Sometimes, I feel like you're from the stone age.
Those jokes were so bad.
What are you?
- I'm your friend. - You're my manager.
I'm warming myself up before I go into shooting.
- What did you say? - I was joking.
Be quiet.
A manager shouldn't demoralize the actor.
Know your place.
Go make me some coffee.
Okay.
That was funny, right?
Here's your coffee.
You took that long just to get this?
There weren't any coffee shops nearby.
People here don't have time for these.
We all drink instant coffee.
That's not what I saw on television.
What?
Do you want to drink this, Joon?
Instant coffee is the way to go. "Instant coffee, ready to go."
You always said it's too sweet.
I'm on set right now.
Why are you so stupid?
You don't meet the requirements to become a manager.
You should let Ho Jin teach you a thing or two.
I'm a manager, not a slave. What's wrong with you?
You're not a slave.
What am I, then?
You're not, but you have to take care of me.
And you're doing none of that.
Don't make a scene in front of all the staff members.
Get it together.
Get yourself together.
Aren't you going around meeting agencies anymore?
Did you decide to work with my mom?
Yes, I think so.
I see.
You're not doing it because of me, are you?
No way.
It was where we used to belong. And Ms. Kang is good to us.
Yes. It doesn't concern me.
So make your decision wisely.
Yes, Ma'am.
Why would you knock if you're not going to wait for the response?
At least, I knocked.
What is it? Were you touching yourself?
I'm not in the mood for that.
Was it that bad?
I'm not sure if I didn't do good enough...
or if Joon is being picky.
Joon's always been a sensitive guy. You know that.
But...
being friends and working together are two different things.
It's amazing how Ho Jin is getting the job done.
Are you trying to diss me as well?
You actors.
It must run in your family. Let's just put it at that.
Am I like Joon, too?
You know I'm right. You're so fickle.
I was only a manager for a day, but it's a tough task.
Ho Jin and Mr. Kim must have it rough.
I see.
Do you want me to work with Eun Gab rather than Ms. Kang?
Why do you ask me that? Did Ho Jin say so?
It's just that he still talks about him.
You should listen to Ho Jin.
He betrayed his future mother-in-law to do the right thing.
What's wrong with everyone?
You ought to listen to your manager,
you Cha Brothers.
I don't know anymore. Get to work, you apprentice.
I'm going to play League of Legends.
What's my manager doing...
when I have a shooting with female guests the day after tomorrow?
Shouldn't he be more considerate?
What don't you like about Turtle?
What is it?
I was mean to him on purpose.
He's never been through a tough time in his life.
It's a jungle out there. I need to give him tough love.
This is his first time.
He's been my manager all this time we've lived together.
Not exactly.
Be good to him. You know he has a soft heart.
That is exactly why I need to be like this.
You, me, and Young Bin had it hard when growing up.
We've been through the hardest times in our lives.
Turtle needs to go through this.
He needs to learn a lesson.
Joon.
When I first became a manager,
it really lowered my self-esteem. I didn't know what I was doing.
That's how everyone starts.
I want to shape Turtle into a rock.
The Cha Brothers are really something.
Gosh.
What is it? Is your penis hurting again?
Talking about Turtle made me want to poop.
- Gosh. - Are you going to watch me poop?
That's nasty.
One, two, three, four.
That's the highest number of viewers I got. Thank you.
I don't think I'll be streaming for sometime.
I started working. I got a job.
That's right. I got a job.
Today was my first day and I don't think I can make it to the second.
But I'll try my best.
The world is a cruel place.
I have respect for all the white collars out there.
"I go to elementary school."
You go to elementary school?
Get out of here and go study.
You don't want to be like me when you grow up.
Stay healthy.
The world is a brutal place.
We can do it.
We can.
Hey, Boss.
- In your room... - What is it?
- Boss. - What?
What is she doing in here?
What are you doing?
Are you still hungover from last night?
What brings you here? Did you come to check on me?
It's a nice office, isn't it? It's cozy and fancy.
It's a much better office than one in Ok Entertainment.
This is it?
It's so small just like what's in your pants.
What's so good about it?
You talk like you've seen it.
I don't have to see it to know.
You...
gave Young Bin a script, didn't you?
I need coffee. Is anyone there?
Why did you give him that script?
Do you still have attachments to him?
I do.
Give it up. I'm going to sign him.
He won't do that.
Why wouldn't he? I can top any other offer.
I even got him a big role.
Young Bin can't be moved by money.
Does he move by loyalty, then?
Is that why he abandoned you?
You're the one who abandoned me.
You spit me right back out as soon as I lost value to you.
Don't you ever look in the mirror?
You have a face of a money-grubbing hag.
Watch it.
You're on my turf now. Do you want me to get serious?
I'm sick of fighting with you.
I'll leave you to your petty tasks.
I'll be busy with Young Bin.
You came here to tell me that?
Yes.
Don't you ever go near Young Bin again.
First, the agency and now, Young Bin.
Let's see how it goes.
(Deer antlers)
Eat this and eat my words.
I wish you a long and healthy life. It's deer antlers.
(New Seoul)
Hello. It's me, Ho Jin.
How have you been?
Can I ask you for a favor?
It's about "Lim Hwa Su".
Hello?
Yes. It's me, Ho Jin.
Weren't you an assistant director at New Seoul?
Right?
Can you tell me the CEO's number?
(Lim Hwa Su)
(Young Bin)
- Hey. - Where are you?
I'm working at a nearby cafe.
Why aren't you working at home?
I get sleepy when I'm home. I'm going over the script.
- Is there something wrong? - I'll tell you later.
Joon and Turtle left me all alone. I'm bored.
Can't you let me do my job? I'm not your girlfriend.
- I'll be back soon. - Hurry.
- Don't forget to eat. - Okay.
Ho Jin.
- Hello. - Long time no see.
- It's been so long. How are you? - I'm good.
- This place is nice, right? - It is.
Don't be fooling around. Come on in.
What? We can't say hello?
This isn't the back alley of Brooklyn or Itaewon.
- Bye. - Catch you later.
What brings you here?
I've been meaning to take a look around here.
Why did you name it "Tiger's Den"?
Because it's a habitat of tigers like Young Bin.
- Is it weird? - No.
I think it's a good name.
"Bear's Den" would've been weird, though.
What? Are you making fun of me?
Not at all.
- Why did you... - Mr. Kim...
- Never mind. - You go first.
Well... I'm not so sure about Young Bin's signing the contract.
It's been giving me a headache.
I thought you were going to sign the contract with Ms. Kang.
I heard she renamed the agency to something ridiculous.
We haven't made the decision yet.
About the script you gave us...
Does Young Bin want to do it?
Of course, he does.
But things are complicated with the film company involved.
Ms. Kang wants him to do this Chinese drama.
I came to seek your advice.
What kind of advice? I don't even work with him anymore.
It's for you to worry about now. And since when do you listen to me?
I did.
You always put it bluntly,
but you always said the right things.
You should've done better when you had the chance.
The same goes for you.
Look at you all grown up.
You're on your own. A Chinese drama sounds nice.
You know how Young Bin wants to do movies.
"Lim Hwa Su" isn't looking good.
I looked into the situation as well.
If another production company buys the publication rights,
things could work out.
I do want to help Young Bin out, but...
Please help us, Mr. Kim.
But then,
it'd look like I'm luring him.
So be it, then.
What?
What are you talking about?
To be honest,
I still think the right thing to do is to work with you.
What's with you today?
How does Young Bin feel about it?
He didn't say much,
but I think he's not as opposed as before.
Really?
Should I pull some strings, then?
You look so happy.
I'm joking, of course.
- I'm not interested. - Okay.
I'll do it solely on behalf of wishing Young Bin well.
Do you want me to look into it?
A production company who can kick-start things?
Please.
- Is that what you got this morning? - It's nice, isn't it?
From now on, I'm going to wear refined and sophisticated clothes.
Like Jung Woo Sung and Lee Jung Jae.
I'm a gentleman from now on.
You're dying to make fun of me, aren't you?
I didn't say anything.
You forgot to talk to the stylist again, didn't you?
What are you doing?
Fine. I'm on it.
Are you two still fighting?
Did you see that? This is how he treats me.
Fine. I'll call her.
- Hello, Hye Jin. - Hello.
I'm calling about Joon's outfit tomorrow.
I said I wasn't up for it, but he forced me to style him.
I'm sorry about that. Thank you. I'll come pick it up tomorrow.
Thank you. You're very kind.
Well, you're good to me so...
- Of course... - Hey!
- What are you doing? - Excuse me.
- What do you want me to say to her? - What are you doing with her?
You're not supposed to be flirting with the staff members.
She was just saying thank you for picking up your outfit tomorrow.
Get it together, will you?
She's your co-worker.
You're completely clueless.
I'm sorry. Joon has lost his mind.
Get out.
I heard him yelling. Are you okay?
It's okay. He's not himself these days.
He's picking on me for no reason.
I didn't know this side of him.
He's even more sensitive than usual.
He is. By the way, do you know anyone whom I can introduce him to?
I think he'll get better with a woman in his life.
He's been asking me to introduce someone I know for long.
You should introduce him to her.
That's great. I'll do that. Okay.
Jerk. Joon.
Looks like this isn't that good of a fishing spot.
Why are you doing this to me, Mr. Kim Eun Gab?
I just came to say hello after starting my own agency.
I haven't gotten over from what happened last time. Go away.
Let's not dwell on the past. It's time to join forces.
Do you come here often?
You're not getting anything. Is this fun to you?
It is.
It's so much fun. Are you satisfied?
For goodness' sake. You startled me.
I startled you?
Do you want me to show you what I'm really capable of?
You scared me last time with that webfoot octopus.
So what do you want now?
And you. You were there too, weren't you?
- Yes. - My gosh.
You have some nerves coming to see me after what you did.
And we talked it all out.
Not for me. I'm still angry.
- That's enough now. - "That's enough now"?
- Why you little... - Please.
- This is really important for us. - Shut it!
Stay right there.
- He's really going to throw it. - Hey!
Come back here!
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
Those brats.
Drink up.
Coffee tastes the best on fishing spots.
I like "Lim Hwa Su".
It's got a big scale and the gangster action people like.
It's got quality and potential.
It's a move that can't go wrong.
Let's do it, then.
Like you said, I can make people invest with Cha Young Bin.
CJ and Lotte will all line up to be a part of it.
Then we're good to go, right?
I'm not.
Start catching some fish. I told you loud and clear.
But even you can't catch anything here.
Shut it. You have to catch a big one.
It has to be a local carp. The big one.
You promised that you'll produce this movie if we do.
Yes. Please do.
If you do, I'll go purchase the publication rights right away.
I'll sign Young Bin right away. Please do catch it.
Why is he being so mean?
I've never caught fish other than fishing for my wife.
This is my very first time.
And I'm scared of fish.
- Aren't they really slippery? - Do you want me to be scary?
You can give up now if you're not up to it.
How can he hear us from that far out? I'm not getting anything.
It went in.
Did I get something?
Wait, I got something. It's coming up.
What is this?
- I caught one. - Hold on.
- Oh, gosh. - Hold on. Give it to me.
Oh, it's a strong one.
- There it is. - It's coming out.
- Hand me the net. - Okay.
We got it.
Look at that.
We caught it.
This is the one, right? You have to do the movie.
- We did it. - We did it.
- How is this possible? - Look at that.
What are you doing?
What have you been up to the entire day?
Have you eaten?
I don't like eating alone.
You're an actor. Take care of your body.
You're a manager. Take care of your actor.
What did you do all day?
I had to see someone. Gosh, let's just break up.
I read the script of that Chinese drama.
I haven't gotten the chance to read it myself.
It's good.
But I can't keep reading when I don't want to do it.
I want to do "Lim Hwa Su".
You know how stubborn I get when I set my mind on something.
Where are Turtle and Joon?
They were busy all day preparing for shooting.
- There they are. - Guys.
Do you know what day it is tomorrow?
It's the day I get to shoot with actress Moon Geun Young.
- What? - Why?
You know how our show is about celebrities going through hard time?
I'll be Moon Geun Young's manager for tomorrow and the day after.
I'm jealous. I want to be Moon Geun Young's manager.
Not this jerk.
- Me, too. - Be quiet.
Stay put. I'll make you dinner after I get washed up.
Hey. Water.
I'm his water cooler.
That's harsh, Joon.
- Water. - Shut it.
This is going to hurt.
- Fine. - Brace yourself.
Stop it.
How long has it been since they went bankrupt?
New Seoul Production. That's a long forgotten name.
How did a film company with 30 years of experience go bankrupt?
At school, they taught us they're the cradle of Korean film industry.
That's right.
(New Seoul)
Hello?
I don't think there's anyone in there.
- Hello? - Who's that?
Who are you people?
- Hello. - Hello.
Aren't you...
Kim Eun Gab?
Yes. It's been too long.
- I think it was three years ago. - What was?
I asked you to take a look at a script...
and you didn't get back to me for two long months.
I can't remember clearly,
but I think the actor was involved in many lawsuits.
Not only did you not get back at us,
but you kept making demands after demands.
That's how it works these days.
That was never the case in the old days.
Actors have difficult personalities.
And investors behave like they own everything.
Making movies these days is too darn difficult.
Everyone takes the film company for granted.
I hear you loud and clear.
By the way, I heard the production for "Lim Hwa Su" has been halted.
The project was about to get started...
before the actor bailed out on us.
It's so irresponsible of them.
This is my retirement project.
I spent a lot of time and effort on this.
I couldn't keep the company afloat after what happened.
Do you still have the rights for "Lim Hwa Su"?
Yes, I do.
I see. The script is really good.
We really want to do "Lim Hwa Su".
If it's with Young Bin, I'll definitely get funding.
- Yes. - By the way,
you said you're his manager, right?
- Go. - Yes.
- You like the script? - Yes.
Did you...
really read it?
Of course.
Gosh.
Does a manager even know how to read scripts?
Don't be so old-fashioned.
I'm not old-fashioned.
Even these days, they read...
only their actor's parts and talk nonsense to me.
One should read the full script and understand it as a whole.
They talk about how big or small their parts are,
and that the character is too dark or too light.
Not all managers are like that.
Sure, they used to be gangsters.
These days, they're more sly.
Are you going to hand over the rights or not?
It's up to me. It's my film.
Are you going to make the film or not?
Hold on. Sir, I...
Gosh.
Do you know Mr. Ahn from Fish Film?
We already had a talk with them.
As long as you give us the permission,
we'd like to move forward with it. Please consider it.
Let's do it this way.
300,000 dollars for research and development.
I want 30 percent of the production company's share. How's that?
That's a bit too much.
You're not trying to make the film. You're just trying to make money.
What are you talking about?
- Just don't do it, then! - No, Sir.
Forget it!
- Gosh. - My goodness.
What a stubborn man.
He's trying to ruin us.
He's so old-fashioned. He's putting up a show.
Let's just try to persuade him.
Persuade him? Didn't you just see?
He thinks managers are gangsters. He won't listen to us.
What? 300,000 dollars? 30 percent?
Isn't he saying this because of what you did before?
I only did what I should do as a manager.
We all try to collaborate,
but they only care about the film while we only care about talents.
No wonder we run into conflicts when we work together.
- That's true, but... - Hey, let's go.
They have a young producer at this production company.
I bet they have some say in this. It'd be faster to talk to them.
I'll just try to persuade the CEO.
I want to make this film, too.
However, I can't work with him. He's impossible to talk to.
Just let me try.
I'm sure something will work out if I keep trying.
You're so stubborn. You're just like Young Bin.
You're doing something useless.
I don't care. I'm leaving.
Do what you want. I need some coffee.
Gosh.
I don't know anymore.
Hey!
Be quiet.
What about this?
I'm looking at the cue sheets.
Can't you see?
Don't play music in the car anymore.
Then you should have stayed at the cafe. Why did you come here?
I'm focusing on the cue sheets while waiting for Moon Geun Young.
I'm sensitive. I'm really sensitive right now.
Are you filming "The Throne"?
I'm her biggest fan.
It may be short, but I want to do it properly.
Can you be a proper manager for once?
You're talking better than usual.
Why are you doing this to me?
Is this how you're like when you work?
Why are you so cranky?
If you keep this up, I'll get mad.
I'm even planning to set you up with girls.
I'm setting you up...
What? What? What is it now?
Are you listening to music? I thought you wanted it turned off.
Even Yoo Jae Seok doesn't let people play music in the car.
It's actually nicer to listen to music with earphones.
We'll see you in a moment.
Don't change the channel.
Cut. Lunch break.
Enjoy your lunch. Enjoy.
- Enjoy your lunch. It's hot, right? - Yes.
- Enjoy your lunch. - Thank you.
Enjoy your lunch. Enjoy.
- Enjoy your lunch. - Okay.
Let's go eat. I heard we're going to finish early today.
- I guess so? - You guess so?
They didn't get enough content, so they have to shoot tomorrow.
Why are they shooting one episode over two days?
Did you tell them I'm available?
Yes.
Are you stupid? You really...
You need to use your brain.
Joon, did you hear the news? I'm so sorry.
It's okay. We should shoot until we get enough content.
It doesn't matter even if it's three days.
- Okay. - Good luck.
- What is that? - You're supposed to fight for me.
The manager is supposed to be evil while the actor is kind.
Those are our roles. Don't you know?
You're always with Young Bin and me. Why don't you know it?
Sorry.
I have good news.
What is it?
I set up a blind date for you to cheer you up.
A blind date?
- I guess that's nice. - What is it?
Ever since seeing Geun Young, I don't feel like it.
Are you crazy? That's nonsense. You guys don't match.
She's not that much younger than me.
I'm talking about your faces.
You guys would look so weird together.
Are you kidding me?
It's the truth. I was just being honest.
I'm on a reality show.
I have to make people laugh. Why do you keep making me angry?
Also, I have to focus on work. A blind date?
Are you going to be responsible for scandals?
Please put some sense into you.
Aren't you curious what common sense is?
I'm not eating. No, I can't eat.
I have no appetite because of you. Bring me cup noodles.
Sorry.
Look at this part.
What are you doing?
You're still here?
Yes. I wanted to talk to you.
I already told you the conditions.
Yes.
Why are you looking at this?
I'm sorry. It was just here.
You don't even know what it is.
I was young so I didn't get to see this film when it was released,
but I know of "Suddenly at Midnight".
You know "Suddenly at Midnight"?
Of course. It's a psychological mystery film...
that was ahead of its time.
It's a popular horror film from the 1980s, along with "Woman's Wail".
You know "Suddenly at Midnight"? I'm surprised.
What does a manager know about scripts?
Sir.
I don't know if I can say this,
but I used to work in film.
There were people who were good and bad at reading scripts.
I think it's the same thing when it comes to managers.
Were you in film before?
Yes, I was in a production team before.
That's nothing. You call that work? You don't know anything.
Right. It's nothing.
I don't know much and I'm not a film person.
However, I know that "Lim Hwa Su" is a good film.
You know that as well.
You're a knowledgeable person in film,
yet you're about to lose your chance in giving life to that project.
Are you...
I'm not trying to offend you.
I'm telling you all this because I really want to do it.
As you know, I'm Young Bin's manager,
but we've also been best friends since we were kids.
Young Bin is very eager to do this, too.
Please help us out. Please consider taking less on the cost and profit.
Then...
there's one more condition.
- Hey. - Hello, Mr. Kim.
The CEO of New Seoul...
is willing to go easy on the budget and profit.
On one condition, though.
What is it?
Well, it's...
He would like you...
to apologize to him. Then he'll help us out.
What? Why should I apologize to him? What did I do wrong?
I think that he has been holding a grudge against you.
He also said that you were out of line earlier.
Do you think I'm crazy? I went easy on that old wretch because he's old.
Forget it and just stay right there. I'll be there shortly.
Does he think I'm a joke or what?
Mr. Kim.
Please help us out. Even a little bit would be a big help to us.
I sincerely apologize if I've made you upset in any way.
Well, all right.
Apology accepted.
Then how does 150,000 dollars with a 15-percent profit sound?
170,000 dollars with a 17-percent profit.
Sure! I'll pass that information along.
- Let's settle it at that. - Okay.
Thank you. I've always admired you.
- I had to hold myself back. - Thank you for doing that.
You annoy me just as much. How can you...
We got what we wanted, so it's all good.
That bull-headed old grouch...
He said he didn't feel good about "Lim Hwa Su" going to waste.
He's a real cineaste. He certainly lives up to his name.
We're real managers, too.
That old man has bias against managers.
Anyway, I got him to give us permission,
so you should persuade Mr. Ahn about the profit structure.
I've done my job.
You sure have a way with words.
I know. I learned it all from you.
- Don't I look like a manager now? - Cut it out, you fool.
Gosh, Mr. Ahn will lose it on me.
- What should I do? - You'll figure it out.
Darn it.
I have no money...
Why am I broke even on this thing?
Game over!
Everything in my life is going bust, including this game.
(Joon)
What now?
Right, I know. I had to haggle to get it down to that amount.
It's good enough to be a win-win situation.
Win-win situation, my foot.
Mr. Park must think that I'm a complete idiot.
- Do you want some of this? - He doesn't.
Why are both of you so money hungry? You'll die before me anyway.
People live to be 100 years old nowadays.
I'll need money even if I go senile and end up smearing feces on walls.
- Why are you talking about feces? - Gosh, that's disgusting.
I am going to buy the rights from him,
but the share he's asking... I guess I'll have to give it to him.
If we ask him to lower it more, he'll cause a scene at my office.
I'll have to clean up after his dead body.
I'll clean up after his dead body with you. Just buy the rights.
Mom, I can't eat this anymore.
Honey, come eat spaghetti with us.
Cha Young Bin is signing a contract with you, right?
- Well, that's... - I'll think that it's the case.
I'll move ahead with this right away.
Okay. Buy the rights as soon as possible. Yes, let's talk soon.
What? What is it?
Are you going to eat this or not?
I should eat, of course. It looks delicious. I live to eat, you know?
Bring a fork.
Yes, Ma'am. Where do we keep forks?
Where are they? Down here? Where are all the forks?
Yes, just a moment. I was just in the elevator. Hang on.
Yes, you can talk now.
I can't even talk on the phone comfortably at home anymore.
Even if it's about work?
Get married, and you'll find out what it's like.
Anyway, I had a talk with Mr. Ahn and he's on board.
Don't worry about me and just move ahead with the project.
Pardon me?
Mr. Ahn thinks that Young Bin has signed a contract with me.
He won't want to work with me, though.
Whether it's with Ok Ja or whoever else, just go ahead with it.
How could I? You're the one who made it happen.
What can I do, though? It's all right.
What matters is Young Bin does the film he likes.
Okay.
All right, then. You're at home, right?
Pass on the great news to Young Bin.
- And don't tell him about me. - Pardon me?
I should tell him that you helped. You don't want him to know?
He has a lot of pride, you know? He doesn't like getting help.
He and I are strangers now.
Well, all right. I'll call you again soon.
Okay.
Gosh, there you are. My busy bee, Mr. Lee.
I've been busy because of you. It's all because of you.
It looks like you can do "Lim Hwa Su".
What?
How?
You know Mr. Ahn, right? He's going to produce the film.
You're going to sign a contract as soon as he buys the rights.
- He's not exactly fond of me. - He hates you.
You'll have to win him over now.
Gosh, I had no idea you were this capable.
How did you do that?
Stop asking. You're so full of questions.
That's why I was busy today. Are we good now?
No. You're acting strange.
You got all of that done without telling me a word about it?
I wanted to tell you only if I succeeded.
Otherwise, you'd get all stressed out and take it out on me.
I can't put up with that. No way.
Well, it's such great news but...
- it's a bit... - That's enough. I'm exhausted now.
Anyway, let's speak with Ms. Kang in person.
Gosh, we still have to go through that step.
Young Bin!
Where is Turtle?
He's been stuck in his room.
Did you guys have another fight?
- What's going on? - What's happening?
You irresponsible jerk.
- Get up. - What happened?
He took off from the set without a word.
Did you get a sudden urge to play games?
Did you come home to watch porn or what?
Turtle.
I didn't want to do anything.
Be more specific, will you?
Everything was getting on my nerves.
I get that you don't want to work.
You're finally doing something after wasting your life away.
Is it really that hard?
I hate you the most because you're so mean.
Why are you two being like this?
Calm down. Why are you getting so worked up?
Yes, let's drink together and shake it off. Get up, Turtle.
Look at him. Doesn't he look like a typical loser?
Yes.
I felt like a complete loser.
Everyone else on set has specialized tasks,
yet I was making instant noodles and delivering coffee for everyone.
What bothered me the most is how no one talked to me.
I had no presence there.
I thought I was a ghost.
Did they think I was a shadow?
Anyhow, I came home because I felt so pathetic.
Does that answer your question? Sorry.
Hey, I can certainly relate to that experience.
I went through the same thing when I worked in a film crew.
And when I was starting out as his manager... This guy was a handful.
I also went through that when I used to work as a background actor.
Who does he think he is?
- Joon, stop. - Are you...
- a hothouse flower or what? - Please.
- I'm sorry. - Say it again.
I said I'm sorry.
I did it to toughen you up.
People are cold. Everyone is alone after all.
I wanted to teach you that.
Look who's talking.
You need to learn before you teach me.
All right, I'm sorry.
Let's go to the set together tomorrow. I'll go easy on you.
I'll have to think about it.
Also, stop telling me that I'm clueless.
I heard it thousands of times from my teachers. I'm still traumatized.
Okay, I won't say it anymore.
Great. You guys are good now, right?
Come on. That's it. Everything's been resolved now.
You guys are so silly.
Hey, Ji An.
"Hey, Ji An."
What is he doing? His friend is depressed.
That betrayer.
Is a girl that important to you?
I really didn't want to say this.
You ugly brats, you two are just the same.
You little... Are you serious?
You'll regret saying that.
- Hey! - Hey!
Stop there!
You were here. What are you doing?
I'm picking out outfits for Joon's shoot tomorrow.
I'm supposed to hand them over to his stylist.
You really are his manager.
- Was it hard? - It's embarrassing. Stop now.
Everything's hard at first. I've been there.
I'll work really hard from tomorrow.
- Is Ho Jin asleep? - He passed out.
He's working so hard to get me that movie.
He's already asked around about who will produce the movie.
Ho Jin is the real manager.
He is, but don't say that to him. He'll get stuck up.
On my first day at work, I only caused trouble.
You're lucky to have Ho Jin and Mr. Kim.
Right. Mr. Kim is not with you anymore.
You said that on purpose, right?
No, I didn't. I'm not Ho Jin.
I'm going to hold hands with Ms. Kang.
Well, all right.
I thought you'd quit right away. You've grown up.
Young Bin, I'm more mature than you.
What? I have a job and used to have a girlfriend.
Do you have to touch your friend's sore spot?
It's bleeding.
- Let's have some beer. - I'd rather not.
Joon is working early tomorrow.
Let's just have 40 cans. Here.
- Let's have 50. - I can't do that.
Hello, Ms. Kang.
The production company will buy the rights,
so I think I'll be able to do "Lim Hwa Su".
Really?
I'd like to talk to you in person.
Are you saying...
you'd rather do that movie than the Chinese drama?
- Yes. I'll tell you in person. - I can't meet today.
I'm out of town today.
You are?
When could we...
Let's talk in a few days.
The situation might change by then. Let's talk again.
Okay.
I sent the contract by email to Manager Lee.
Check with him.
- It'll make you feel good. - Okay, I'll do that.
Is the film company owned by Mr. Ahn?
Yes, it is.
I'll call you back. Check the contract first.
Okay.
Who had Chinese food in the office?
The whole office stinks.
Eat somewhere else!
- Has the contract arrived? - Yes, it just came.
Why?
(Section 5: Sharing the Profits)
Are they offering that much down payment?
It's twice the amount Ms. Kang said last time.
What should I do?
She's determined to make you sign the contract.
The lunch break was a long time ago.
After eating delivery food, put the plates somewhere hidden.
They were at the door. I stained my clothes while moving them.
Give me wet wipes.
Be careful.
Hello, Mr. Ahn.
Right now?
Welcome.
Things have become so difficult.
I miss the old days.
I see you have company.
You're here.
Sit down.
I'd love to have a little drink.
Scoot over.
I'll pour you one.
Gosh.
Mr. Ahn and I haven't met in a while.
- We did a little catching up. - I see.
We're among the few old people left.
This field is full of those still wet behind the ears now.
Then get a coffin and chill out at home.
Watch your language in front of your senior.
Leave him alone.
I should have taught him a lesson a long time ago.
He's so stubborn,
and he thinks he now has his own head.
I've always had my own head.
You used to be so big.
You always had two portions of cup noodles.
If I remember correctly,
you had three portions.
- What? - That's right.
I've seen you doing that.
- I'm sure it was 2 portions. - It was 3.
When we went to karaoke,
you always mimicked Jung Won Kwan.
That's right.
Please forget it.
That was such a long time ago.
It's getting hot.
Jung Won Kwan has lost weight unlike a certain someone.
Let's stop talking about the past.
Say what you have to say. I know you two are up to something.
What is it? Spit it out.
You catch on fast.
You're so good at ruining others' plans...
and pushing ahead with yours. You haven't changed.
You even got Mr. Ahn involved behind my back.
That was fast.
I almost got tricked.
What are you talking about?
I was just helping Young Bin get a role.
That's nonsense.
You wanted to win his heart by helping him.
Young Bin is...
not going to do "Lim Hwa Su".
Why didn't you tell me?
You sounded like you were working with him.
He's going to make a contract with her.
And she's not going to let him do "Lim Hwa Su".
Who will do "Lim Hwa Su", then?
I'll introduce a top actor.
They can do it with another actor.
That sounds good.
- My goodness. - Do you want to help me, too?
I'll leave the old people alone.
I've sent him a contract, too.
The down payment will be double the original amount.
That much?
I take it seriously. He's worth it, too.
In addition to the down payment, if he appears on the Chinese drama,
he'll start making some money. That's a good thing, right?
Don't you think so?
Now,
get your hands off of him.
Please take good care of him.
- This way. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
She needs a little break.
Give her a little break, please.
See you.
- Thank you for today. - Thank you.
I had a lot of fun.
- See you. - See you.
Let's go.
Thank you for today. Drink some water.
She's an angel.
She's so cute.
She's prettier in real life. Are we done now?
There's just a short interview left.
They'll ask me how it was to be her manager.
I'll only say good things about her.
Hey, I heard it's her birthday tomorrow.
Shouldn't we prepare a cake?
- A cake? Right now? - Can you get one?
- Buy a nice one. - All right.
- Give it to me. - What do you mean?
Your credit card. I lost all my money to the girl in Jeju Island.
- I'm broke. - Gosh.
Hurry.
Give it to me.
Gosh, what are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
What's with you?
Why did it take so long?
There was no bakery around here.
Where's my card?
- Here. - Give me the receipt.
(56 dollars)
Are you crazy? It's too expensive.
It's for Geun Young.
Still, you could have bought something cheaper.
I'll take 30 dollars off your salary next month.
- Why? - Let me see the cake.
Gosh. When are we eating? I'm starving.
I ate while you were away.
- Darn it. - Take the cake out.
It's so annoying.
Hey!
Why did you stick your hand in there?
Can't you even do this?
How can you be so stupid?
- This way. - Why does he want to see me?
- She's here. Take this. - I'm not sure.
Why did you want to see me?
Happy birthday, dear Geun Young
Happy birthday to you
Ta-da!
Gosh.
The stupid brat bought such a tasty cake.
What? Do you want some?
Gosh, you jerk.
Darn it.
Seriously.
Happy birthday to you.
That punk.
What is this?
Hey!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I am.
You're out. You're fired.
I'm out? Are we playing baseball? I didn't want to do it anyway.
You won't be able to work in this field again.
I've never wanted to.
You brat.
I won't cook for you anymore. Clean your room yourself.
Young Bin is my cousin. Get out of his house.
Get lost, you idiot!
You're so childish.
I don't want to hang out with you anymore, either!
Let me give you a new nickname.
What about Mr. Prostate?
Look who's standing behind you.
You got a new nickname in front of her.
This is a historic moment.
What's with him?
Gosh!
Hey, stop right there, you punk!
- Stop her! - Geun Young!
Why are they delivering the contract in the parking lot?
I have no idea.
- What's that? - What's going on?
Isn't that the bread guy?
He is.
Look at that.
What's going on?
- Hello. - Hello.
Did you get a new car?
It looks amazing.
Here's the contract signed by Ms. Kang.
Please sign it and send it to the office.
Okay.
Also, here's a present from Ms. Kang.
- Sorry? - Sorry?
Check your contract.
It says, "Down payment plus some extra benefits".
Is this...
Exactly.
- I'll get going then. - Okay.
- See you. - Are you leaving it here?
See you.
What's going on?
She's almost forcing you to sign the contract.
I think she's overestimating you.
What should I do now?
This is really nice but...
But?
Wait.
(Ms. Kang Ok Ja)
- It's Ms. Kang. - Answer it.
- Hello. - Hi.
Did you get the present?
Yes, we just did.
Is Young Bin there? Can you put him on, too?
Okay.
Hello, Ms. Kang.
I have some updates on "Lim Hwa Su".
Okay.
I think someone else will do it.
Wait. Did Mr. Ahn say that?
Yes, I met him.
He did consider Young Bin, but then he changed his mind.
That's... But I met him...
I'll explain tomorrow.
Let me tell you this.
You can start on the Chinese drama right away.
Enjoy my present today.
I'll be looking forward to good news tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Gosh, I'm getting a headache.
- What happened? - Let's try the car.
This is nice indeed.
It must be extremely expensive. It makes me nervous.
Do you like it?
I don't even like driving. She didn't have to buy me this.
What are you going to do?
I'm not sure.
Am I really not doing "Lim Hwa Su"?
I don't know what happened. Mr. Ahn said you could do it.
You met him, right?
Yes, we met him.
"We"? Were you with someone?
Mr. Kim.
- It's just... - Why didn't you tell me?
He was with me.
- What are you doing? - Me?
- You're making that face again. - What do you mean?
I think I should call the pastor again.
No, no. That's not it.
Hello, Mr. Kim.
- Young Bin. - Have you been well?
Yes, I've been working and pooping.
- As always. - You haven't changed.
Why are you here?
Young Bin has something to tell you.
He does? What is it?
- Tell him. - Go ahead.
I heard you tried to get me on "Lim Hwa Su".
Well...
Manager Lee did most of it. I just tagged along.
I heard everything.
Despite your effort, I lost the role.
Did Ms. Kang not approve?
Mr. Ahn chose another actor.
I see.
I was feeling depressed,
so I came to see you with this car.
Is it from Ms. Kang?
She must have spent a fortune.
But I can't have it.
Why not?
I'm going to work with you.
What?
- Is he using drugs? - That's absurd.
Or is he drinking a lot?
My goodness.
Are you serious?
Yes, I've been regretting my decision.
I also feel indebted to you for helping me.
Ho Jin has been nagging me to work with you, too.
He's a smart boy. He'll become successful.
He's not Cup Noodles anymore.
He's the King of Cup Noodles now.
What's so funny?
It's just a little bit funny.
Just as little as Hee Dong's.
Who's Hee Dong?
He's my old friend. His thing is this small.
- Gosh. - What are you talking about?
This is so funny.
Let me see. What are you going to do with this car?
I should return it.
Should we have some fun with it before that?
Can I drive?
Sure.
I'll give it some scratches. Get in.
What?
- Okay. - Look at this.
- It's fantastic. - It's nice, right?
This is what a car should be like.
- Can't you buy me one of these? - Are you kidding me?
My foot is barely on, but it goes so fast.
It's amazing.
- It's nice. - You look happy.
Of course. We're back together.
(Entourage)
We're not here to butter up the director.
We want to see if we like the director.
We don't need you two here.
Young Bin, come alone next time.
He's crazy.
I was so touched by your works.
What is this place?
Come out!
Hey!
Since he started working for the actress, he's been ignoring us.
That crazy brat caused another problem.
The main character is a girl, not you.
We should tell them.
I'll tell them to stick to the original version.