(Entourage)
One, two, three.
Gosh.
Keep your rods high up.
Like that. There you go.
Is this really necessary?
You need some practice beforehand. Fishing is not easy.
We don't have to go sea fishing.
We should celebrate working on "Lim Hwa Su" together.
It'll be fun. I already borrowed a boat, too.
Now that we're on the same boat, why don't we get on a real boat?
A while ago, you were on Ok Ja's side and didn't want the movie.
Back then, I didn't know you'd bring Young Bin.
Also, you've gone behind my back many times.
Let's say we're even now.
- We're even. - Fine.
Let's work hard and make some progress.
All right.
By the way, don't we know who will direct the movie yet?
The dramatization process has already begun.
We'll make a contract with a director soon, too.
- Who will it be? - It'll be Director Yang Man Ho.
He's directed many short films.
He's won many awards at overseas independent film festivals, too.
Have you watched any of his works?
No. What about you?
I've only heard of his name.
Will it be his first full-length film?
- Yes. - Will it be okay?
Trust me.
He's a rare talent. He's amazing.
What about investors?
There's been one investment company that has shown interest.
Nothing is determined yet.
Just meet the director first. The script is being written.
- Okay. - Okay.
Enough of business talk. Let's throw the lines again.
We're ready.
Are you ready? Remember what we practiced.
One, two, three.
Okay.
We could have met outside.
He must be working on the script.
We haven't watched any of his previous works. Will it be okay?
Should we have postponed the meeting?
Forget it. We're not here to flatter him.
We just want to see if we like him.
He's a newbie.
If we don't like him, I'll tell Mr. Ahn to find a replacement.
What? We can't do that.
We should. We set up this project. Am I wrong?
It's here.
- Is it here? - Yes.
Okay.
Hello.
Did Cuckoo in Yangpyeong send you here?
I told him I'd pay him back when I get the down payment.
Why does he keep sending these people here?
- I'm not scared at all. - Wait.
I'm Kim Eun Gab from Tiger's Den.
- This is Young Bin. - Hello.
I see.
All right.
- Let's go in. - Should we go in?
Are we going in?
- Take a seat. - Go ahead.
I have such a terrible hangover.
- Should I order something for you? - We're okay.
I'm Kim Eun Gab.
Thank you. I have no business cards.
You must be the CEO, and this is Young Bin.
Who are you?
I'm his manager.
Could you leave us alone?
I don't like to have too many people in here.
He's Young Bin's manager. Introduce yourself.
I see.
You look so young.
I'm Lee Ho Jin.
By the way,
you look just like a bully we had in the army.
- Sorry? - His name was Lee Ho Sun.
I even remember his name. He was such a jerk.
Are you related by any chance?
- No, we aren't. - I see.
You do look like him, though.
You look exactly like him. Gosh, that jerk.
Well...
Why don't we talk outside?
I've been here for a few minutes, and the dust is irritating my nose.
Those Hollywood idiots.
They always have to mutilate women. Those perverts.
Well...
Have you heard about the erotic movie "Sticking the Flag In"?
It's a parody movie.
In the movie, Koreans slaughter Americans. I'm suddenly reminded.
What were you saying?
I suggested we talk about "Lim Hwa Su" outside.
I don't go out while working on scripts.
Also,
I can talk to Young Bin.
I don't need you two here.
Young Bin, come alone next time.
You've been so...
- What's wrong? - Sorry?
My goodness.
I thought you were alone.
Why didn't you call me before you come?
- Go in. - What's going on here?
Let's go in.
- Goodness. - I think I'm getting a stroke.
- Gosh. - What's with him?
I know.
I've met many directors so far,
but he's just too weird.
He's like that all the time.
You need to be weird to make good movies.
You know that.
I'm not sure if I want to let Young Bin work with that newbie.
All right.
Okay. Bye.
What did he say?
The contract will be signed after the script is finished.
He'll reconsider it if you really don't want him.
What do you think?
I have no idea. We didn't have any conversation.
As soon as we met, he talked about a bully...
that looked like me. How could he do that?
There are many crazy directors.
Some of them do make good movies,
but some are just downright crazy. He belongs to the latter.
He's just crazy.
I'm scared he'll ruin the movie. What do you think, Young Bin?
Let's talk after watching his movie.
Keep your eyes peeled.
If the movie is not good, we'll dump him.
Ho Jin, come to the office every morning from tomorrow.
Sorry?
Why? I have only one actor to manage.
I'm thinking of giving you another one.
- Sorry? - You don't like it?
- Who? - Are you getting nervous?
I'll tell you who it is.
This is a nice office.
I'm sharing it with the other managers anyway.
This desk doesn't look good. Let's get a new one.
That's unnecessary.
By the way, are you okay with my working for another actor?
You decide. Don't worry about me.
If you're not happy about it, I'll talk to Mr. Kim.
If you start to care less about me, I won't...
Take this.
Gosh.
Eun Gab must trust you.
- You won his recognition. - They're just short-handed.
Are things okay between you and Ji An?
It must be awkward because I didn't make a contract with Ms. Kang.
She hasn't said anything about it, but I feel a bit bad.
I don't feel comfortable about meeting Ms. Kang, either.
I see.
You lost favor with your future mother-in-law.
Where are Turtle and Joon, by the way?
I don't know.
Look at this hat I found.
I think it'll be my favorite hat.
It's old-fashioned, just like you.
It looks like it's from the times of "Lim Hwa Su".
Don't you think people recognize me?
Not even clerks are paying attention to us.
Excuse me, are you the one in "I'm Just Me"?
- Yes, I am. - Oh, my.
- I'm Cha Joon. - Really? I was right.
My goodness. Can I have a picture with you?
- Sure. - Really? Thank you.
My pleasure.
What should we do?
- I'm just me. - I'm just me.
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
Oh, my.
- Did you see that? - I did.
Can I get a bag?
- What are you looking at? - I'm searching social media...
for the picture we just took.
Here it is.
Why? What does it say?
"With Comedian Cha Joon..."
You were very funny on that show.
Doesn't she know I'm an actor?
You're introduced as a television personality on portals.
Still?
I asked my company to change it to actor.
Then again, I'm not an actor.
Why are you so depressed? You found a nice hat.
Forget it. An actor should act.
Mr. Kim will take care of you now that you signed the contract.
He'll probably just find me some auditions.
I'm over 30, and I haven't had any significant roles.
I'm not even given any names. I'm just Friend 1 or Neighbor 3.
I'm just a number.
I'd love to have a role that has a name.
Let's just call Mr. Kim now.
Forget it.
Is it that hard, you coward?
Coward? Do you think I don't have the courage?
Can't he do a better job?
This is why he got fired.
Speak clearly.
Mr. Kim, are you busy?
Yes, I'm too busy to even clean my ears.
My ears have been itchy. Is someone talking about me?
- Were you? - No.
I wasn't.
My occupation hasn't changed on the portals.
What?
Give me a second.
Just a second.
Gosh, what is it?
Haven't you revised Joon's profile?
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Did you tell me to?
I write down everything you tell me to do.
- Hang on. - Cha Joon's profile...
Look carefully.
You have terrible handwriting. Can't you write any better?
Wait.
Joon, I'll call you back. I have an urgent call coming in.
It's me.
Yes.
Really?
Tomorrow? It's perfect. Okay.
All right. Bye.
Did you hear any good news?
Order a plant.
One of the biggest actors will join us.
- Who is it? - Oh Chang Seok.
Who's that?
Watch some movies and dramas. Don't just watch music videos.
By the way, when will I get a regular employment?
You don't even know actors' names. You can't become a manager yet.
Just revise Joon's profile, okay?
Okay, Boss.
Gosh.
You're so annoying.
- Am I annoying? - What is wrong with you?
What happened now?
I can't stand his mood swings.
That's what I want to say.
Did you fight again? Just break up. Aren't you getting sick of it?
You two are just the same.
You came in time. Let's watch the movie together.
I'm not in the mood. What are you watching?
It's by the director who will direct "Lim Hwa Su". We met him today.
- What was he like? - He's crazy.
Crazy people make good movies.
They just put on a show to look like artists.
Think of Bong Joon Ho or Park Chan Wook.
They're normal people, and they make great movies.
- I thought he was funny. - Do you think that's funny?
Did anything happen?
He said Ho Jin reminded him of a bully he met in the army.
It's not about that.
Anyway, I didn't like him.
Let's watch the movie first.
(Put your hands up.)
That was amazing.
What did you think?
Gosh, that jerk knows how to make a great movie.
He'll be perfect as the director of "Lim Hwa Su".
- I know. - Gosh.
I was so touched.
I'd love to work with him.
Could we all be invited to Cannes?
Wouldn't it be hilarious if I tagged along?
You pay for your flights.
- I'll pay for them. - Forget it.
- Don't. - Are you tagging along there, too?
Gosh.
Do you feel guilty about something?
Or are you having a fit? Why do you flinch?
Because we go to similar restaurants, we keep crossing paths.
Let's get something straight. I come here more often than you.
Exactly eight years ago, I introduced this place to you.
Are you forgetting things? Is it dementia? Go see a doctor.
Why did you get an office near mine?
Gosh. Forget it. I don't want to talk to you.
You just ran out of things to say. You're ridiculous.
I introduced this place to you.
And you tried to take Young Bin from me, too. You must be feeling guilty.
You...
Gosh.
She's going senile.
I wanted to eat here.
You're late.
I'm on time. You were early.
Hey, you look great. Are you getting injections?
I was just born this way.
Anyway, you made the right decision.
A small and competent company like this is the best.
But...
I haven't said that I decided to work with you.
You said so on the phone yesterday.
I even prepared a contract.
I said it'd be nice. I didn't say I'd do it.
I'm thinking about it.
You think for so long.
You don't think a lot when you meet women.
You don't need to think when you meet them.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Hey, Boss. - Knock before you come in.
- Sorry. Hello. - Hello.
Give it to me.
Who is she?
She's my employee, of course. What else would she be?
Gosh.
You're very handsome.
Oh, my.
You're very funny. You have good eyes for people, too.
Eun Gab.
I'll sign the contract right away if she can be my manager.
Me?
- Are you sure? - Yes.
Yes!
What's up, man?
My goodness.
How old are you?
- I'm... - Go back to work.
Bye.
Keep this.
- Has he left? - Yes, he has.
Gosh, he keeps changing his mind.
He's so sly.
Really? He seemed nice.
If he signs the contract, can I be his manager?
You've been talking about becoming a manager a lot.
You don't seem to trust me.
I can do it. Trust me.
Wait a little more.
You should also be able to write Korean.
Practice, okay?
I'm darn good at Korean now.
This is what I'm talking about. Watch your language.
All I hear are swear words.
I learn it from you.
- That little... - Cut it out.
I decide what I say.
You're good. Is playing games the only thing you do?
I almost failed to get into university because of it.
Gosh.
I hate to have people in my studio,
but I like you.
Who's that old man?
He's my cousin. He's an actor, too.
Hello, I'm actor Cha Joon.
I was so touched by your movie.
I see.
And... The bully is here again. You annoy me.
Sorry?
Is the script ready?
I'm working hard on it. It'll be ready soon.
Exactly when will it be ready?
Are you bullying me?
It'll be ready in time. What are you worried about?
I'm sorry, but can you stop calling me a bully?
Mr. Lee majored in film. He has an eye for movies.
Goal!
Gosh, I quit.
You want to be on the movie?
It'd be great if you could give him an audition.
Yes. I'd love...
to appear as one of Lim Hwa Su's subordinates.
- Which one? - General Lee Choon Bong.
Try it.
- Do you remember the lines? - Right now?
There's no special time for acting.
You need to be able to do it right away. Forget it if you can't.
I can do it. I'll try.
I'll do it right now.
"You jerks. Do you know who I am?"
"I'm Lim Hwa Su's right-hand man, Lee Choon Bong. I'm so dumbfounded."
"My name means a phoenix."
"Choon Bong."
"A cuckoo lays eggs in front of a phoenix?"
"I'll cut your head off."
That was nice.
"I'll cut your head off." It was so dramatic. Good job.
- Thank you. - Let's play another round.
Go, Director Yang.
- Hello. - Isn't this office so nice?
Don't watch any pornography in here.
It's a nice office, indeed.
You don't look so happy.
We met Director Yang today. It was annoying.
Why?
I don't know why, but he keeps picking on me.
He is weird.
I'll talk to Mr. Ahn...
and see what we can do.
Young Bin likes him, though.
We watched his movie,
and it was nice.
They were?
Really?
Then there's no problem.
As long as he can do his job,
what can we do even if he's a jerk?
("The Restructuring of Memory")
Have you read this?
Yes, I liked it.
There have been many fantasy movies,
but it has interesting characters.
Right? I went to so much trouble to get this one.
Lee El doesn't like it. She doesn't have an eye for movies.
- She only listens to her mother. - I'll talk to her.
Good luck.
You've only worked for Young Bin.
Yes.
It'll be different with her.
She's not your friend. You need to win her trust.
I see.
Are you scared or something? Be confident.
Make her trust you.
You're meeting her for the first time today, right?
Yes. I'm heading out soon.
Do you want me to come with you?
I'm okay.
Good luck. Don't get nervous in front of a beautiful actress.
- All right. - Okay.
Hello, I'm Lee Ho Jin.
Hello. Just a second.
I've heard a lot about you from Mr. Kim.
You look young.
Thank you.
You're working for only Young Bin, right?
Yes.
Why did you want to see me?
It's about the next movie.
I heard you didn't like the script.
I didn't. The story is too complicated.
Going back and forth in time. Will people like it?
You have a point. They might be tired of fantasy movies.
But the script was quite nice.
I think it'll be a hit if you ask me.
But it's a supporting role. I don't want any more of those.
Well...
You could see it that way, too.
But the character itself is even stronger than the main one.
That's what burdens me.
It's too strong.
Right, but you had a few strong roles when you had just debuted.
I love your acting.
Those roles were...
so nice that I can never forget.
- Is that so? - Yes.
Still, I want to do something else.
I heard you usually choose works by yourself.
Yes. I need to like the movie. Otherwise, I don't do it.
Of course.
Now, you're working with us.
Why don't you have a little trust in us?
Mr. Kim and I think it'd be great if you could do this movie.
You're very unusual.
You seem very nervous, but you say all you want to say.
- I do? - Yes.
I'm sorry.
Fine.
I'll read the script again.
Really? Thank you.
Are you getting a desk for Ho Jin's office?
Yes. It's his first office.
A desk would be meaningful.
You care so much about your manager unlike someone.
Are you still thinking about it?
He said I did a good job, but he hasn't given me the role.
Meet up with him and talk some more.
Meet him often and win his heart.
I'm too shy.
Why do I feel so uncomfortable around older men?
You still feel uncomfortable around Eun Gab, too.
They must feel uncomfortable because you look even older than them.
You look older than Young Bin and Ho Jin, too.
- Is it because of porn? - That's correct.
- I'll tell Ho Jin to come here. - Do that.
Where are you? Do you want to come here?
I can't. I'm having a meeting.
I see. When will you be done?
I think I'll stay for dinner. Did something happen?
It's nothing. All right.
He's been ignoring us since he started working for the actress.
You're not his top priority anymore.
Cut it out. I'll have to choose.
Should I give the director some furniture as a present?
Just buy him some drinks and take him to clubs.
That sounds great.
Oh, my.
Gosh.
Why is he sleeping here half-naked?
Be quiet.
Don't wake him up.
Why did you bring him here?
It's his fault. He made him drink.
He was a handful when he was drunk.
- Do you know what he said? - What did he say this time?
I don't remember well,
but he apparently implied that he'd cast Joon.
Although he was very drunk, he clearly said,
"You're great."
"The role is yours."
Will he remember it?
Of course.
Congratulations. Send him home now.
- You really don't like him. - He looks down on me.
You deserve to be looked down on.
That's life.
You need to be patient and flatter others.
Are you using your cousin to get a role?
If I try to put up with him, we'll end up in a fight.
You're up. I made some soup.
I don't eat anything after drinking.
You'll hurt your stomach. I'll get you a glass.
Gosh.
Young Bin, are you busy today?
- No, I'm not. - That's great.
Can you go somewhere with me?
I'm visiting there for the script. It'll help you as well.
- All right. - Okay.
You're not coming, are you?
- No. - All right.
Can I come with you?
Sure.
Young Bin, can I borrow some clothes?
This way.
Come this way.
He's like a butler.
- Gosh. - Are you really not coming?
I'm meeting Lee El.
Again? Are you favoring her because she's a woman?
It seems like you're enjoying it.
It's just work.
You're neglecting me these days.
Have fun with the director.
Are you a couple?
What?
I hope I don't end up tagging along.
Joon, why is he wearing that hat?
I told him I bought it for the movie, and he took it.
What is this place?
Let me introduce you to the guys.
You've seen him on television, right? This is Young Bin.
Hello.
They're his friends.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Sit down. - Okay.
Who's that?
Where are we?
He's a former member of a gang.
He's retired now. He runs a business here.
I see.
I come here often to cover stories. You should, too.
It'll come in handy when you do "Lim Hwa Su".
Okay.
Excuse me.
What exactly is the business they're running?
The deadline is coming up. Are you ready for it?
- You're telling me that now? - They must be lenders by name...
when in fact, they're something else.
I know what you mean. Be quiet.
I want to leave.
The director wants us to observe the people here.
He said it'll improve our acting.
What does that have to do with me? It won't be of any help to me.
How will this help me?
If you keep this up, I'll have to pay you a visit!
Can you keep it down?
Yes, Sir.
Joon.
They must really be gangsters.
I said be quiet.
Where's Young Bin?
He went outside to talk to the director.
We should go outside, too.
Should we?
I'm going to kill that scumbag.
Cheers. Drink up.
We emailed you the new script.
Let us know what you think.
Already?
Okay, I will.
We just added a new female character to the original script.
A female character?
You'll see.
Young Bin.
I'd like you to put on 10kg.
That'll make you look more like a gangster.
- I'll do that. - Okay.
Forget being handsome and dashing.
We need you to focus on acting.
We want something lifelike and realistic.
Okay. That's the kind of movie I like.
I like Kathryn Bigelow's movies and "Sicario".
subtitles ripped and synced by riri13
Exactly.
You read my mind.
I'm going to make a perfect reproduction of the era.
You know the theater scene at the climax, right?
I really want to do a good job on that one.
- The scene where the fire starts? - Yes.
I don't want to shoot it on a set. I'll go down to the countryside...
and either buy or rent a theater.
I'm just going to set the whole thing on fire.
I'd like that, too,
- but what about the budget? - I'll ask the production company.
That's what the director and the actor think is best for the movie.
What are they going to do about it?
- Right. - Yes.
That being said, I'll call them right now.
Now?
That man is a lunatic!
I told you so.
Does he think this is my lunch money he's taking?
Does he expect me to hand him over millions of dollars just like that?
We never said we're shooting a block-buster.
What are we going to do, then?
He wants to build a complete set in the countryside.
He won't use computer graphics. He wants the real thing.
I mean, this isn't Hollywood.
What did I tell you? I told you he'd be like that.
Yes.
Hey, Joy. Tell Manager Lee that I want to see him.
He didn't come in yet.
Give him a call and tell him I need to discuss something.
Why the sour face? Are you upset with me?
I'm not your secretary.
All I do is make phone calls. When am I going to be a manager?
Then don't do it. Gosh, you're so whiny.
What? Are you talking to me?
No, not at all.
What are you going to do? Should we get a new director?
Isn't your skin dry? Come closer.
It's nice that you work at an office now.
You even have time to drink tea with me.
- Have you met Lee El? - Yes.
It's weird having to work with someone other than Young Bin.
I bet it is.
It must feel like you're getting real work done.
I guess you could say that.
Is she pretty?
She's all right.
What? Does it bother you?
Of course, it does. You're tagging along with a pretty woman.
I found a new side in you, Suh Ji An.
What about Young Bin? Is he sad to let you go?
He's best friends now with the director of "Lim Hwa Su".
People might think they've been friends forever.
You're the one who's bothered the most.
That's nonsense.
- Are you sad to see them like that? - Of course not. Why would I be?
Hold on.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
We have to go with Director Yang. Why would they get a new director?
I knew you'd say that.
But Mr. Kim doesn't like him and Mr. Ahn is furious.
He's asking for a bigger budget and was very rude to them.
What else did he say?
He called Mr. Ahn a miser who knows nothing about movies.
That's just the way he talks.
He's doing all that for the movie.
That's not right.
You can't take his side for something like that?
I'm not taking his side.
Forget it. I just wish we find investors for the movie.
- Are you still with him? - Yes.
I really shouldn't have had that last drink.
Hey, I'm really liking this hat.
You can have it.
Should I wear this and run around in my panties.
In my panties, in my panties
Would you like that?
Director.
That role of Lee Choon Bong...
I'm doing it, right? That's what you said.
I said that?
That's what you said. I heard you say it.
I don't remember saying that.
You think you can pull off a gangster role?
You don't have the face for it.
Not to mention your body.
There are skinny and fast gangsters out there.
You know, like Sirasoni.
Lee Choon Bong has to be big.
He's a real tough guy with a muscular body.
I'll work out, then.
I'll work out.
I'm confident that I'll look like Ma Dong Seok by the day of shooting.
Having the body is one thing,
but you also need to have the look and the aura.
You're lacking them.
I'm not feeling it.
I have to go to the bathroom. I can't hold it in anymore.
He doesn't remember.
What if he doesn't remember about today?
At least he hasn't rejected me yet.
Okay.
I'm going to do method acting. I'll be a real gangster.
A real gangster.
You're wasting your time again.
Hey.
Actors who played homeless roles...
lived with actual homeless people for months.
I know that, but what does getting a tattoo have to do with acting?
Don't you get it?
Did you not see their tattoos? Tattoos are symbolic.
I'll be able to immerse myself in the character with this.
Actors like Tom Hardy do look cool with tattoos. But you?
I'll look like a real man.
A real man.
You'd look like a South American drug dealer.
Shut it.
This feels like the time I got circumcised. I'm so nervous.
What kind of tattoo are you going to get?
Dragon? Tiger? Carp?
Aren't they too much?
You need a tiger on your body to look like a real gangster.
Wouldn't a big tattoo like that hurt a lot?
I have a good idea. You should get it on your face.
You should get a tattoo of a tiger's whiskers and a nose.
Do you want me to beat you up?
Mr. Cha Joon?
(Lee Choon Bong)
Yes, Toni Kroos.
Can you take a shower?
I can't get water on my tattoo just yet.
Don't I look tough?
No, you look old and nasty.
You don't know what it feels like to be a strong man.
Why "Lee Choon Bong"? Aren't you worried about after the movie?
It's okay.
It's the name of my first role ever.
I've always been something like Friend 2, Neighbor 3.
Now, I'm Lee Choon Bong.
What if you don't get the part?
That'll be worse than a tattoo of an ex-girlfriend's name.
Watch it.
Don't touch me with Vaseline on your hand.
Watch your mouth. Jerk.
Did you go over the new script?
I was going to after you go over it.
Why did that lunatic edit it like this?
Can you ask him? I think I'm going crazy.
What is it this time? Stop picking on him.
You're not the leading role anymore. It's some female character.
What are you talking about?
I knew this would happen. That psycho has done it again.
A female leading role?
You and Young Bin have to go see Director Yang. Got it?
Get him to revert the changes he's made.
Do as I say. Hold on.
I'm getting a call. I'll call you back.
Chang Seok. I called you yesterday. Thanks for calling me back.
I have good news for you.
I'm going to sign the contract.
You made a good decision.
Send me the contract and I'll sign it.
Can you get Joy Jung to deliver me the contract?
What? Why?
She'll be my manager anyway. I'd like to befriend her in advance.
Of course.
Okay. Bye.
We'll sign Oh Chang Seok today. Actually, you will.
Me? Why?
Can you stop being like that?
I'm making you a manager.
- Are you serious? - Of course.
- Seriously? - Yes.
But you have to be careful. He's a real lady's man.
He hits on every woman he sees.
He hits women?
He... He hits on them.
- He hits them? - No.
He hits on them. He likes to hit on women.
What does that mean?
It means...
How do I explain this?
What does "hitting on someone" mean? "To hit on someone"...
- A playboy? - A playboy.
He's a real scumbag.
I see.
I'll take care of myself. Don't worry.
Okay.
Good thing Director Yang will be coming here.
I can't go out with Joon looking like that.
That's how much I look like a gangster.
It's because you're embarrassing.
What are you going to tell him?
We need to be straightforward.
I'm going to tell him that we should stick to the original script.
Let's start talking.
By the way, shouldn't we be drinking...
when we're talking about the script?
Do you have any malt whiskey at home?
Director, about that edited script...
Don't call it that. It's our new script now.
I'm not going to change anything about it now.
How did you like it?
To be honest, I couldn't understand it.
I can't understand that you don't understand it.
What could you not understand about it?
- It's the female role. - I wasn't asking you.
Tell me.
The female role stands out too much that it overshadows Lim Hwa Su.
And it's nothing like the true story.
We're not doing a documentary here.
I changed it like that to give it a cinematic aspect.
Then why is the movie called, "Lim Hwa Su"?
It's a story about some actress from the 1950s.
What does a mere manager know about movies?
Are managers not allowed to have their say? Let go of me.
Frankly, the original script was much better than this.
What?
Gosh, find yourself a new director, then.
Sure.
- I quit. - Suit yourself.
Director Yang. Please.
- Ho Jin. - He started it.
I get it. I'll go talk to him.
Did you talk to him? Is he going to change it back?
We're going with the new script.
What did you say just now?
He has his intentions.
Stop being so negative and take a look at it again.
Don't be so judgmental.
You're the one who can't see clearly.
You're trusting him way too much.
He's trustworthy.
You said so yourself that you like his movies.
Don't you trust me?
You just don't like him for who he is.
Think whatever you like.
Where are you going now?
I have to go take care of something for Lee El. What?
But we're not done here.
You're going to do what Director Yang tells you to anyway.
Do whatever you want with "Lim Hwa Su". I don't care anymore.
How can you do this to me?
Do you only work with that person now?
Yes. She actually listens to me. Are you satisfied?
- Director Yang. - Yes?
I...
I got a tattoo.
- You got that? - Yes.
Lee Choon Bong is pretentious and narcissistic.
So I thought he'd have a tattoo of his own name.
Is this real?
It's not henna. It's a real tattoo.
That's amazing.
You flatter me.
This is the least an actor could do to get into character.
I am Lee Choon Bong and Lee Choon Bong is me.
I am one with Lee Choon Bong.
That's nice.
("I'm Just Me")
These are all scripts for variety shows.
Do you not have any movie scripts?
No.
Wait. You're Horse Lady Cha Joon?
- He's also known as Mr. Prostate. - I see.
I've never seen that show.
It's pretty funny.
By the way,
how long are you going to do variety shows?
Actors shouldn't do variety shows.
It gives actors comical images.
You said you want to do method acting.
You shouldn't be funny.
Come on. Have a drink.
It's just that I'm working right now.
May I have your signature?
I'm going to sign it.
Okay. I'll sign it right now...
if you knock this back.
What?
But that's...
You're really stubborn, aren't you?
I thought you were the cute type.
You should listen to me.
Women should listen to men.
Excuse me,
but women don't have to listen to men.
You're adorable. My gosh.
You're my manager, right?
You just need to listen to me.
Bottoms up.
If you don't drink this, I won't sign the contract.
Can you imagine how furious Eun Gab will be?
There you go.
There you go. It's not bad, is it?
Sit next to me.
It's okay. Come on.
Where are you? I've been waiting for you forever.
I'm almost there. I just need to cross the bridge.
You sound happy. Did you sign him today?
Yes, he dragged on for long, but he signed it eventually.
He should be signing it as we speak.
Let's go somewhere fancy tonight. I'll be there soon.
Okay.
Where are you?
He signed the contract, right?
Yes, but the thing is...
I think he's very drunk.
He keeps making me drink. He won't let me go home.
What? You should've left after you got his signature.
You said you'd take care of it.
He said we had to celebrate.
He's contracted with our agency now.
I couldn't refuse.
Just get out of there.
How will I ever trust him with you now?
I'm sorry.
Did you drink a lot, too?
Yes, but...
I'll take care of myself.
I'll do well. Don't worry.
Hello?
Are you hanging up on me now?
It doesn't sound like you're taking care of it.
Do I have to go over there? Gosh.
That little...
That scumbag.
Gosh.
You're cute.
Chang Seok.
Hey, Eun Gab.
What are you doing here?
I thought I should have a drink with you.
Let's send her home. You're busy, aren't you? Go home.
Why would you send her home? I like the mood right now.
I like the mood, too.
Get out.
What is this, Eun Gab?
You talk like I'm going to do something to her.
I don't mind it,
but other people might get the wrong idea.
You should be careful not to get involved in scandals.
Speaking of which, let's have a guy be your manager.
Are you kidding me?
What do you take me for?
You sure know how to tick someone off.
Hey.
Let's not get vulgar.
Eun Gab.
Is this how you treat me right after I sign the contract?
You said you'd be good to me if I signed it.
Where's that contract again?
I'm not signing you. Let's call it off.
You only pretend to be a gentleman on screen.
I'm not going to sign a dog in heat like you.
Don't you try this again with any other person.
I'll go talk to the reporters.
Come out.
Why you little...
Mr. Kim.
Is this really okay? We had to go through trouble to sign him.
Forget it. The last thing we need is a lowly scumbag like him.
Did you drink a lot?
My gosh.
Follow me. I'll give you a ride.
I'm really sorry.
There are...
way more good-natured actors like Young Bin.
Have some patience. I'll make you a manager one day.
A manager?
Manager Joy? Are you serious?
Do you do drugs?
Are you bipolar or something?
One moment, you're upset and suddenly, you're nice.
You're like that, too.
But you were so cool back there.
Good boy.
Don't be rude.
How am I going to explain this to my wife?
I got a call from Mr. Ahn. Stay right there.
I have a missed call.
Hello, Mr. Ahn. You called?
Mr. Kim. Aren't we going fishing?
Fine. Let's go fishing.
By the way, a big investor wants to meet up.
I'm going to meet him today to decide.
Really? Where are you?
Oh, there he is. I'll call you back.
Hello?
Follow me.
- Have a seat. - Thank you.
You must've been surprised when I said I wanted to meet.
I was. I thought you weren't interested in "Lim Hwa Su".
Not at all. We used to be the main investing company.
We did bail out, but we've always been interested.
- I see. - Do you have a director?
You've probably heard of Mr. Yang Man Ho.
Oh, Mr. Yang. He's a good director.
Yes.
I'm expecting a lot from him. He has a distinct philosophy.
He can also be a lunatic.
It's better than being ordinary.
Such actors and directors get the job done.
Of course.
I've always wanted to work with him. I hope I do this time.
Whom do you have in mind for the role of Lim Hwa Su?
We have an actor already.
You've heard of Cha Young Bin, right?
- Oh, Cha Young Bin? - Yes.
Did you go over the script?
Yes.
I didn't like it that you wanted to see me without my manager,
but I liked the script, so here I am.
That's a relief.
When I was working on my script, I was thinking about you.
I've always considered you as a talented actor.
You're only a rookie, but you're so good.
You're fearless.
Most importantly, you're so beautiful.
You don't have a boyfriend, do you?
No.
- You're playing Lim Hwa Su, right? - Yes.
I'm such a big fan. You look much better in person.
Thank you.
How can an actress be a fan of another actor?
Let's be honest. Young Bin isn't the good-looking type.
He's about average.
Compared to actors like Won Bin and Kang Dong Won,
he's on the ugly side.
You're right.
No, he's not.
Young Bin is much better looking.
How do you like me?
- What? - Oh, I didn't mean it that way.
How do you like me as your partner? Do I fit the role?
I'm not sure. It's Director Yang's opinion that matters.
Do you have a girlfriend?
- Am I coming off as rude? - No, I don't have one.
Why not? Rumor has it that you're quite the lady's man.
You always end up dating the female actress of your movies.
Was it An So Hee? That's right. You've dated her.
Are you drunk?
No, not at all.
Let me make this clear just in case.
Actors should only be focused on their acting.
I don't tolerate their getting romantically involved.
You can't call someone like that an actor.
Someone like that is a scumbag.
A playboy. That's all.
I really hope you work on that.
Okay.
Yes, Mr. Kim.
How did things go with the script for "Lim Hwa Su"?
Young Bin said he'll take care of it.
Take care of what?
- Did you two fight? - No, it's not like that.
Is he with you now?
No, I'm at work right now.
I have a meeting with Lee El.
But I've been waiting for three hours now.
She said she'd be back from dinner, but she hasn't called back yet.
She's never on time.
She thinks her manager should always wait for her.
Get an answer from her about the drama.
- Okay. - By the way,
don't forget we're going fishing with Mr. Ahn tomorrow.
Okay.
Hello, Lee El. I'm Manager Lee.
Where are you right now? Are you still at the dinner?
Yes. I don't think I can make it today.
Can we do the meeting tomorrow?
Yes. I guess it can't be helped.
By the way, what are your thoughts on the drama?
You said you'd give me an answer by today.
I don't want to do it. Keep looking for something else.
What?
Why all of a sudden?
My mom says it's too serious and boring.
I want to do romantic comedy or just romance.
Okay, then.
Have a good night.
He's still hitting on her.
What's wrong with him? He's so weird.
I don't know anymore.
Just let it go, Joon. You'll feel much better.
I even got a tattoo.
It feels like I'm branded for not getting the role.
Are you really not going to do variety shows?
He says he doesn't like actors doing variety shows.
This is so frustrating.
It hasn't even been a month since I started.
I've worked so hard for it.
What's going on here? Why are you all so down?
I thought you said you weren't coming?
I thought you'd be happy to see Lee El,
but you don't look like it at all.
She doesn't listen to me.
I thought you said she listens to you.
She values her mom's opinions more than mine.
Nobody listens to me.
You have me.
You also have that mom of yours that you listen to more.
Where is that mom of yours?
- Who's that girl? - She's a rookie actress.
I think he wants to make her the female lead.
What?
- He'll give it to a rookie? - That's what I'm saying.
Goodness gracious.
Can I go talk to him?
- Don't fight with him. - I can't promise you that.
Where's she going? She's coming here.
Why is she?
- Young Bin. - Oh, yes.
I'll get going. He's pretty drunk now.
All right.
- See you soon. - See you.
Bye.
Director.
What do you want? Why are you here?
I'm here because I'm his manager.
I've been thinking...
and I think we should talk about the script.
Gosh, what do you want from me?
Your opinion doesn't matter so don't even talk to me.
I know that you're not fond of me, but we should still talk...
We should still talk. Don't you think so?
I read through it.
Won't it change the direction entirely? What's your take on it?
Okay!
I'm going to get rid of that female character.
- Pardon me? - Why?
I can't find an actress who can portray that character well.
That girl won't be good enough.
So I'll just go with the original script.
You're fine with it, right?
- And I bet you're thankful. - Well...
Goodness.
I'm fine with everything, but there's one problem.
What is it?
I can't work with you if you keep being disrespectful to my manager.
What?
I heard that you two are friends.
Is this about your loyalty to your friend?
Young Bin, you should study the script of "Lim Hwa Su" again.
Do you think the film is about gang loyalty? Not at all.
Betrayal and ambition.
That's what the film is about.
I won't be disrespectful to you from now on, Mr. Lee.
Are we good now?
All is good now, right?
Gosh, I need to go relieve myself.
Gosh, I just can't get along with him. Goodness.
He really rubs me the wrong way.
Anyway, I'm glad that he's sticking with the original script.
Gosh, she's waiting outside.
Why are you out here?
You're too much. What took you so long?
I even had to cancel the reservation for dinner.
Don't even get me started. All sorts of things happened.
I'll tell you everything over a delicious dinner.
- It's Mr. Ahn. - Again? Don't answer it.
Don't worry. I'm sure it's nothing.
Hello, I'm on my way to have dinner with my wife. Let's keep it short.
Did something happen between Ms. Jo and Young Bin?
Ms. Jo?
Yes.
And?
Director.
I've made up my mind.
I won't do any more variety shows.
Really? You made the right decision.
- Then the role, Lee Choon Bong... - No.
You look too feeble for that character.
Someone like Ma Dong Seok should play that role.
That's what I'm looking for. A tough guy.
It's a supporting role, so I'm not too confident,
but I'm still going to send the script to Ma Dong Seok.
I see.
Director, Joon has anger management issues...
so he can look like a psycho when he loses it.
In what way?
To be honest with you, a gangster role doesn't suit you.
You're not charismatic at all.
And you're too tall.
You'd make a great punching bag. Don't you agree?
Yes.
Well... How about the Actor Number Two role?
Gosh, another insignificant role?
Why are you chugging down my drink?
Yes, you would be perfect for that role.
That character is a cowardly guy who likes to bluff.
You'll be good at it.
Yes.
Gosh, I get hot whenever I drink.
I went through hoops to get that.
So? Do you have a problem with it?
Yes.
Joon went through a lot to get this hat.
Joon, this is why you haven't made a name for yourself yet.
Do you think that a hat can complete an actor's performance?
Does your acting rely on props or what?
You must use your body. It has to come naturally.
Why is this hat so important to you?
Please don't throw it around.
- You did it again. - What's your problem?
I went through so much trouble to get that hat for the role,
and I even got a tattoo for it.
- Come on, Joon. Are you drunk? - No, I'm not.
You said you'd give me the role...
then kept changing your words. And what now?
What's your problem?
What's wrong with doing variety shows?
What is wrong with this hat?
Gosh, you look like a total lunatic.
Do you think this is funny?
Do you think I'm a joke?
You said that I look like a punching bag. Get up!
Get up and check for yourself.
You're laughing again?
My goodness.
Hey.
Take the Lee Choon Bong role. I like this.
Pardon me?
You can have the Lee Choon Bong role, you lunatic.
Actors should be like that. That was great. You're pretty good.
Director, you're not going to forget that you said this, right?
Hold on. I think I need to record this.
- Hurry up. Go sit beside him. - Okay.
All right. Get ready.
Director.
Could you please repeat what you just said?
- Please go ahead. It's rolling. - Goodness.
You psycho. You can have the Lee Choon Bong role. Is that good?
Joon, say something.
- Go, "Lim Hwa Su"! - What are you doing?
- "Lim Hwa Su" rocks! - No, say your name.
I, Cha Joon...
- He gave me Lee Choon Bong... - Gosh.
- I'm having second thoughts. - Please...
- It's already saved. - You saved it?
- You're too goofy. - Not at all.
- Hello. - Hey.
Why are you guys out here?
Joon wanted to talk with Director Yang alone.
I told you guys that the psycho director would cause trouble.
- Sorry? - Why? What happened?
Mr. Ahn told me that they've managed to secure an investor.
That's great news.
It's Ms. Jo's idea. Goodness.
- Pardon? - How did that happen?
It happened because the director wanted a bigger production budget.
They obviously needed a big company.
She apparently said that she'd fund the entire project if you're out.
Gosh.
(Entourage)
I really want to do it.
Isn't he letting people take photos of him on purpose?
It's not like that will change Jo Tae Young's mind.
We're getting so many offers.
Ms. Jo...
- Casting for "Lim Hwa Su"... - We're working on it.
I'm trying to get out of unemployment.
Hello.
- Hey! - Gosh.
I'm shooting a commercial.
Gosh, what is this?
You didn't come with Young Bin today?
I came alone.
I think you're a good person.
What should I do to make you forgive me?
Do you know the real reason?