(This program is suitable
for viewers ages 15 and up)
(Episode 2)
Cha Young Bin.
- Cha Young Bin.
This is no Pokemon. Is there Squirtle?
You looked like a shot-putter.
I thought you threw a grenade.
You'll be shooting a war movie.
It's been a long time. That's why.
You're a successful actor.
"The Flowers of Evil" attracted
six million viewers.
I have no high expectations.
- You mean the movie?
- I mean his throwing.
He wasn't good with balls as a kid, either.
He only watched television
and movies at home.
You were right there next to me.
By the way, I'm surprised.
I thought the movie would fail big time.
It's all thanks to Young Bin.
It's also because there are no
strong opponents right now.
You're right. I was lucky.
"You're right. I was lucky."
- Hello.
- That's Cha Young Bin.
Cha Young Bin?
Can we take a picture together?
Sure.
One, two, three.
You can take one, too.
I'm okay.
Hey, kid. I'll show you something.
I'll show you a light-speed ball.
- You'll hurt yourself.
- Go ahead.
I'm worried.
His position looks nice at least.
Look at his eyes.
Is someone giving him signs?
- Look at those eyes.
- Who's giving you signs?
- Be careful.
- What are you doing?
Should we call an ambulance?
When is Kim Kwang Hyun coming?
We need his help.
Well,
have you been practicing?
Yes, but it's hard.
Please give me some tips.
Just hold the ball and throw it.
I'm your fan. Can I be honest?
Sure.
You wouldn't be like this if I was a girl.
You would try your best.
I know a lot of female celebrities.
Do you know An So Hee, too?
I do. We're close.
Let's start our practice then.
It still hurts.
Young Bin, please come with me.
- Okay.
- Is it time?
You don't have to get nervous.
- He's getting nervous.
- What's with him?
- Are you okay?
- Of course.
- You don't seem okay.
- Young Bin.
- Good luck!
Good luck!
The first ball will be...
thrown by Actor Cha Young Bin...
who recently appeared in the
movie, "The Flowers of Evil".
Please give him a big hand.
My back is killing me.
You tried too hard to
impress those cheerleaders.
That was so humiliating.
There's something even more humiliating.
Ho Jin went to see his ex-girlfriend
and ran into her new boyfriend.
She said he was just a friend.
Stop it.
Also, I don't care even if
he's her new boyfriend.
I know you're upset.
I'll set you up with all the girls I know.
You'll get a hot girlfriend soon.
Find a hot girl for yourself first.
I don't want a girlfriend
for the time being.
Hey, kid.
To get over a girl, you need a new girl.
That sounds so old.
I'm busy with work.
I can't even take care of myself. Stop now.
Have you given up on getting a girlfriend?
Do you know what will happen?
You'll end up like him.
- Take that back.
- I take it back.
When I was your age, I had so many girls.
- What?
- Who would believe that?
If you find a girl you like,
we'll be your wing-men.
Mind your own business.
Who are you texting to by the way?
It's just a fan.
Why isn't she answering?
There you go again. Are you
still not over So Hee?
Just show up in front
of her like Ho Jin did.
Don't drag me down to his level.
Stop it.
An article has been published about today.
"He looked like a professional."
- Wait.
- What's wrong?
Is the reporter crazy?
They blurred my face.
That's so humiliating.
They didn't know you are an actor.
Did they think you were his stylist?
Or a fan?
I can't believe this.
That happens.
He's right.
Right.
They probably thought
your face looked strange.
Stop it already.
I didn't pass the audition,
and my management company
doesn't care about me.
Hey. I'll ask Eun Gab to
give you more auditions.
- I'll talk to him, too.
- Me, too.
Congratulations!
- Congratulations!
- Go, Young Bin!
Thank you.
- Congratulations!
- We made it!
Congratulations on your movie's success.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Hi, Young Bin.
Hello.
- Who are you?
- Me?
I work here. I work for Mr. Kim.
I see.
- Is Mr. Kim in?
- Yes.
By the way, you look better in real life.
Can I take a picture with you?
Sure.
Are you going to ask every celebrity
to take a picture with you?
Don't worry about her. Go in.
- Let's do it later.
- Okay.
You two wait here.
I told you not to try getting
closer to the celebrities.
Do you think you're at a
signing event or something?
What did I do so wrong?
By the way, Mr. Kim, I
want to be a manager.
How long do I have to work at this office?
You still have to wait a bit.
Also, what was that? Are
you a hip hop singer?
Fine.
- You grumpy old man.
- What?
What did you just say?
Is she new? She seems unusual.
She's too unusual. She's
giving me a headache.
How do you feel?
Your first movie became a huge success.
I guess you're feeling like when
you first slept with a girl.
I really didn't expect this.
I know. I didn't expect it, either.
It feels like I suddenly found out...
there's an inheritance meant for
me that I had no idea about.
Here. This is to celebrate your success.
What is this?
We should renew the contract.
Note the changed percentage
and the down payment.
Don't be surprised.
It's a lot.
The real present...
is here.
Be careful. Take a look.
- Are you sure it's okay?
- Take a look.
Is this a script? "War Terminator"?
"War Terminator".
It's a hero movie like "The Avengers".
- A hero movie?
- Yes.
What is it about?
It's set at the time of
the Japanese Invasion.
Admiral Yi Sun Sin succeeds to
terminate the war with help of...
a tiger, a nine-tailed
fox and a death angel.
I don't think a Korean
hero movie will work.
Just give it a read.
I went through so much...
to get you this role.
Who's the production company?
Idea. CJ Entertainment
will be a co-investor.
- Idea?
- Really?
Mr. Lim quit?
He set up his own company
after receiving investments.
He took all his actors and actresses.
Mr. Kim is furious about it.
What about me?
I was his actor, too.
Doesn't the CEO hate me? After
what happened in Busan.
What happened in Busan?
It's nothing.
Your movie is a huge success.
You're a star now.
Who wouldn't want you?
They're very excited about it.
That's great. Then tell them I
want to be in "Lim Hwa Su".
What are you talking about?
That's over. They found another actor.
I'll persuade the CEO.
Hey.
If you try to sleep with your ex-wife,
she'll sue you. You'll be charged.
As you said, "The Flowers
of Evil" became a success.
That's why you can do this.
Otherwise, they would have wanted
either Yoo Ah In or Song Joong Ki.
- Do you understand?
- Please let me meet her then.
I'll talk to her.
- About "War Terminator"?
- About "Lim Hwa Su".
- Young Bin, what's with you?
- Please.
I appreciate your presents,
but I want "Lim Hwa Su".
- I'll get going.
- Young Bin.
You always walk out on me.
Make it happen.
You might be able to do "Lim Hwa Su".
She probably forgot about Joon's butt.
What's up with Joon?
He's frozen.
He took all the young actors
and actresses with him.
You're too old.
This is no time for joking around.
My bad luck doesn't seem to end.
Don't worry. I'll find you a new manager.
Young Bin, you already have a nice car.
With the movie's success,
I can afford this much.
You haven't signed the next movie yet.
Which do you like the most?
I don't know much about cars. You choose.
I'd recommend...
a Lamborghini.
G-Dragon owns one, too.
I think...
it'll suit you very well.
It's too expensive.
Choose something cheaper.
Why are you telling me? Tell Young Bin.
- You should choose.
- Why?
What's going on?
Oh, my. Lucky you.
You'll get to own such a nice car.
Let only girls get in your car.
- Don't ever let Turtle get in.
- What's going on?
It's for you.
- What?
- It's to celebrate...
my movie's success and your breakup.
- Choose one.
- Forget it.
You looked so happy saying that.
Stop it.
Your car is a piece of trash.
Get a new one now.
No, it's not.
It still works fine.
Just think of it as me
letting you drive my car.
Forget it.
You don't deserve a car like this yet.
Would you like to test-drive?
I can explain the details to you.
Sure.
Isn't it nice?
We're just test-driving.
It's so fast.
Hey, just admit that you want it.
It's like your turning down Seol Hyun...
or Son Na Eun when they ask you out.
- Should I just take it?
- Isn't it too fast?
It's too fast!
Let's go!
- Hi.
I did grocery shopping on the way.
What's that?
It's a mink cactus. It's
popular these days.
Every actress owns one. Do you know why?
It resembles man's...
You know.
Hi, Ho Jin.
Have you heard anything from Eun Gab yet?
He said he'd let me meet the CEO of Idea.
I haven't heard anything yet.
- Have you heard anything about me?
- No.
They seem to have completely
forgotten about me.
Should I transfer to another company?
By the way, stop sending me on an errand.
It's on your way anyway.
Live with us if you have a problem with it.
Maybe I should. I can
barely afford my rents.
Really? Then move in with me.
Wait.
Have you given up playing hard to get?
That's good news.
- Just like the old days.
- I'm still thinking.
Let's move to a place with a nice view.
- Call a realtor.
- Now?
Right now.
Why not?
Will we get to live in UN Village?
This is perfect for celebrities.
It's so safe.
No one will know even if you bring girls.
My goodness.
Now, we're talking.
Moving is really not necessary.
Don't think I'll let you sleep in my room.
I don't want to see you making
love with your hand, either.
What do you think? I quite like it.
Me, too.
Which actresses live here?
We might run into them.
How much is this place?
It's 1.8 million dollars.
- What?
- That much?
Gosh.
It's too expensive.
I'll sign a new movie soon.
You don't know yet if you'll
get to do "Lim Hwa Su".
It's Eun Gab. Just in time.
Hi.
Really?
Okay. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
What did he say?
I'm meeting the CEO of Idea tomorrow.
Will it be all right?
Think about what happened in Busan.
I'll talk to her tomorrow.
Let's put our place on sale.
We'll move as soon as I sign.
- Okay.
- Just a second.
Take your time. We don't know anything yet.
Be positive. I'm a lucky guy.
Be positive. He's a lucky guy.
They have a nicer office
than investment companies.
I told you. They run a
20-million-dollar fund.
They're just like an investment company.
Ms. Jo isn't scared of
huge companies, either.
- She even dates a celebrity.
- Who?
You know, from the movie...
- Please come this way.
- Okay.
Let's see what she has to say, okay?
Cup Noodles, don't say anything stupid.
Okay.
Cup Noodles?
- Hello.
- Yes, hello.
This is Young Bin, Cha Young Bin.
- Nice to meet you, Mr. Cha.
- Nice to meet you.
We met at the Busan International
Film Festival, right?
Did you attend the event hosted by CJ?
Yes.
It's too bad I couldn't attend it.
It would've been great if I had
introduced you to Young Bin there.
I know. It's too bad, indeed.
- Let's stop talking about Busan.
- Okay.
What did you think of the
script for "War Terminator"?
Pardon me?
Before we talk about that...
The preparation for the film, "Lim
Hwa Su", is going well, right?
Young Bin is interested in it.
To be frank, I'm more interested
in it than "War Terminator".
She might get the wrong idea
if you put it that way.
I thought we were meeting today to
discuss "War Terminator", Mr. Kim.
Yes, of course. That's why we're here.
Young Bin is just saying...
that he's interested in both films
you're preparing currently.
He's just interested. That's all.
We already finished casting
all roles for "Lim Hwa Su".
- Pardon me?
- I see.
Then let's stop talking about "Lim Hwa Su".
Please tell him more
about "War Terminator".
The amount allocated for its
production budget is unprecedented.
And your pay will be high, too.
Ms. Jo. I'm sorry to interrupt,
but I heard that there are
four main characters.
We revised the plot of the novel
which the script is based on.
Mr. Lee Woo Hyuk agreed, too.
The story will revolve around
one character, Black Tiger.
I'd love to cast you for that role.
- Black Tiger...
You said "tiger", right?
Tiger?
Yes, that tiger.
I see.
It's not just any tiger. I
mean, it's Black Tiger.
Hey, Young Bin. Wait.
They already finished
casting for "Lim Hwa Su".
It's gone out the window.
Why are you so hung up on it?
Hey, Young Bin. Please.
I came here because of "Lim Hwa Su".
You've been stubborn,
so I brought you here so that we
can ask her about it at least.
You heard what she said about
the production budget, right?
You also heard what your pay will be like.
It's like having a Miss
Korea winner wanting...
to move in with you when you were
just looking for a cute girl.
Did you not hear what she said?
She wants me to be a tiger.
She won't make you wear a tiger mask.
It's not a kid's movie.
The original plot has been revised a lot.
Just read the script, okay?
I'm not interested. I'll
look for something else.
I guarantee that "War Terminator"
will attract 10 million viewers.
Compared to "Lim Hwa Su",
"War Terminator" is like...
that expensive imported
spring water, Fiji Water.
I'm not sure if that was
a good use of analogy.
I don't want to play Black Tiger.
Hey, Young Bin.
- Young Bin.
What's the matter with him?
He didn't even say goodbye.
That means he's very angry.
I've never seen him like that.
He thought he'd be able to get
a role in "Lim Hwa Su", but...
Did he not read "War Terminator"?
No. He doesn't read things that
he's not interested in, you know.
You didn't read it, either?
No. I also thought this
meeting was for "Lim Hwa Su".
This happened because you showed
him the script for "Lim Hwa Su".
Do not show him any scripts
without my permission. Got it?
Okay.
Go persuade Young Bin.
And you must read the script, too.
Pretend it's pornography you
used to watch as a teenager...
so that you can get all excited about it.
You have to like
the script first, you fool.
Have a good day.
Turtle, someone is here!
- Who is it?
- They're from the realtor's office.
I see.
Girls.
Go through everything.
Those crazy fans. I want to
report them to the police.
They really pretend to be realtors
and go through everything...
when celebrities list their
places on the market.
I know, right?
They opened every drawer and
took photos of everything.
- Also...
- I won't pass any auditions.
They took Turtle's lucky underwear
thinking that it's yours.
Call the realtor and cancel it.
Because of this?
I didn't get the role in the film.
We can't move.
- How did that happen?
- I don't want to talk about it.
- Where is Ho Jin?
- He went home.
That underwear is so important to me.
It's handed down from my dad...
Things are already bad enough for me.
What's Ho Jin going to do? It's
not like he can live in a tent.
Shall we fix up one of the dressing rooms?
That's a good idea. Do you
know any interior designers?
Yes, I do.
It's Ho Jin.
We just saw each other.
Why are you summoning me like this?
Did you miss me already?
Cut it out.
What are Turtle and Joon up to?
Joon is going through social media
to find who stole his underwear.
We haven't been here in ages.
We came here often when you were
broke trying to produce films.
What are you talking about?
We used to come here often when
you were unpopular and broke.
Is something going on?
We always meet here when you have
something serious to tell me.
The script for "War Terminator".
- You haven't read it yet, right?
- No.
I just read it, and it's
actually better than I expected.
It's not tacky.
I think you should do it.
I was wondering what you were going to say.
Forget it. Let's just drink.
Just read it.
Would you want to wear tiger makeup?
As Mr. Kim said, they won't
make you wear a tiger mask.
I'm sure they'll use computer
graphics or special effects.
They'll make it look cool.
Give it some thought.
Why are you being like this suddenly?
Did Eun Gab say that he'll promote you?
I read it because Mr. Kim was going
on about it, and it's really good.
That's why I'm telling you this.
No, I don't want to do it.
Why not?
Hey, would you date a girl whom
you're not even attracted to?
What are you talking about?
Are you copying Mr. Kim now?
That analogy doesn't even work.
I'm just saying.
I can't be in the film I wanted to do.
I'm not in a good mood,
so let's not talk about work.
Can you just think about it...
Just go through it once...
(SO HEE)
Why didn't you call me sooner?
Sorry. I was so busy that I
forgot to message you back.
- It's okay.
- Congratulations. The film's a hit.
We should all get together soon.
All right. I'll be in touch soon.
Okay.
Was it So Hee?
Yes.
- What did she say?
- She wants to go for food with us.
With everyone. You, Joon, Turtle, and me.
Are you bipolar or what?
You were grimacing until a few seconds ago,
but you're grinning from ear to ear now.
Are you all right?
You know actors have serious mood swings.
Give me the bottle.
Stop being so stubborn and read it...
Enough. Let's just drink, please.
Fine, drink all you want.
I wonder if Turtle has
found the underwear yet.
- I don't know.
- He's so obsessed with it.
You fell here a long time ago
and almost broke your head.
You tripped right here.
You should thank me.
- Did you see?
- Don't roll your eyes like that.
- I saw one in black. How about you?
- I saw one in black stripes.
It took me less than a second.
I have excellent vision.
I knew you had it in you.
Where's the designer we're supposed to see?
Are you sure she's good as she says?
She has a lot of experience
working with celebrities.
Where's Ho Jin?
There he is.
You seem to be in a good mood. Did
you find money on the street?
No.
He did.
Hello. I'm Suh Ji An.
I'm sorry I kept you waiting.
Not at all. We just got here.
Take a seat.
We can wait all day.
We want there to be one more room.
And can you do something about
the noise coming from his room?
He goes to bed listening
to his old dance songs.
I should be the one to talk.
It's so loud every night.
Just keep that strange noise down.
We watched together. Remember?
Also, can you change the
bathroom to a wet-type?
This guy floods the bathroom every day.
I don't even go that often.
You practically live there since
you have sensitive bowels.
You have sensitive bowels, too.
I want the construction to
start as soon as possible.
- Of course.
- It used to be just us three,
but that guy is moving in with us.
The break-up hasn't been easy on him.
He needs to be around people
for his mental health.
I'll have to look around the house first.
- When are you available?
- Ho Jin's my manager.
You can talk with him.
- Can you give me your number?
- What?
(LEE HO JIN)
Are you on a blind date or something?
Why are you making such a fuss?
It's Eun Gab. Can you answer it for me?
Excuse me.
Hello, Mr. Kim. This is Ho Jin.
Why are you answering his phone?
Is he avoiding me on purpose?
No, he's just busy right now.
Tell him I'll move into his house
if he continues to be like this.
CJ is waiting for his answer.
What is he going to do about this?
I read the script...
- and I thought it was good.
- I don't care what you think.
Did you talk to Young Bin about it?
I did, but he's pretty persistent.
- What?
- He doesn't like the tiger role.
Just keep telling him that
the script is a masterpiece.
Do that for me.
You and me are on the same side now.
- Okay.
- So listen to me carefully.
What are you doing in the men's room?
I came looking for you.
There's a call from Ms. Jo Tae Young.
Go and tell her I'm really
busy with a meeting.
You could still talk to her over
the phone in the middle of it.
Then tell her I got admitted to
the emergency room or something.
Just make something up. Get out of here.
All right.
Did you hear that? The CEO
of Idea is looking for me.
Listen up.
Young Bin has to be in this movie.
He has to be. Got it?
What was that?
- Mr. Kim.
- Hold on.
Why would she...
Hey. Where are we on "War Terminator"?
We're looking into it.
Why are you still looking into it?
I got a call from Ms. Jo Tae Young.
Yes, I'm getting it now.
Hey.
Yes, Boss.
Didn't I tell you to tell her
I'm in an important meeting?
Well...
I didn't get what you meant, but I
told her you're at the hospital.
Did I say that to you?
Mr. Kim, why should you be at the hospital?
Forget it, punk.
By the way, the big boss is
looking for you, the small boss.
Who are you calling the small boss?
You little...
Where is she?
What now?
Her pose is like a professional.
Is Young Bin not doing "War Terminator"?
Where did you hear that from?
You're so good at getting news.
You know I'm friends with Tae Young.
I talked to her into casting Young Bin.
You don't seem to be getting
a simple job done, though.
You impotent tool. What are your balls for?
That's what you think.
I made the whole thing possible
working together with CJ.
Did you get Alzheimer's already?
That's yours. Double serving, right?
You always had double servings for lunch.
I don't even remember that.
I'm cutting down on carbohydrates.
How's the contract renewal
going with Young Bin?
Can you let me handle it?
You're the one who put me in
charge and ran off on vacation.
Then stop making such a mess.
He's going to renew the contract.
He's going all the way with me.
He's a loyal guy.
He can't be bought with money.
He's a better man than you think.
You don't know that.
Keep a close eye on him.
Check to see whom he hangs out with.
He didn't knock up anyone, did he?
What are you talking about?
No one does that any more.
This isn't the 80s.
I told you.
You can never trust those who wear masks.
Enough with that. I'm leaving.
You're going to make me sick.
Old people should just die.
Do you want me to teach you a lesson again?
I'm not going to let you do that any more.
That hurts! Why'd you do that?
Go do your job.
You must be under a lot
of stress these days.
I know a place where they'll
make you feel better.
Are you crazy?
She's out of her mind.
- Seriously.
- You little punk.
How long are you going to avoid Mr.
Kim's calls?
Until he stops talking
about that hero movie.
Don't be like that. Can you
give it another thought?
Please?
Mr. Kim has a point.
You're taking his side again.
Stop being immature. I'm
not taking anyone's side.
Let's stop talking about that.
I'm not doing it.
I'm stubborn, right? Those are your words.
Do you guys like this table?
Let's put this in the living room.
(3,000 DOLLARS)
No way. This is way too expensive.
It's okay. Young Bin can
get a 30-percent discount.
Really?
- That's perfect.
- This is unfair.
I'm an actor, too. Why
don't I get a discount?
Pick anything you like. I'll buy you.
Isn't this cute? Should
I get this for So Hee?
You'll make her feel uncomfortable.
You're not even her boyfriend.
You don't let me get a new house.
You don't let me pick my own movies.
And I can't even buy furniture.
- I can't buy gifts now.
- That's not what I meant.
I can't live like this.
Why did you have to say that?
He said he was going to get it for So Hee.
Fine, have it your way.
- Can we buy the table, then?
- Not that.
- Can I buy you a car, then?
- That's not what I'm talking about.
You don't have to do the movie.
I'll find something else.
You're finally on my side
and not on Eun Gab's.
- What is he saying?
- You're on his side now.
The other guy will pay.
Here you go.
What are you doing here?
Long time no see. I work here.
You work here? What about the theater?
I quit.
- I'm not acting any more.
- Why not?
I thought you were going to
be the next Song Kang Ho.
You know how it things are.
My wife got pregnant.
I need to cover the living expenses.
You can't quit acting like that, though.
You have it easy because
of your celebrity cousin.
You should come to your senses, too.
Are you intending on living in
your brother's shadow forever?
We're in our 30s now.
We have to consider quitting as an
option if it's not going to work.
- I'll see you later.
- See you.
- Turn that off.
- Yes, it's so loud.
Gosh.
Stop it.
What are you doing?
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
The movie isn't over yet.
Can you clean up later?
Joon. I talked to the agency. They'll
call you for auditions soon.
I don't know when I'll see Eun Gab again,
but I'll talk to him.
Don't worry too much.
Young Bin, I don't want to
hear that from you today.
Leave me alone.
I have things to worry about in solitude.
Can you take that to your room?
Stop spilling.
- Do you not have a jaw?
- What are you doing?
You're so nasty.
Hey.
At least don't make a mess if
you're not going to clean up.
Jerk.
Why is this traitor calling me?
- Who? Mr. Lim?
- Yes.
Hello? What's this about?
Long time no see, Actor Cha.
That's because you bailed on
me without saying anything.
There must be a misunderstanding.
We should talk face to face.
We're throwing an opening party
for our agency. You should come.
- Why would I go there?
- I have things to discuss with you.
You're not going to stick with
Mr. Kim, are you?
- What?
- You're our rising star.
I couldn't ask you to come
with me because of Young Bin.
You should definitely come.
Mr. Lim invited me over to his party.
I think he's going to ask
me to join his agency.
- You're moving agencies?
- I don't know yet.
It is true that Mr. Kim
doesn't give a darn about me.
I think this could be a good
chance to receive special care.
I don't think so.
He called me...
a rising star.
You're all going, right?
Sure. Where is it?
I didn't know it was this kind of party.
There was a reason why it's
so far away from the city.
Mr. Lim always gets crazy about clubbing.
Joon, this agency has bright future ahead.
You should join right away.
Are you here?
- Hello, Sir.
- Hello.
- The traffic was so heavy.
- Hello, Young Bin.
It must've been a long trip. Come this way.
What's going on? Did he call
you over to see Young Bin?
No way.
It's not like that.
You're right.
It's so crowded in here. Let's go.
This party is sponsored by Maxim.
Everyone related to the agency is
here, including my acquaintances.
We also have Ms. Maxims with us.
This is a real party, isn't it?
Yes, but don't you have
something to discuss with Joon?
Of course. I don't even
know where to start.
The thing is...
I want to talk to you first.
How are things with Mr.
Kim Eun Gab these days?
Why do you ask?
Don't you get frustrated by him?
He's so stubborn and self-centered.
Frankly speaking, other actors left
him because they share my opinion.
Yes, he can be like that.
What about you, Ho Jin? Aren't you tired?
- He must roll all over you.
- Not really. I'm fine.
He did that to me, too.
He talked down to me and called me names.
He used to call me Ms. Lim when
he got me to bring coffee.
Goodness.
He's still a capable man.
"Capable"? He didn't do anything.
Ms. Kang Ok Ja is the one
who did all the work.
The way he gets things
done is too old-fashioned.
Speaking of which,
isn't your contract expiring soon?
I got heavily invested this time.
We're having talks with famous
celebrities at the moment.
If you'd like to know, I consider
my actors' opinions most important.
I won't force you to do a movie
that you don't want to be in.
That's nice.
But you know what?
I don't like talking behind someone's back.
I don't like it.
Congratulations on starting
a new agency, Mr. Lim.
Sure. We'll talk more later.
Excuse me. Aren't you a
member of Sugar Boys?
How do you know that?
I was a huge fan.
You're Cha Joon, right?
Can I take a picture with you?
I'll have to ask my manager first.
He said yes.
- Well then.
- Say cheese.
How does it look?
- What are you doing here?
- Thank you.
Did you just take a picture with Ms.
Maxims?
It's amazing that there are
fans who still remember you.
- Yes.
- Wait.
- You staged this, didn't you?
- What?
You got her to say that to me.
I can read you like a book.
You're so fast when it comes to
things like this. You're amazing.
I just wanted you to feel better.
He's right. I asked them, too.
Whatever. You completely ruined my mood.
That's enough now. Don't get too drunk.
- Let's go home, Joon.
- I don't think so.
Not until we finish all these drinks.
Mr. Lim...
called me over here to
sweet-talk Young Bin.
I'm so pathetic.
- Where are you going?
- Bathroom.
I might just pee in the pool.
- Is he really going to do it?
- I think he already did.
Joon. Did you really do it?
There you are.
Young Bin, I want you to meet someone.
Let's go.
Come on.
What is going on?
Hello.
Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
- Nice to meet you, too.
Clara says she's a big fan of you.
That's right. I'm a huge fan.
You were so good in "The Flowers of Evil".
- I'm a big fan of you, Clara.
- Thank you.
We're currently negotiating
terms with Clara.
You two should talk.
Gosh, I'm sorry.
My hair is wet from the pool.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, but could you
pass me my clothes?
Sure.
What a gentleman.
Take a seat.
It's really chaotic outside, right?
A little bit.
What are you doing after the party?
I'm not sure.
Hold your dad's hand.
Hello.
- Hello.
What?
That jerk...
I knew that would happen.
Where are you right now?
Turn it off right now.
The pastor is waiting.
This is more urgent than
having North Korea invade us.
You missed it last week, too.
I told you to turn it off
for service, didn't I?
I know, but a snake is
trying to seduce Young Bin.
Is this about Cha Young Bin again?
If you miss service like this,
you'll be punished after death.
Why would I be punished? Do you
know how much offering I handed in?
It's enough to build a few churches.
I really have to leave right now.
- Hey.
- He's seeing Clara.
Some actors change their
agency because of women.
If Young Bin leaves me, are you
going to take responsibility?
You won't, right? Please.
I'm coming right now. Yes,
I know where that is.
I love you, Honey.
What brings you here?
I...
I know the CEO here.
What about you?
I designed the interior for the agency.
I see.
Are you here alone? What
about your friends?
They're all here, but we separated.
Are they inside?
- Are you a loner?
- Pardon?
I'm just kidding. You
guys look really tight.
I see.
- Will you go inside with me?
- Pardon?
I didn't know the party would be like this.
I'm glad I ran into someone I know.
We don't really know each other, though.
- You don't want to go in with me?
- I do.
It's our second time. Come on.
What's going on with Ho Jin?
He's getting better.
You need to step up your game.
More like getting stiff.
Are you getting stiff?
I see.
- Hello.
What brings you here?
I know the CEO as well.
I see.
I know some people over there.
I better get going.
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- What? Why?
- We need to talk about business.
- Right.
- See you later.
- Goodbye.
Bye.
- Have you been well?
- Yes.
- Why are you two together?
- I ran into her here.
Okay.
- Are you sad she left?
- Yes. No. What?
Are you okay?
I'm suffering under the weight of life...
while Young Bin...
went to meet Clara...
and Turtle...
Gosh.
I trusted you,
but you were flirting with the designer.
It's not like that.
Don't bother.
Where are you going?
Joon.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
Joon, look.
Go.
You can cool down a little.
Hey!
I fell in.
You're too old for this.
The pool looks cool.
Who are you?
Jerk.
I came to retrieve what's mine.
- What do you mean?
- Don't try to fool me around.
You used to have a habit
of stealing things.
Old habits die hard, I guess.
You got massages with
the company's money...
and stole presents from fans back then.
Let's talk outside.
- Don't mind me.
- Let me go.
What's wrong with you?
Don't make up lies.
I'm not a manager any more.
I'm a CEO, too.
CEO?
The person who invested in your company...
goes to my church.
"The person you're investing in..."
"is using your precious money
to get himself a car,"
"to go to bars and to buy girls."
"He also makes new
actresses go around bars."
Should I tell him what a jerk you are?
Mr. Kim... Well...
I know you stole actors from my agency.
And now, you're trying to
steal Young Bin as well.
You have no conscience whatsoever.
If I see you try to pull a trick again,
I'll crush your puny company.
Where is he?
Over there, Sir.
Do your wife and daughter know
that you have fun like this?
My goodness.
Is this how you're going to back stab me?
What brings you here?
You've been ignoring my calls.
And you're at another
company's opening party.
We're just here to party.
What will other people think?
And should you really be hanging
out with these cheap people?
- Cup Noodles.
- Yes?
- You and I will talk later.
- Okay.
You, too.
All right. What do you have against me?
Just tell me. Let it out.
- I don't have anything.
- Why are you not answering me then?
Also, why are you here?
Because you keep on talking
about "War Terminator".
Do you think I want to ruin you?
Did I ever make you do something bad?
I'm doing all this for you.
Please listen to me this time.
Talk to him. You liked the script, too.
Yes, it was good...
I already told him I won't do it.
- You won't reconsider?
- No.
You should give up, too.
I remember when you first
came to my office.
I thought you were a handsome
kid with an empty head.
However, you had a way with your speech.
You had your own ethics and were stubborn.
After working with you,
I realized you were loyal, too.
I thought, "this guy is the real deal."
I've put a lot in you.
However,
I'm disappointed in you for the first time.
I mean it. I'm really disappointed.
- Please don't be like that.
- Forget it.
I'm giving up on you as well.
Do whatever you want,
but if you won't do "War Terminator,"
it's over between us.
If you must have it your way,
I can't work with you.
Kim Eun Gab, you jerk.
Women... I love women.
I've never seen Eun Gab
so mad like this time.
He's usually like that to me, not you.
I think he's really mad this time.
You should have taken his calls.
It's not a surprise he misunderstood.
Do we have the script for
"War Terminator" at home?
Are you going to read it?
Yes. I feel bad. I should at least read it.
What's gotten into you? You never
do when you don't feel like it.
Didn't you hear Eun Gab?
He says I'm loyal.
Are you sure you're not scared?
Hello?
(SO HEE)
Yes, So Hee.
I was going to call you.
Where do you want to meet tomorrow?
I'm sorry. Something came up.
I can't see you tomorrow.
Really?
It's okay.
Sorry. I really wanted to
hang out with you guys.
Tell everyone I said sorry.
It's loud in the back.
- Are you still filming?
- Yes, we're filming outside.
- It's another overnight shoot.
- Really?
Where are you right now?
Cut.
Okay. Next scene.
- Good job.
- Great work today.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
Good work.
What do you think you're doing?
- Did I surprise you?
- Hey.
How did you get here?
I dropped by while passing.
Why did you surprise me?
I came to see you since
you can't meet tomorrow.
I'm sorry.
- Are you finished?
- No, we're far from being done.
- So Hee.
- Yes?
Ta-da.
What is this?
Isn't it cute? I bought it at a shop.
Hey...
Now, I feel bad.
I wish we could grab
something to eat together.
I won't finish until early morning.
They gave the script to us so late.
- I look tired, right?
- No. You look pretty.
You must know my weak spot.
Fine, I'll treat you to dinner next time.
Let's meet up often when
your drama is over.
You'll take a break, right?
No. I'll start shooting a movie.
I don't get a break.
Really?
Which film is it?
Hey.
- Did you make enough for me?
- Yes.
I made enough. Come and eat it.
I told you not to make him anything.
It looks good.
Did you meet her?
Yes.
What?
Nothing happened, right?
No, I just gave her a present.
I got nervous thinking you might...
come onto her again and get dumped.
What were you thinking?
Gosh, it's hot.
It's hot.
It's delicious.
You should have just cooked
the whole bag for me.
No, an actor should take care of his body.
Your face will swell tomorrow.
- What about you?
- Who cares?
I'm not going to be an actor,
so why should I bother?
- You didn't go home yet.
- No, I waited for you.
- Good. I have to talk to you.
- What is it?
I'll do "War Terminator".
What?
- You didn't read it yet.
- Is it because of Mr. Kim?
Yes.
Actually,
So Hee might star in "War Terminator".
- What?
- No way.
Tell him tomorrow that I'll do it.
Let's tell him I'm doing it for him.
It'll make him happy.
You sprayed all over me. How disgusting.
Are you saying you can't stop it?
You're not new in the industry.
If you keep this up, I'll... I have to go.
You're here. You're here. Yes.
I want to give you a kiss.
Sit down. Sit down.
I heard something good happened.
If you hear this, you'll want to kiss me.
- Make a guess, Cup Noodles.
- Me?
Is he getting a bigger guarantee?
Guarantee? You were meant to be a manager.
Are you sure you studied film?
Listen.
The director of "War Terminator"...
Really?
- Director Lee Joon Ik.
- Hey.
Be quiet.
He hasn't signed yet, so
this is under embargo.
Gosh, this is great.
- You watched all of his films.
- He did.
He's one of the best directors in Korea.
- Great.
- Sit down.
You can order all you want today.
- I'll buy. Do you want wine?
- Can we?
Don't you care your appearance?
You look worse every time I see you.
What's the point? It's not like I'll...
Someone will call you from the office.
Your manager changed.
They have at least three
auditions lined up.
- What?
- That's great news.
They're just auditions for now.
Why is he so happy?
You should be thankful.
I'll wear my lucky
underwear, so don't worry.
You're an abhorrence.
- He doesn't know what it means.
- What is it?
- Fool.
- What should we eat?
Once the director signs
on, let's have a meeting.
Sure.
Is there an actress you want to work with?
- I'll tell them.
- Not really.
I prefer someone who acts well.
What's taking the car so long?
Isn't that...
Who is that guy?
An So Hee and Kang Ha Neul are dating.
What?
Hello?
(NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW)
I thought you were finally getting a break.
Why are you so dressed up?
- Idiot.
- Fool.
Just tell her how you feel. Stop peeking.
Hello.
How can both you and Eun
Gab hide this from me?
You need to help Young Bin feel better.
It's awkward to reach out to him.
We'd be happy if you came on board.
Why aren't you signing, then?
Tell them you'll sign this week.
That's what life is about.
What was that?
Something's suspicious.