(THIS PROGRAM IS SUITABLE
FOR VIEWERS AGES 15 AND UP.)
(THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS INDIRECT
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISEMENTS)
Subtitles by VIU
Ripped, edited and synced by
gabbyu@subscene
Why are you working out so hard?
I have nothing better to do.
Now, I understand why you and
Young Bin work out so often.
I guess you'll come here often now.
Do they look cool to you?
Big muscles make you look stupid.
Who are you talking about?
Those guys in the back.
A slender yet toned body...
is what makes girls go crazy.
Look at my pubic bones.
- Stop it.
- That's disgusting.
I saw your hair.
The problem is your face, not your body.
He has a small bottom, too.
Be quiet, you hobbits.
Stop envying me and save
the world by destroying the ring.
That movie is so old.
Why are you working out from
this early in the morning?
How could he sleep?
He saw director Lee Joon Ik
and Kim Soo Hyun together.
I better work out.
Hey.
I'll stay here a bit longer.
Look at those muscles.
As you said, your body is not everything...
when your face...
He's Jin Goo.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Young Bin.
I heard you'll be in Director
Lee Joon Ik's movie.
It's not decided yet.
I hope it'll work out.
See you around.
Salute! I loved your drama.
What is he doing?
I see. Bye.
- Bye.
You didn't watch that drama
because you failed the audition.
I didn't watch because of Song Joong Ki.
Has Eun Gab said anything about
the meeting with the director?
I haven't heard anything yet.
Let's just wait.
Why don't you do something about it?
When Mr. Kim can't do anything,
there's nothing I can do.
What makes you think so? You
want to become a manager.
Show them what you have.
What are you talking about?
If I lose this movie,
I'll go back to Busan and start
a comic book cafe or something.
What?
He sounds serious.
I don't want to end up at a comic
book cafe. Put yourself together.
Are you going to follow him there?
Mr. Kim, where are you?
Why?
It's Sunday. I'm at church.
Do you have no faith?
- Sorry?
- Do you have no conscience?
Stop playing around...
and have some faith.
It's about Young Bin.
If you're ready,
- let's start.
- What about him?
Kneel down...
He's wondering when he'll
get to meet the director.
He seems worried.
He looks very serious.
- While exhaling...
- Gosh.
Come to my church alone.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Exhale again.
Three, four...
Turtle.
- Aren't you going to work out?
- No.
Working out makes you age.
Look at his face. He got so many wrinkles.
Don't get on my nerves.
- I'm about to explode.
- Your face will explode.
Gosh.
I'll go meet Mr. Kim now.
Tell him that I'm dying here.
You haven't heard anything
about the audition yet?
No. Do tell him about me.
I'm so stressed out that I
lost all my motivation.
I have no energy when I wake up.
Isn't that because you're getting old?
- See you.
- Hey.
I want to meet the director this week.
Should we try again? Start.
One, two, three...
- Someone wants to talk to you.
- Please stay with him.
Okay.
- Let me help you.
- Okay.
Lower your arms slowly.
Push your bottom backwards.
Stay in this position.
Slowly.
How do you do this?
I'm lost here.
Please give me a second.
One more.
Continue.
Am I doing this right?
- I'm confused.
- Let me take a look.
Okay.
- Try going down.
- Okay.
Stay there.
Do you feel me on your bottom?
- Yes.
- Try pushing me backwards.
Further.
All right. Stop.
In that position, raise your upper body.
- Raise what?
- Sorry?
Gosh.
I'm sorry.
Are you okay? What was I thinking?
Wait.
Come on.
- I'm sorry.
- I can raise my upper body.
- Gosh.
- Is the service over?
I can't talk on the phone
in the middle of a service.
My wife would kill me if she
finds me standing here.
What did Young Bin say?
- Is he doing bad?
- Yes.
He grills me about when he can
meet Director Lee Joon Ik.
Gosh.
Seriously.
What can I do when he's
actively avoiding me?
I've been praying so hard.
Young Bin seems to be having
trouble sleeping at night.
I raised my dose of sleeping pills.
Young Bin said if he loses this movie,
he'll start a comic book cafe in Busan.
- That sounds serious.
- It is.
What should I do?
Give me a second.
What time is it?
Follow me.
I forgot my car keys in there.
- Let's walk.
- I have a car.
I can't get in that shabby car.
I have a family. Follow me.
(CATHOLIC CHURCH)
What are we doing at a catholic church?
- Were you baptized?
- No.
Wait here then.
The director goes to this church.
- I'll go meet him.
- Sorry?
This wasn't planned. Wouldn't it annoy him?
I'll pretend it's a coincidence.
Can I go with you?
I have something to tell him.
What is it?
Do you think this is a
customer service center?
If we go together,
he'll see we're here to see him.
Wait here.
What?
Pray to your ancestors at least.
- All right.
- I'm praying.
See you.
Mr. Kim.
How did it go?
- The director is...
- Yes.
Thinking of casting another
actor for that role.
He made it clear that he
doesn't want a meeting.
Why is he so against Young Bin?
I asked him over and over again,
and he gave an honest answer.
He wants to work with an actor,
not just a star.
Young Bin did a good job
in "The Flowers of Evil".
Hasn't he watched that one?
He watched one of his television dramas.
He thinks he's just a good-looking model.
I'm so stressed out.
I can't believe this.
What should we do then?
- For now, you and me...
- Yes.
Hang on.
My goodness.
Stay quiet.
- What's the matter?
- Where are you?
I was going to the bathroom,
but then I ran into a friend.
I'm trying to bring him to our church.
We should guide lost sheep, right?
I know you're lying.
I saw you talking on the phone.
Did you sneak out of a service to work?
- Are you serious?
- That's not true.
- I'll be right there.
- The service is over.
I'll take the car.
Honey.
What should we do?
- Bring your car here.
- Sorry?
Where are we going?
Why is Ho Jin so quiet?
Did he meet Eun Gab?
Be patient.
Actors need patience.
It's a spam.
I thought it was about the audition.
To make your waiting easier,
why don't we have some fun?
I don't want to be at a
crowded place today.
Is it a spam again? It's about my audition.
- What happened?
- I didn't pass.
You said it went well.
I must have been wrong.
Why am I so unlucky these days?
I wonder that, too.
Me, too.
Turtle.
Hi.
- Hi, Young Bin.
- Hi.
Hey, don't you see me?
I'm saying hi right now.
What's wrong with you?
- Did you get dumped again?
- Again?
Turtle, did you see G-Dragon
wearing that t-shirt?
It's on his Instagram.
I should have asked Yoo Ah In to wear it.
You're so unlucky, too.
I think we're all cursed. Should
we hire an exorcist or something?
What? Try visiting a
fortune teller at least.
I know someone famous.
Her nickname is Lady Chopstick.
Even Lee Jung Jae and Jang
Dong Gun are her clients.
She's famous among celebrities.
- Lady Chopstick?
- Yes.
(FORTUNE TELLING)
- Hello.
Hello.
You have no male energy.
You're full of female energy.
That's why you fail every time.
Female energy? There's no girl around him.
Now, I see. You're a woman.
You're a woman at home, too.
You're a mother.
You like doing house chores.
You like staying at home.
In a word, you're a woman on the inside.
You're a woman.
You're just an empty man.
Sorry?
That's impossible.
- I'm such a manly man.
- Cut it out.
Cut it out.
Why is she upset?
Your body lost all energy too, right?
I heard it's because I'm stressed out.
You need to fill up some male energy.
Stay away from girls for the time being.
You can't sleep with girls either.
Stay around guys.
Fill up your male energy.
Then job offers will start pouring in.
Okay.
You're supposed to live like a beggar,
but you're a well-off beggar.
Your efforts only benefit others.
You dance at someone else's party.
You live an okay life by
sticking around lucky ones.
That's interesting.
What should I do?
Everything you do will fail.
Don't try anything. Just get married.
Find a woman. You'll make a good husband.
It'll be red under your feet all your life.
Your eyes resemble those of foxes.
You seduce people.
This time, you have to give up.
- Sorry?
- It's over now.
Another guy already took it.
If you become greedy,
you'll get an upset stomach.
Find something else.
You're working even on a weekend.
You're taking my weekend away.
We have no weekends as long
as we stay in this field.
Have you been working out?
I drank too much.
My body was feeling heavy.
- You don't drink, do you?
- Of course not.
I suffered so much when I just started out.
- Would you like some coffee?
- I'm okay.
Who are you?
I'm Young Bin's manager.
- We met...
- I see.
Go ahead.
I met the director.
He made it clear that he
doesn't want Young Bin.
I was going to call you on Monday.
I don't think Young Bin
will get the contract.
Didn't we make a verbal contract?
Let's sign the contract and
persuade the director together.
He won't change his mind.
There's nothing I can do.
You have so much power these days.
I do?
I don't know about that.
Have you even tried?
Did you negotiate with other
actors behind our back?
Mr. Kim.
How will I work with your actors
if you speak to me so rudely?
If you keep stabbing us in the back,
I can't let my actors work with you.
Don't you see that?
Mr. Kim, why did you fight with her?
We might lose the movie.
Were you dozing off?
We already lost the movie.
My goodness.
Are you breaking down?
If you can't handle this much,
you better quit.
I'm just worried about Young Bin.
- What should I tell him?
- Don't say anything to him.
Let me take care of it.
What are you going to do?
Manager Kim, it's me.
Send me a list of the
movies we're considering.
I'm camping with my wife.
We just set up the tent.
How are you going to pay back
your loan when you're fired?
You'll have to live in that tent.
Mr. Kim, I really can't work today.
Please wait until tomorrow.
I'll beat you up until you
can't set up that tent again.
Send it to me right now, okay?
Are you going to...
Why do you talk so much today?
Where's the parking lot?
(YOUNG BIN)
It's Young Bin.
Hi, Young Bin.
Make something up.
- Tell him you're driving.
- I'm driving right now.
I've been waiting for your call.
How did it go?
I'm driving right now.
- I'll call you back.
- Okay.
What did he say?
He's driving. He'll call me back.
It doesn't feel right.
Could the fortune teller be right?
Gosh, I shouldn't have visited her.
You at least know what to do.
Young Bin has to give up the movie,
and I shouldn't even try anything.
Let's not trust her too much.
Should we have some fun?
- Where do you want to go?
- Garosu-gil.
No. There are too many girls.
Are you going to trust the fortune teller?
She knew everything about me.
Go somewhere full of men.
Somewhere full of male energy.
Somewhere full of men?
I need male energy.
Look at that.
Let's go.
I know who those players are.
I'm a fan. I should get their autographs.
Do that.
Are you feeling better?
Yes. Male energy is filling up.
I wish Ho Jin was here.
- Give him a call.
- Should I?
Hello? He's not picking up.
He's not?
Do you feel nervous without him?
Give him some space.
Just focus on the game.
It's starting.
It's been always the best
since it started in 2012.
The most exciting match ever...
is about to start.
The finals...
start...
now.
Yes!
Why are the lights on?
Young Bin keeps asking me where I am.
Tell him we're in a meeting.
Is someone in the meeting room?
Gosh.
- Wait here.
- Okay.
What are you doing?
The whole board of directors
are here without me.
Are you conspiring something?
Watch your language.
What are you doing here on a weekend?
Did your wife kick you
out of her apartment?
We own it together.
That's nice.
Don't give her full ownership.
You'll be left with nothing
if you get a divorce.
Are you here with a girl?
- Are you having an affair?
- I need to talk to you.
That rude brat.
Well...
You're Young Bin's manager.
- It's nice to see you again.
- Hello.
- Wait in my office.
- Okay.
Please excuse me now.
What are you doing here?
We're just building our friendship.
Why on a weekend behind my back?
You're too young to understand it.
Don't try to fool me.
You're trying to sell our company.
Do you think I'm an idiot?
How did you know that?
You're smarter than I thought.
You're afraid I'll oppose.
Let's sell some shares and take
some money in our pockets.
Take some in your pocket
before it's too late.
That's absurd.
They know nothing about
entertainment industry.
You said what we wanted was
management, not business.
You were the one who said that.
Don't you remember?
- Do you have dementia?
- Why do you think I'm doing this?
Do your job first.
I got a call from Ms. Jo Tae Young.
You made such a mess.
She stabbed me in the back.
I even got CJ involved.
Is this all you can do?
You're unbelievable.
Forget it. I don't see
the point of talking to you.
In any case, I'll never go along with it.
Gosh.
That lady is blinded by money.
Never let her meet Young Bin, okay?
How could I do that? She's a co-CEO.
She's just lending us her name.
I'm the real CEO and your boss.
Okay.
Hey.
These movies start shooting this year.
Read them all and pick
one by tonight, okay?
Well...
What now?
Are you going to tell Young Bin
the truth and make him get up?
- You'll ignore me anyway.
- That's right.
Yes.
If he knows what's happening
right now, he'll go awry.
You can't discuss with someone
that doesn't have the right mind.
Let's say his loving fiancee left
on the day of their wedding.
Then we should bring to
him someone more lovable.
Actors are simpler than you think.
If he finds a good script,
he'll forget about it.
- Yes, Sir.
- How can you read this?
The font is too small.
- Did you talk to Young Bin earlier?
- Yes.
How did he sound?
I think he's okay since he
doesn't know what's happening.
He looks rather happy.
Let's see.
He's fine then, right?
Okay.
Hurry up and read.
(CJ ENTUS AUTOGRAPH EVENT)
Why is the line so long?
It's not getting shorter.
We look the oldest here.
It's embarrassing. Let's go.
There are a lot of girls, too.
Let's just...
- Gosh.
- Let's go.
No, we have to get their signatures.
- Aren't you getting one?
- Of course, I want one.
Hey, watch out.
Protect me.
What are you doing? Let go.
Anyway, who do you keep calling?
Who else? It's Ho Jin.
You must be missing him dearly.
Both Ho Jin and Eun Gab aren't picking up.
Something must have gone wrong.
That's the only time
Eun Gab doesn't pick up.
Why is Ho Jin being like Eun Gab?
Do you want to show security your face...
so we can leave after
getting the signature?
We're already in the line. Let's wait.
Okay.
Turtle. Turtle.
- Hello.
Don't take photos.
Thank you.
She's my favorite character.
I need a picture.
He's so excited.
- Were you really upset earlier?
- That's what I mean.
I'm sorry, but that's it for photo time.
No.
No...
Gosh, nothing ever works.
That fortune teller was right.
Excuse me. I'm sorry,
but could I ask you for a favor?
Look at him.
You should take one, too.
It's okay.
Who cares what the fortune teller said?
You'll regret this later.
I need to get a role if
this is what I have to do.
I don't need her picture.
I'm not jealous of Turtle.
My gosh.
Is that you, Ji An?
You got me.
Why are we... Why are you here?
I came to pick up my mom.
We're having dinner.
- Your mother?
- Yes.
Right, I see.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
Are you working on a weekend?
Yes. It's something urgent.
Ms. Kang is in the meeting room.
Here.
- What's this?
- I was going to leave it here.
- See you next time.
- Okay.
(YOU LOOK TIRED. HAVE SOME
COFFEE AND CHEER UP.)
By the way...
- Yes?
- What happened...
to your friend whom you wanted
to set up a blind date for?
Well, I...
I didn't contact him.
Did you get a girlfriend?
Pardon?
Your friends told me you broke up.
Yes, I don't have one.
I didn't have one.
Why do you ask?
I have people asking me to
introduce them to guys.
Thanks for the coffee.
Really?
Are you sure?
All right, that's good.
What? The tent?
Fine, keep it up.
What happened? Why are you smirking?
It's nothing.
- Read this one.
- Okay.
If Young Bin says okay, we can go with it.
There are two main roles,
and Kim Yun Seok is in it.
- Read it fast.
- Okay.
(METROPOLITAN INVESTIGATION TEAM)
I didn't get the document yet.
- Did you finish it?
- Yes.
It has a good story,
but is this the final version?
It needs a lot of edits.
It's good enough.
Call Young Bin.
- Right now?
- Yes.
Make sure you do as I told you.
- Don't say anything stupid.
- Okay.
Why does he want to meet here?
I'm not sure.
Over there.
Young Bin.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Why is this place so loud?
Joon wanted to go someplace without women.
Without women? What kind
of nonsense is that?
Are you coming out of the closet?
No, but I have a reason for...
Hey, I was with this guy the whole day.
We're like Sherlock and
Watson or Mulder and Scully.
What did you do?
Well...
There's this detective buddy film.
You'd be partnering up with Kim Yun Seok.
The script is good, and they're
almost confirmed for investment.
- What do you think?
- Why are you bringing that up?
What about "War Terminator"?
They cast Kim Soo Hyun.
Let's forget about that one.
Is this true?
Gosh.
I think it turned out for the better.
It was a bad film anyway.
This one is so much better.
It's a buddy film. Bromance is so trendy.
Also, you'll act with Yun Seok.
Your acting will look so much better.
Do you get me?
Also, your character is really nice.
It's realistic.
What happened to the meeting
with Director Lee Joon Ik?
They've already confirmed the cast.
A meeting is unnecessary.
I still want to meet him.
What do you think?
Can I be honest with you?
Of course.
We went to see the director at the church,
and he declined.
In his words, he says you're...
more like a model than an actor.
Don't say it like that.
He'll misunderstand.
He should know exactly what happened.
I'm sorry, but we'll have
to look for something else.
This is an alternative.
Okay.
If you don't like it,
I'll look for something else.
There are a million scripts.
Are you all right? Are you mad?
If you are, take it out on me.
I'll let you do it.
I'll ring the golden ball...
I mean the golden bell.
No.
Why would I be mad at you? It's my fault.
It's not your fault.
It has nothing to do with you.
It just wasn't the right film.
You run into some of these time to time.
It can happen.
You shouldn't do such a film.
I'm okay.
I understand the situation.
Thank you for trying.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to go.
Okay.
- Young Bin.
- Good night.
Bye.
- Take care.
- Bye.
See you.
Young Bin.
I said not to say anything stupid.
Why are you being so direct?
You're so inexperienced.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm sorry.
I'll go talk to him.
Let's go. I'll drive you.
Forget it.
Go and talk to Young Bin.
Also,
keep an eye on him at night just in case.
Actors...
often do something idiotic at night.
Young Bin won't do that, though.
Yes.
Go.
You must be upset.
Do you want me to cook something?
No. This is why I don't
have enough stamina.
- You cook.
- Why?
Let's just eat cup noodles.
I don't want any. I'm going to bed.
- Do you want to talk?
- No, I had enough today.
Don't ignore me. That
scenario earlier isn't bad.
I don't know what to make of this.
I thought I was in "War Terminator"
for the last few weeks.
Today, I'm suddenly not in it.
I feel so strange. I don't know what to do.
It's not just you. I feel that way, too.
What can we do? We have to get over it.
Do you want a drink?
I don't even want to drink.
I'm going to bed.
Just let him be.
I bet he'll just sleep for a few days.
It's a little scary.
What the Lady Chopstick said all came true.
What are you talking about?
We went to get our fortunes read.
She said Young Bin will
have trouble with work.
- Gosh.
- My goodness.
She really is talented.
I didn't want her to be right.
I don't want to end up living off
others like what she told me.
She's really good.
- Why didn't you read mine, too?
- We did.
You will neither get married nor even date.
Your partner is your left hand.
This is no time to joke.
Why? Did you want to ask
her about your love life?
No, about career.
I thought you were with Eun Gab
the whole day as partners.
Partners? No way.
I was only chasing things around.
I have nothing else to do.
I don't even know if this
is helpful for Young Bin.
What have I been doing all day?
Not you, too.
You guys are sighing all day.
It's annoying.
I need something to cheer me up.
Hey!
Didn't you hear the fortune teller?
Young Bin...
Starting today, women are forbidden.
You can't talk about them.
Anything with women are all forbidden.
It's Kim Do Yeon.
Gosh, you idiots.
What is that smell?
Is that eel?
You're cooking eel in the morning?
You're really too much.
He's killing me.
He's trying so hard to
get his man energy back.
We went to Garak Market this morning.
You're awesome.
Should I have some
raspberry wine with this?
Why would you? It would be useless for you.
Be quiet. All she said was right.
You'll jinx me, so stop complaining.
How long are you going
to take to clean those?
- Where is Young Bin?
- He didn't come out yet.
I think he was walking around when
I was playing games last night.
This is too much for breakfast.
Didn't you make any soup?
Soup? No way.
Just eat what I give you.
I don't like this.
Eels for breakfast?
Don't we have soup?
Why are you copying Ho Jin?
- Just eat what I make you.
- Okay.
I thought you couldn't sleep.
Why are you up?
I'll sleep after breakfast. I
don't have anything to do anyway.
Is Ji An starting the construction today?
I don't want it to be noisy.
No, don't worry. She'll start next week.
That's good. Don't let any women
come in here for a while.
There isn't a single woman
that would come here.
- That makes me sad.
- Hold on.
You don't want Ji An to come?
Until when?
Why? Are you upset you
won't get to see her?
Ask her out for a date then.
No, I'm talking about the construction.
You should call So Hee then.
- Are you making fun of me?
- Do you feel guilty?
I mean, you should tell her about the film.
Later.
How is the new film's scenario? Is it good?
- I think it's good.
- Do you mean Ji An?
- Gosh.
- Then I'll do it.
- Really?
- Yes.
If you think it's okay,
I'm sure it's okay.
I don't want to waste my time.
Tell Eun Gab I'll do it.
Yes. Don't worry so much.
- Things will work out.
- Between you and Ji An?
That's great.
I feel like the film's
finished with all of you here.
Anyway, let's do our best, Mr.
Cha Young Bin.
Okay.
To be honest,
I know you declined our offer before.
Did you really get out of the other film?
Yes, that's why we came to see you.
Let's not talk about that.
All right.
- Let's sign our papers this week.
- Sure.
Right, Mr. Kim...
Gosh, it's so awkward for
me to call you formally.
I've known Mr. Kim for a long time.
Let's not bring up the past.
Time really flies, doesn't it?
I used to call him by
his first name before.
Mr. Kim, you had a tough time...
holding up the umbrella
for actors, didn't you?
That's why I don't use one even
when it rains. I'm sick of it.
I think we're done here,
so we'll get going.
No, not yet. Don't get up.
Do you like fishing?
No, I've never done it.
Is that so?
Let's go fishing later.
Right.
To commemorate this day,
I'll give you a present.
We're okay with fishing...
He's such a healthy guy.
All right.
This is good.
- Here, take it.
- I'm okay.
Come on. Take it. This is really expensive.
Watch.
How does it look?
It's long and thick. Doesn't it look great?
With this,
you can hook in the audience...
and women, too.
All right, take it.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- We'll get going now.
- Okay.
- Okay, bye.
- Bye.
- Let's go fishing next time.
- Okay.
That's what happened.
It's been a while since I worked with him.
Anyway, you made the right decision.
Okay. By the way, this
isn't a fishing film, right?
All we talked about was fishing.
I was confused. Weren't you?
I thought we were fishing. I almost yawned.
If he saw you, he would bug you forever.
He's known for his bad temper.
He beat up the director and actor
for a badly performing film once.
You need to be careful around him.
Got that?
Yes.
Hello.
- Did it go well?
- Yes, we decided to sign.
- We'll get going.
- Okay.
Rest well, and don't get stressed.
Don't you take care of yourself?
You and I could be friends.
You look like you're 40.
I do?
- I'm going.
- Okay.
Take better care of yourself.
- Bye.
He never talks about work.
Your face looks bad, though.
Are those dark circles?
What's wrong with my face?
You're piling up your man energy.
You have nowhere to use it.
Let's go.
- It's called imposing charms.
- Sure.
He doesn't even masturbate alone.
You're going to burst if you keep it up.
What if you really faint?
You really need to stop all this silliness.
How long do I have to do this?
She said I'd get a lot of
work just like a dog in heat.
At this rate, you'll become the dog.
How long do you have to do this? 20 years?
This isn't working.
Should we go see Lady Chopstick again?
What is it now?
Yes?
- Yes, this is Cha Joon!
- Gosh, he's loud.
Yes, I understand.
Of course, I'm available.
Yes. Yes. See you tomorrow.
Bye.
- What is it?
- What did they say?
Who is it?
I auditioned for this before,
and the actor fell through.
They're asking me to fill in.
That's great.
This is impossible.
How can it be just as she said?
I'm driving.
I'm glad I listened to her.
I really got an offer.
But I'm suddenly getting upset about this.
I guess I'll live off someone
for the rest of my life then.
You're all responsible for me.
Is it So Hee?
How did you know?
You should be a fortune teller.
You're pathetic.
How can you run over to
her as soon as she asks?
He's in no place to play hard to get.
If he does, she'll forget about him.
Don't you think?
These three eunuchs don't
have right to say anything.
- I'm just going to keep quiet.
- I'm a eunuch?
- How can this be?
- You're one, too.
- No way.
You're crazy.
- Hey, So Hee.
- Hello.
Why are you here so early?
I'm not late, am I?
- No, no.
- No.
He just couldn't wait.
- Did you get my manager one?
- Yes.
- Hello.
You asked us out for dinner...
and this is where you treat us.
I've been craving it. That's why.
Hey, did you get soju?
Can you drink?
Don't you have a shoot tomorrow?
- It's okay. Ma'am.
- Yes?
- Can we have a bottle of soju?
- Sure thing.
- What?
- You look pretty.
That's disgusting. What's wrong with you?
- Are you out of your mind?
- She's pretty.
Why isn't Joon saying anything?
I'm sorry, but tell her not to talk to me.
He's sorry, but don't talk to him.
- Stop that.
- What?
- It's because...
- Stop.
Don't mind him. He has his reasons.
He's still the same.
What happened?
Are you not doing "War Terminator"?
No, I'm doing something else.
Already? What is it?
It's a detective film. What about you?
Did you sign?
Yes.
I had my doubts since it's a hero film.
I wasn't sure until the end,
but I decided to do it after
meeting the director.
Listening to his ideas excited me so much.
I think it'll be really fun.
I wish you were in it, too. I'm sad.
Me, too.
- What's your problem?
- Don't touch me.
Stop it already.
Tell her to stop. I have a reason.
- He's sorry that he's ugly.
- Hey.
- Thank you.
I'd love for another round of drinks,
but I have a shoot early in the morning.
It's too bad.
Visit our place next time.
We can drink then.
Sure! I want to see what
your place looks like.
Who's doing the interior design?
The designer's name is Suh Ji An.
She's well known in the industry.
Yes, I've heard of her name.
I heard that she's popular
among male celebrities.
- Did you hear that?
- What's going on, Ho Jin?
- What?
- Are you interested in her?
- No.
He's very interested in her.
What are you talking about?
Don't listen to him. He's teasing me.
- My van is here. I have to go.
- Bye.
Joon, are you not even
going to say bye to me?
- Don't worry about him. Just go.
- Yes, just get going.
- Think of him as a stranger.
- Bye.
Young Bin, the film will become a hit.
Ho Jin, good luck with your love life.
- I said I'm not interested.
- Hey, what about me?
- I'll see you on social media.
- Sweet!
Bye, guys!
Bye.
I think...
she's also interested in Young Bin.
- What are you talking about?
- What's with you?
You've been quiet all night.
What's with this nonsense now?
Gosh, you're so slow-witted.
Then why did she make time out
of her busy schedule to see you?
Because we're friends.
All right. Let's go.
Hey, men and women can't be friends.
I think Young Bin and So Hee will go out.
Do you think you've become
a fortune teller or what?
You don't stand a chance with Ji An.
She's way out of your league.
Hey, that was mean.
Oh, my. That was similar.
- Didn't I sound like him?
- No.
Wasn't I close?
- I think I was pretty good.
- I don't think so.
- Gosh! Who are you?
- Hey.
Keep it down. You'll wake Turtle up.
It's me.
You startled me. What are you doing now?
- You weren't sleeping?
- No. Come on out.
- Gosh, that lunatic.
- Be quiet.
I thought I was seeing a ghost.
My goodness.
What is going on?
What time is it now?
Gosh, you startled me.
Around 5am.
What's that eye mask for?
Turtle broadcasts his shows on
the internet until very late.
Did you go out?
Yes.
I couldn't sleep, so I went for a run.
Even guys have to be careful being
outside alone at this hour.
What's up by the way?
I thought about it,
and I think I still want to do it.
That sounds weird.
You want to do it? What is it? With me?
You psycho. Why are you...
What are you thinking? Are
you still half asleep?
- It's about "War Terminator".
- What?
Why are you bringing it up again?
Is it because of So Hee?
No, it's not because of her.
I don't think I should give up like this.
I haven't even met the director.
That's what bothers me.
I saw the director while following Mr.
Kim around.
But it's...
Just forget it. It's impossible.
Plus, it made me want to quit.
What was that about? Why do you
have to be treated like that?
Aren't I right?
Aren't you an actor? You are.
That was ridiculous.
Well...
I'm not used to getting
compliments from you.
I'm speaking the truth.
Anyway,
I want to give it a try.
Frankly, I'd love an opportunity
to be auditioned. I'm serious.
Hold on a second. Let me think.
So Hee said that listening to the
director got her all excited.
Hearing that got me excited, too.
I don't even know.
Goodness.
So just one meeting with the
director is good enough, right?
Yes. How will you arrange it?
That I don't know.
- Hey, what are you talking about?
- What's your problem?
You're such an incompetent manager.
I should've gone to work
for Kim Soo Hyun...
or become friends with Yoo Ah In.
This is...
My mom told me not to hang out with you.
I should've listened to her.
Look into it. Try to think of a way.
What's going on? What's that sound?
What are you doing now?
Are you not sleeping?
I can't sleep. I have too much energy.
It's about to explode.
What should I do? Working out
like this will tame it, right?
He has lost his mind. Let's go.
Don't go. Guys!
Help me!
Hey, this car makes me nervous.
Drive carefully.
Then you shouldn't have
let Turtle take your car.
I let him use it because
he's going to the shoot.
Will we really be able to meet
the director at Cinematheque?
I heard that Directors Yim Pil Sung
and Lee Joon Ik go there a lot.
We'll wait until he shows up.
Right. We have so much time on our hands.
That's right.
It's Mr. Ahn. Why is he calling me?
- Yes, Mr. Ahn.
- Young Bin?
- Give me your address.
- Pardon me?
Why do you need my address?
I went fishing and caught so many
octopuses. I want to send you some.
No, it's okay. No one is home anyway.
Really? Then I will send them to Eun...
I mean, I'll send them to Mr. Kim's office.
Pick up the package before they go bad.
Okay, I will. Thank you.
Take care.
He'll send me small octopus.
Small octopus?
I feel like we're backstabbing him.
- I don't like this feeling.
- I know.
I should tell him that I
can't be in that film.
What are you talking about?
Don't go too far.
You must be kidding, but that's too much.
- Frankly, I didn't want to do it.
- Goodness.
Then why did you agree to it?
I guess I decided thoughtlessly
because I felt empty.
And you said the script is well written.
So you're going to tell
him that you won't do it?
You can meet the director,
but that film is...
- You have to do it.
- No, I can't.
- I won't do it.
- Well, I...
I don't know. I didn't hear anything.
What are you going to do, then?
You're so extreme.
Excuse me for a second.
(YOUNG BIN)
Hey, Young Bin. What's up?
- Eun Gab, are you busy?
- I'm in a meeting,
but I can talk to you.
- I'm going to meet Mr. Lee Joon Ik.
- Who?
Is it Mr. Kim?
- Whom are you meeting?
- On that note,
I think I should say no
to the detective film.
Gosh, is today April Fool's Day or what?
Is Ho Jin with you?
Here.
- Please go ahead.
- Is Young Bin serious?
- Yes, he is.
- Hey!
I'm sick and tired of...
- actors changing their minds.
- Mr. Kim...
- How can you encourage him?
Hey, he's obviously out
of his mind right now.
- Sir, you're on speakerphone now.
- What?
Young Bin, I wasn't badmouthing you.
I know. I'm sorry.
Then go ahead and meet
the director if you can.
But let's keep this film
as an option, okay?
I don't want to.
That'll make me look dishonest.
Hey, it's...
All right. Let's say you went clubbing.
A girl starts talking to you.
Then will you call your girlfriend
right away and break up with her?
Cup Noodles. Help me out if you're there!
You idiot...
- Cup Noodles!
- I'm here.
I'll pick the next film.
I want to take my time with it.
I don't think rushing into a
decision like this is a good idea.
Hey, do you want to see me dead or what?
I told you about Mr. Ahn's
flying kick, right?
- He'll seriously kill me.
- I'm sorry, Eun Gab.
Sort it out for me.
I think you should tell
him sooner than later.
He said he's sending small
octopus to your office for me.
What? Small octopus?
Hey, he's calling.
I'll call you back later.
- Oh, dear.
- Mr. Kim, what about the meeting?
Gosh, be quiet! Everyone, stay still.
Don't say a word.
Yes, Mr. Ahn.
Yes.
Small octopus? I see.
It's okay. Well...
I actually have something to tell you.
Yes. Please calm down first.
It's about...
Young Bin...
Hey, Kim Eun Gab!
Hey, where is Kim Eun Gab?
- This prick.
- Hello, Mr. Ahn.
- Sir.
- Hey, where is Kim Eun Gab?
- Mr. Kim was here...
- Where is he now?
He left a little while ago.
I know that he's here!
- He's really not here.
- Don't lie to my face.
You, Kim Eun Gab! You better come out!
Hey!
- Can I help you?
- What are you?
Where's Kim Eun Gab?
How dare he does this to me again?
He's not available right now.
I doubt that. Get out of my way.
Move!
Kim Eun Gab!
Stop him.
I said stop him.
- Hello.
Excuse me,
but I heard Mr. Lee Joon
Ik comes here often.
He does.
Can you maybe...
give me a call next time he comes around?
This is my business card.
(LEE HO JIN)
- What?
- I don't have ill intentions.
- Can you do us a favor?
- That scared me.
Please. It's an urgent matter.
I will.
Can I get your autograph in exchange?
Of course. Give me a pen.
I'm a big fan. My gosh.
Thank you.
- My number's on there.
- Thank you.
Please let me know.
Thank you.
Young Bin.
I'm jealous.
You should become an actor, too.
What do you want to do now?
Should we go somewhere else?
Let's watch a movie now that we're here.
What?
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
What are you doing? Get
your hands off of me.
Can't you read?
I'm supposed to hug her.
I have to practice this.
You don't even have that many lines.
Why do you need to practice?
Continue.
- What was the line again?
- Are you a goldfish?
You're like that guy from the movie
who was wearing a fish mask.
- Why can't you memorize these?
- I'm nervous.
Why am I so nervous?
Gosh.
Don't worry. Don't worry.
Don't worry. I'm here.
Do not worry. I am here.
You didn't get any sleep, did you?
You look so old.
I couldn't get any sleep
because of my man energy.
You know what I mean.
I pictured it in my head.
I have to go throw up now.
Look.
Look over there.
Hello.
You're here early.
I think it's a must-have
virtue as an actor.
This is Cha Joon. Cha Young
Bin's cousin brother.
- Hello.
I'm a big fan. I have so
much respect for you.
- All right. I'll see you in a bit.
- Yes.
It's not a complicated scene.
Don't get too nervous.
Didn't you get any sleep?
I stayed up all night intentionally.
I wanted to make myself look
like the worried character.
I like that.
Thank you.
That was...
really Jin Jae Young.
Look at that body.
She used to be my dream girl.
You get to hug her.
I'm so jealous.
Not really. She's much older.
She's still beautiful.
But I won't let that get in the way.
I'm a professional.
I'm going to focus on the role I'm playing.
What do you know about acting?
Focus.
Are you okay?
Gosh.
Cut.
Joon.
That's your blood-related sister.
Stop looking at her like that.
This is how I always look at people.
I get that a lot.
I'm sorry.
Okay. Let's start from the top.
Let's go again. Ready.
Action.
Are you okay?
Yes. I'm fine.
Don't worry.
I'm here.
Can I have a word?
I can't do this.
What's wrong?
He has an erection.
Gosh.
My man energy won't go away.
One more?
That's enough for today.
My eyes are so sore.
Me, too. This is my first time
doing this since college.
- Is he coming today?
- Hello?
Mr. Lee Joon Ik is here.
Over there.
Hey.
Thank you.
Let's go.
The last time I saw this
movie was 10 years ago.
Don't you remember this movie?
What do we do now?
I don't know. Let's wait
until this finishes.
I feel like a kid waiting to ask
out a girl I have a crush on.
I feel like when I realized
my mom opened my porn folder.
I'm so nervous right now.
How many movies are we watching today?
We finally met him, though.
It's over.
- Let's go.
- I feel bad.
Hey.
There he goes. He's leaving.
- Mr. Lee.
Hello.
Hello, I'm an actor, Cha Young Bin.
I'm Lee Ho Jin, his manager.
Nice to meet you.
Are you here to watch movies?
We're here to see you actually.
- Me?
- For "War Terminator".
Oh, that.
I already talked with
the agency about that.
We know that.
But we had something to
say to you in person.
Can you make some time for us?
Time?
You know around the place, right?
I can walk around with my eyes closed.
Hey.
Yes, Mr. Kim?
Where are you right now? Did you meet him?
We did.
But we didn't get to talk
about anything in details.
What about Mr. Ahn?
Don't even get me started.
He came looking for me
here saying he'll kill me.
I'm hiding from him right now.
I thought he was some kind of loan shark.
He's going to look everywhere
until he finds me.
By the way, what did he say?
He said he has an appointment, so
we're meeting him somewhere else.
Where's that?
(WELCOME)
Where is he?
There he is.
- Cheers.
- Congratulations.
This place isn't exactly
where we can talk about it.
What should we do?
- Hey.
- Eun Gab.
- Hello.
- Are you meeting him with us?
No. You guys go ahead. I
was just feeling uneasy.
Why are there so many people here in
a wrap party for a movie premiere?
And they say the movie
industry is in recession.
Look at all these freeloaders.
I know.
This place is so crowded. I
wonder how we're going to talk.
Just go up to him.
I'll be sitting over there.
Don't tell him that I'm here, okay?
- Let's go.
- All right.
(WRAP PARTY)
- Hello.
They're here.
- Hello, Mr. Lee.
- You're here.
What were you saying?
(WRAP PARTY)
- I'm sorry I'm late.
- It's okay.
I already kept you waiting
watching that boring movie.
I slept through the whole thing.
I've already seen "Nostalghia"
a dozen times since college.
- You did?
- He did.
Young Bin loves movies
directed by Tarkovsky.
Tarkovsky movies? Which ones?
I like "Nostalghia", but I
like "The Sacrifice" better.
That movie goes on for
more than four hours.
- He likes it.
- You watched all that?
Of course.
- Really?
- We watched a dozen times.
Hey.
Why are Mr. Lee Joon Ik and
Cha Young Bin together?
I thought he wasn't going
to be on "War Terminator".
Pretend you didn't see anything.
What are you doing here anyway?
Go look after your kid when
you're finished from work.
Are you looking for a date here?
- I invested in this movie.
- I knew it.
No wonder it's such a mess.
The casting is a train wreck.
I already know it's going to be a flop.
Why are you always like that when
people don't cast your actors?
When you say that, the movies
turn out to be mega hits.
Go away. I'm worried he'll notice me.
What are you intending to do?
This is getting interesting.
I don't know. I feel like I'm
spying on my cheating wife.
I wish this movie's a hit.
Get away from me.
The thing is...
We heard that you already have
an actor in mind for the role.
I do.
I'm sorry,
but can you maybe reconsider
with Young Bin in mind?
I'd like to do a script read
with other actors if I can.
I don't understand...
why you desperately want this movie.
What's the reason for...
making you want to do this so badly?
It's because of you.
Because of me?
Yes.
Please reconsider.
- Mr. Lee.
- Hello.
- Young Bin, long time no see.
I saw "The Flowers of Evil". You were good.
Thank you.
I read the news article that you'll
be working with Mr. Lee Joon Ik.
No.
It's not like that.
This is a misunderstanding.
I'm just here to discuss something.
I have customers to attend to.
I'll talk to you later.
It's not like that.
He got it all wrong.
I mean...
Oh, gosh.
You little...
Goodness.
What?
Mr. Ahn?
You're here to see me, right? Let's talk.
- Let go of me.
- Gosh.
You jerks are trying to stab
me in the back. Is that right?
Stop making a scene. Let's talk outside.
Let's take this outside.
Why you little...
You're the worst of all.
Mr. Kim.
What are you doing here?
I'm fine.
- Are you all right?
- Of course.
It's fine really.
Do I smell bad?
Not really.
- Do I?
- Yes.
Did Mr. Ahn leave?
You wouldn't believe what he said...
about my unborn grandchildren.
I don't think he's that
upset any more, though.
Don't worry about me. Go back to Mr. Lee.
We're done talking.
What did he say?
It didn't work out. He told
us to wait for another time.
I see.
It's fine. We tried our best.
We tried everything we possibly could.
What's done is done.
You have to know when to let it go.
It's just like forgetting
your girl after a breakup.
I understand. We have to start fresh.
We should.
- Get the phone.
- Okay.
I said to get the phone.
Who could be calling me
at this time of the day?
Is it Mr. Ahn again?
He texted you until 3am.
I never saw anyone cursing
like that before.
I told you to turn it off
before you go to bed.
What if I miss an important call for that?
Will you take responsibility?
That's an obsession.
Where did it go?
(MS. JO TAE YOUNG)
What was it doing in there?
Hello? Thanks for calling me so early.
Is this too early?
Of course.
This is awfully rude of you.
You're the one who wanted to
have a meeting on Sunday.
You stabbed me in the back.
You called me this early in the morning.
What is it this time? Go on.
What? Okay.
Right.
Okay, I understand. Let
me call you right back.
Bye.
Honey, where are my car keys?
They should be at the door. Why?
The door? Okay. I'll be right back.
Eun Gab.
Is he going out dressed like that?
- Young Bin.
- Mr. Kim?
- Where's Young Bin?
- What's going on?
Young Bin?
Is he sleeping over at
his girlfriend's house?
You know he doesn't have one.
You don't know anything for certain.
He needs temporary tattoos
for one-night stands.
We need proof in case a
video of him gets leaked.
What's with this nonsense?
Wake up!
- I'm awake.
- Okay.
- Young Bin?
- Young Bin.
- What's going on?
- I have no idea.
- You came here dressed like that?
- Something came up.
- Hello.
- Right.
- Yes.
- What's going on?
What are you doing?
Be quiet.
It's me. Are you available to talk now?
I'll put him on right now.
- You should talk to him.
- Who is it?
- Hello?
- I hope this isn't a bad time.
I'm sorry. I have a flight soon.
Mr. Lee?
- What?
(DIRECTOR LEE JOON IK)
What's going on?
On my way back home yesterday,
I went to watch "The Flowers of Evil".
- What?
- He watched "The Flowers of Evil".
About "War Terminator"...
Let's do it together.
Who is it? What are you talking about?
Of course. Thank you.
What is it?
- Okay.
- It's the director.
What is it?
He wants me on "War Terminator".
That's right.
What?
How did you convince him?
I tried so much and it didn't work.
I don't know. What's the
reason behind this?
How should I know?
Congratulations.
It's because of my man energy. I know it.
This is unbelievable.
- This is crazy.
- Quiet.
Get dressed. Let's go have breakfast.
- Let's go.
- You should get changed, too.
- Is the dressing room that way?
- Yes.
Good job.
- What?
- Well...
For the first time, you did something.
Do you have a wish?
This slipper is very expensive.
Do you want it?
Can you give the fishing
rod back to Mr. Ahn?
I'll tell Joy to do it.
Subtitles by VIU
Ripped, edited and synced by
gabbyu@subscene
(NEXT EPISODE PREVIEW)
About Kang Ha Neul...
Wasn't he involved in a
scandal with An So Hee?
Why would he play a supporting
role for Young Bin?
Do you have any proof?
Young Bin likes So Hee.
Did you have to blabber all
over the neighborhood?
That's you, big mouth.
Take your love quarrels off the set.
You're much better looking than on screen.
It won't even make the news
because it's so embarrassing.
Hey!
What do you think we're doing? We're
camping out here by ourselves.
Did you have a change of
heart after getting so old?
Do I have to get old, too?
Please let me land a part-time job!
Please also let me get a boyfriend.
I beg you!
- Is it you?
- Oh my...You started me
Was it you who called me?
[GOBLIN]